(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Omar : Hey, look! Over there!
Lian : Wow!
Lian : Their ship is so big.
Omar : Wish ours was that fancy.
Lian : I'd be so happy if ours was that fancy. 'Cause then...
Genie : Why is that?
Genie : Because it looks better?
Genie : This boat has seen us through many a storm.
Genie : It may not look like much but, It has something theirs never will.
Omar : What? Wood rot and rats?
(OMAR AND LIAN GIGGLE)
Dalia : Are the children learning something, dear?
Genie : It is unclear.
Genie : All right,
Genie : sit, children.
Genie : I think it's time that I told you the story...
Genie : of Aladdin, the princess, and the lamp.
Lian : What's so special about a lamp?
Genie : Oh, this is a magic lamp.
Omar : Maybe if you sing.
Lian : It's better when you sing.
Genie : No, no. No singing. It's been a long day.
Genie : Oh, imagine a land It's a faraway place Where the caravan Camels roam
Genie : Where you wander among Ev'ry culture and tongue
Genie : It's chaotic But hey, it's home
Genie : When the wind's From the east
Genie : And the sun's From the west
Genie : And the sand In the glass is right
Genie : Come on down, stop on by Hop a carpet and fly
Genie : To another Arabian night
Merchant : Hey! Psh!
Genie :  As you wind Through the streets
Genie : And the fabled bazaars
Genie : With the cardamom-cluttered Stalls
Genie : You can smell e'vry spice While you haggle the price
Genie : Of the silks And the satin shawls
Genie : Oh, the music that plays As you move through a maze
Genie : In the haze Of your pure delight
Genie : You are caught in a dance You are lost in the trance
Genie : Of another Arabian night
Genie : Arabian nights
Genie : Like Arabian days
Genie : More often than not Are hotter than hot
Genie : In a lot of good ways
Genie : Arabian nights
Genie : Like Arabian dreams
Genie : This mystical land Of magic and sand
Genie : Is more than it seems
Genie : There's a road That may lead you To good or to greed
Genie : Through the power Your wishing commands
Genie : Let the darkness unfold Or find fortunes untold
Genie : Well, your destiny Lies in your hands
Genie;The Cave of Wonders : Only one may enter here.
The Cave of Wonders : One whose worth lies far within.
The Cave of Wonders : The diamond in the rough.
Genie :  Arabian nights
Genie : Like Arabian days
Genie : They seem to excite Take off and take flight
Genie : To shock and amaze
The Cave of Wonders : Seek thee out the diamond in the rough.
Genie : Arabian nights 'Neath Arabian moons
Genie : A fool off his guard Could fall and fall hard
Genie : Out there on the dunes
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Woman Theif : What's your monkey's name?
Aladdin : Abu.
Woman Theif : He's a lovely monkey.
Aladdin : Hmm. That's a lovely necklace.
Woman Theif : So, where does Abu come from?
Aladdin : He, uh... Oh!
Aladdin : I think this belongs to me.
Aladdin : Good day, ladies.
Aladdin : Okay.
Aladdin : Abu.
Aladdin : (MAN SHOUTING)
Aladdin : (GRUNTS)
Aladdin : How'd we do, Abu?
Aladdin : Good monkey.
Merchant Zulla : Stop right there, Aladdin.
Merchant Zulla : Whatever it is you stole today, I don't want it.
Aladdin : Whoa, whoa. I didn't steal anything.
Aladdin : It's a family heirloom that's worth a lot.
Merchant Zulla : I'll give you a bag of dates for it, nothing more.
Aladdin : Zulla, we both know it's worth at least three bags.
Merchant Zulla : Take the bag of dates and get out!
Merchant Zulla : (ZULLA SHOUTS IN ARABIC)
Man1 : Go!
Beggar : Please.
Soldier1 : Move it, you street rat.
Aladdin : Here you go, Abu.
Aladdin : Shh.
Woman1 : Come here!
Merchant2 : Fresh fish! We catch them, you buy,
Merchant3 : Try this, please. Please.
Merchant2 : Sugar dates and pistachios!
Jasmine : Hello.
Jasmine : Oh.
Jasmine : Are you hungry? Here, take some bread.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING) (WOMAN CHUCKLES)
Merchant Jamal : Hey! Hey!
Merchant Jamal : You steal from my brother.
Jasmine : Stealing? No, I...
Merchant Jamal : You pay, or I take bracelet.
Jasmine : Sir, I don't have any money.
Jasmine : Let go of me...
Aladdin : No!
Aladdin : Take it easy, Jamal.
Merchant Jamal : Kalil walks away from the stall... and this one, she steals the bread.
Jasmine : Those children were hungry!
Jasmine : I...
Aladdin : Okay, give me a minute.
Merchant Jamal : You keep your little street rat nose out of it! Huh?
Aladdin : Do you have any money?
Jasmine : No.
Aladdin : Okay, trust me.
Aladdin : Here you go.
Jasmine : Wait!
Aladdin : This is what you wanted, right?
Merchant Jamal : Yeah. Thank you.
Aladdin : Okay, and an apple. For your troubles.
Merchant Jamal : Nice!
Jasmine : That was my... I'm not leaving without my bracelet!
Aladdin : You mean this bracelet?
Aladdin : Come on.
(JAMAL VOCALIZING MELODY)
(VOCALIZES HALTINGLY)
Merchant Jamal : Aladdin! Thief with Aladdin!
Jasmine : Are we in trouble?
Aladdin : Only if you get caught.
Merchant Jamal : Aladdin!
Aladdin : Down that alley.
Aladdin : Monkey knows the way.
Merchant Jamal : Guards!
Aladdin : Abu.
Merchant Jamal : (GASPS)
Merchant Jamal : (ABU CHITTERS)
Aladdin : You'll be fine.
Merchant Jamal : stole from me!
Merchant Jamal : Over there!
Soldier1 : Hey, you!
Merchant Jamal : Aladdin!
Aladdin : You looking for this, Jamal?
Merchant Jamal : Aladdin, you street rat!
(GUARDS GRUNTING)
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
Aladdin :  Gotta keep one jump Ahead of the bread line One swing Ahead of the sword
Aladdin : I steal Only what I can't afford
Aladdin : And that's ev'rything
Aladdin : One jump Ahead of the lawmen That's all And that's no joke
Aladdin : These guys Don't appreciate I'm broke
Soldiers : Riffraff! Street rat! Scoundrel!
Aladdin : Take that!
Aladdin : Try a dif'rent tack, guys
Aladdin : Rip him open!
Aladdin : 'Round the back, guys
Aladdin : I can take a hint Gotta face the facts Could really use A friend or two!
Women : Oh, it's sad Aladdin's hit the bottom
Aladdin : Ooh, ladies!
Women : - He's become A one-man rise in crime
Aladdin :  Well...
Woman2 : I'd blame parents 'Cept he hasn't got 'em
Aladdin : Gotta eat to live Gotta steal to eat Tell you all about it When I got the time
Soldier1 : Huh?
(YELLS)
(ALADDIN GRUNTING)
(WOMAN YELPS)
Jasmine : There are stairs, you know.
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
Aladdin : Where's the fun in that?
Aladdin : One jump Ahead of the slowpokes One skip ahead of my doom
Aladdin : Next time Gonna use a nom de plume
Aladdin : (GASPS)
Aladdin : One jump Ahead of the hit men One hit ahead of the flock
Aladdin : I think I'll take a stroll Around the block
Aladdin : (WOMEN GASP)
Soldiers : Stop, thief!
Woman3 : Vandal!
Aladdin : Abu!
Man2 : Scandal!
Aladdin : Let's not be too hasty
Woman4 : Still, I think He's rather tasty
Aladdin : Gotta eat to live Gotta steal to eat Otherwise we'd get along
Soldiers : Wrong!
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
Soldiers : No, no, no!
(BOTH SCREAM)
Aladdin : Together on three!
Jasmine : Together on three?
Aladdin : We jump.
Jasmine : We jump?
Aladdin : Why are you repeating everything I say?
Aladdin : The pole.
Soldiers :  Move, move!
Soldiers :  This way!
Aladdin : One, two, three!
Soldier1 : Thief! Stop! On the roof!
Jasmine : I'm sorry!
Jasmine : I can't do this.
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
Soldier2 : Stop him!
Aladdin : Look at me. Look at me.
Aladdin : You can do this.
Jasmine : Okay.
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
(SCREAMING)
(YELPS)
Aladdin : oh!
Jasmine : Oh.
Aladdin : Nicely done.
Jasmine : Thank you.
Aladdin : One jump Ahead of the hoof beats One hop ahead of the hump
Aladdin : One trick Ahead of disaster They're quick But I'm much faster
Aladdin : Here goes!
Aladdin : Better throw my hand in Wish me happy landin' All I gotta do is jump!
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
Soldier1 : Move back!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ABU CHITTERING)
Jasmine : Oh, dear.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(CHITTERING EXCITEDLY)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Aladdin : Come on. I know somewhere we'll be safe.
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
Iago : Here comes the master.
(SNIFFING)
Jafar : You bring me the rough but never a diamond.
Jafar : Take them away.
Soldier1 : Move!
Iago : Take them away.
Soldier2 : My vizier...
Soldier2 : perhaps this diamond in the rough does not exist?
Jafar : He is out there.
Soldier2 : But we've searched for months!
Jafar : I do not understand what could possibly be in that cave... that could help a man as great as you.
Jafar : You are already second only to the sultan!
Iago : Second! Uh-oh!
Iago : Who's in trouble now?
Jafar : And you think second is enough?
Soldier2 : Of course.
Soldier2 : You were not born to be sultan.
Iago : Not smart.
Jafar : Do you know what I had to do to get the power that I have?
Jafar : The sacrifices that I've made, the bodies that I've buried?
Jafar : The five years spent in a Shirabad jail?
Jafar : People need to understand that they will pay for underestimating me.
Jafar : Second is not enough! And it will never be enough!
Jafar : That's why I need the lamp, and why I no longer need you!
(SCREAMS)
(IAGO CACKLES)
Aladdin : This way.
Jasmine : Oh.
Jasmine : Where are we, exactly?
Aladdin : You'll see.
Jasmine : Oh, my.
Jasmine : Is this... Is this where you live?
Aladdin : Yep.
Aladdin : Just me and Abu. Come and go as we please.
Aladdin : Welcome to my humble...
Aladdin : You'll see.
Jasmine : You are quite the magician.
Aladdin : Thank you.
Aladdin : Abu, no, help!
(EXHALES)
Jasmine : I can't believe...
Aladdin : What?
Jasmine : I can't believe we did that. That I did that. (SCOFFS) That we're alive!
Jasmine : With the chase.
Aladdin : Abu, tea?
Jasmine : Jumping buildings. That was incredible.
Aladdin : Tea?
Jasmine : Thank you. And thank you for getting me out of there.
Jasmine : Aladdin, isn't it?
Aladdin : Uh, you're welcome...
Jasmine : I'm... I'm Dalia.
Aladdin : Dalia.
Aladdin : From the palace.
Jasmine : How could you tell?
Aladdin : Well, only someone from the palace could afford a bracelet like that.
Aladdin : And that silk lining is imported, too.
Aladdin : It comes from the merchant boats, straight to the palace.
Aladdin : But not to servants.
Aladdin : At least, not most servants, which means you are a handmaid to the princess.
Jasmine : Impressive.
Aladdin : You think that's impressive,
Aladdin : you should see the city from up there.
Jasmine : Oh.
Jasmine : Agrabah. It's so beautiful.
Jasmine : I should get out more.
Aladdin : You should tell the princess to get out more.
Aladdin : The people haven't seen her in years.
Jasmine : They won't let her.
Jasmine : Ever since my...
Jasmine : The queen was killed, the sultan's been afraid.
Jasmine : So she's kept locked away.
Aladdin : Seems everyone's been afraid since then.
Aladdin : But the people of Agrabah had nothing to do with that.
Aladdin : The people loved her.
Jasmine : They did, didn't they?
Aladdin : (CLEARS THROAT)
Jasmine : Is this yours?
Aladdin : It's kind of borrowed.
Aladdin : My mother taught me that song.
Jasmine : Mine too.
Aladdin : It's all I remember of her.
Jasmine : And what about your father?
Aladdin : I lost them both when I was young.
Aladdin : Been on my own ever since.
Aladdin : It's all right, it's just...
Jasmine : What?
Aladdin : It's a little sad.
Aladdin : Having a monkey as the only parental authority in your life.
(CHUCKLES)
Aladdin : We get by.
Aladdin : Every day I just think things will be different... but it never seems to change.
Aladdin : It's just sometimes, I feel like I'm..
Jasmine : Trapped.
Jasmine : Like you can't escape what you were born into?
Aladdin : Yes.
Jasmine : Hmm.
Soldier1 : Welcome Prince Anders!
Jasmine : I have to get back to the palace.
Aladdin : Uh... Now?
Soldier1 : Make way for Prince Anders!
Aladdin : It's just another prince coming to court the princess.
Jasmine : Yes, and I have to get her ready.
Jasmine : Oh! Do you have my bracelet?
Aladdin : Sure.
Soldier2 : Make way for Prince Anders.
Aladdin : I'm sure I put it in here.
Aladdin : Somewhere.
Aladdin : Abu, did you take it?
Jasmine : That was my mother's bracelet.
Aladdin : Yes. It's beautiful.
Jasmine : You are a thief.
Aladdin : No, no. Yes, but...
Jasmine : I'm so naive.
Aladdin : Abu.
Jasmine : Excuse me.
Aladdin : Wait, wait, wait! Wait, it's not like that!
Soldier1 : Clear the way!
Soldier2 : No! Watch it!
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
Soldier1 : Street rat, get out of the way!
Aladdin : Who do you think you're calling a street rat?
Soldier1 : Are you talking back to me?
Soldier1 : You were born worthless and you will die worthless.
Soldier1 : And only your fleas will mourn you.
Soldier1 : (CLICKS TONGUE)
Aladdin : Come on, Abu.
Aladdin : Let's go home.
Aladdin : (SIGHS)
Aladdin :  Riffraff, street rat
Aladdin : I don't buy that
Aladdin : If only they'd look closer
Aladdin : Would they see a poor boy?
Aladdin : No, siree
Aladdin : They'd find out
Aladdin : There's so much more to me
Aladdin : (CHITTERING)
Aladdin : (SIGHS)
Aladdin : Abu.
Aladdin : There's a time that we do steal, and a time we don't.
Aladdin : This was definitely a don't.
Aladdin : (CHITTERS DEJECTEDLY)
Sultan : Welcome, Prince Anders!
Sultan : We trust you had an enjoyable journey.
Prince Anders : Oh, wow.
Sultan : Prince Anders, my daughter, Princess Jasmine.
Prince Anders : So, why did no one tell me of your beauty?
Jasmine : No one mentioned yours, either.
Prince Anders : Oh! Thank you. They say that in Skånland.
Prince Anders : Yeah. Right?
Prince Anders : (ALL LAUGHING)
Prince Anders : It's very, very amusing.
Jasmine : Is it?
Prince Anders : Yeah.
Jasmine : We have the same title, yet are never described the same way.
Sultan : Jasmine.
Prince Anders : Yeah.
Prince Anders : Oh.
Prince Anders : What is that?
Prince Anders : Don't, Don't tell me.
Prince Anders : It's a cat with stripes!
Iago : He likes you.
Prince Anders : I know.
Prince Anders : 'Cause in Skånland, cats love me. Here, puss, puss. Hey, puss, puss.
Prince Anders : Hey, puss, puss, puss...
Prince Anders : (ANDERS SCREAMS)
Prince Anders : (LAUGHTER)
Jafar : My sultan, our enemies grow stronger every day...
Jafar : yet you allow your daughter to dismiss Prince Anders... and a possible military alliance.
Sultan : Which enemies?
Jafar : Shirabad continues to amass.
Sultan : Shirabad is our ally.
Jafar : Was our ally!
Sultan : You would drag us into a war with our oldest...
Jafar : And you would allow your kingdom to sink into ruin for mere sentiment!
Sultan : Jafar!
Sultan : Remember your place.
Jafar : I apologize.
Jafar : Forgive me, my sultan.
Jafar : I went too far.
Jafar : But...
Jafar : if you would only reconsider...
Jafar : I think you will see...
Jafar : that invading Shirabad is the right thing to do.
Jafar : Invading Shirabad is...
Jasmine : Invade Shirabad?
Sultan : What?
Jasmine : Why would we invade Mother's kingdom?
Sultan : We would never invade Shirabad.
Jafar : But an ally in Skånland would improve our situation.
Sultan : Yes, if you consider giving Prince Anders a chance.
Jasmine : To rule? Baba, Rajah would make a better ruler.
Sultan : My dear, I'm not getting any younger.
Sultan : We must find you a husband, and we are running out of kingdoms.
Jasmine : What foreign prince could care for our people as I do?
Jasmine : I could lead if only...
Sultan : My dear, you cannot be a sultan...
Sultan : because it has never been done in the 1,000-year history of our kingdom.
Jasmine : I have been preparing for this my whole life. I have read...
Jafar : Books? But you cannot read experience.
Jafar : Inexperience is dangerous.
Jafar : People left unchecked will revolt.
Jafar : Walls and borders unguarded will be attacked.
Sultan : Jafar is right.
Sultan : One day...
Sultan : you will understand.
Sultan : You may leave now.
Jasmine : (HUFFS)
Jasmine : (RAJAH GROWLS)
Jasmine : (SIGHS)
Jafar : Life will be kinder to you, Princess,
Jafar : once you accept these traditions... and understand it's better for you to be seen and not heard.
Jafar : (INHALES DEEPLY)
Jafar : (RAJAH GROWLING)
Jafar : (SIGHS)
Jasmine :  Here comes a wave Meant to wash me away
Jasmine : A tide That is taking me under
Jasmine : Broken again Left with nothing to say
Jasmine : My voice drowned out In the thunder
Jasmine : But I can't cry
Jasmine : And I can't Start to crumble
Jasmine : Whenever they try
Jasmine : To shut me or cut me down
Jasmine : I can't stay silent
Jasmine : Though they wanna Keep me quiet
Jasmine : And I tremble When they try it
Jasmine : All I know is I won't Go speechless
Soldier1 : Open the gate!
Aladdin : You know what to do, Abu.
Soldier2 : Get off me! Get off me, you dirty monkey!
Soldier2 : Go away! Go away! Go away!
Soldier1 : Close the gate!
Iago : Dirty monkey!
Iago : Street thief. Street thief.
Jafar : Remember your place, Jafar.
Iago : Remember your place!
Jafar : If I hear that one more time...
Iago : Sorry, master!
Jafar : Another petty insult from that small-minded fool.
Jafar : (IAGO LAUGHING)
Jafar : He sees a city where I see an empire.
Iago : Such vision.
Jafar : Once that lamp sits in my hand...
Jafar : then I shall sit on his throne.
Iago : Thief. Thief in the palace.
Jafar : Thief in the palace?
Iago : That's what I said. Thief!
Jafar : What have you seen, Iago?
Iago : Diamond in the rough.
Soldier1;Palace Worker : I told you, now, come on!
Palace Worker : Bigger circles. Bigger circles.
Iago : Who's a clever boy?
Jasmine : But, Dalia, there has to be something I can do.
Dalia : A handsome prince wants to marry you.
Dalia : Oh, when will life get easier?
Jasmine : It's not that I don't want to marry, it's just...
Dalia : You want to be sultan. But why?
Jasmine : You remember my mother used to say... we would only ever be as happy as our least happy subject?
Jasmine : If she saw what I saw today, she would be heartbroken.
Dalia : She would also want you to be safe.
Dalia : And clean. I'll draw the bath.
Jasmine : Jafar's guards on every corner.
Jasmine : Soon, he'd have them invading our neighbors, risking lives, for what?
Jasmine : I can help.
Jasmine : I know I can.
Jasmine : I was born to do more than marry some useless prince.
Dalia : If you had to marry a useless prince, you could certainly do worse than this one.
Dalia : He's tall and handsome. And yes, he's a little dim,
Dalia : but you're just getting married.
Dalia : It's not like you have to talk to him.
Dalia : But you'd prefer that boy from the market.
Dalia : (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Jasmine : Can I help you?
Aladdin : Tea?
Jasmine : You? You!
Jasmine : What are you doing here? Get in here, now!
Aladdin : I came back to return your bracelet.
Jasmine : My bracelet? Where is it?
Aladdin : On your wrist.
Jasmine : What?
Aladdin : Not bad.
Aladdin : I like what she's done with the place.
Jasmine : How did you get past the guards?
Aladdin : That was challenging, but I have my ways.
Aladdin : While the princess is out, would you like to go for a stroll?
Aladdin : Have a little chat?
Jasmine : You are unbelievable.
Jasmine : You cannot just break into a palace and walk around like you own the place.
Aladdin : If you don't have anything, you have to act like you own everything.
Aladdin : So, what do you say? I did find your bracelet.
Jasmine : You did not find it, you stole it!
Aladdin : Correction, the monkey stole it.
Jasmine : He's your monkey.
Aladdin : He's still just a monkey.
Dalia : Who ordered the tea?
Aladdin : Uh...
Jasmine : I did.
Jasmine : For you, Princess Jasmine.
Aladdin : Your Majesty!
Dalia : Why are you being weird?
Dalia : Oh, I'm the princess. Yes.
Dalia : Mmm-hmm. And it is good to be me... with all my
Dalia : palaces... and wagons of gold things...
Dalia : and dresses for every hour of the day.
Dalia : Now it is time for my cat to be cleaned.
Jasmine : She doesn't get out much.
Aladdin : Mmm-hmm.
Aladdin : Clearly.
Aladdin : (ALADDIN GASPS)
Jasmine : Oh.
Aladdin : Aren't you supposed to be in the bath?
Aladdin : (SNIFFING)
Dalia : Oh, servant girl, this cat isn't going to clean itself!
Aladdin : But don't cats clean themselves?
Jasmine : You have to go now.
Aladdin : Oh, okay. But I'm coming back tomorrow night.
Jasmine : What? No, you can't... Meet me in the courtyard beside the fountain when the moon is above the minaret.
Aladdin : To return this.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
Aladdin : I promise.
(CHUCKLES)
(ABU CHITTERS)
Aladdin : Can you believe it, Abu?
Aladdin : The most heavily guarded place in all of Agrabah...
Soldier1 : Evening.
Aladdin : Evening.
Aladdin : (CLEARS THROAT)
Aladdin : Guards are behind me.
Aladdin : Hello, boys.
(GUARDS CHATTERING)
Aladdin : Where am I?
Jafar : In a world of trouble, boy.
Aladdin : That bracelet, is that what this is about?
Aladdin : Because I didn't steal it. The handmaid...
Jafar : What was a handmaid doing wearing the queen's bracelet?
Aladdin : The queen? No, no.
Aladdin : She said that it belonged to her...
Jafar : Her mother.
Jafar : (SCOFFS)
Jafar : Well, at least she told the truth about one thing.
Aladdin : Are you saying that was the princess?
Aladdin : I was talking to the...
Jafar : She was toying with you.
Jafar : It amuses her to meet commoners.
Jafar : Did you actually think she liked you? (CHUCKLES)
Jafar : What do they call you?
Aladdin : Aladdin.
Jafar : Aladdin. People like us must be realistic if...
Aladdin : Us?
Jafar : You see, I was once like you.
Jafar : A common thief.
Jafar : Only I thought bigger.
Jafar : Steal an apple and you're a thief,
Jafar : steal a kingdom and you're a statesman.
Jafar : Only weak men stop there.
Jafar : You're either the most powerful man in the room, or you're nothing.
Jafar : You, you stumbled upon an opportunity.
Jafar : I can make you rich.
Jafar : Rich enough to impress a princess.
Jafar : But nothing comes for free.
Aladdin : What would I have to do?
Jafar : There's a cave nearby, and in it, a simple oil lamp.
Jafar : Retrieve it for me and I will make you wealthy enough to impress a princess.
Jafar : You're nothing to her, but you could be.
Jafar : Your life begins now, Aladdin.
Dalia : Still waiting?
Jasmine : No. No, I came out to... (INHALES)
Jasmine : (SIGHS)
Jasmine : He promised.
Dalia : (DALIA SIGHS)
Dalia : I'll be upstairs if you need me.
Jasmine : Good night, Dalia.
Jasmine : (SIGHS)
Jafar : The Cave of Wonders.
Jafar : When you enter, you will see more riches than you ever dreamed of...
Jafar : gold, diamonds, and the lamp.
Jafar : Bring it to me and I will make you rich and free.
(IAGO WHISTLES)
Jafar : But take no other treasure, no matter how sorely you are tempted.
Jafar : And you will be tempted.
Jafar : (LION'S HEAD GROWLING)
The Cave of Wonders : Only one may enter here.
The Cave of Wonders : One whose worth lies far within.
The Cave of Wonders : The diamond in the rough.
Jafar : Remember...
Jafar : take nothing but the lamp.
Jafar : (IAGO SQUAWKS)
Jafar : (ALADDIN SCREAMING)
Jafar : (RUMBLING)
Jafar : (GRUNTING)
Jafar : (CHITTERING) (GRUNTS)
Aladdin : Abu, don't touch. Remember?
Aladdin : (CHITTERS) (GASPS)
Aladdin : (CHITTERING)
Aladdin : (CLATTERING) (SCREECHES)
Aladdin : (GRUNTING)
Aladdin : (YELPS)
Aladdin : Whoa.
Aladdin : Abu.
Aladdin : This is a magic carpet. These really do exist.
Aladdin : Hello, Carpet.
Aladdin : (CHUCKLES)
Aladdin : (SCREECHES)
Aladdin : Let's see what we can do about your situation here.
Aladdin : (STRAINING)
Aladdin : (CLINKING)
Aladdin : Oh, hey. Don't mention it.
Aladdin : (CHITTERS, SCREECHES)
Aladdin : Abu, keep your little monkey hands to yourself.
Aladdin : (WHINES)
Aladdin : (EXHALES SHARPLY)
Aladdin : (GRUNTS)
Aladdin : (GRUNTING)
Aladdin : (SCREECHES)
Aladdin : (CLINKING)
Aladdin : (ABU WARBLES)
Aladdin : (DIAMOND CLINKING)
Aladdin : (EXHALES)
Aladdin : (CHITTERING SOFTLY)
Aladdin : (LION'S HEAD GROWLING) (RUMBLING)
Aladdin : Abu, no!
The Cave of Wonders : You have touched the forbidden treasure.
The Cave of Wonders : Now you will never again...
The Cave of Wonders : see the light of day!
Aladdin : (GRUNTING)
Aladdin : (YELLS)
Aladdin : Carpet!
Aladdin : Abu, jump!
Aladdin : (SCREAMING)
Aladdin : (GRUNTS)
Aladdin : (GRUNTING)
Aladdin : Could you give me a hand?
Jafar : First, the lamp.
Aladdin : No, first your hand.
Jafar : We don't have much time.
Jafar : Give me the lamp.
Aladdin : Your hand!
Iago : Second no more, master.
Aladdin : Now your hand.
Jafar : How about my foot?
Aladdin : No! No!
Aladdin : (SCREAMING)
Aladdin : (YELPS)
Jafar : Get off me, monkey!
(ABU SCREECHING)
(RUMBLING) (JAFAR COUGHING)
Jafar : Stop. (IAGO
SQUAWKS)
Iago : Dirty monkey! Second, second!
(IAGO SQUAWKS AND CACKLES)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
Aladdin : Whoa.
Aladdin : We're alive.
Aladdin : I think.
Aladdin : Thank you, Carpet.
Aladdin : (CHITTERS)
Aladdin : (WHISTLES)
Aladdin : Abu.
Aladdin : How did you...?
Aladdin : You cunning little monkey.
Aladdin : Now, all we need's a way out.
Aladdin : (GRUNTS)
Aladdin : Hey, Carpet, do you know a way out of here?
Aladdin : The lamp?
Aladdin : What is that?
Genie : (DEEP VOICE) Oh, great one who summons me, terrible one who commands me...
Genie : I stand by my oath, loyalty to wishes three.
Genie : (WHIMPERS SOFTLY)
Genie : (CLEARS THROAT)
Genie : I said, Oh, great...
Genie : (NORMAL VOICE) Excuse me, boy, where's your boss?
Genie : Help me out here. Where's your boss?
Genie : If I was gonna talk to myself, I could've just stayed in the lamp.
Aladdin : Uh... Uh...
Genie : Hello?
Aladdin : I'm... (GULPS)
Genie : Use your big boy voice.
Aladdin : I'm talking to a smoking blue giant?
Genie : No! (WARBLES)
Genie : I am not a giant,
Genie : I am a genie. There is a difference.
Genie : Giants are not real.
Genie : Where's your boss?
Aladdin : Uh, my boss?
Genie : Look, kid, I've been doing this a long time, all right?
Genie : There's always a guy, you know... he's cheated somebody or buried somebody...
Genie : I mean, you get my point. Where's that guy?
Aladdin : I know that guy. He's outside.
Genie : So, it's just you and me down here?
Genie : And a monkey?
Genie : That's your personal business... but we gonna need to talk about that monkey later.
Genie : It's a pretty little monkey.
Genie : So, you rubbed the lamp?
Aladdin : Uh-huh.
Genie : Oh. Okay. Hey, do you mind... if I could just stretch it out over here, do you mind?
Aladdin : Uh... Are you asking me?
Genie : Yes. You're my master. (EXHALES)
Aladdin : I'm your master?
Genie : Downward dog.
Aladdin : No, no no. You look like you should be my master.
Genie : Right, but that's not quite how it works, though.
Genie : How long have you been trapped in here?
Genie : (SIGHS) 'Bout thousand years.
Aladdin : A thousand years?
Genie : (IMITATES ALADDIN) A thousand years.
Genie : Kid, is it me or does, like, everything surprise you?
Genie : So, you really don't know who I am?
Genie : Genie, wishes, lamp, none of that ringing a bell?
Genie : Wow! Well, that's a first.
Genie : Monkey! (SCREECHES)
Genie : (PIPE SQUEAKS)
Genie : Oh, you don't need to worry about him. He's fine.
Genie : (PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
Genie :  Well, Ali Baba He had them 40 thieves Scheherazade Had a thousand tales
Genie : But, master, you're in luck Because up your sleeve You got a genie That never fails
Genie : Whoo!
Genie : I'm the best.
Genie : Yeah.
Aladdin : Heh.
Genie : (CHUCKLES)
Genie : Not enough, huh?
Aladdin : Uh...
Genie : I'm kidding. Watch this.
Genie : Here I go!
Genie : Uh! Ooh! Whoo!
Genie : Back up.
Genie : Uh-oh! Watch out!
Genie : You done wound me up.
Genie : 'Bout to show you what I'm working with. Uh!
Genie :  Well, Ali Baba He had them 40 thieves Scheherazade Had a thousand tales
Genie : But, master, you're in luck Because up your sleeves You got a brand of magic Never fails
Genie : You got some power In your corner now
Genie : Heavy ammunition In your camp
Genie : You got some punch, pizzazz Yahoo, and how
Genie : All you gotta do Is rub that lamp
Genie : And then I'll say
Genie : Mister, man What's your name?
Genie : Whatever What will Your pleasure be?
Genie : Let me take your order I'll jot it down You ain't never had A friend like me
Genie : Life is your restaurant And I'm your maître d'
Genie : Come whisper to me Whatever it is you want
Genie : You ain't never had A friend like me
Genie : We pride ourselves On service
Genie : You the boss The king, the shah
Genie : Say what you wish It's yours, true dish How about A little more baklava?
Genie : Have some of column A Try all of column B
Genie : I'm in the mood To help you, dude You ain't never had A friend like me
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Genie : Oh! Uh!
Genie : This the big part! Watch out!
Genie : This the big part! Oh!
Genie : Can your friends do this? Can your friends do that?
Genie : Can your friends pull this
Genie : Outta they little hat?
Genie : Can your friends go
Genie : (BEATBOXING)
Genie : I'm the genie of the lamp I can sing, rap, dance If you give me a chance
Genie : Don't sit there buggy-eyed I'm here to answer All your midday prayers
Genie : (GENIES VOCALIZING)
Genie : You got me bona fide Certified Got a genie For your charge d'affaires
Genie : I got a powerful urge To help you out So what you wish? I really wanna know
Genie : You got a list that's Three miles long, no doubt
Genie : All you gotta do Is rub like so
Genie : Mister...
Aladdin : Aladdin.
Genie : Yes!
Genie : One wish or two or three
Genie : Well, I'm on the job You big nabob You ain't never had a friend Never had a friend
Genie : You ain't never had a friend Never had a friend
Genie : You ain't never had A friend Like me
Genie : You ain't never had A friend like me
Genie : You can clap now.
Genie : (MIMICS MIC DROP)
Genie : (MIMICS CHEERING)
Genie : No, no, no. Please, please.
Genie : You can thank me outside. In the sun.
Genie : When you wish us out.
Aladdin : So, how does it work?
Genie : You're kidding, right?
Genie : The whole song was the instructions!
Genie : Obviously, you can't dance and listen at the same time.
Genie : So, here's the basics. Step one, rub the lamp.
Genie : Step two, say what you want. Step three...
Genie : there is no step three. See, it's that easy.
Genie : You get three wishes... they must begin with rubbing the lamp and saying, "I wish." Got it?
Aladdin : I think so.
Genie : Couple other rules.
Genie : You can't wish for more wishes. Three is enough.
Genie : Now, I can't make anybody love anybody or
Genie : (EVIL VOICE) bring anybody back from the dead.
Genie : (NORMAL VOICE) Feel free to interrupt me anytime you don't understand.
Genie : I'm kidding, don't ever interrupt me, no matter what.
Genie : Now, I usually don't have to go through all of this... because by the time the guy gets to me,
Genie : he pretty much knows what he wants... and it generally has to do with
Genie : (EVIL VOICE) tons of money and power!
Genie : (LAUGHING EVILLY)
Genie : (NORMAL VOICE) Do me a favor, do not drink from that cup.
Genie : I promise you there is not enough money and power on earth for you to be satisfied.
Genie : Good? So, what's your first wish?
Aladdin : Mmm... Well, I have to think about it.
Aladdin : I mean, if there are only three...
Aladdin : Why are there only three anyway?
Genie : I don't know, who cares?
Aladdin : You don't know?
Aladdin : I thought you were all-knowing.
Genie : That's 'cause you don't listen.
Genie : I never said I was all-knowing.
Genie : I said I was all-powerful.
Genie : The most powerful being in the universe.
Genie : Look, whatever I don't know, I know I can learn it. Outside in the sun.
Genie : Why are you playing hard to wish?
Genie : I know you can't tell, but I am very pale.
Genie : This is sky blue. My natural pigmentation is navy.
Genie : Give us some sun.
Aladdin : Okay, Genie. I wish for you to get us out of this cave.
Genie : Boom! Booyah! He has made his first wish!
Genie : Thank you for choosing Carpets, Camels and Caravans. Please don't forget to tip your genie on the way out.
Genie : Hey. Hold yourself, kid!
Genie : (GENIE WHOOPING)
Genie : (CONTINUES WHOOPING)
Aladdin : Whoa.
Genie : Man, look at this world. It's so big!
Genie : Inside the lamp, everything is, like, brass, brass, brass!
Genie : You're like, "Oh! Is that some copper?" Nope, brass!
Genie : Sorta the problem with the genie life... phenomenal cosmic powers, but itty-bitty living space.
Aladdin : So, is this magic, or are you magic?
Genie : Eh, kind of a package deal.
Genie : (SNAPS FINGERS)
Genie : (EXCLAIMS)
Aladdin : Can you warn me before you do that?
Genie : Oh, you'll get used to it.
Aladdin : Right.
Aladdin : So, do I have to make all my wishes here?
Aladdin : I mean, if I take you back to Agrabah, won't people...?
Genie : No, no, no! I can look totally normal.
Genie : Boo!
Aladdin : Right, totally normal.
Genie : (EXCLAIMS)
Aladdin : Still blue.
Aladdin : Do we need the top knot?
Genie : That's my little cherry on top!
Aladdin : Okay, okay.
Genie : So, what are you gonna wish?
Aladdin : Oh, I haven't thought about that.
Genie : Mmm. You really are not that guy.
Aladdin : Okay.
Genie : So, what would you wish for?
Genie : Mmm.
Genie : No one's ever asked me that before.
Genie : It's an easy one, though.
Genie : I'd wish to be free.
Genie : To not have to say, "Poof! Can I help you?"
Genie : "Poof! What would you like?"
Genie : "Welcome to the lamp. May I take your order, please?"
Genie : Freedom. I wish to be... to be human.
Aladdin : Why don't you just set yourself free?
Genie : (LAUGHING)
Genie : Carpet! Did you hear what this boy said? Why don't I set myself free?
Genie : Only way a genie gets to be free... is if the owner of the lamp
Genie : uses one of his wishes to set him free...
Genie : and the last time that happened was, like, the fourth of Never-ary.
Aladdin : I'll do it. I've got three, right?
Genie : Actually, you have two left.
Genie : You used one to get out of the cave. Remember?
Aladdin : Did I? Or did you?
Aladdin : I thought I had to be rubbing the lamp.
Genie : Okay, little street boy. Let's rewind the tape.
Aladdin : Okay, Genie. I wish... Ooh! Little monkey with the lamp trick!
Genie : Never seen that one before.
Genie : I'll keep my eye on you.
Aladdin : At least now, I can use my third wish to set you free.
Genie : Here's the thing about wishes...
Genie : the more you have, the more you want.
Aladdin : That's not me.
Genie : Mmm.
Genie : We'll see about that.
Aladdin : But there is something.
Genie : Uh-oh.
Genie : Seen that face before.
Genie : Who is she? Who's the girl?
Aladdin : She's a princess.
Genie : Aw, aren't they all?
Genie : "Treat your woman like a queen," I always say.
Aladdin : No, she's an actual princess.
Genie : Well, I already told you, I can't make anyone love anyone,
Aladdin : No, no. We had a connection.
Genie : Did they?
Aladdin : She is smart, and kind, and so beautiful.
Aladdin : But she has to marry a...
Aladdin : Hey! Can you make me a prince?
Genie : There's a lot of gray area in "make me a prince."
Genie : I could just make you a prince.
Aladdin : Oh, no.
Genie : Right. You'd be snuggled up with that dude for the rest of your life.
Fake Prince : Yo, y'all seen my palace?
Genie : Be specific with your words. The deal is in the detail.
Aladdin : Got it.
Genie : Which I don't really understand because if she already likes you... why change?
Aladdin : I told you, she has to marry a prince.
Fake Prince : I just wanna go home, man!
Genie : Okay, I can do that.
Genie : An official wish this time, for those of us who are counting... which now, I am one.
Aladdin : Genie, I wish...
Genie : Lamp.
Aladdin : Oh, sorry.
Aladdin : All right. Genie...
Genie : Don't hurt him, Genie!
Aladdin : I wish to become a prince.
Genie : Back up, boy. I need some room to work.
Genie : I'm about to fabulize you.
Aladdin : (GENIE WHOOPING) Genie?
Genie : (GENIE SHOUTING)
Genie : Little head-spinney. Better though, right?
Aladdin : (BREATHLESSLY) I think I'm getting used to it.
Genie : Okay, a prince, a prince.
Genie : Obviously, the ghetto-chic is not gonna work.
Genie : I'm feeling a periwinkle.
Aladdin : What's periwinkle?
Genie : No! Chartreuse.
Genie : (GASPS) Cerise!
Genie : Ah! (GROANS)
Genie : The lines are all wrong.
Aladdin : What is this?
Genie : The color clashes with your skin tone, the silhouette is confused.
Aladdin : This is a big hat!
Genie : No, that is not a big hat.
Genie : Come on, Genie! Gotta kick the door down! We gotta go bold and gold!
Genie : (GENIE YELLS)
Genie : (EXCLAIMS) No!
Aladdin : We've gone too far.
Genie : Genie, you're slippin'! It's gotta be neutral for the desert.
Genie : Ivory, beige, bone, Albion.
Aladdin : It's a little heavy.
Genie : (GASPS DEEPLY)
Genie : White.
Genie : Oh! And the crowd goes wild! Oh!
Genie : The genie! The genie's on fire!
Genie : The genie's on fire, folks!
Genie : Don't hurt him, Genie! Don't scald him!
Genie : Somebody cool me down!
Genie : Somebody put me out! I'm too much!
Genie : Ow! I'm back!
Genie : So, what do you think?
Aladdin : I like it.
Genie : Of course you like it, boy! I made it!
Aladdin : I think that's me.
Genie : Strictly speaking, it is me. I mean, I did most of the work. You was just standing there.
Genie : But I hear you.
Aladdin : But won't people recognize me?
Genie : Nobody'll recognize you. That's how genie magic works.
Genie : People see what they're told to see.
Aladdin : Right. Who am I?
Genie : Who...? (SCOFFS)
Genie : Prince Ali?
Aladdin : From?
Genie : Duh! From Ababwa.
Aladdin : A-bub-wha?
Genie : (SIGHS) You're not listenin'. Ababwa.
Aladdin : Is that a real place?
Genie : Yeah! Like, everybody knows about it.
Genie : It has a brochure.
Genie : Little hot in the summer, temperate in the fall. But no, I'll let you read it en route.
Aladdin : How are we gonna get there?
Genie : I guess you can't ride a chimp.
Genie : Don't you just love a moonwalking monkey?
Genie : Uh-uh. Hold it there, Abu.
Genie : Donkey. Too small.
Genie : Too obvious.
Genie : We need somethin' robust!
Genie : (TRUMPETS)
Genie : (TRUMPETING)
Genie : Relax, Abu. It's just for a minute.
Aladdin : Whoa.
Aladdin : Prince Ali of Ababwa.
Genie : And now, for your entourage!
Aladdin : What?
Aladdin : What's happening? Genie?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DISTANT THUDDING)
(ALARMED CHATTER)
Soldier1 : Clear the way!
Soldier2 : Clear the way!
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Soldier1 : Clear the way!
(DRUMS POUNDING)
(PLAYING FANFARE)
All : Make way for Prince Ali
All : Say hey, it's Prince Ali
Genie : Hey, clear the way In the old bazaar Hey, you, let us through It's a brand new star
Genie : Oh, come Be the first On your block To meet his eye
Genie : Make way, here he comes Ring bells, bang the drums You're gonna love this guy
Genie : Prince Ali, fabulous he Ali Ababwa
Genie : Show some respect Boy, genuflect Down on one knee
Genie : Now, try your best To stay calm Brush up Your Friday salaam
Genie : Then come and meet His spectacular coterie
Genie : Prince Ali, mighty is he Ali Ababwa
Genie : Strong as ten regular men Definitely
Genie : (GENIE LAUGHS)
Genie : He's faced The galloping hordes A hundred bad guys With swords
Genie : Who sent those goons To their lords? Why, Prince Ali
Genie : Fellas, he's got
All : 75 golden camels
Genie : Now the ladies What he got?
All : Purple peacocks He's got 53
Genie : When it comes To exotic-type mammals Everybody, help me out!
All : He's got a zoo I'm telling you
Genie : It's a world-class Menagerie!
Genie : Prince Ali, handsome is he Ali Ababwa
Genie : That physique How can I speak? Weak in my knees So yummy boy!
Genie : So get on out In that square Adjust your veil And prepare
Genie : To gawk and grovel and stare At Prince Ali! Oops. -(WOMEN GASP)
All : - He's got 95 white Persian monkeys
Genie : - He's got some monkeys A bunch of monkeys!
All : - And to view them He charges no fee  He's generous, so generous
All : He's got 10,000 servants And flunkies Proud to work for him
All : Bow to his whim Love serving him
Genie;All : - They're just lousy With loyalty To
All : - Ali Prince Ali
Genie;All : Prince A...
Genie : We waitin' for you!
Genie : We're not goin' till you go!
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
Genie : You can do it!
Genie : There it is!
Genie;All :  Prince Ali Amorous he Ali Ababwa
Genie : Heard your princess was hot Where is she?
Genie : And that Good people, is why He got all cute And dropped by
Genie : - With
All : - With 60 elephants Llamas galore
Genie : For real?
All : With his bears and lions A brass band and more
Genie : What?
All : With his 40 fakirs His cooks, his bakers His birds that warble on key Make way
All : For Prince Ali
(MUSIC ENDS) (CROWD CHEERING)
(CRACKERS BURSTING)
(TRUMPETING)
Aladdin : Where are they?
Genie : Relax.
Aladdin : What is taking so long?
(DOOR OPENS)
Genie : Here comes the man.
Genie : What are you doing? Put your arms down.
Aladdin : I'm presenting it.
Genie : Put your arms down!
Sultan : It's a pleasure to welcome you to Agrabah, Prince Ali.
Aladdin : Oh.
Genie : How did you break that?
Aladdin : I don't know, it fell off.
Genie : It's a pleasure to meet him, probably.
Aladdin : Uh... It's just as much a pleasure for me, Your Highness, sir.
Aladdin : You look very serene.
Genie : That's a curtsy, not a bow. Stand up.
Jafar : I'm afraid I'm unfamiliar with Ababwa.
Genie : Well, it's North.
Aladdin : It's south.
Aladdin : Uh, we have a north and a south.
Iago : What?
Genie : It's near, if you were to go, it's...
Aladdin : Around there, you can find it, if you just look.
Genie : Don't help me.
Sultan : The world is changing quickly, Jafar.
Sultan : It seems as if there is a new country every day. (CHUCKLES)
Aladdin : (LAUGHING)
Genie : Don't touch me. Don't touch me.
Aladdin : Well, yes, you are very wise.
Genie : Uh, tell him that we have gifts, please.
Aladdin : (CLEARS THROAT) Oh, right! We have things.
Aladdin : Gifts!
Aladdin : Did you organize this?
(EXCLAIMS) (DOOR OPENS)
Aladdin : Yes, here we are. Gifts coming right up!
Aladdin : We have spices, golden camels, and spoons, tiny spoons!
Dalia : Spoons!
Aladdin : How do they make them that tiny?
Aladdin : We have jams!
Jafar : Jams?
Iago : Jams?
Aladdin : Yes, jams! Yam jams, fig jams.
Dalia : Yam jams!
Aladdin : And date jams.
Aladdin : Seedless, delicious, exotic jams.
Genie : Move away from the jams.
Aladdin : What?
Genie : We have jewels.
Aladdin : (CLEARS THROAT) Jewels! We have them! And, uh, that!
Aladdin : Over there,
Aladdin : hidden for suspense.
Genie : Whew!
Aladdin : Ta-da!
Aladdin : Uh...
Jasmine : It's a wheel?
Aladdin : It's, uh, very expensive.
Jasmine : And what do you hope to buy with this expensive?
Aladdin : You!
Aladdin : (PEOPLE GASP) (IAGO SQUAWKS)
Genie : (WHISPERS) Wow!
Aladdin : No! No, no, no. A moment with you, a moment. That's not...
(MIMICS EXPLOSION)
Jasmine : Are you suggesting I am for sale?
Aladdin : Of course...
Aladdin : not! No, of course not! No!
Genie : It's cold and it's dark in that lamp.
Genie : But I prefer it to this.
Jasmine : Please excuse me. I need to go and find some bread.
Dalia : For the jams.
Aladdin : No! That's not what I meant. I...
Dalia : You did great.
Aladdin : That's not what I meant.
Genie : Just leave her alone. You didn't do great.
Sultan : You will get the chance to speak again.
Sultan : We hope you can join us tonight, Prince Ali,
Sultan : when we celebrate our harvest.
Aladdin : Of course, your serene self.
Aladdin : We will join you.
Iago : Smooth.
Genie : In 10,000 years... I've never been that embarrassed.
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING AND CHEERING)
Genie : Don't worry. You are not out of the game yet. Just do whatever you'd normally do at a party.
Aladdin : I've never been to a party.
Genie : What?
Aladdin : What?
Genie : Oh, you're gonna need to go back to the room, then. You're not messing up my night.
Jafar : Prince Ali.
Jafar : (FIREWORKS CONTINUE)
Jafar : May I have a word? Privately.
Jafar : This doesn't concern your servant.
Genie : Well, be over there minding my business.
(ALADDIN CLEARS THROAT)
Jafar : I know who you are.
Aladdin : You do?
Jafar : Yes.
Jafar : You're a man of great ambition like myself.
Aladdin : I, uh, don't believe we've been properly introduced.
Jafar : Jafar, vizier to the sultan.
Jafar : I could be a valuable ally to help you get what you want.
Aladdin : I, uh... I will think on that. I don't wanna keep the princess waiting.
Jafar : Perhaps I'm not making myself clear.
Jafar : This offer will not be on the table for long, you see.
Jafar : (ECHOING) Prince Ali.
Genie : Excuse me. Prince Ali, your presence is requested.
Genie : So, I guess that's the guy.
Aladdin : Mmm-hmm. That's the guy.
Aladdin : (FOLK MUSIC PLAYING) (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Genie : Okay, there she is. This is your chance.
Aladdin : You know what? There are a lot of people. I don't think I can do this.
Genie : You'll be fine.
Aladdin : Okay.
Genie : This one's gonna be easy.
Genie : Ooh! And look at her handmaid.
Genie : And she's going to get some punch. Feelin' a little thirsty myself.
Aladdin : No! No, no! You can't leave me. They'll see right through me.
Genie : No, they won't. All you have to do is walk over there.
Aladdin : And speak. I also have to speak.
Genie : Okay, listen to me.
Genie : I live in a lamp.
Genie : This is a party.
Genie : Do not mess this up for me. Okay?
Genie : I like to party.
Genie : Go get her!
Aladdin : Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
(ANDERS EXCLAIMS)
Prince Anders : Princess Jasmine! (LAUGHS)
Jasmine : You? You're still here?
Prince Anders : Yes.
Prince Anders : (ANDERS LAUGHING)
Genie : What are you doing?
Aladdin : Hmm
Aladdin : I'm just making sure the water is a good temperature.
Genie : Why are you not over there?
Aladdin : How am I supposed to compete with that?
Aladdin : Look at him. He's so princely.
Genie : You have got to be more confident about what you have to offer.
Aladdin : What do I have to offer? Knowledge of how to steal food? How to jump between buildings?
Aladdin : Now, Prince Ali, he has jewels.
Genie : stop, stop!
Genie : I made you look like a prince on the outside.
Genie : But I didn't change anything on the inside.
Genie : Prince Ali got you to the door... but Aladdin has to open it.
Aladdin : Oh.
Aladdin : See, the sultan does like me!
Genie : Okay, well, maybe he'll let you be his wife.
Jasmine : Look at that, another prince more interested in Baba.
Dalia : I don't know, I think this one might be different.
Dalia : And he comes with an incredibly attractive friend. Please make it work.
Jasmine : And what about Prince Ali?
Dalia : Oh, look at him. He's trying so hard.
Jasmine : And that's the problem.
Genie : Showtime.
Aladdin : No. I'm waiting for the right moment.
Genie : No. No waiting. We're done waiting.
Aladdin : No, I'm in charge. Okay? I say when it's the right moment.
(BLOWING) (SHOES SQUEAKING)
Aladdin : Really? Really?
Dalia : He's here. Say something, act natural.
Dalia : (FORCING LAUGH) Hi!
Aladdin : I'm sorry for the jams, and the jewels... (STAMMERS) and the buying you.
Aladdin : That wasn't me. It was me, I don't... It was me, I don't have a twin or anything, but I...
Aladdin : Um...
Aladdin : (APPLAUSE)
Jasmine : Dance? I'd love to.
Aladdin : Yes.
(MOUTHS)
(WHISPERS)
(SLOW FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS) (WHISPERS)
(MOUTHING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC PICKS UP TEMPO) (CROWD EXCLAIMS)
(MOUTHING)
(CROWD EXCLAIMS)
(PEOPLE GASP)
(CROWD CLAPPING RHYTHMICALLY)
(ALL GASP)
(CHEERING)
All : Bravo! Well done!
Jafar : Something very strange about him.
Jafar : Keep a close eye on Prince Ali.
Aladdin : She just walked out.
Genie : Maybe I went a tad far with the back flip... but that dance may be the best thing you ever do in your life!
Aladdin : I was pretty good.
Aladdin : But nothing seems to impress her.
Genie : Yeah, it's crazy. Not gems or jams or jewels.
Genie : If I can't impress her, I wonder who can.
Aladdin : What's that supposed to mean?
Genie : I'm just sayin' try being yourself.
Aladdin : But she has to marry a prince.
Aladdin : (SIGHS) If I just had a few more minutes with her, I know I could...
Aladdin : You need to get me over there.
Genie : Is that an official wish?
Aladdin : No. It's a favor. For a friend.
Genie : Oh, yeah, see, genies don't really have friends.
Aladdin : I thought you said you never had a friend like me.
Genie : No, I said you never had a friend like me!
Genie : When you're a genie, somebody always wants something from ya. It's awkward.
Aladdin : You're right, you're right. Besides, it would've involved distracting a certain handmaiden...
Genie : Ooh! Ha! I see what you're doing!
Genie : You hooked me. See you there?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Genie : Good evening.
Dalia : How did you get past the guards?
Genie : Oh, uh, I snuck past.
Dalia : All 48 of them?
Dalia : Even the ones that eat fire? Impressive.
Genie : Yes, well, that's what people say about me! (CHUCKLES)
Genie : Well, that didn't come out the right way.
Genie : No one says that. I don't know why I said that.
Genie : Uh...
Dalia : (GASPS) They're beautiful! She will hate them.
Dalia : Tell Prince Ali the way to her heart is through her mind.
Genie : Oh, actually, these are from me to you.
Dalia : Could you excuse me one moment?
Genie : Wait, no, just...
(BOTH MOUTHING)
Genie : "That's what people say about me." Come on, Genie!
Dalia : My favorites. I accept. Please continue.
Genie : I was noticing how pleasant the evening is.
Genie : At the party, I noticed you noticing...
Genie : how pleasant I am.
Genie : Right. How's this going?
Dalia : It's clumsy, but in a charming sort of a way.
Genie : A stroll.
Genie : Would you like to take an evening stroll?
Dalia : Just the two of us? On purpose?
Genie : Yes, as people.
Dalia : Just one more second.
Genie : Okay.
Genie : Why would I say "as people"?
Genie : That kid is contagious!
Dalia : I've never done this before. How does it work?
Dalia : Do you like sheep cheese?
Genie : Uh...
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Jasmine : Come in.
Aladdin : Actually, I'm already in.
Jasmine : Don't move.
(GROWLING)
Aladdin : I just came back because you left...
Jasmine : How did you get there?
Aladdin : Magic carpet?
Aladdin : (SCOFFS)
Jasmine : Actually, I'm glad you are here.
Aladdin : You are?
Jasmine : I've been trying to find Ababwa, but it doesn't seem to be on any of my maps.
Jasmine : Care to show me?
Aladdin : I'd love to.
Aladdin : (GROWLS)
Jasmine : Rajah, let's not eat the prince today. He needs his legs for dancing.
Aladdin : Did I go too far with the back flip?
Jasmine : A little.
Jasmine : Ababwa?
Aladdin : Yes, Genie, I need to find Ababwa.
Dalia : My other brother... the short one, not the one who gifted me a goat, he's married...
Aladdin : She has maps, lots of maps. (CLEARS THROAT)
Aladdin : Ababwa, of course.
Aladdin : Ababwa.
Dalia : Yak napkins are not easy to find...
(GENIE CHUCKLES)
(MOUTHING)
Jasmine : Have you lost your country?
Aladdin : My country? No, no. (CHUCKLES) Uh...
Aladdin : There it is.
Jasmine : (SCOFFS) I don't think so. I've been...
Jasmine : How did I not see that?
Aladdin : Who needs maps anyway?
Aladdin : They're old and useless, and add no practical value.
Jasmine : Maps are how I see the world.
Aladdin : I thought a princess could go anywhere.
Jasmine : Not this princess.
Aladdin : Well, would you wanna...? Oh. Uh...
Aladdin : Sorry, sorry.
Aladdin : Rajah!
Aladdin : (GROWLS) Oh.
Aladdin : Thanks for that. (PURRS)
Aladdin : I was saying you should see these places.
Aladdin : I mean, there's a whole world outside of books and maps.
Aladdin : Do you want to?
Jasmine : How? Every door is guarded.
Aladdin : Who said anything about a door?
Jasmine : What are you doing?
Aladdin : Sometimes, Princess...
Aladdin : sometimes, you just have to take a risk.
(JASMINE GASPS)
Jasmine : What just happened?
Jasmine : What?
Jasmine : Is this...?
Aladdin : A magic carpet?
Aladdin : Do you trust me?
Jasmine : What did you say?
Jasmine : Yes.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(RAJAH WHINES)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING IN DISTANCE)
Aladdin : (SINGING) I can show you the world
Aladdin : Shining, shimmering Splendid
Aladdin : Tell me, Princess
Aladdin : Now when did you last Let your heart decide?
Aladdin : I can open your eyes
Aladdin : Take you wonder by wonder
Aladdin : Over, sideways and under On a magic carpet ride
Aladdin : A whole new world
Aladdin : A new fantastic Point of view
Aladdin : No one to tell us no Or where to go
Aladdin : Or say we're only dreaming
Jasmine : A whole new world
Jasmine : A dazzling place I never knew
Jasmine : But when I'm way up here It's crystal clear
Jasmine : That now I'm in A whole new world With you
Aladdin : Now I'm in A whole new world with you
Jasmine : Unbelievable sights
Jasmine : Indescribable
Aladdin;Jasmine : Feeling
Jasmine : Soaring, tumbling Freewheeling Through an endless Diamond sky
Jasmine : A whole new world
Aladdin : Don't you dare Close your eyes
Jasmine : A hundred thousand Things to see
Aladdin : Hold your breath It gets better
Jasmine : I'm like a shooting star I've come so far
Jasmine : I can't go back To where I used to be
Aladdin : A whole new world
Jasmine : Ev'ry turn a surprise
Aladdin : With new horizons To pursue
Jasmine : Ev'ry moment red-letter
Aladdin;Jasmine : I'll chase them anywhere There's time to spare
Aladdin;Jasmine : Let me share This whole new world With you
Aladdin : A whole new world
Jasmine : A whole new world
Aladdin : That's where we'll be
Jasmine : That's where we'll be
Aladdin : A thrilling chase
Jasmine : A wondrous place
Jasmine;Aladdin : For you and me
(DRUMS BEATING) (RHYTHMIC CLAPPING)
(EXCITED CHATTER)
(JASMINE CHUCKLES)
Jasmine : Of all the places you've shown me, this is by far the most beautiful.
Aladdin : Sometimes, you just have to see it from a different perspective.
Jasmine : It's them, the people. They make it beautiful.
Jasmine : And they deserve a leader who knows that.
Jasmine : I don't know why I think it could be me.
Aladdin : Because it should be you.
Jasmine : You think so?
Aladdin : Does it matter what I think?
Jasmine : Oh, look at that adorable monkey down there. Is that Abu?
Aladdin : No, no, it couldn't be Abu, he's...
Aladdin : (SIGHS)
Jasmine : So, how many names do you have, Prince Aladdin?
Aladdin : No, no, I...
Jasmine : So who is Prince Ali?
Aladdin : I am Prince Ali.
Jasmine : But how would you know the city so well?
Aladdin : I came to Agrabah early...
Aladdin : because to know a people, you have to see them for yourself. But you already know that.
Aladdin : When we first met, you were disguised in your own city.
Aladdin : You saw us arrive with dancers, an elephant, and a magic carpet.
Aladdin : How could a street thief have all that?
Jasmine : But how could I not recognize you?
Aladdin : People don't see the real you when you're royalty.
Jasmine : I'm sorry. I'm embarrassed. I mean,you've seen more of Agrabah in days than I have in an entire lifetime.
Aladdin : We should... probably head back.
Jasmine : Already?
Aladdin : Until tomorrow, Princess.
Jasmine : Good night.
Aladdin : Good night.
Aladdin : Yes!
(WHOOPING)
Iago : Fascinating.
Genie : Ooh.
Genie : I like that face. Good date?
Aladdin : The best.
Jasmine : But it was better than the best.
Aladdin : She figured out I was Aladdin. You said that wouldn't happen.
Genie : Wow! I mean, genie magic is really just a facade. At some point,
Genie : real character's always gonna shine through.
Genie : But that's a good thing, right? Now, she knows.
Aladdin : Well...
Genie : Well, what?
Jasmine : He told me he was only pretending to be a thief to see the city... but he's actually a prince.
Aladdin : I convinced her that I really was a prince.
Dalia : And you believed him?
Genie : And she believed you?
Jasmine : I think so.
Genie : Eventually, you are going to have to tell her the truth.
Aladdin : Eventually, I will tell her.
Aladdin : Anyway, I sort of am a prince now.
Genie : Oh!
Genie : So, you're gonna drink from that cup.
Dalia : You don't think maybe you want to believe him... because you have to marry a prince, but you can't marry a thief?
Jasmine : No, I believe him. I do.
(IAGO SQUAWKING)
Aladdin : When the time is right, I will tell her.
Aladdin : (CHITTERING)
Aladdin : Morning.
Soldier1 : Morning.
Aladdin : (SIGHS)
Aladdin : Not again.
Aladdin : Please, please.
Aladdin : Gentlemen, I think there's been some sort of confusion. I don't think you know who I am.
Jafar : Oh, no, no.
Jafar : I know who you are.
Jafar : Aladdin.
Aladdin : Aladdin?
Iago : Aladdin.
Aladdin : I don't know who that is. I'm Prince Ali...
Iago : Street rat!
Aladdin : of Ababwa.
Jafar : Prince from a kingdom that doesn't exist...
Jafar : who now possesses a magic carpet from the Cave of Wonders.
Jafar : Seems to me, the only way that's possible...
Iago : Where's your monkey?
Jafar : is if you found a certain treasure.
Jafar : My treasure.
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
Jafar : Where's the lamp?
(SCREECHING)
Aladdin : There's clearly been some sort of misunderstanding. I'm Prince Ali.
Jafar : If I throw you off of that balcony,
Jafar : and you are who you say you are...
Jafar : you will die a watery death.
(GRUNTS)
Jafar : If you survive, it can only be because of the lamp.
Jafar : In which case, I will have my answer.
Jafar : For the last time...
Jafar : where is the lamp?
Aladdin : Listen to me. I don't know who you think I am.
Jafar : Goodbye, Aladdin.
Aladdin : No! No!
(SCREAMING)
Jafar : Hmm.
(CHITTERING)
Genie : Boy, what in the...?
Genie : Whoa. Hey, kid, okay.
Genie : I can't get you out of this unless you make a wish! You have to make a wish! Come on, wake up!
Genie : Okay, try and form the words "I wish."
Genie : Kid, come on, wake up! Wake up.
Genie : You need to think. Think, think.
Genie : Think.
Genie : Okay, okay! A little gray area here, but it's worth a try. (CLEARS THROAT)
Genie : "I, Aladdin, being of sound body and mind... "declare that my second wish "is to be saved from certain doom."
Genie : I took the liberty to backdate that a day. I hope you don't mind.
Genie : Yes! Here we go! Come on!
Genie : (GENIE YELLING)
Genie : (CONTINUES YELLING)
Genie : Come on, kid! Come on! Kid? Kid? Kid, please. Come on! Wake up! Wake up, wake up!
Genie : Kid, wake up. Please.
Genie : (COUGHING)
Genie : Ew.
Genie : Probably could've done that the other direction, but...
Genie : (GASPING)
Genie : How you doing?
Aladdin : (SIGHS) Thanks, Genie.
Genie : Hey, no problem, you know. I was in the neighborhood.
Aladdin : I thought you said no favors.
Aladdin : (STAMMERS)
Aladdin : I thought you said no friends.
Genie : Right. Um... It actually cost you a wish.
Aladdin : (PANTING) Whatever it cost, you saved my life.
Genie : Yeah, that's true.
Genie : I mean, strictly speaking though, it was a team effort.
(CHITTERING)
Aladdin : Thank you.
Aladdin : We have to stop Jafar.
Genie : That's not gonna be easy.
Genie : The sultan trusts him completely.
Genie : He has everybody fooled.
Aladdin : Maybe not everyone.
(DOOR OPENS)
Jafar : I overheard Prince Ali talking to his advisor... about returning with an army to conquer Agrabah.
Sultan : What?
Jafar : Now it appears he's fled in the night.
Sultan : Jasmine.
Jasmine : You heard him say this, Jafar, and you saw him leave?
Iago : Uh-oh.
Jafar : Yes, with my own ears and my own eyes.
Jafar : So, what's the problem now, Princess?
Jasmine : This is the problem, Jafar.
Jasmine : If what you say is true, then why is Prince Ali still here?
Aladdin : Your Majesty.
Jafar : Prince Ali.
Jafar : This is a surprise.
Aladdin : Your Highness, your advisor's not who he says he is.
Jafar : Oh.
Jafar : I'm not who I say I am?
Jasmine : Baba, he tried to kill Prince Ali.
Sultan : Jafar, can you explain this to me?
Jafar : Yes.
(WHOOSHES)
Jafar : My sultan... you know my loyalty belongs to you.
Sultan : Your loyalty... Your loyalty...
Jafar : Yes.
Sultan : Prince Ali, you invited yourself into our city... and we welcomed you as our guest.
Sultan : But I believe your intentions are...
(WHOOSHES)
Sultan : ...deceitful.
Sultan : You're a grave danger to Agrabah and you shall be dealt with as such.
Jasmine : Baba, what are you saying?
Sultan : Enough, Jasmine!
Sultan : Jafar told me of Prince Ali's ambition.
Aladdin : (QUIETLY) His staff.
Sultan : He's here for my throne.
Sultan : Hakim!
(YELLING)
(WHOOSHES)
Jasmine : Baba?
Sultan : (GASPING) What happened?
Aladdin : He had you under a spell.
Jafar : He's not to be trusted, Your Majesty.
Aladdin : He wants your throne.
Sultan : Jafar! You were my most trusted advisor.
Sultan : Hakim! Put him in the dungeon!
(CHUCKLES)
(SQUAWKING)
Jafar : You should think about how quickly the sands of power shift in a storm, Hakim.
Hakim : I am loyal to my sultan, as you should have been.
Hakim : The law is the law.
Sultan : Prince Ali, I must apologize.
Aladdin : Well, Your Highness, there's something I'd like to explain.
Sultan : Your honor and integrity will never again be questioned here in Agrabah.
Aladdin : I...
Sultan : A more noble and sincere young man has never graced the chambers of this palace.
Aladdin : Well, uh...
Genie : Wow.
Sultan : I would be honored to call you my son...
Genie : Ooh!
Sultan : ...if that were something anyone wanted.
Genie : So, you got the girl. I mean, trust me, I had my doubts after your whole jam debacle.
Genie : But you pulled yourself back together a little bit.
Aladdin : I did, didn't I?
Aladdin : I think I finally got the hang of being a prince.
Genie : Oh, well, that's not exactly what I meant.
Aladdin : You were right! People see what they wanna see.
Aladdin : Aladdin is gone. I'm Prince Ali now.
Genie : Wow. Got it all figured out now, huh, kid?
Aladdin : And, you know, I was thinking about my last wish... and I just can't do this without you.
Aladdin : I know I told you I'd use it to set you free, but you heard the sultan.
Aladdin : I can't let everything we worked for fall apart.
Genie : So, you just never tell her the truth?
Genie : You're gonna keep living the lie?
Aladdin : It's not a lie. People can change.
Genie : (SCOFFS) Oh, they can change all right.
Aladdin : And that's a bad thing?
Aladdin : Everything is better now. No one got hurt.
Aladdin : You'd rather me be back on the streets stealing to survive? I thought you'd be happy for me.
Aladdin : But all you cared about was that I use my last wish to set you free.
Genie : Well, kid, I don't care nothin' about that wish.
Genie : This is about you, what's happening to you.
Genie : You'd rather lie to somebody you love than give all of this up.
Aladdin : You don't get it, Genie.
Aladdin : People like me don't get anything except by pretending.
Genie : I think maybe you don't get it.
Genie : The more you gain by pretending, the less you're actually gonna have.
Genie : In 10,000 years, I have never once, ever... called a master a friend.
Genie : I broke the rules for you, I saved your life.
Genie : And for what?
Genie : You are breaking my heart here, kid.
Genie : You're breaking my heart.
Aladdin : Genie, no! Hey, come on!
Aladdin : (GRUNTS)
Aladdin : (SIGHS)
Aladdin : (ABU CHITTERS)
Aladdin : (IAGO SQUAWKS)
Iago : Lamp. Lamp. Lamp. Master. Lamp.
Aladdin : Who does he think he is? He's supposed to serve me.
Aladdin : I'm the same as I always was on the inside. Right, Abu?
Aladdin : (ABU SCREECHES)
Aladdin : Hey!
Genie : Aah! Are you kidding? Now, why would you rub the thing under the...
Genie : archway?
Jafar : (LAUGHING)
Aladdin : Riffraff Street rat
Aladdin : Would they think that
Aladdin : If they look much closer?
Aladdin : Still, I can't Play a prince here No, siree
Aladdin : Gotta tell the truth I can't pretend
Aladdin : Even if it means This dream will end
Aladdin : Even if she walks away
Aladdin : From me
Aladdin : (PEOPLE CHATTERING IN DISTANCE)
Sultan : Jafar.
Sultan : You should have left Agrabah while you had the chance.
Jafar : Why leave when the city belongs to me now?
Sultan : It's over, Jafar.
Iago : Oh, good for you.
Jafar : I've endured your spineless incompetence for long enough now.
Sultan : Hakim.
Iago : Old fool.
Jafar : Genie! For my first wish,
Jafar : I wish to be sultan of Agrabah!
Sultan : What?
Genie : As you wish, Master.
Jasmine : No!
(CRACKLING)
(IAGO SQUAWKS)
(YELLING)
(YELLING CONTINUES)
(PANTING)
(RAJAH GROWLS)
Sultan : Hakim.
Jafar : Hakim!
Jafar : You obey the sultan, so you obey me now.
Jafar : You know the law, Hakim!
Jasmine : No.
Jafar : My sultan!
Soldiers : My sultan!
(SPEARS THUMPING)
Jafar : Hakim.
Jafar : Marshal an army to invade Shirabad.
Sultan : Shirabad!
Jasmine : You cannot...
Jafar : I think we've heard enough from you, Princess.
Jafar : It's time you start doing what you should have done all along.
Jafar : Stay silent.
Jafar : Guards, remove her!
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
(SNARLING)
Jafar : Control that cat if you know what's good for you.
Jasmine : Rajah.
Jasmine : Rajah!
Jasmine : Rajah! It's all right.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(CHUCKLES)
Sultan : Don't touch her!
Jasmine : Baba.
Sultan : Jasmine.
(RAJAH WHINES)
Jafar : And understand it's better for you to be seen and not heard. I think we've heard enough from you, Princess.
Jafar : Stay silent.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
Jasmine : (SINGING) Written in stone Ev'ry rule, ev'ry word
Jasmine : Centuries old And unbending
Jasmine : "Stay in your place Better seen and not heard"
Jasmine : Well, now that story Is ending
Jasmine : (INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Jasmine : 'Cause I I cannot start to crumble
Jasmine : So come on and try Try to shut me And cut me down
Jasmine : I won't be silenced You can't keep me quiet
Jasmine : Won't tremble When you try it
Jasmine : All I know is I won't go speechless Speechless
Jasmine : Let the storm in I cannot be broken
Jasmine : No, I won't live unspoken
Jasmine : 'Cause I know That I won't go speechless
Jasmine : Try to lock me In this cage
Jasmine : I won't just lay me down And die
Jasmine : I will take These broken wings And watch me Burn across the sky
Jasmine : Hear the echo saying I won't be silenced
Jasmine : Though you wanna see me Tremble when you try it
Jasmine : All I know is I won't go speechless Speechless
Jasmine : 'Cause I'll breathe When they try To suffocate me
Jasmine : Don't you underestimate me
Jasmine : 'Cause I know that I won't go speechless
Jasmine : All I know is I won't go speechless
Jasmine : Speechless
(PANTING)
Jasmine : Hakim!
Jafar : Take her away!
Jafar : Tell them, Hakim.
Jasmine : You were just a boy when your father came to work the grounds.
Jasmine : But you have risen up to become our most trusted soldier.
Jasmine : As a man, I know you to be both loyal and just.
Jasmine : But now you have to choose.
Jasmine : Duty isn't always honor.
Jasmine : Our greatest challenge isn't speaking up against our enemies...
Jasmine : but defying those whose approval we seek the most.
Jasmine : Jafar is not worthy of your admiration nor your sacrifice.
Jafar : I wish nothing but glory for the kingdom of Agrabah.
Jasmine : No. You seek glory for yourself.
Jasmine : And you would win it off the backs of my people!
Jasmine : Hakim, these men,
Jasmine : they will follow where you lead... but it's up to you.
Jasmine : Will you stand silent while Jafar destroys our beloved kingdom... or will you do what is right...
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Jasmine : and stand with the people of Agrabah?
Hakim : My princess.
Hakim : Forgive me, my sultan.
Jafar : Hakim.
Hakim : Guards, arrest the vizier!
(IAGO SQUAWKS) (RAJAH ROARS)
Iago : Lamp! Rub the lamp.
Jafar : So, this is how it will be.
Jafar : Not even the title of sultan will wake the herd from their sleep.
Jafar : I should've known.
Jafar : If you won't bow before a sultan, you will cower before a sorcerer.
Jafar : Genie! I wish to become the most powerful sorcerer there is!
Genie : As you wish, Master.
(CRACKLING)
(SQUAWKING)
(HISSING)
Iago : (SQUAWKS) This could be fun.
(RAJAH GROWLS)
Jafar : Hakim, I had such big plans for you.
Jafar : But now...
Jafar : you are no longer of any use to me.
Jafar : Perhaps your men would like to follow you to the dungeon.
(STAFF THUDS) (GUARDS SCREAMING)
Jafar : You too.
Iago : Prince Ali!
Jafar : If it isn't our Prince Ali.
Jasmine : Ali!
Jafar : Or should I say...
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
Jafar : Aladdin.
Jasmine : Aladdin.
Jafar : He's been pretending the entire time.
Jafar : An impostor. There is no Prince Ali. There never was.
Jafar : He's nothing but a lying thief.
Aladdin : I'm sorry.
Jafar : You're insignificant. An irritation I no longer need to tolerate once I...
Jafar : ensure your agonizing death by banishing you to the ends of the earth.
Jasmine : No!
Aladdin : (SCREAMING)
Aladdin : (WIND WHISTLING)
Aladdin : (SHIVERING)
Aladdin : No. No!
Aladdin : Abu.
Aladdin : Abu!
Jafar : I could simply kill you all.
Jafar : But that would be inadequate repayment for years of humiliation and neglect.
Jafar : (BLOWS)
Jafar : "Remember your place, Jafar." "You forget yourself, Jafar."
Sultan : Jafar.
Jafar : No, what you need, Baba, is to suffer.
Jafar : Like I have suffered.
Jasmine : Baba?
Jafar : Would watching me rule your kingdom be enough?
Jasmine : Stop!
Jafar : Or watching my armies devour your toothless ally?
Jasmine : Please, make it stop.
Jafar : No, the most suitable punishment would be to make you watch... while I take what you love most.
Jasmine : No, please. Baba.
Jafar : And marry your daughter.
Dalia : No!
(GASPS)
Genie : No.
Sultan : She will never marry you.
(WHOOSHING)
Jasmine : Baba.
Jasmine : I will do as you wish!
Jasmine : Make it stop.
(CHOKING)
(STAFF THUDS)
(DALIA GROANS)
Jasmine : Baba! Baba, are you all right?
Sultan : Jasmine.
Aladdin : Abu!
Aladdin : Abu! Abu!
Aladdin : (WEAK WHISTLING)
Aladdin : (GRUNTING)
Aladdin : Abu.
Aladdin : Are you okay?
Aladdin : Let's get out of here.
Aladdin : No.
Aladdin : (SCREAMING)
Aladdin : (ABU WHIMPERING) (BREATHING WEAKLY)
Aladdin : (GASPING)
Aladdin;Wedding Host :  Your Highness, Sultan, in honesty and sincerity... do you accept Princess Jasmine...?
Jafar :  Yes
Jafar : Yes, I accept.
Jafar : Princess.
Wedding Host : Princess Jasmine, do you accept the sultan to be your husband?
Jafar : Come on, woman.
Iago : Accept.
Jasmine : I...
Jafar : Yes?
Jasmine : I... do not!
Iago : The lamp! The lamp!
Jafar : Stop her!
Sultan : No, Jasmine! No!
Jafar : No! No!
Sultan : (CHUCKLES)
Jafar : The lamp! Iago!
Aladdin : Are you okay?
Jasmine : Yes.
(SQUAWKING)
(ROARS)
Aladdin : Hold on!
(PEOPLE YELPING)
Jasmine : The lamp!
Aladdin : Abu!
(ROARS)
(JASMINE YELPING)
Iago : The lamp!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Aladdin : Carpet, get me up there!
Aladdin : Abu!
(ALADDIN GRUNTS) (IAGO SCREECHES)
Aladdin : Jump!
(JASMINE YELPS)
(SCREAMING)
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
Jafar : No!
(SQUAWKS)
(SCREECHES)
(ALADDIN GRUNTS) (CHITTERS)
Sultan : You're nothing without your staff! Nothing!
(ROARS) (THUNDER CRASHING)
(YELLING)
(PANICKED CHATTER)
(BOTH YELLING AND SCREAMING)
Jasmine : The lamp!
(JASMINE SCREAMING)
Aladdin : Carpet!
Jafar : (CONTINUES YELLING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Sultan : Jasmine.
(SQUAWKS)
Iago : Punish them. Punish them.
Iago : Genie should witness.
(CHITTERING)
Jafar : As the old man said... you should've left Agrabah when you had the chance.
Jafar : I told you before to think bigger.
Jafar : You could've been the most powerful man in the room.
Jafar : But now I hold the lamp. I hold the power.
Jafar : (RUMBLING)
Aladdin : You can't find what you're looking for in that lamp, Jafar.
Aladdin : I tried and failed, and so will you.
Jafar : You think so, but I am sultan!
Jafar : I am the greatest sorcerer the world has ever seen.
Jafar : I will create an empire that history cannot ignore.
Jafar : I can destroy cities.
Jafar : I can destroy kingdoms.
(GRUNTS)
Jafar : And I can destroy you.
Aladdin : True. But who made you a sultan?
Aladdin : Who made you a sorcerer?
Aladdin : There will always be something, some
man, some being... more powerful than you.
Genie : What are you doing?
Aladdin : Genie gave you your power, and he can take it away...
Jafar : He serves me!
Aladdin : For now!
Aladdin : But you'll never have more power than the genie.
(WHOOSHING) (GROANING)
(SCREECHES)
Aladdin : You said it yourself.
Aladdin : You're either most powerful in the room... or you're nothing.
Aladdin : You'll always be second.
Iago : Second! Second!
(IAGO LAUGHS DERISIVELY)
Jafar : Second?
Jafar : Only second?
Jafar : He serves me!
Jafar : I will make sure no one will ever say these words again.
Jafar : Genie!
Jafar : For my final wish, I wish to become the most powerful being in the universe.
Jafar : More powerful than you!
Genie : A lot of gray area in that wish, but, uh...
Genie : most powerful being in the universe coming right up!
(WHOOSHING) (LAUGHING)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(SQUAWKS)
(GROWLING)
(LAUGHING)
Jafar : The most powerful in the universe, at last... second to no one.
Jafar : And I thought I had power before!
Jafar : First, I'll lay waste to those fools in Shirabad.
(YELLING) (CRACKLING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING) (CUFFS CLANG)
What have you done to me?
Aladdin : I haven't done anything to you, Jafar.
Jafar : What have you done to me?
Aladdin : This was your wish, not mine.
(GRUNTS)
Aladdin : A genie might have phenomenal cosmic powers...
Genie : But an itty-bitty living space.
Genie : You see, a genie without a master goes back in their lamp.
Jafar : No! Not the lamp!
(GRUNTING)
Jafar : I will not forget you, boy! Mark my words, I will not forget what you have done to me!
Iago : Goodbye, Jafar!
Jafar : Parrot! You're coming with me!
Jafar : (SQUAWKS) (SCREAMS) No!
(SCREAMING)
Jasmine : Baba, Baba.
Aladdin : Come on.
Genie : Couple thousand years in the Cave of Wonders ought to cool you off.
(LAMP WHISTLING)
(DISTANT BOOM)
(CHITTERING)
Sultan : (PANTING) Wait. Wait.
Sultan : How can I ever thank you?
Aladdin : Oh, no. No, you don't need to thank me.
Aladdin : But I hope you accept my apology.
Aladdin : I'm sorry to the both of you.
Jasmine : Especially you.
Jasmine : You deserve so much.
Sultan : We all make mistakes.
Jasmine : Aladdin?
Aladdin : I hope you find what you're looking for.
Genie : Ooh, that's a bit of a mess there, Abu. Let me take care of that for you.
(CHITTERING EXCITEDLY)
(GRUNTS, CHITTERS)
Genie : Beautiful.
Genie : Uh-uh-uh. No, no long faces, all right?
Genie : I got an idea. All right? This is your last wish.
Genie : Royalty was the right idea, okay? We should just riff on that a little bit.
Genie : All right, here's what I'm thinking.
Genie : (DEEP VOICE) Aladdin, warrior prince, a noble heart in a land where thieves run feral!
Genie : Jasmine!
Genie : (NORMAL VOICE) You like it?
Genie : No? Okay, all right. I hear you loud and clear. All right. But this is what you need.
Genie : The governing laws of Agrabah by royal decree.
Genie : Okay? And here it is. "Must marry a prince."
Genie : Right. But you say the words... and this law just, kinda like, goes away.
Genie : And you and the princess are in it together forever.
Aladdin : You can just make the law disappear?
Genie : Pfft! Please. Like it never existed.
Genie : All right. Last wish, let's get it.
Aladdin : Okay. (SIGHS) Last wish.
Aladdin : Genie?
Genie : I'm ready, hold on. Here we go.
Aladdin : I wish...
Genie : Third and final wish.
Aladdin : I wish to set you free.
Genie : What?
Genie : Whoa. What? Oh!
Genie : (GASPS) Wait.
Genie : Wait, am I...?
Genie : Wait, wait, wait. Um... Tell me to do something.
Aladdin : Um... Get me some jams.
Genie : (HESITANTLY) Get it yourself?
Genie : (CHUCKLES) Get your own jams!
(CHUCKLES)
Genie : Thank you. Thank you.
Aladdin : No. Thank you, Genie. I owe you everything.
Aladdin : What are you gonna do now?
Genie : Um...
Genie : Actually, there is this handmaiden...
Genie : that I would love to travel the world with.
Genie : If she'll have me.
Dalia : When do we leave? Also, I want children.
Genie : Yes. Two of them.
Dalia : Lian and Omar, three years apart.
Dalia : They will worship us both and ask lots of questions... and you will entertain them with stories and songs.
Genie : ...and he's handsome like me.
Genie : We'll have a boat.
Dalia : A large one with multiple levels and magnificent sails.
Genie : I was thinking more of a smaller one.
Dalia : Perfect.
Genie : Perfect. (CHUCKLES)
Sultan : Sit with me, my child.
Sultan : I'm sorry.
Jasmine : Baba, why are you...?
Sultan : Please, let me finish.
Sultan : I feared losing you. Like I lost your mother.
Sultan : All I saw was my little girl, not the woman you have become.
Sultan : You have shown me courage and strength.
Sultan : You are the future of Agrabah.
Sultan : (GASPS)
Sultan : You shall be the next sultan.
Sultan : (SULTAN EXHALES)
Jasmine : Thank you, Baba.
Sultan : And as sultan, you may change the law.
Jasmine : He is a good man.
Genie : Where'd he go?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(SIGHS) (ABU CHITTERS)
Jasmine : Stop, thief. Your sultan commands it.
(CROWD MURMURS)
Aladdin : Sultan?
Aladdin : Does that mean I'm in trouble?
Jasmine : Only because you got caught.
(ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(UPBEAT JAZZY MUSIC PLAYING) (CROWD CHEERING)
(CROWD SHOUTING IN UNISON)
Genie : (SINGING) Can your friends do this?
(PLAYING FLUTE)
(JASMINE BEATBOXING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(CROWD CHEERS)
(CROWD SHOUTING IN UNISON)
Genie : You ain't never had A friend like me
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
-Yeah -Another one
You know it's Will Smith And DJ Khaled!  Whoo!
Too late Y'all done wound me up Hurry up! Too late Y'all done wound me up Hurry up!
'Bout to show you What I'm workin' with
It's the Ali Baba It's the big papa
It's the blue pants Jasmine, like the flower
It's the grant you wishes That don't even cost a dollar
You ride in on a carpet When you ride in Wanna holler like
Ay Tell me where you wanna go
Hold up! Don't tell me, I already know Watch out It's the genie with a attitude
Three wishes What I need to make true? Mister, Mister
-Tell me whatever you need -What you need?
Anything rearranged Even climate can change You ain't never had A friend like me
Just a lamp and a rub away From whatever you want
Habibi, let me show you The dream
Just whisper If you don't wanna Shout out what you need But I promise you ain't never Had a friend like me
Tell the angels and gods Pass the baklava Make 'em travel from close Or make 'em travel from far Well, this is your chance, man Wish from the soul
When I'm out of the lamp, man I'm out of control I got gold on my shoes Temple with jewels
A room for wise men And plenty for fools I don't want you to lose Tryin' to help ya, dude
You ain't never had A friend like me
-Go big time! Wish big time! Go big time!
-Go big time! -Big time! Wish big time! -Big time! Go big time!
-Let me see you flex on her, Shine on he, Style on her, Slide on her
Too fly, too fly on her
Just glide on her
Cool as a fan I'm the coolest Bluest one of 'em all
You can wish to be rich You can wish to be tall You can wish away the haters You just give me a call
You can wish for what you want 'Cause I'm grantin' 'em all
Mister! Mister! Tell me whatever you need -What you need?
Anything rearranged Even climate can change You ain't never had A friend like me
Just a lamp and a rub away From whatever you want
Habibi, let me show you The dream!
Just whisper If you don't wanna Shout out what you need But I promise you ain't never Had a friend like me
Please don't get me started
Fly like magic carpet
You ain't never had a friend Never had a friend -Never!
-You ain't never Never -Had a -Had a
-Friend -Friend -Like -Like Me!
You ain't never had A friend like me
Never!
I can show you the world
Shining, shimmering splendid
Tell me, Princess
Now when did you last Let your heart decide?
I can open your eyes
Take you wonder by wonder
Over sideways and under On a magic carpet ride
A whole new world
A new fantastic point of view
No one to tell us no Or where to go
Or say we're only dreaming
A whole new world
A dazzling place I never knew
But when I'm way up here
It's crystal clear
That now I'm in A whole new world with you
Now I'm in a whole new world With you
Unbelievable sights
Indescribable feeling
Soaring, tumbling Freewheeling
Through an endless diamond sky
- A whole new world  Don't you dare close your eyes
- A hundred thousand things To see  Hold your breath It gets better
I'm like a shooting star I've come so far
- I can't go back To where I used to be  A whole new world
With new horizons to pursue
I'll chase them anywhere There's time to spare
Let me share This whole new world with you
-A whole new world -A whole new world
A new fantastic point of view
No one to tell us no Or where to go
Or say we're only dreaming Every turn, a surprise A whole new world -
-With new horizons to pursue -Every moment, red-letter
I'll chase them anywhere There's time to spare
-Anywhere, ooh -There's time to spare
Let me share This whole new world with you
-A whole new world -A whole new world
-That's where we'll be -That's where we'll be
-A thrilling chase -A wondrous place
For you and me