Peddler : Oh, I come from a land From a faraway place Where the caravan camels roam
Peddler : Where it's flat and immense And the heat is intense It's barbaric, but hey, it's home
Peddler : When the wind's from the east And the sun's from the west And the sand in the glass is right
Peddler : Come on down, stop on by Hop a carpet and fly To another Arabian night
Peddler : Arabian nights Like Arabian days
Peddler : More often than not Are hotter than hot In a lot of good ways
Peddler : Arabian nights 'Neath Arabian moons
Peddler : A fool off his guard Could fall and fall hard
Peddler : Out there on the dunes
Peddler : Ah, salaam  and good evening to you, worthy friend.
Peddler : Please, please, come closer. Too close. A little too close.
Peddler : There. Welcome to Agrabah,
Peddler : city of mystery, of enchantment,
Peddler : and the finest merchandise this side of the River Jordan, on sale today. Come on down.
Peddler : Look at this. Yes. Combination hookah and coffeemaker. Also makes julienne fries.
Peddler : Will not break. Will not... It broke.
Peddler : Ohh! Look at this. I have never seen one of these intact before.
Peddler : This is the famous Dead Sea Tupperware. Listen. Ah, still good.
Peddler : Wait. Don't go.
Peddler : I can see that you're only interested in the exceptionally rare.
Peddler : I think, then, you would be most rewarded to consider this.
Peddler : Do not be fooled by its commonplace appearance.
Peddler : Like so many things, it is not what is outside, but what is inside that counts.
Peddler : This is no ordinary lamp.
Peddler : It once changed the course of a young man's life.
Peddler : A young man who, like this lamp, was more than what he seemed.
Peddler : A diamond in the rough.
Peddler : Perhaps you would like to hear the tale?
Peddler : It begins on a dark night,
Peddler : where a dark man waits with a dark purpose.
(HORSE NICKERS)
Jafar : You are late.
Gazeem : A thousand apologies, O patient one.
Jafar : You have it, then?
Gazeem : I had to slit a few throats, but I got it.
Gazeem : Ah-ah-ahhh. The treasure.
Gazeem : Ow!
Jafar : Trust me, my pungent friend. You'll get what's coming to you.
Iago : What's coming to you. Awk!
Jafar : Quickly! Follow the trail.
Jafar : Faster.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
Jafar : At last, after all my years of searching,
Jafar : the Cave of Wonders.
Iago : Awk. Cave of Wonders.
Gazeem : By Allah.
Jafar : Now, remember. Bring me the lamp.
Jafar : The rest of the treasure is yours, but the lamp is mine.
Iago : Awk, the lamp. Awk, the lamp.
Iago : Jeez, where'd you dig this bozo up?
Jafar : Shh.
The Cave of Wonders : Who disturbs my slumber?
Gazeem : It is I, Gazeem, a humble thief.
The Cave of Wonders : Know this. Only one may enter here,
The Cave of Wonders : one whose worth lies far within.
The Cave of Wonders : A diamond in the rough.
Jafar : What are you waiting for? Go on.
Jafar : No!
The Cave of Wonders : Seek thee out the diamond in the rough.
Iago : (COUGHING)
Iago : I can't believe it. I just don't believe it. We're never gonna get a hold of that stupid lamp.
Iago : Just forget it. Look at this. Look at this. I'm so ticked off that I'm molting.
Jafar : Patience, Iago. Patience.
Jafar : Gazeem was obviously less than worthy.
Iago : Oh, there's a big surprise. That's incredible, I think I'm gonna have a heart attack and die from that surprise.
Iago : What are we gonna do? We got a big problem here, a big...
Jafar : Yes. Only one may enter.
Jafar : I must find this one, this... Diamond in the rough.
Soldier : Stop! Thief! I'll have your hands for a trophy, street rat.
Aladdin : All this for a loaf of bread?
Aladdin : Whoa!
Aladdin : (SCREAMING)
Soldier : There he is! You won't get away so easy!
Aladdin : You think that was easy?
Aladdin : (GIGGLING)
Soldier : You two, over that way, and you, follow me. We'll find him.
Aladdin : Morning, ladies.
Woman1 : Getting into trouble a little early today, aren't we, Aladdin?
Aladdin : Trouble? No way. You're only in trouble if you get caught.
Soldier : Gotcha.
Aladdin : I'm in trouble.
Soldier : And this time...
(MONKEY SQUEAKING)
Aladdin : Perfect timing, Abu, as usual.
Aladdin : Come on. Let's get outta here.
Aladdin : Gotta keep one jump Ahead of the bread line One swing ahead of the sword
Aladdin : I steal only what I can't afford That's everything
Aladdin : One jump ahead of the lawmen That's all, and that's no joke
Aladdin : These guys don't appreciate I'm broke
Soldier : Riffraff
Soldiers : Street rat
Aladdin : Just a little snack, guys
Soldiers : Rip him open Take it back, guys
Aladdin : I can take a hint Gotta face the facts You're my only friend, Abu
Belly dancers : Oh, it's sad Aladdin's hit the bottom He's become a one-man rise in crime
Woman2 : I'd blame parents Except he hasn't got 'em
Aladdin : Gotta eat to live Gotta steal to eat Tell you all about it When I got the time
Aladdin : One jump ahead of the slowpokes One skip ahead of my doom
Aladdin : Next time gonna use a nom de plume
Soldier : There he is
Aladdin : One jump ahead of the hit men One hit ahead of the flock
Aladdin : I think I'll take a stroll Around the block
Soldier : Stop, thief
Merchant : Vandal
Aladdin : Abu
Woman3 : Scandal
Aladdin : Let's not be too hasty
Woman4 : Still I think he's rather tasty
Aladdin : Gotta eat to live Gotta steal to eat Otherwise we'd get along
Soldiers : Wrong
Soldier : Get him!
Soldier : He's got a sword!
Soldier : You idiots. We've all got swords.
(GROANING)
Aladdin :  One jump ahead of the hoof beats
All :  Vandal!
Aladdin :  One hop ahead of the hump
All :  Street rat!
Aladdin :  One trick ahead of disaster
All :  Scoundrel!
Aladdin : They're quick, but I'm much faster
Aladdin : Here goes, better throw my hand in Wish me happy landin' All I gotta do is jump
(SCREAMING)
Soldier : Yuck! Oy!
Aladdin : And now, esteemed effendi, we feast. All right.
Abu : Yum, yum!
Abu : Uh-oh.
(SIGHS)
Aladdin : Here. Go on. Take it.
(GIGGLING)
(GROANS)
Abu : Ah, don't. Huh?
Man1 : On his way to the palace, I suppose.
Man2 : Another suitor for the princess.
(GIGGLING)
Prince Achmed : Out of my way, you filthy brats.
Aladdin : Hey!
Aladdin : If I were as rich as you, I could afford some manners.
Prince Achmed : Oh. I'll teach you some manners.
Aladdin : Ugh!
(MEN LAUGH)
Aladdin : Look at that, Abu. It's not every day you see a horse with two rear ends.
Prince Achmed : Hah! You are a worthless street rat.
Prince Achmed : You were born a street rat, you'll die a street rat, and only your fleas will mourn you.
Aladdin : I'm not worthless. And I don't have fleas.
Aladdin : Come on, Abu. Let's go home.
Aladdin : Riffraff, street rat
Aladdin : I don't buy that
Aladdin : If only they'd look closer
Aladdin : Would they see a poor boy? No, siree
Aladdin : They'd find out
Aladdin : There's so much more
Aladdin : To me
Aladdin : Someday, Abu, things are gonna change.
Aladdin : We'll be rich, live in a palace, and never have any problems at all.
(ROOSTERS CROWING)
Prince Achmed : I've never been so insulted.
Sultan : Oh, Prince Achmed. You're not leaving so soon, are you?
Prince Achmed : Good luck marrying her off.
Sultan : Oh! Jasmine.
Sultan : Jasmine! Jasmine!
Sultan : Jasmine!
Sultan : (SNARLING)
Sultan : oh!
Sultan : Confound it, Rajah.
Sultan : So, this is why Prince Achmed stormed out.
Jasmine : Oh, Father.
Jasmine : Rajah was just playing with him. Weren't you, Rajah?
Jasmine : You were just playing with that overdressed, self-absorbed Prince Achmed, weren't you?
Jasmine : (BOTH LAUGHING)
Jasmine : (CLEARS THROAT)
Sultan : Dearest, you've got to stop rejecting every suitor who comes to call.
Sultan : The law says you must be married to a prince
Sultan : by your next birthday.
Jasmine : The law is wrong.
Sultan : You've only got three more days.
Jasmine : Father, I hate being forced into this. If I do marry, I want it to be for love.
Sultan : Jasmine,
Sultan : it's not only this law.
Sultan : I'm not going to be around forever, and, well, I...
Sultan : I just want to make sure you're taken care of.
Sultan : Provided for.
Jasmine : Please try to understand. I've never done a thing on my own.
Jasmine : I've never had any real friends.
Jasmine : (GRUMBLES)
Jasmine : Except you, Rajah.
Jasmine : I've never even been outside the palace walls.
Sultan : But, Jasmine, you're a princess.
Jasmine : Then maybe I don't want to be a princess anymore.
Sultan : Oooh! I... I...
Sultan : Allah forbid you should have any daughters.
Rajah : Hmm?
Sultan : I don't know where she gets it from.
Sultan : Her mother wasn't nearly so picky.
Sultan : Oh! Ah, Jafar.
Sultan : My most trusted advisor. I am in desperate need of your wisdom.
Jafar : My life is but to serve you, my lord.
Sultan : It's this suitor business. Jasmine refuses to choose a husband. I'm at my wit's end.
Iago : Awk! Wit's end!
Sultan : (LAUGHING) Oh!
Sultan : Have a cracker, pretty Polly.
Jafar : Your Majesty certainly has a way with dumb animals.
Iago : (GRUMBLES)
Jafar : Now, then, perhaps I can divine a solution to this thorny problem.
Sultan : If anyone can help, it's you.
Jafar : But it would require the use of the mystic blue diamond.
Sultan : Oh. Uh, my ring? But it's been in the family for years.
Jafar : It is necessary to find the princess a suitor.
Jafar : Don't worry.
Jafar : Everything will be fine. Everything will be fine.
Jafar : The diamond.
Sultan : Here, Jafar. Whatever you need will be fine.
Jafar : You are most gracious, my liege. Now, run along and play with your little toys, hmm?
Sultan : Yes. That will be pretty good.
Sultan : (SPITS, COUGHS)
Iago : I can't take it anymore!
Iago : If I gotta choke down on one more of those moldy, disgusting crackers...
Iago : Bam! Whack!
Jafar : Calm yourself, Iago.
Iago : Then I'd grab him around the head. Whack!
Jafar : Soon I will be sultan, not that addlepated twit.
Iago : And then I stuff the crackers down his throat. Ha, ha!
(WHINING)
Jasmine : Oh, I'm sorry, Rajah.
Jasmine : But I can't stay here and have my life lived for me.
Jasmine : I'll miss you.
Jasmine : (WHIMPERS)
Jasmine : Goodbye.
Jasmine : (VENDORS CALLING OUT)
Aladdin : Okay, Abu. Go.
Merchant : Try this. Your taste buds will dance and sing.
Merchant : (SQUEAKING) igh!
Merchant : Hey, Get your paws off that.
(TAUNTING)
Merchant : Why, you...
Merchant : Get away from here, you cursed, filthy ape!
Abu : (Goodbye.)
Aladdin : Nice going, Abu.
(monkey)
Aladdin : Breakfast is served.
Merchant2 : Pretty lady, buy a pot. No finer pot in brass or silver.
Merchant3 : Sugar dates. Sugar dates and figs. Sugar dates and pistachios.
Merchant4 : Would the lady like a necklace? A pretty necklace for a pretty lady.
Merchant5 : Fresh fish!
We catch 'em, you buy 'em!
Jasmine : Oh, no.
Jasmine : I don't think so.
Fire Player : Oh!
Jasmine : Oh!
Jasmine : Excuse me.
Fire Player : oh! (BELCHES)
Jasmine : I'm really very sorry.
Aladdin : Wow.
Abu : Uh-oh.
Abu : Hello? Hello?
Jasmine : Oh, you must be hungry. Here you go.
Merchant6 : You'd better be able to pay for that.
Jasmine : Pay?
Merchant6 : No one steals from my cart.
Jasmine : Oh, I'm sorry, sir. I don't have any money.
Merchant6 : Thief!
Jasmine : Please...
Jasmine : If you let me go to the palace, I can get some from the sultan.
Merchant6 : Do you know what the penalty is for stealing?
Jasmine : No! No, please!
Aladdin : Oh! Thank you, kind sir. I'm so glad you found her.
Aladdin : I've been looking all over for you.
Jasmine : What are you doing?
Aladdin : Just play along.
Merchant6 : You, uh, know this girl?
Aladdin : Sadly, yes. She is my sister. She's a little crazy.
Merchant6 : She said she knew the sultan.
Aladdin : She thinks the monkey is the sultan.
Jasmine : O wise Sultan, how may I serve you?
(GIBBERISH)
Aladdin : Tragic, isn't it? But no harm done.
Aladdin : Now, come along, sis. Time to go see the doctor.
Jasmine : Oh, hello, Doctor. How are you?
Aladdin : No, no, no. Not that one. Come on, Sultan.
(GIBBERING)
(GASPING)
Merchant6 : Huh? What?
Merchant6 : Come back here, you little thieves!
Iago : With all due respect, Your Rottenness,
Iago : couldn't we just wait for a real storm?
Jafar : Save your breath, Iago. Faster.
Iago : Yes, O mighty evil one.
(PANTING)
Jafar : Part, sands of time.
Jafar : Reveal to me the one who can enter the cave.
Jafar : Yes! Yes!
Jafar : There he is. My diamond in the rough.
Iago : That's him? That's the clown we've been waitin' for?
Jafar : Let's have the guards extend him an invitation to the palace, shall we?
Iago : Swell.
(COUGHS)
(SINISTER LAUGHTER)
Aladdin : Almost there.
Jasmine : I want to thank you for stopping that man.
Aladdin : Uh, forget it.
Aladdin : So, this is your first time in the marketplace, huh?
Jasmine : Is it that obvious?
Aladdin : Well, you do kind of stand out.
Aladdin : I mean, uh, you don't seem to know how dangerous Agrabah can be.
Jasmine : Hmm. I'm a fast learner.
Abu : Wow.
Aladdin : (CHUCKLING) Hey.
Aladdin : Come on. This way.
Aladdin : Whoa. Watch your head there. Be careful.
Jasmine : Is this where you live?
Aladdin : Yep. Just me and Abu. Come and go as we please.
Jasmine : That sounds fabulous.
Aladdin : Well, it's not much, but it's got a great view.
Aladdin : Wow. The palace looks pretty amazing, huh?
Jasmine : Oh, it's wonderful.
Aladdin : I wonder what it would be like to live there, and have servants and valets.
Jasmine : Oh, sure. People who tell you where to go and how to dress.
Aladdin : It's better than here. You're always scraping for food and ducking the guards.
Jasmine : You're not free to make your own choices.
Aladdin : Sometimes you feel so...
Jasmine : You're just...
Aladdin;Jasmine : Trapped.
Aladdin : (CLEARS THROAT) So, where are you from?
Jasmine : What does it matter? I ran away and I am not going back.
Aladdin : Really? How come?
Abu : Why, you...
Jasmine : My father's forcing me to get married.
Aladdin : That's... That's awful.
Aladdin : Abu!
(ANGRY SQUEAKING)
Jasmine : What?
Aladdin : Abu says, uh, that's not fair.
Abu : What?
Jasmine : Oh, did he?
Aladdin : Yeah, of course.
Jasmine : And does Abu have anything else to say?
Aladdin : Well, uh, he wishes there was something he could do to help.
Abu : Oh, boy.
Jasmine : Hmm.
Jasmine : Tell him that's very sweet.
Soldier : Here you are.
Aladdin;Jasmine : They're after me! They're after you?
Aladdin : My father
must have sent them...
Aladdin : Do you trust me?
Jasmine : What?
Jasmine : Yes...
Aladdin : Then jump!
Soldier : We just keep running into each other, don't we, street rat?
Aladdin : Run! Go! Get out of here!
Soldier : Get this thing off of me!
Soldier : It's the dungeon for you, boy.
Aladdin : Get off of me.
Jasmine : Let him go.
Soldier : Looky here, men. A street mouse.
Jasmine : Unhand him, by order of the princess.
Soldier : Princess Jasmine.
Aladdin : The princess?
Abu : Princess?
Soldier : What are you doing outside the palace? And with this street rat.
Jasmine : That's not your concern. Do as I command. Release him.
Soldier : I would, Princess, except my orders come from Jafar.
Soldier : You'll have to take it up with him.
Jasmine : Believe me, I will.
Jasmine : Jafar?
Jafar : Oh, Princess.
Iago : Awk! Jafar, I'm stuck.
Jafar : How may I be of service to you?
Jasmine : The guards just took a boy from the market, on your orders.
Jafar : Your father has charged me with keeping peace in Agrabah. The boy was a criminal.
Jasmine : What was his crime?
Iago : I can't breathe, Jafar.
Jafar : Why, kidnapping the princess, of course.
Iago : If you could just... Aah! That hurt!
Jasmine : He didn't kidnap me. I ran away.
Jafar : Oh, dear.
Jafar : Oh, how frightfully upsetting. Had I but known...
Jasmine : What do you mean?
Jafar : Sadly, the boy's sentence has already been carried out.
Jasmine : What sentence?
Jafar : Death.
(GASPING)
Jafar : By beheading.
Jasmine : No.
Jafar : I am exceedingly sorry, Princess.
Jasmine : How could you?
(WEEPING)
(COUGHING)
(GASPING)
Iago : So, how did it go?
Jasmine : I think she took it rather well.
(JASMINE CRYING)
Jasmine : It's all my fault, Rajah.
Jasmine : I didn't even know his name.
Aladdin : She was the princess. I can't believe it.
Aladdin : I must have sounded so stupid to her.
Abu : Yoo-hoo! Aladdin! Hello!
Aladdin : Abu. Down here.
(SQUEAKING)
Aladdin : Come on, help me out of these.
Aladdin : (SCOLDING)
Aladdin : Hey, she was in trouble. Ah, she was worth it.
Abu : Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Aladdin : Don't worry, Abu. I'll never see her again. I'm a street rat, remember? And there's a law.
Aladdin : She's gotta marry a prince.
Aladdin : She deserves a prince.
Abu : Ta-da!
Aladdin : I'm a fool.
Disguised Jafar : You're only a fool if you give up, boy.
Aladdin : Who are you?
Disguised Jafar : A lowly prisoner, like yourself.
Disguised Jafar : But together, perhaps we can be more.
Aladdin : I'm listening.
Disguised Jafar : There is a cave, boy, a Cave of Wonders, filled with treasures beyond your wildest dreams.
Abu : Ooh!
Disguised Jafar : Treasure enough to impress even your princess, I'd wager.
Iago : Jafar, can you hurry up? I'm dyin' in here.
Aladdin : But the law says only a prince can...
Disguised Jafar : You've heard of the golden rule, haven't you? Whoever has the gold makes the rules.
Disguised Jafar : (WHEEZING LAUGH)
Aladdin : Why would you share all of this wonderful treasure with me?
Disguised Jafar : I need a young pair of legs and a strong back to go in after it.
Aladdin : Uh, one problem.
Aladdin : It's out there. We're in here.
Disguised Jafar : Uh-uh. Things aren't always what they seem.
Disguised Jafar : So, do we have a deal?
Abu : Oh, I don't know.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
The Cave of Wonders : Who disturbs my slumber?
Aladdin : Uh, it is I, Aladdin.
The Cave of Wonders : Proceed.
The Cave of Wonders : Touch nothing but the lamp.
Disguised Jafar : Remember, boy, first fetch me the lamp,
Disguised Jafar : and then you shall have your reward.
Aladdin : Come on, Abu.
(SQUEAKING)
Aladdin : Would you look at that!
Aladdin : (WHIMPERING)
Aladdin : Just a handful of this stuff would make me richer than the sultan.
Aladdin : Abu!
Aladdin : (WHINES)
Aladdin : Don't touch anything. We gotta find that lamp.
Aladdin : (GRUMBLES)
Abu : Huh?
Abu : Aladdin!
Aladdin : Abu, will you knock it off?
(SCREECHES)
Aladdin : Abu, what are you, crazy?
Aladdin : A magic carpet.
Aladdin : Come on. Come on out. We're not gonna hurt you.
Aladdin : (SCREECHES)
Aladdin : Hey, take it easy, Abu. He's not gonna bite.
Aladdin : Thanks.
Aladdin : (SQUEAKING)
Aladdin : Wait a minute. Don't go.
Aladdin : Maybe you can help us.
Aladdin : Hey! Whoa! You see, we're trying to find this lamp.
Aladdin : I think he knows where it is.
Aladdin : (ECHOES)
Aladdin : (WHISPERS) Wait here.
Aladdin : (MOANING)
Abu : Oh!
Aladdin : This is it? This is what we came all the way down here to...
Aladdin : Abu! No!
The Cave of Wonders : Infidels!
The Cave of Wonders : You have touched the forbidden treasure!
The Cave of Wonders : Now you will never again see the light of day!
Aladdin : Whoa!
Abu : Help! Help! Help!
Aladdin : Gotcha!
Aladdin : Carpet, let's move.
Aladdin : Abu! Abu, this is no time to panic.
Aladdin : Start panicking.
Aladdin : Whoa!
Aladdin : (ABU PANTING)
Aladdin : (THUNDER CRACKS)
Aladdin : (ROARING)
Aladdin : Help me out.
Disguised Jafar : Throw me the lamp.
Aladdin : I can't hold on. Give me your hand.
Disguised Jafar : First give me the lamp.
(MANIACAL LAUGHTER)
Disguised Jafar : Yes! At last!
(WICKED LAUGHTER)
(ALADDIN STRUGGLES)
Aladdin : What are you doing?
Disguised Jafar : Giving you your reward.
Disguised Jafar : Your eternal reward.
(SCREAMING)
(YELLING)
(ROARING)
(CHUCKLING)
Jafar : It's mine. It's all mine.
Jafar : I... Where is it? No.
Jafar : No!
Sultan : Jasmine?
Sultan : Oh, dearest. What's wrong?
Sultan : (SNIFFLING)
Jafar : Jafar has done something terrible.
Sultan : There, there, my dear. We'll set it right.
Sultan : Now, tell me everything.
Abu : Oh. Aladdin. Wake up.
Abu : Aladdin.
Aladdin : Oh! My head.
Aladdin : We're trapped. That two-faced son of a jackal!
Aladdin : (SNARLING)
Aladdin : Whoever he was, he's long gone with that lamp.
Abu : Aha!
Aladdin : (CHUCKLING) Why, you hairy little thief.
Aladdin : Looks like such a beat-up, worthless piece of junk.
Aladdin : Hey, I think there's something written here, but it's hard to make out.
Genie : Aaaaahhhhh! Oy!
Genie : 10,000 years will give you such a crick in the neck.
Genie : Hang on a second.
Genie : Whoa! Whoa! Wow! Does it feel good to be outta there.
Genie : I'm telling you, nice to be back, ladies and gentlemen. Hi. Where you from? What's your name?
Aladdin : Uh... Uh, Aladdin.
Genie : Aladdin. Hello, Aladdin. Nice to have you on the show. Can we call you Al? Or maybe just Din?
Genie : How about Laddie? Sounds like, "Here, boy. C'mon, laddie."
Aladdin : I must have hit my head harder than I thought.
Genie : Do you smoke? Mind if I do?
Genie : (GIGGLING)
Genie : Oh, sorry, Cheeta. Hope I didn't singe the fur.
Genie : Yo, Rugman. Haven't seen you in a few millennia. Give me some tassel. Yeah. Yo, yo.
Genie : Say, you're a lot smaller than my last master.
Genie : Either that or I'm gettin' bigger.
Genie : Look at me from the side. Do I look different to you?
Aladdin : Wait a minute. I'm your master? That's right. He can be taught. What would you wish of me?
Genie : The ever impressive,
Genie : the long contained,
Genie : the often imitated,
Genie : but never duplicated... Duplicated, duplicated...
Genie : Genie of the Lamp!
Genie : Right here direct from the lamp, right here for your very much wish fulfilment.
Genie : Thank you.
Aladdin : Whoa Whoa whoa whoa!
Aladdin : Wish fulfilment?
Genie : Three wishes, to be exact. And ixnay on the wishing for more wishes.
Genie : That's it. Three. Uno, dos, tres.
Genie : No substitutions, exchanges or refunds.
Aladdin : Now I know I'm dreaming.
Genie : Master, I don't think you quite realize what you've got here.
Genie : So why don't you just ruminate whilst I illuminate the possibilities.
Genie : Well, Ali Baba had them 40 thieves Scheherazade had a thousand tales
Genie : But, master, you're in luck 'Cause up your sleeves You got a brand of magic never fails
Genie : You got some power In your corner now Some heavy ammunition in your camp
Genie : You got some punch, pizzazz Yahoo and how See, all you gotta do Is rub that lamp and I'll say
Genie : "Mr. Aladdin, sir What will your pleasure be?"
Genie : Let me take your order Jot it down You ain't never had a friend like me
Genie : Life is your restaurant And I'm your maitre d'
Genie : Come on, whisper what it is you want You ain't never had a friend like me
Genie : Yes, sir We pride ourselves on service
Genie : You're the boss, the king, the shah
Genie : Say what you wish It's yours, true dish How 'bout a little more baklava?
Genie : Have some of column A Try all of column B
Genie : I'm in the mood to help you, dude You ain't never had a friend like me
Genie : Oh, my
Genie : No, no
Genie : My, my
Genie : (SCATTING)
Genie : Can your friends do this? Can your friends do that?
Genie : Can your friends pull this Out their little hat?
Genie : Can your friends go poof
Genie : Hey, looky here Ha-ha!
Genie : Can your friends go "Abracadabra, let her rip"
Genie : And then make the sucker disappear?
Genie : So don't you sit there Slack-jawed, buggy-eyed I'm here to answer All your midnight prayers
Genie : You got me bona fide certified You got a genie For your charge d'affaires
Genie : I got a powerful urge to help you out
Genie : So what's your wish? I really wanna know
Genie : You got a list That's three miles long, no doubt All you gotta do is rub like so
Genie : Mr. Aladdin, sir Have a wish or two or three
Genie : I'm on the job, you big nabob You ain't never had a friend Never had a friend
Genie : You ain't never had a friend Never had a friend
Genie : You ain't never had a friend Like me Ah-ha-ha!
Genie : Wah-ha-ha!
Genie : (GREEDY LAUGH)
Genie : You ain't never had a friend like me
Abu : (CHATTERING) Huh?
(GROANS)
Genie : So, what'll it be, master?
Aladdin : You're gonna grant me any three wishes I want, right?
Genie : Ah, almost. There are a few provisos, a couple of quid pro quos.
Aladdin : Like?
Genie : Ah, rule number one, I can't kill anybody.
Genie : So don't ask.
Genie : Rule number two. I can't make anybody fall in love with anybody else.
Genie : You little ponem  there.
Genie : Rule number three. I can't bring people back from the dead.
Genie : It's not a pretty picture. I don't like doing it.
Genie : Other than that, you got it.
Genie;Abu : Hmm. Oh!
Aladdin : Provisos? You mean limitations?
Aladdin : On wishes? Some all-powerful genie.
Aladdin : Can't even bring people back from the dead.
Aladdin : I don't know, Abu. He probably can't even get us out of this cave.
Aladdin : Looks like we're gonna have to find a way out of here.
Genie : Excuse me? Are you lookin' at me? Did you rub my lamp?
Genie : Did you wake me up? Did you bring me here? And all of sudden you're walking out on me?
Genie : I don't think so, not right now.
Genie : You're gettin' your wishes, so sit down!
(ABU SCREECHES)
Genie : In case of emergency, the exits are here, here, here, here, anywhere.
Genie : Keep your hands and arms inside the carpet.
Genie : We're... Outta here!
Sultan : Jafar, this is an outrage.
Sultan : If it weren't for all your years of loyal service...
Sultan : From now on, you are to discuss sentencing of prisoners with me, before they are beheaded.
Jafar : I assure you, Your Highness, it won't happen again.
Sultan : Jasmine...
Sultan : Jafar. Let's put this whole messy business behind us.
Sultan : Please.
Jafar : My most abject and humblest apologies to you as well, Princess.
Jasmine : At least some good will come of my being forced to marry.
Jasmine : When I am queen, I will have the power to get rid of you.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Sultan : There, now. That's nice. All settled, then. Now,Jasmine, getting back to this suitor business...
Sultan : Jasmine? Jasmine!
Jafar : (GROWLS) If only I had gotten that lamp.
Iago : "I will have the power to get rid of you."
Iago : (GROWLING) To think we gotta keep kissing up to that chump and his chump daughter
Iago : for the rest of our lives...
Jafar : No, Iago.
Jafar : Only until she finds a chump husband. Then she'll have us banished.
Jafar : Or beheaded.
Jafar;Iago : Eww!
Iago : Oh. Wait a minute. Jafar.
Iago : What if you were the chump husband?
Jafar : What?
Iago : Okay, you marry the princess, all right?
Iago : And, uh, then you become the sul,
Jafar : Oh.
Jafar : Marry the shrew. I become the sultan.
Jafar : The idea has merit.
Iago : Yes, merit. Yes.
Iago : And then we drop papa-in-law and the little woman off a cliff.
Iago : Yaaah! Kersplat!
Iago : (WICKED LAUGHTER)
Jafar : I love the way your foul little mind works.
Jafar : ha ha
Iago : hee hee
(BOTH LAUGH SINISTERLY)
Genie : Thank you for choosing Magic Carpet for all your travel needs.
Genie : Don't stand until the rug has come to a complete stop.
Genie : Thank you. Goodbye now. Good-bye. Good-bye. Thank you. Good-bye.
Genie : Well, how about that, Mr. Doubting Mustafa?
Aladdin : Oh, you sure showed me. Now, about my three wishes.
Genie : Dost mine ears deceive me?
Genie : Three? You are down by one, boy.
Aladdin : Ah, no. I never actually wished to get out of the cave. You did that on your own.
Genie : Well, I feel sheepish. All right, you bad boy, but no more freebies.
Aladdin : Fair deal. So, three wishes. I want them to be good.
Aladdin : What would you wish for?
Genie : Me? No one's ever asked me that before.
Genie : Well, in my case... Ah, forget it.
Aladdin : What?
Genie : No, I can't. I...
Aladdin : Come on. Tell me.
Genie : Freedom.
Aladdin : You're a prisoner?
Genie : It's all part and parcel of the whole genie gig.
Genie : Phenomenal cosmic powers...
Genie : Itty bitty living space.
Aladdin : Genie, that's terrible.
Genie : But, oh, to be free...
Genie : Not have to go, "Poof. What do you need? "Poof. What do you need? Poof. What do you need?"
Genie : To be my own master.
Genie : Such a thing would be greater than all the magic and all the treasures in all the world.
Genie : But what am I talking about? Let's get real here. It's not gonna happen.
Genie : Genie, wake up and smell the hummus.
Aladdin : Why not?
Genie : The only way I get outta this is if my master wishes me out.
Genie : So you can guess how often that's happened.
Aladdin : I'll do it. I'll set you free.
Genie : Uh-huh, yeah, right.
Aladdin : No, really, I promise. After I make my first two wishes, I'll use my third wish to set you free.
Genie : Well, here's hopin'. All right.
Genie : Let's make some magic.
Genie : So how 'bout it? What is it you want most?
Aladdin : Well, there's this girl.
Genie : Wrong. I can't make anybody fall in love, remember?
Aladdin : Oh, but, Genie, she's smart and fun and...
Genie : Pretty?
Aladdin : Beautiful.
Aladdin : She's got these eyes that just... And this hair. Wow. And her smile... (SIGHS)
Genie : Ami. C'est l'amour.
Aladdin : But she's the princess. To even have a chance, I'd have to be...
Aladdin : Hey, can you make me a prince?
Genie : Let's see here. Chicken  la king? Nope.
Genie : Alaskan king crab. Ow. I hate it when they do that. Caesar salad. Ah! Et tu, Brute? No.
Genie : Aha. "To make a prince."
Genie : Is that an official wish? Say the magic words.
Aladdin : Genie, I wish for you to make me a prince.
Genie : All right! Yo, yo! Woof! Woof!
Genie : First, that fez-and-vest combo is much too third century.
Genie : These patches. What are we trying to say, beggar? No. Let's work with me here.
Genie : Ooh. I like it. Muy macho.
Genie : Now, it still needs something. What does it say to me? It says mode of transportation.
Genie : Excuse me, monkey boy. Aqu.  Over here.
Abu : Uh-oh.
Genie : Here he comes.
Genie : What better way to make your entrance on the streets of Agrabah
Genie : than riding your very own, brand-new camel?
Genie : Watch out. They spit.
Genie : Mmm. Not enough.
Genie : Still not enough. Let's see. What do you need?
Genie : Yes!
Genie : Esalalumbo shimin Dumbo.
Genie : Whoa!
Genie : Talk about your trunk space. Check this action out.
Abu : (TRUMPETS)
Abu : (FRIGHTENED MONKEY NOISES)
Aladdin : Abu, you look good.
Genie : He's got the outfit. He's got the elephant.
Genie : But we're not through yet.
Genie : Hang on to your turban, kid. We're gonna make you a star.
Jafar : Sire, I've found a solution to the problem with your daughter.
Iago : Awk. The problem with your daughter.
Sultan : Oh, really?
Jafar : Right here.
Jafar : "If the princess has not chosen a husband by the appointed time,
Jafar : "then the sultan shall choose for her."
Sultan : bu,bu,bu, But Jasmine hated all those suitors.
Sultan : How could I choose someone she hates?
Jafar : Not to worry, my liege. There is more.
Jafar : "If in the event a suitable prince cannot be found..."
Iago : Jerk.
Jafar : "A princess must then be wed to..."
Jafar : Hmm. Interesting.
Sultan : What? Who?
Jafar : The royal vizier. Why, that would be me.
Sultan : But I thought the law says that only a prince can marry a princess.
Sultan : I'm quite sure that...
Jafar : Desperate times call for desperate measures, my lord.
Sultan : Yes. Desperate measures.
Jafar : You will order the princess to marry me.
Sultan : I will order the princess to...
Sultan : But you're so old.
Jafar : The princess will marry me.
Sultan : The princess will marry...
Sultan : What? What is that? oh,
Sultan : That music.
Sultan : (CHUCKLING)
Sultan : Jafar, you must come and see this.
Men Ensemble : (SINGING) Make way for Prince Ali
Men Ensemble : Say, "Hey, it's Prince Ali"
Genie : Hey, clear the way in the old bazaar
Genie : Hey you, let us through It's a bright new star Oh come, be the first on your block To meet his eye
Genie : Make way, here he comes Ring bells, bang the drums
Genie : You're gonna love this guy
Genie : Prince Ali, fabulous he Ali Ababwa
Genie : Genuflect, show some respect Down on one knee
Genie : Now, try your best to stay calm
Genie : Brush up your Sunday salaam
Genie : Then come and meet His spectacular coterie
Genie : Prince Ali, mighty is he Ali Ababwa
Genie : Strong as 10 regular men definitely
Disguised Genie : He faced the galloping hordes
Disguised Genie : A hundred bad guys with swords
Disguised Genie : Who sent those goons to their lords? Why, Prince Ali
Men Ensemble : He's got 75 golden camels
Genie : Don't they look lovely, June?
Women Ensemble : Purple peacocks, he's got 53
Genie : Fabulous, Harry. I love the feathers.
Genie : When it comes to exotic-type mammals
Disguised Genie : Has he got a zoo I'm telling you
Disguised Genie : It's a world-class menagerie
Genie : Prince Ali, handsome is he Ali Ababwa
Genie : That physique, how can I speak Weak at the knee
Genie : Well, get on out in that square
Genie : Adjust your veil and prepare
Genie : To gawk and grovel and stare At Prince Ali
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : -He's got 95 white Persian monkeys -He's got the monkeys
Men Ensemble : Let's see the monkeys
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : And to view them he charges no fee
Women Ensemble : He's generous So generous
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : He's got slaves He's got servants and flunkies
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : Proud to work for him They bow to his whim, love serving him
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : They're just lousy with loyalty to Ali
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : Prince Ali
Men Ensemble;Genie;Women Ensemble : Prince Ali, Amorous he Ali Ababwa
Genie : Heard your princess Was a sight lovely to see
Genie : And that, good people, is why
Genie : He got dolled up and dropped by
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : With 60 elephants, llamas galore With bears and lions A brass band and more
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : With his 40 fakirs His cooks, his bakers His birds that warble on key
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : Make way
Men Ensemble;Women Ensemble : For Prince Ali
Sultan : Splendid. Absolutely marvelous.
Sultan : (CLEARS THROAT)
Aladdin : Your Majesty,
Aladdin : I have journeyed from afar to seek your daughter's hand.
Sultan : Prince Ali Ababwa.
Sultan : Of course. I'm delighted to meet you.
Sultan : This is my royal vizier, Jafar. He's delighted, too.
Jafar : Ecstatic.
Jafar : I'm afraid, Prince Abubu...
Aladdin : Ababwa.
Jafar : Whatever.
Jafar : You cannot just parade in here uninvited and expect (to...)
Sultan : By Allah, this is quite a remarkable device.
Sultan : Ooh.
Sultan : I don't suppose I might...
Aladdin : Why, certainly, Your Majesty. Allow me.
Jafar : Sire, I must advise against this.
Sultan : Oh, button up, Jafar. Learn to have a little fun.
Iago : Ow, ow, ow.
Sultan : Ahh! Whoa!
Jafar : Just where did you say you were from?
Aladdin : Oh, much farther than you've traveled, I'm sure.
Jafar : Try me.
Sultan : (Look) out, Polly.
Iago : Hey, watch it.
Iago : Watch it with the dumb rug.
Iago : Aah!
Iago : Whew! Aah!
Sultan : Out of the way. I'm coming in to land. Jafar, watch this. Aah!
Jafar : Spectacular, Your Highness.
Sultan : Woo, That was lovely.
Sultan : Yes, I do seem to have a knack for it.
Sultan : This is a very impressive youth. And a prince besides.
Sultan : If we're lucky, you won't have to marry Jasmine after all.
Jafar : I don't trust him, Sire.
Sultan : Nonsense.
Sultan : One thing I pride myself on, Jafar, I'm an excellent judge of character.
Iago : Oh, excellent judge. Yeah, sure. Not!
Sultan : Jasmine will like this one.
Aladdin : And I'm pretty sure I'll like Princess Jasmine.
Jafar : Your Highness, no. I must intercede on Jasmine's behalf.
Jafar : This boy is no different from the others.
Jafar : What makes him think he is worthy of the princess?
Aladdin : Your Majesty, I am Prince Ali Ababwa. Just let her meet me. I will win your daughter.
Jasmine : How dare you. All of you. Standing around deciding my future?
Jasmine : I am not a prize to be won.
Sultan : Oh, dear.
Sultan : Don't worry, Prince Ali. Just give Jasmine time to cool down.
Jafar : I think it's time to say good-bye to Prince Abubu.
Aladdin : (SIGHS) What am I gonna do? Jasmine won't even let me talk to her.
Aladdin : I should've known I couldn't pull off this stupid prince wish.
Aladdin : (GROWLING)
Genie : So move.
Genie : Hey.
Genie : That's a good move.
Genie : I can't believe it. I'm losing to a rug.
Aladdin : Genie, I need help.
Genie : All right, Sparky, here's the deal.
Genie : If you wanna court the little lady, you gotta be a straight shooter. Do you got it?
Aladdin : What?
Genie : Tell her the TRUTH!
Aladdin : No way.
Aladdin : If Jasmine found out I was really some crummy street rat,
Aladdin : she'd laugh at me.
Genie : A woman appreciates a man who can make her laugh.
Genie : Al, all joking aside, you really ought to be yourself.
Aladdin : Hey, that's the last thing I wanna be.
Aladdin : Okay, I'm gonna go see her.
Aladdin : I just... I gotta be smooth, cool, confident.
Aladdin : How do I look?
Genie : Like a prince.
Jasmine : (SIGHS)
Aladdin : Princess Jasmine?
Aladdin : (GROWLING)
Jasmine : Who's there?
Aladdin : It's me, Prince Ali.
Aladdin : Ahem. Uh, Prince Ali Ababwa.
Jasmine : I do not want to see you.
Aladdin : No, no, please, Princess. Give me a chance.
Jasmine : Just leave me alone.
Aladdin : Down, kitty.
Genie : So, how's our little beau doing?
Aladdin : come on, scat. come on. Good kitty, take off, come on. Down, kitty.
Jasmine : Wait. Wait. Do I know you?
Aladdin : Uh, no. No.
Jasmine : You remind me of someone I met in the marketplace.
Aladdin : The marketplace? I have servants who go to the marketplace for me.
Aladdin : Why, I even have servants who go to the marketplace for my servants, so it couldn't have been me you met.
Jasmine : No. I guess not.
Genie : Enough about you, Casanova. Talk about her.
Aladdin : Huh?
Genie : She's smart, fun, the hair, the eyes. Anything. Pick a feature.
Aladdin : Ahem. Uh, Princess Jasmine? You're very...
Genie : Wonderful, magnificent, glorious, punctual.
Aladdin : Punctual.
Jasmine : Punctual?
Genie : Sorry.
Aladdin : Uh, beautiful.
Genie : Nice recovery.
Jasmine : Hmm.
Jasmine : I'm rich, too, you know.
Aladdin : Yeah.
Jasmine : The daughter of a sultan.
Aladdin : I know.
Jasmine : A fine prize for any prince to marry.
Aladdin : Uh, right. Right. A prince like me.
Genie : Warning! Warning!
Jasmine : Right. A prince like you.
Jasmine : And every other stuffed shirt, swaggering peacock I've met.
Genie : Mayday! Mayday!
Jasmine : Just go jump off a balcony!
Aladdin : What?
Genie : Stop her. Stop her!
Genie : Want me to sting her?
Aladdin : Buzz off.
Genie : Okay, fine. But remember, "bee" yourself.
Aladdin : Yeah, right.
Jasmine : What?
Aladdin : Uh... Uh, you're right.
Aladdin : (SIGHS) You aren't just some prize to be won. You should be free to make your own choice.
Aladdin : I'll go now.
Jasmine : No!
Aladdin : What? What?
Jasmine : How... How are you doing that?
Aladdin : It's a magic carpet.
Jasmine : It's lovely.
Aladdin : You, uh... You don't want to go for a ride, do you?
Aladdin : We could get out of the palace, see the world.
Jasmine : Is it safe?
Aladdin : Sure. Do you trust me?
Jasmine : What?
Aladdin : Do you trust me?
Jasmine : Yes.
Aladdin : I can show you the world
Aladdin : Shining, shimmering, splendid
Aladdin : Tell me, Princess Now, when did you last Let your heart decide
Aladdin : I can open your eyes
Aladdin : Take you wonder by wonder
Aladdin : Over, sideways and under On a magic carpet ride
Aladdin : A whole new world
Aladdin : A new fantastic point of view
Aladdin : No one to tell us no Or where to go
Aladdin : Or say we're only dreaming
Jasmine : A whole new world
Jasmine : A dazzling place I never knew
Jasmine : But when I'm way up here It's crystal clear
Jasmine : That now I'm in A whole new world with you
Aladdin : Now I'm in A whole new world with you
Jasmine : Unbelievable sights
Jasmine : Indescribable feeling
Jasmine : Soaring, tumbling, freewheeling Through an endless diamond sky
Jasmine : A whole new world
Aladdin : Don't you dare close your eyes
Jasmine : A
hundred thousand things to see
Aladdin : Hold your
breath, it gets better
Jasmine : I'm like a shooting star I've come so far
Jasmine : I can't go back to where I used to be
Aladdin : A whole new world
Jasmine : Every turn a surprise
Aladdin : With new horizons to pursue
Jasmine : Every moment red-letter
Aladdin;Jasmine : I'll chase them anywhere There's time to spare
Aladdin;Jasmine : Let me share This whole new world with you
Aladdin : A whole new world
Jasmine : A whole new world
Aladdin : That's where we'll be
Jasmine : That's where we'll be
Aladdin : A thrilling chase
Jasmine : A wondrous place
Jasmine;Aladdin : For you and me
Jasmine : It's all so magical.
Aladdin : Yeah.
Jasmine : It's a shame Abu had to miss this.
Aladdin : Nah. He hates fireworks. He doesn't like flying, either.
Aladdin : Uh, that is, um... Oh, no.
Jasmine : You are the boy from the market. I knew it. Why did you lie to me?
Aladdin : Jasmine, I'm sorry.
Jasmine : Did you think I was stupid?
Aladdin : No!
Jasmine : That I wouldn't figure it out?
Aladdin : No, I mean, I hoped you wouldn't. No, that's not what I meant.
Jasmine : Who are you? Tell me the truth.
Aladdin : The truth?
Aladdin : The truth. Um...
Aladdin : The truth is... I, I,I sometimes dress as a commoner, um, to escape the pressures of palace life.
Aladdin : But I really am a prince.
Jasmine : Why didn't you just tell me?
Aladdin : Well, you know, Umm royalty going out into the city in disguise, it sounds a little strange, don't you think?
Jasmine : Hmm.
Jasmine : Not that strange.
Jasmine : Good night, my handsome prince.
Aladdin : Sleep well, Princess.
Aladdin : (SIGHS)
Aladdin : Yes!
Aladdin : For the first time in my life, things are starting to go right.
Aladdin : (YELLING)
Aladdin : (STRUGGLING)
Aladdin : Abu. Abu.
Jafar's Soldiers : Hold him, hold him.
Jafar : I'm afraid you've worn out your welcome, Prince Abubu.
Aladdin : Why, you...
Jafar : Make sure he's never found.
(LAUGHING)
Genie : Never fails. You get in the bath and there's a rub at the lamp.
Genie : Hello? Al?
Genie : (GASPING) Al! Kid, snap out of it.
Genie : You can't cheat on this one. I can't help unless you make a wish.
Genie : You have to say, "Genie, I want you to save my life." Got it?
Genie : Come on, Aladdin!
Genie : I'll take that as a yes.
Genie : (IMITATING ALARM)
Genie : Up scope.
Genie : (BABBLING IN GERMAN)
Aladdin : (COUGHING)
Genie : Don't you scare me like that.
Aladdin : Genie, I, uh... I...
Aladdin : Thanks, Genie.
Genie : Oh, Al. I'm gettin' kind of fond of you, kid.
Genie : Not that I wanna pick out curtains or anything.
Jasmine : (HUMMING)
Jasmine : Jasmine.
Jasmine : Oh, Father, I just had the most wonderful time. I'm so happy.
Sultan : You should be, Jasmine. I have chosen a husband for you.
Jasmine : What?
Sultan : You will wed Jafar.
(GASPING)
Jafar : You're speechless, I see. A fine quality in a wife.
Jasmine : I will never marry you.
Jasmine : Father, I choose Prince Ali.
Jafar : Prince Ali left.
Aladdin : Better check your crystal ball again, Jafar.
Jasmine : Prince Ali!
(GASPING)
Iago : How in the... Uh. Awk!
Aladdin : Tell them the truth, Jafar. You tried to have me killed.
Jafar : What? Ridiculous nonsense, Your Highness. He is obviously lying.
Sultan : Obviously lying.
Jasmine : Father, what's wrong with you?
Aladdin : I know what's wrong.
Sultan : Oh, my!
Aladdin : Your Highness, Jafar's been controlling you with this.
Sultan : (STAMMERING) What? Jafar? You, you traitor!
Jafar : Your Majesty, all this can be explained.
Sultan : Guards! Guards!
Iago : Well, that's it. We're dead. Forget it. Just dig a grave for both of us. We're dead.
Sultan : Arrest Jafar at once.
Jafar : This is not done yet, boy.
Jafar : (LAUGHING) (COUGHING)
Sultan : Find him! Search everywhere!
Aladdin : Jasmine, are you all right?
Jasmine : Yes.
Sultan : Jafar, my most trusted counselor, plotting against me all this time.
Sultan : This is horrible, just horrible. How will I ever...
Sultan : Huh?
Sultan : Can this be true? My daughter has finally chosen a suitor?
Sultan : Ha, ha! Praise Allah!
Sultan : You brilliant boy, I could kiss you.
Sultan : I won't. I'll leave that to my... But you two will be wed at once.
Sultan : And yes, yes. And you'll be happy and prosperous, and then you, my boy, will become sultan.
Aladdin : Sultan?
Sultan : Yes. A fine upstanding youth such as yourself, a person of your unimpeachable moral character
Sultan : is exactly what this kingdom needs.
Iago : We gotta get outta here. I gotta start packing. Only essentials. We gotta travel light.
Iago : Bring the guns, the weapons, the knives, and how about this picture? I think I'm making a weird face in it.
Jafar : (LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Iago : Oh, boy. He's cracked. He's gone nuts.
Iago : Jafar! Jafar! Get a grip!
Iago : Good grip.
Jafar : Prince Ali is nothing more than that ragged urchin, Aladdin.
Jafar : He has the lamp, Iago.
Iago : Why, that miserable...
Jafar : But you are going to relieve him of it.
Iago : Me?
Aladdin : Sultan? They want me to be Sultan?
Genie : Huzzah! Hail the conquering hero
Genie : (PATRIOTIC TUNE PLAYS)
Genie : Aladdin, you've just won the heart of the princess. What are you gonna do next?
Aladdin : (SIGHS DEEPLY)
Genie : (WHISPERING) Psst. Your line is, "I'm going to free the genie." Any time.
Aladdin : Genie. I can't.
Genie : Sure you can.
Genie : You just go, "Genie, I wish you free."
Aladdin : I'm serious. Look, I'm sorry. I really am. But they wanna make me sultan.
Aladdin : No. They wanna make Prince Ali sultan.
Aladdin : Without you, I'm just Aladdin.
Genie : Al, you won.
Aladdin : Because of you. The only reason anyone thinks I'm worth anything is because of you.
Aladdin : What if they find out I'm not really a prince?
Aladdin : What if Jasmine finds out? I'd lose her.
Aladdin : Genie, I can't keep this up on my own.
Aladdin : I can't wish you free.
Genie : Fine. I understand. After all, you've lied to everyone else. Hey, I was beginning to feel left out.
Genie : Now, if you'll excuse me, master.
Abu : (SIGHING)
Aladdin : Genie, I'm really sorry.
(RASPBERRY)
Aladdin : Well, fine. Then just stay in there.
Aladdin : What are you guys looking at?
Abu : (WHIMPERING)
Abu : (SNIFFLING)
Aladdin : Look, I... I'm sorry. Abu, I'm sorry. I didn't... Wait. Come on.
Aladdin : (SIGHING)
Aladdin : What am I doing?
Aladdin : (SIGHS) Genie's right.
Aladdin : I gotta tell Jasmine the truth.
Jasmine;Iago faking Jasmine : Ali. Oh, Ali. Will you come here?
Aladdin : (SIGHING) Well, here goes.
Aladdin : Jasmine? Where are you?
Iago faking Jasmine : Out in the menagerie. Hurry.
Aladdin : I'm coming.
Iago : (WICKED LAUGHTER)
Iago : You got a problem, Pinky?
Iago : Jerk.
Iago : (GLEEFUL CACKLING)
Iago : Boy, Jafar's gonna be happy to see you.
Iago;Iago faking Jafar : "Excellent work, Iago."
Iago : Ah, go on.
Iago faking Jafar : "No, really. On a scale of one to 10, you are an 11."
Iago : Oh, Jafar, you're too kind.
Iago : I'm embarrassed. I'm blushing.
Sultan : People of Agrabah, my daughter has finally chosen a suitor.
Sultan : Jasmine.
Jasmine : Ali, where have you been?
Aladdin : Jasmine, there's something I got to tell you.
Jasmine : The whole kingdom's turned out for Father's announcement.
Aladdin : No. But, Jasmine, listen to me, please.
Aladdin : You don't understand...
Jasmine : Good luck.
Sultan : Ali Ababwa!
Aladdin : Oh, boy.
(CHEERING)
Iago : Look at them, cheering that little pipsqueak.
Jafar : Let them cheer.
Genie : You know, Al, I'm getting really...
Genie : I don't think you're him. Tonight, the part of Al will be played by a tall, dark and sinister ugly man.
Jafar : I am your master now.
Genie : I was afraid of that.
Jafar : Genie, grant me my first wish.
Jafar : I wish to rule on high as sultan.
Aladdin : Whoa!
Sultan : Bless my soul.
Sultan : What is this? What's going on? Oh, my goodness, what's happening?
Jasmine : Father.
Jafar : (CACKLING)
Sultan : Jafar, you vile betrayer.
Iago : That's Sultan Vile Betrayer to you.
Aladdin : Oh, yeah? We'll just see about that.
Aladdin : (GASPS) The lamp.
Jafar : (JAFAR LAUGHS) Finders keepers, Abubu.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Aladdin : Genie, no!
Genie : Sorry, kid. I got a new master now.
Sultan : Jafar, I order you to stop.
Jafar : Ah, but there's a new order now.
Jafar : My order. Finally, you will bow to me.
Jasmine : We will never bow to you.
Iago : Why am I not surprised?
Jafar : If you won't bow before a sultan, then you will cower before a sorcerer!
Jafar : Genie, my second wish...
Jafar : I wish to be the most powerful sorcerer in the world!
Aladdin : Genie, stop!
Jafar : Ladies and gentlemen, a warm Agrabah welcome for Sorcerer Jafar!
Jafar : Now, where were we?
Jafar : Ah, yes. Abject humiliation.
Jafar : Down, boy.
(MEOWS)
Jafar : Oh, Princess. There's someone I'm dying to introduce you to.
Aladdin : Jafar. Get your hands off her.
Jafar : Prince Ali Yes, it is he But not as you know him
Jafar : Read my lips And come to grips with reality
Jafar : Yes, meet a blast from your past Whose lies were too good to last
Jafar : Say hello To your precious Prince Ali
Iago : Or should we say Aladdin?
Jasmine : Ali?
Aladdin : Jasmine, I tried to tell you. I'm just...
Jafar : So Ali turns out to be Merely Aladdin
Jafar : Just a con, need I go on Take it from me
Jafar : His personality flaws Give me adequate cause
Jafar : To send him packing On a one-way trip - Genie! So his prospects Take a terminal dip
Jafar : His assets frozen, the venue chosen Is the ends of the Earth, whoopee!
Jafar : So long!
Iago : Good-bye, see ya.
Jafar : Ex-Prince Ali
Jafar : (LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Aladdin : (SHIVERING)
Aladdin : Abu.
Aladdin : Abu!
Abu : (ABU WHIMPERING)
Aladdin : Oh, this is all my fault. I should have freed the genie when I had the chance.
Aladdin : Abu. Are you okay?
Abu : (TEETH CHATTERING) Mmm-hmm.
Aladdin : I'm sorry, Abu.
Aladdin : I made a mess of everything.
Aladdin : Somehow, I gotta go back and set things right.
Aladdin : Carpet.
Aladdin : (ABU CHITTERS)
Aladdin : (ALADDIN STRAINS)
Aladdin : Abu, start digging.
Aladdin : (FRANTIC PANTING)
Aladdin : That's it.
Aladdin : Yeah! All right!
Abu : (WHINES)
Aladdin : Now, back to Agrabah. Let's go.
Iago : Puppet ruler want a cracker?
Iago : Here's your cracker. Shove them all the way down your throat.
Iago : Here. Have lots.
Jasmine : Stop it. Jafar, leave him alone.
Iago : (GROWLING)
Jafar : It pains me to see you reduced to this, Jasmine.
Jafar : A beautiful desert bloom such as yourself should be on the arm of the most powerful man in the world.
Jafar : What do you say, my dear? Why, with you as my queen...
Jasmine : Never.
Jafar : (ENRAGED GROWL)
Jafar : I'll teach you some respect.
Jasmine : (GASPING)
Jafar : No. Genie.
Jafar : I have decided to make my final wish.
Jafar : I wish for Princess Jasmine to fall desperately in love with me.
Genie : Ah, Master, there are a few addendas, some quid pro quos...
Jafar : Don't talk back to me, you big blue lout.
Jafar : You will do what I order you to do, slave.
Jasmine : Jafar. I never realized how incredibly handsome you are.
Jafar : Mmm. That's better.
Jafar : Now, pussycat, tell me more about myself.
Jasmine : You're tall, dark,
Jasmine : well dressed...
Genie : Al. Al, little buddy.
Aladdin : Shh.
Genie : Al, I can't help you. I work for Seor Psychopath now. What are you gonna do?
Aladdin : Hey, I'm a street rat, remember? I'll improvise.
Jasmine : Cute little gaps between your teeth.
Jafar : Go on.
Jasmine : And your beard is so twisted.
Jasmine : You've stolen my heart.
Iago : (GASPING) Jafar...
Jafar : And the street rat?
Jasmine : What street rat?
Aladdin : (GASPING)
Abu : Yech!
Jafar : That was...
Jafar : You!
Jafar : How many times do I have to kill you, boy?
Aladdin : Get the lamp.
Jafar : No!
Jafar : Ah, ah, ah, Princess. Your time is up.
Jafar : (GROWLING)
Aladdin : Jasmine.
Iago : Oh, nice shot, Jaf...
Jafar : Don't toy with me.
Aladdin : Abu!
Jafar : Things are unravelling fast now, boy.
Jafar : (JAFAR LAUGHING)
Jafar : Get the point?
Jafar : (LAUGHING)
Jafar : (STRAINING)
Jafar : I'm just getting warmed up.
Jafar : Are you afraid to fight me yourself, you cowardly snake?
Jafar : A snake, am I?
Jafar : Perhaps you'd like to see how snakelike I can be.
Jafar : (SCREAMING)
Genie : Rick 'em, rack 'em, rock'em, rake Stick that sword into that snake
Jafar : You stay out of this.
Genie : Jafar, Jafar, he's our man. If he can't do it... Great!
Aladdin : Aladdin.
Jafar : (SCREAMS)
Aladdin : Jasmine, hang on.
Jafar : You little fool.
Jafar : You thought you could defeat the most powerful being on Earth.
Iago : Squeeze him, Jafar. Squeeze him like a... Awk!
Jafar : Without the genie, boy, you're nothing.
Aladdin : The genie. The genie. The genie has more power than you'll ever have.
Jafar : What?
Aladdin : He gave you your power. He can take it away.
Genie : Al, what are you doing? Why are you bringing me into this?
Aladdin : Face it, Jafar. You're still just second best.
Jafar : You're right. His power does exceed my own.
Jafar : But not for long.
Genie : The boy is crazy. He's a little punch-drunk. One too many hits with the snake.
Jafar : Slave, I make my third wish.
Jafar : I wish to be an all-powerful genie!
Genie : All right, your wish is my command. Way to go, Al.
Jafar : Yes.
Jafar : Yes!
Jafar : The power.
Jafar : (JAFAR LAUGHS)
Jafar : The absolute power!
Jasmine : What have you done?
Aladdin : Trust me.
Jafar : The universe is mine to command, to control!
Aladdin : Not so fast, Jafar. Aren't you forgetting something?
Jafar : Huh?
Aladdin : You wanted to be a genie, you got it.
Jafar : What?
Aladdin : And everything that goes with it.
Jafar : No! No!
Iago : I'm gettin' out of here.
Aladdin : Phenomenal cosmic powers...
Iago : You're the genie. I don't want...
Aladdin : Itty bitty living space.
Genie : Al, you little genius, you.
Sultan : Ahh!
Rajah : (MEOWS)
Jafar : Get your blasted beak out of my face.
Iago : Oh, shut up, you moron.
Jafar : Don't tell me to shut up.
Genie : Allow me.
Genie : Ten thousand years in a Cave of Wonders ought to chill him out.
(IAGO YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
Jafar : Shut up!
Aladdin : Jasmine... I'm sorry I lied to you about being a prince.
Jasmine : I know why you did.
Aladdin : Well, I guess this is good-bye?
Jasmine : Oh, that stupid law. This isn't fair.
Jasmine : I love you.
Genie : (SNIFFLES) Al, no problem. You've still got one wish left.
Genie : Just say the word and you're a prince again.
Aladdin : But, Genie, what about your freedom?
Genie : Hey, it's only an eternity of servitude.
Genie : This is love.
Genie : Al, you're not gonna find another girl like her in a million years.
Genie : Believe me, I know. I've looked.
Aladdin : Jasmine, I do love you, but I got to stop pretending to be something I'm not.
Jasmine : I understand.
Aladdin : Genie, I wish for your freedom.
Genie : One bona fide prince pedigree coming up. What?
Aladdin : Genie, you're free.
Genie : I'm free. I'm free.
Genie : Quick. Quick. Wish for something outrageous. Say, "I want the Nile." Wish for the Nile. Try that.
Aladdin : Uh, I wish for the Nile.
Genie : No way!
Genie : (LAUGHING GLEEFULLY)
Genie : Oh, does that feel good! Oh! I'm free! I'm free at last!
Genie : I'm hittin' the road. I'm off to see the world. I'm...
Aladdin : Genie, I'm... I'm gonna miss you.
Genie : Me, too, Al. (SNIFFLES)
Genie : No matter what anybody says, you'll always be a prince to me.
Sultan : That's right. You've certainly proven your worth as far as I'm concerned.
Sultan : It's that law that's the problem.
Jasmine : Father?
Sultan : Well, am I sultan or am I sultan? From this day forth,
Sultan : the princess shall marry whomever she deems worthy.
Jasmine : Him. I choose...
Jasmine : I choose you, Aladdin.
Aladdin : Call me Al.
Genie : Oh, all of you, come over here. Big group hug. Group hug.
Genie : Mind if I kiss the monkey?
Genie : Ooh, hairball.
Genie : Well, I can't do any more damage around this popsicle stand. I'm outta here!
Genie : Bye-bye, you two crazy lovebirds!
Genie : Hey, Rugman, ciao. I'm history.
Genie : No, I'm mythology. I don't care what I am. I'm free!
Aladdin : A whole new world
Jasmine : A whole new life
Aladdin;Jasmine;All : For you and me
All : A whole new world
(Singing)
(LAUGHING)
Genie : Made you look.