Madame de la Grande Bouche : Once upon a time in the hidden heart of France
Madame de la Grande Bouche : a handsome young prince lived in a beautiful castle
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Poof Poof
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Although he had everything his heart desired the prince was selfish and unkind
Lumière : Master it's time
Madame de la Grande Bouche : He taxed the village to fill his castle with the most beautiful objects
Madame de la Grande Bouche : And his parties with the most beautiful people
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Oh how divine
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Glamour music and magic combine
Madame de la Grande Bouche : See the maidens so anxious to shine
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Look for a sign that enhances chances
Madame de la Grande Bouche : She'll be his special one
Madame de la Grande Bouche : What a display What a breathtaking thrilling array
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Ev'ry prince Ev'ry dog has his day
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Let us sing with passion gusto fit to bust oh
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Not a care in the world
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Then one night
Madame de la Grande Bouche : an unexpected intruder arrived at the castle seeking shelter from the bitter storm
Madame de la Grande Bouche : As a gift she offered the prince a single rose
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Repulsed by her haggard appearance the prince turned the woman away
Beast(Prince Adam) : Hmm
Madame de la Grande Bouche : But she warned him not to be deceived by appearances
Madame de la Grande Bouche : For beauty is found within
Madame de la Grande Bouche : When he dismissed her again
Madame de la Grande Bouche : the old woman's outward appearance melted away
Madame de la Grande Bouche : To reveal
Madame de la Grande Bouche : a beautiful enchantress
Beast(Prince Adam) : The prince begged for forgiveness but it was too late
Madame de la Grande Bouche : For she had seen that there was no love in his heart
Mrs. Potts : Chip Chip Oh my
Madame de la Grande Bouche : As punishment she transformed him into a hideous beast
Madame de la Grande Bouche : And placed a powerful spell on the castle
Madame de la Grande Bouche : and all who lived there
Madame de la Grande Bouche : As days bled into years the prince and his servants were forgotten by the world
Madame de la Grande Bouche : For the enchantress had erased all memory of them from the minds of the people they loved
Madame de la Grande Bouche : But the rose she had offered was truly an enchanted rose
Madame de la Grande Bouche : If he could learn to love another and earn their love in return by the time the last petal fell
Madame de la Grande Bouche : the spell would be broken
Madame de la Grande Bouche : If not he would be doomed to remain a beast for all time
Madame de la Grande Bouche : As the years passed
Madame de la Grande Bouche : he fell into despair and lost all hope
Madame de la Grande Bouche : For who could ever learn to love a beast
Belle : Little town It's a quiet village
Belle : Ev'ry day like the one before
Belle : Little town Full of little people
Belle : Waking up to say
Woman1 : Bonjour
Townspeople : Bonjour
Man1 : Bonjour
Man2 : Bonjour
Man3 : Bonjour
Belle : There goes the baker with his tray like always
Belle : The same old bread and rolls to sell
Belle : Every morning just the same
Belle : Since the morning that we came
Belle : To this poor provincial town
Jean : Good morning Belle
Belle : Good morning Monsieur Jean Have you lost something again
Jean : Well I believe I have
Jean : The problem is I can't remember what
Jean : Oh well I'm sure it will come to me
Jean : Where are you off to
Belle : To return this book to Père Robert
Belle : It's about two lovers in fair Verona
Jean : Sounds boring
School Boys : SCHOOL BOYS Look there she goes That girl is strange no question
Teacher : Dazed and distracted Can't you tell
Townspeople : Never part of any crowd
Townspeople : Cause her head's up on some cloud
Townspeople : No denying she's a funny girl that Belle
Man4 : Bonjour good day how is your family
Woman2 : Bonjour good day how is your wife
Woman3 : I need six eggs That's too expensive
Belle : There must be more than this provincial life
Père Robert : Ah if it isn't the only bookworm in town
Père Robert : So where did you run off to this week
Belle : Two cities in Northern Italy
Belle : I didn't want to come back
Belle : Have you got any new places to go
Père Robert : I'm afraid not
Père Robert : But you may reread any of the old ones that you'd like
Belle : Thank you
Belle : Your library makes our small corner of the world feel big
Père Robert : Von voyage
Belle : Bye
Townspeople : Look there she goes The girl is so peculiar
Man1 : I wonder if she's feeling well
Townspeople : With a dreamy far off look And her nose stuck in a book
Townspeople : What a puzzle to the rest of us is Belle
Belle : Oh Isn't this amazing
Belle : It's my favorite part
Belle : because you'll see
Belle : Here's where she meets Prince Charming
Belle : But she won't discover that it's him
Belle : Til chapter three
Woman1 : Now it's no wonder That her name means beauty
Woman2 : Her looks have got no parallel
Townspeople;Women : But behind that fair façade I'm afraid she's rather odd
Woman1 : Very different from the rest of us
Women : She's nothing like the rest of us
Women : Yes different from the rest of us
Women : Is Belle
Gaston : Look at her LeFou
Gaston : My future wife
Gaston : Belle is the most beautiful girl in the village
Gaston : That makes her the best
LeFou : But she's so wellread
LeFou : And you're so
LeFou : athletically inclined
Gaston : I know
Gaston : Belle can be as argumentative as she is beautiful
LeFou : Exactly Who needs her when you've got us
Gaston : Yes
Gaston : But ever since the war I've felt like I've been missing something
Gaston : And she's the only girl that gives me that sense of
Gaston : I don't know what that means
Gaston : Right from the moment When I met her saw her
Gaston : I said she's gorgeous and I fell
Gaston : Here in town there's only she Who is beautiful as me
Gaston : So I'm making plans to woo and marry Belle
Women : Look there he goes Isn't he dreamy
Women : Monsieur Gaston oh he's so cute
Women : Be still my heart
Women : I'm hardly breathing He's such a tall dark Strong and handsome brute
LeFou : It's never gonna happen ladies
Women : Bonjour
Man1 : Pardon
Belle : Good day
Woman1 : Mais oui
Man2 : You call this bacon
Woman2 : What lovely flowers
Woman2 : Some cheese
Woman3 : Ten yards
Woman4 : One pound
Gaston : Scuse me
Man3 : I'll get the knife
Gaston : Please let me through
Woman1 : This bread
Man1 : Those fish
Woman1 : It's stale
Man1 : They smell
Man1 : Madame's mistaken
Woman1 : Well maybe so
Belle : There must be more than this provincial life
Townspeople : Good morning
Gaston : Just watch I'm going to make Belle my wife
Townspeople : Oh Good morning
Townspeople : Look there she goes A girl who's strange but special
Townspeople : A most peculiar mademoiselle
Townspeople : It's a pity and a sin She doesn't quite fit in
Townspeople : But she really is a funny girl A beauty but a funny girl
Townspeople : She really is a funny girl
Townspeople : That Belle
Gaston : Good morning Belle
Gaston : Wonderful book you have there
Belle : Have you read it
Gaston : Well not that one But you know books
Gaston : For your dinner table
Gaston : Shall I join you this evening
Belle : Sorry not this evening
Gaston : Busy
Belle : No
LeFou : So moving on
Gaston : No LeFou
Gaston : It's the ones who play hard to get that are always the sweetest prey
Gaston : That's what makes Belle so appealing She hasn't made a fool of herself just to gain my favor
Gaston : What would you call that
LeFou : Dignity
Gaston : It's outrageously attractive isn't it
Woman1 : Gaston
LeFou : Mmm
Maurice : How does a moment last forever
Maurice : How can a story never die
Maurice : It is love we must hold on to
Maurice : Never easy but we try
Maurice : Sometimes our happiness is captured
Maurice : Somehow a time and place stand still
Maurice : Love lives on inside our hearts
Maurice : And always will
Maurice : Oh
Maurice : Belle
Maurice : Hmm
Maurice : Could you Hand me a
Maurice : Thank you
Maurice : And I also need
Maurice : No No No
Maurice : Actually
Maurice : yes that's exactly what I need Thank you
Belle : Papa do you think I'm odd
Maurice : Odd
Maurice : My daughter Odd
Maurice : Where did you get an idea like that
Belle : I don't know People talk
Maurice : This is a small village you know
Maurice : Small minded as well
Maurice : But small also means safe
Maurice : Even back in Paris I knew a girl like you who was so ahead of her time
Maurice : So different
Maurice : People mocked her
Maurice : Until the day they all found themselves imitating her
Belle : Please just tell me one more thing about her
Maurice : Your mother was fearless
Maurice : Fearless
Maurice : So what can I bring you from the market
Maurice : A rose Like the one in the painting
Maurice : You ask for that every year
Belle : And every year you bring it
Maurice : Then I shall bring you another
Maurice : You have my word
Belle : Goodbye Papa
Maurice : Goodbye Belle
Maurice : Come on Philippe
Maurice : You know the way
Belle : I'll see you tomorrow
Maurice : Right Tomorrow with the rose
Belle : Stay safe
Girl : What are you doing
Belle : The laundry
Belle : Come Come
Belle : The blue bird
Girl : That flies
Girl : over the dark
Girl : wood
Belle : That was amazing
Man1 : What on earth are you doing
Man1 : Teaching another girl to read
Man1 : Isn't one enough
Woman1 : We have to do something
Gaston : You are the wildest most gorgeous thing I have ever seen
Gaston : Nobody deserves you
Gaston : But at least I know our children will be beautiful
LeFou : Am I catching you at a bad time
Gaston : What is it LeFou A certain damsel is in distress
Gaston : Ah It's hero time
Gaston : I'm not done with you yet
LeFou : Me neither
Gaston : Belle I heard you had trouble with the Headmaster
Gaston : He never liked me either
Gaston : Can I give you a little advice about the villagers though
Gaston : They're never going to trust the kind of change you're trying to bring
Belle : All I wanted was to teach a child to read
Gaston : The only children you should concern yourself with are your own
Belle : I'm not ready to have children
Gaston : Maybe you haven't met the right man
Belle : It's a small village Gaston I've met them all
Gaston : Well maybe you should take another look
Gaston : Some of us have changed
Belle : Gaston we could never make each other happy
Belle : No one can change that much
Gaston : Oh Belle
Gaston : Do you know what happens to spinsters in this village after their fathers die
Woman1;Agathe : Coins Got any spare coins
Gaston : They beg for scraps like poor Agathe
Gaston : This is our world Belle
Gaston : For simple folk like us it doesn't get any better
Belle : I might be a farm girl
Belle : But I'm not simple
Belle : and I'm never going to marry you Gaston I'm sorry
Belle : Can you imagine
Belle : Me The wife of that boorish brainless
Belle : Madame Gaston can't you just see it
Belle : Madame Gaston his little wife Ugh
Belle : No sir not me I guarantee it
Belle : I want much more than this provincial life
Belle : I want adventure in the great wide somewhere
Belle : I want it more than I can tell
Belle : And for once it might be grand
Belle : To have someone understand
Belle : I want so much more Than they've got planned
Maurice : The woods are lovely
Maurice : I only wish I recognized them
Maurice : Do you know where we are Philippe Because I don't
Maurice : It's all right It's all right Philippe
Maurice : Hmm
Maurice : Yes we can go this way
Maurice : Go on To the right
Maurice : That's it Steady
Maurice : Walk on
Maurice : One path closes another one opens
Maurice : It's all right boy It's just a bit of snow In June
Maurice : Mind your step It's slippery
Maurice : Go Go Philippe Come on Come on
Maurice : Whoa
Maurice : Come on
Maurice : Go Philippe go Go go
Maurice : Whoa
Maurice : Philippe
Maurice : Good boy
Maurice : Go boy Go
Maurice : Oh Philippe you saved my life
Maurice : Well done Yes
Maurice : They'll have to get their dinner somewhere else won't they
Maurice : Look There's hay And water
Maurice : You're all set my old friend
Maurice : I'll go pay my respects to our unwitting host
Maurice : Whoever that may be
Maurice : Hmm
Maurice : Thank you
Maurice : Thank
Maurice : Hello
Maurice : Sorry to intrude I'm just a traveler
Maurice : seeking shelter from the storm
Maurice : Sorry to disturb you
Maurice : Anyone home
Maurice : Anyone awake
Lumière : He must have lost his way in the woods
Cogsworth : Shut up you idiot
Maurice : Excuse me
Maurice : Hmm
Cogsworth : Beautiful
Maurice : Extraordinary
Lumière : A man of taste
Cogsworth : He was talking about me
Maestro Cadenza : Oops
Maurice : Well wherever you are
Maurice : I'm just going to warm myself by the fire
Maurice : That's better
Maurice : Oh much better
Maurice : Ooh
Maurice : Thank you
Chip : Mum said I wasn't supposed to move because it might be scary
Chip : Sorry
Maurice : It's all right
Maurice : I uh I cannot thank you enough for your hospitality
Maurice : I'll
Maurice : bid you adieu and good night
Maurice : Come on Philippe Go Go
Maurice : No wait wait wait
Maurice : Roses I nearly forgot
Maurice : We're safe here
Maurice : I promised Belle a rose
Maurice : There
Belle : Philippe
Belle : What happened
Belle : Where's Papa
Belle : Take me to him
Lumière : Look Cogsworth
Lumière : A beautiful girl
Cogsworth : Yes I can see it's a girl
Cogsworth : I lost my hands not my eyes
Lumière : But what if she is the one The one who'll break the spell
Belle : Who said that
Belle : Who's there
Cogsworth : Uhoh
Belle : Papa
Belle : Papa is that you
Maurice : Belle
Maurice : How did you find me
Belle : Your hands are ice
Belle : We need to get you home
Maurice : Belle you must leave here at once This castle is alive
Maurice : Now go before he finds you
Belle : Who
Belle : Who's there
Belle : Who are you
Beast(Prince Adam) : Who are you
Belle : I've come for my father
Beast(Prince Adam) : Your father is a thief
Belle : Liar
Beast(Prince Adam) : He stole a rose
Belle : I asked for the rose Punish me not him
Maurice : No He means forever
Maurice : Apparently that's what happens around here when you pick a flower
Belle : A life sentence for a rose
Beast(Prince Adam) : I received eternal damnation for one
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'm merely locking him away
Beast(Prince Adam) : Now do you still wish to take your father's place
Belle : Come into the light
Beast(Prince Adam) : Choose
Maurice : Belle I won't let you do this
Maurice : I lost your mother I won't lose you too
Maurice : Now go
Maurice : Go
Belle : All right Papa I'll leave
Belle : I need a minute alone with him
Belle : Are you so coldhearted you won't allow a daughter to kiss her father goodbye
Belle : Forever can spare a minute
Beast(Prince Adam) : When this door closes it will not open again
Belle : I should have been with you
Maurice : Oh no no Belle listen to me
Maurice : It's all right
Maurice : Now go
Maurice : Live your life
Maurice : And forget me
Belle : Forget you
Belle : Everything I am is because of you
Maurice : I love you Belle
Maurice : Don't be afraid
Belle : I love you too Papa
Belle : I'm not afraid
Belle : And I will escape I promise
Maurice : What
Beast(Prince Adam) : You took his place
Belle : He's my father
Beast(Prince Adam) : He's a fool
Beast(Prince Adam) : And so are you
Maurice : Belle
Belle : Papa
Belle : Don't hurt him
Maurice : No
Maurice : I'll come back
Maurice : I promise
Lumière : Forgive my intrusion mademoiselle but I have come to escort you to your room
Belle : My room
Belle : But I thought
Lumière : Oh what That Once this door closes it will not open again
Lumière : I know He gets so dramatic
Lumière : Hello
Lumière : Ooh
Lumière : Oh you are very strong
Lumière : This is a great quality
Belle : What are you
Lumière : I am Lumière
Belle : And you can talk
Cogsworth : Well of course he can talk
Cogsworth : It's all he ever does
Cogsworth : Now Lumière as head of the household I demand that you put her back in her cell at once
Lumière : What do you want to be for the rest of your life Cogsworth A man or a mantle clock
Lumière : Ready miss
Lumière : Trust me
Cogsworth : Oh
Lumière : You must forgive first impressions
Lumière : I hope you are not too startled
Belle : Why would I be startled
Belle : I'm talking to a candle
Lumière : Candelabra please
Lumière : Enormous difference
Lumière : But consider me at your service The castle is your home now so feel free to go anywhere you like
Cogsworth : Except the west wing
Cogsworth : Which we do not have
Belle : Why What's in the west wing
Lumière : Oh nothing
Cogsworth : Nothing
Lumière : Storage space
Cogsworth : Storage space
Lumière : That's it
Cogsworth : That's it
Lumière : Yes that's it
Cogsworth : This way please To the east wing
Lumière : Or as I like to call it the only wing
Lumière : Watch your step s'il vous plaît
Lumière : Welcome to your new home
Lumière : It's modest but comfortable
Belle : It's beautiful
Lumière : But of course Master wanted you to have the finest room in the castle
Lumière : Oh dear We were not expecting guests
Plumette : Enchantée mademoiselle
Plumette : Don't worry
Plumette : I'll have this place spotless in no time
Plumette : This plan of yours is dangerous
Lumière : I would risk anything to kiss you again Plumette
Plumette : No my love I've been burned by you before
Plumette : We must be strong
Lumière : How can I be strong when you make me so weak
Belle : Is everything here alive
Belle : Hello What's your name
Cogsworth : That is a hairbrush
Lumière : Do not be alarmed This is just your wardrobe
Lumière : Meet Madame De Garderobe A great singer
Cogsworth : When she can stay awake
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Cogsworth A diva needs her beauty rest
Lumière : Stay with us Madame
Lumière : We have someone for you to dress
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Finally
Madame de la Grande Bouche : a woman
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Pretty eyes
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Proud face Perfect canvas Yes
Madame de la Grande Bouche : I will find you something worthy of a princess
Belle : Oh I'm not a princess
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Nonsense
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Now let's see what I've got in my drawers
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Oh How embarrassing
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Froufrou come help Mama
Lumière : Subtle Understated I love it
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Froufrou send my love to the maestro
Gaston : Picture it LeFou
Gaston : A rustic cabin
Gaston : my latest kill roasting on the fire
Gaston : adorable children running around us as my love
Gaston : rubs my tired feet
Gaston : But what does Belle say
Gaston : I will never marry you Gaston
LeFou : You know there are other girls
Gaston : A great hunter doesn't waste his time on rabbits
LeFou : Gosh it disturbs me to see you Gaston
LeFou : Looking so down in the dumps
LeFou : Every guy here'd love to be you Gaston
LeFou : Even when taking your lumps
LeFou : There's no man in town as admired as you
LeFou : You're everyone's favorite guy
LeFou : Everyone's awed and inspired by you
LeFou : And it's not very hard to see why
LeFou : No one's slick as Gaston
LeFou : No one's quick as Gaston
LeFou : No one's neck's as incredibly thick as Gaston
LeFou : For there's no man in town half as manly
Women : Perfect a pure paragon
LeFou : You can ask any Tom Dick or Stanley
LeFou : And they'll tell you whose team they prefer to be on
LeFou : Who plays
Men : Darts like Gaston
LeFou : Who breaks
Men : Hearts like Gaston
LeFou : Who's much more than the sum of his parts like Gaston
Gaston : As a specimen yes I'm intimidating
All : My what a guy that Gaston
Gaston : I needed encouragement
Gaston : Thank you LeFou
LeFou : Well there's no one As easy to bolster as you
LeFou : Too much
Gaston : Yep
All : No one fights like Gaston
All : Douses lights like Gaston
LeFou : In a wrestling match Nobody bites like Gaston
Gaston : When I hunt I sneak up with my quiver
Gaston : And beasts of the field say a prayer
LeFou : Aah
Gaston : First I carefully aim for the liver
Gaston : Then I shoot from behind
LeFou : Is that fair
Gaston : I don't care
All : No one hits like Gaston Matches wits like Gaston
LeFou : In a spitting match nobody spits like Gaston
Gaston : I'm especially good at expectorating
All : Ooh
All : Ten points for Gaston
Gaston : Thank you Thank you
Gaston : When I was a lad I ate four dozen eggs
Gaston : Every morning to help me get large
Gaston : And now that I'm grown I eat five dozen eggs
Gaston : So I'm roughly the size of a barge
All : ALL Hey Hey
All : Hey
All : Hey Hey
All : Hey Hey Hey
LeFou : Who has brains
All : Like Gaston
LeFou : Entertains
Gaston : Who can make up these endless refrains like Gaston
Gaston : I use antlers in all of my decorating
All;Gaston : Say it again
All;LeFou : Who's a man among men
All;LeFou : Who's a super success Don't you know Can't you guess Ask his fans and his five hangerson
All;LeFou : There's just one guy in town Who's got all of it down
LeFou : And his name's GAST
LeFou : I believe there's another T
LeFou : It just occurred to me that I'm illiterate
LeFou : And I've never actually had to spell it out loud before
LeFou;All : Gaston
Gaston : Oh LeFou you're the best
Gaston : How is it no girl has snatched you up yet
LeFou : I've been told I'm clingy but I really don't get it
Maurice : Please please Someone someone
Maurice : You help
Tavern Keeper : Whoa whoa
Maurice : You must help me
Maurice : It's Belle He's got he's got Belle She's locked in a dungeon
Tavern Keeper : TAVERN KEEPER Who's got her
Maurice : A beast
Maurice : A huge horrid monstrous beast
Maurice : My daughter's life is in danger Why do you laugh It's not a joke
Maurice : His castle is hidden in the woods
Maurice : It's already winter there
Man1 : Winter in June
Man2 : Crazy old Maurice
Maurice : Listen to me
Maurice : The beast is real
Maurice : Do you understand
Maurice : Will no one help me
Gaston : I'll help Maurice
Maurice : What
LeFou : You will
Gaston : Everybody stop making fun of this man at once
Maurice : Captain thank you
Gaston : Don't thank me Maurice
Gaston : Lead us to the beast
Maurice : Come
Gaston : Hmm
LeFou : Oh
Chip : Mama There's a girl in the castle
Mrs. Potts : Yes Chip we know
Chip : What kind of tea does she like
Chip : Herbal oolong chamomile
Chip : I'm too excited
Mrs. Potts : Slow down before you break your handle
Lumière : Heads up Mrs Potts
Mrs. Potts : Oh
Beast(Prince Adam) : Lumière
Cogsworth : Oh Be calm Let me do the talking
Beast(Prince Adam) : You're making her dinner
Lumière : Well we thought you might appreciate the company
Cogsworth : Master I just want to assure you that I had no part in this hopeless plan
Cogsworth : Preparing a dinner designing a gown for her giving her a suite in the east wing
Beast(Prince Adam) : You gave her a bedroom
Cogsworth : No no no He gave her a bedroom
Lumière : This is true
Lumière : But if this girl is the one who can break the spell then maybe you could start by using dinner to charm her
Lumière : Good thinking Cogsworth
Cogsworth : What
Beast(Prince Adam) : That's the most ridiculous idea I've ever heard Charm the prisoner
Lumière : But you must try Master With every passing day we become less human
Beast(Prince Adam) : She's the daughter of a common thief
Beast(Prince Adam) : What kind of person do you think that makes her
Mrs. Potts : Oh you can't judge people by who their father is now can you
Beast(Prince Adam) : You'll join me for dinner
Beast(Prince Adam) : That's not a request
Mrs. Potts : Gently Master The girl lost her father and her freedom in one day
Lumière : Yes the poor thing is probably in there scared to death
Mrs. Potts : Exactly
Belle : Just a minute
Lumière : You see There she is Now remember be gentle
Mrs. Potts : Kind
Plumette : Charming
Cogsworth : Sweet
Lumière : And when she opens the door give her a dashing debonair smile
Lumière : Come come Show me the smile
All : Oh mon dieu Oh no
Beast(Prince Adam) : Will you join me for dinner
Belle : You've taken me as your prisoner and now you want to have dinner with me
Belle : Are you insane
Plumette : Uhoh He's losing it
Cogsworth : Oh dear
Beast(Prince Adam) : I told you to join me for dinner
Belle : And I told you no
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Ooh What time is it
Madame de la Grande Bouche : What's happening
Belle : I'd starve before I ever ate with you
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well be my guest
Beast(Prince Adam) : Go ahead and starve
Beast(Prince Adam) : If she doesn't eat with me then she doesn't eat at all
Beast(Prince Adam) : Idiots
Cogsworth : You can't talk to us like that I forbid it
Cogsworth : Uh Oh Am I too late
Cogsworth : Shame I was really going to tell him off this time
Lumière : Oh Master you've returned
Cogsworth : Oh very funny
Lumière : I got you there
Beast(Prince Adam) : Show me the girl
Lumière : Another petal fell
Plumette : Lumière
Plumette : I grew three more feathers And I just plucked yesterday
Lumière : I know darling
Lumière : I'm getting more metallic every day
Cogsworth : Oh no It's happening again Pardon me
Mrs. Potts : Oh everyone calm yourselves We still have time
Chip : Mama
Chip : am I ever going to be a boy again
Mrs. Potts : Oh yes Chip You'll have your days in the sun again You just leave it to me
Belle : I told you to go away
Mrs. Potts : Don't worry dear It's only Mrs Potts
Mrs. Potts : Oh Oh aren't you a vision
Mrs. Potts : How lovely to make your acquaintance
Mrs. Potts : It's a very long journey Let me fix you up before you go
Mrs. Potts : I have found that most troubles seem less troubling after a bracing cup of tea
Mrs. Potts : Slowly now Chip
Chip : Pleased to meet you
Chip : Wanna see me do a trick
Mrs. Potts : Chip
Mrs. Potts : That was a very brave thing you did for your father dearie
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Yes
Madame de la Grande Bouche : We all think so
Belle : I'm worried about him
Belle : He's never been on his own
Mrs. Potts : Cheer up my poppet
Mrs. Potts : Things will turn out in the end You'll feel a lot better after dinner
Belle : But he said If she doesn't eat with me then she doesn't eat at all
Mrs. Potts : Mmm people say a lot of things in anger
Mrs. Potts : It is our choice whether or not to listen
Mrs. Potts : You coming poppet
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Go
Lumière : They are coming Final checks everyone Tout de suite
Cogsworth : No you don't
Cogsworth : If the master finds out you violated his orders and fed her he will blame me
Lumière : Yes I will make sure of it
Lumière : But did you see her stand up to him
Lumière : I am telling you this girl is the one
Lumière : They must fall in love if we are to be human again and how can they fall in love if she stays in her room
Lumière : Hey Chapeau you missed a spot
Cogsworth : You know she'll never love him
Lumière : A broken clock is right two times a day mon ami but this is not one of those times Stand up straight
Lumière : It's time to sparkle
Lumière : Mmm I have no taste buds
Lumière : but I can tell this is exquisite
Lumière : Off Off me while I work
Lumière : Pepper get cracking Salt shake a leg
Cogsworth : Not so loud
Cogsworth : Keep it down
Lumière : Of course of course But what is dinner without a little music
Cogsworth : Music
Lumière : Maestro Cadenza are you ready
Maestro Cadenza : It has been so long since I have performed
Maestro Cadenza : I can barely even remember how
Lumière : Ah
Lumière : Ooh
Maestro Cadenza : Another cavity
Maestro Cadenza : Maestro your wife is upstairs
Maestro Cadenza : finding it harder and harder to stay awake
Maestro Cadenza : She's counting on you to help us break this curse
Maestro Cadenza : Then I shall play through the dental pain
Cogsworth : Maestro play quietly please
Maestro Cadenza : Oh quietly Sotto voce Of course
Maestro Cadenza : Are there any other tasteless demands you wish to make upon my artistry
Cogsworth : No that's it
Mrs. Potts : There you are dear
Lumière : Ma chère mademoiselle It is with deepest pride and greatest pleasure that we welcome you tonight
Lumière : Here And now
Lumière : we invite you to relax
Lumière : Let us pull up a chair
Lumière : as the dining room proudly presents
Lumière : Your dinner
Lumière : Be our guest be our guest
Lumière : Put our service to the test
Lumière : Tie your napkin round your neck chérie And we'll provide the rest
Lumière : Soup du jour hot hors d'oeuvres
Lumière : Why we only live to serve
Lumière : Try the grey stuff it's delicious
Lumière : Don't believe me Ask the dishes
Lumière : They can sing they can dance After all miss this is France
Lumière : And a dinner here is never second best
Lumière : Go on unfold your menu Take a glance and then you'll
Lumière : Be our guest oui our guest
Lumière : Be our guest
Cogsworth : Ooh
Lumière : Beef ragout Cheese soufflé Pie and pudding en flambé
Lumière : We'll prepare and serve with flair A culinary cabaret
Lumière : You're alone and you're scared But the banquet's all prepared
Lumière : No one's gloomy or complaining While the flatware's entertaining
Lumière : We tell jokes I do tricks With my fellow candlesticks
All : And it's all in perfect taste That you can bet
Lumière : Come on and lift your glass You've won your own free pass
Lumière : To be our guest If you're stressed It's fine dining we suggest
Lumière : Be our guest
Lumière;All : Be our guest be our guest
Lumière : Life is so unnerving
Lumière : For a servant who's not serving
Lumière : He's not whole Without a soul to wait upon
Lumière : Ah those good old days when we were useful
Lumière : Eh Cogsworth
Lumière : Suddenly those good old days are gone
Lumière : Too long we've been rusting
Lumière : Needing so much more than dusting
Lumière : Needing exercise a chance to use our skills
Lumière : Most days we just lay around the castle
Lumière : Flabby fat and lazy You walked in and whoopsadaisy
Mrs. Potts : It's a guest it's a guest
Mrs. Potts : Sakes alive well I'll be blessed
Mrs. Potts : Wine's been poured and thank the Lord I've had the napkins freshly pressed
Mrs. Potts : With dessert she'll want tea And my dear that's fine with me
Mrs. Potts : While the cups do their softshoeing I'll be bubbling I'll be brewing
Mrs. Potts : I'll get warm piping hot
Mrs. Potts : Heaven's sakes is that a spot
Mrs. Potts : Clean it up we want the company impressed
Mrs. Potts : We've got a lot to do Is it one lump or two
Mrs. Potts : For you our guest
Lumière : She's our guest
Mrs. Potts : She's our guest
Lumière;Cogsworth : She's our guest
All : Be our guest be our guest Our command is your request
All : It's been years since we've had anybody Here and we're obsessed
Lumière;All : With your meal With your ease
Lumière;All : Yes indeed we aim to please
Lumière;All : While the candlelight's still glowing
Lumière;All : Let us help you we'll keep going
Cogsworth : Course by
Lumière : Course One by one
Lumière : Til you shout Enough I'm done
Cogsworth;Lumière : Then we'll sing you off to sleep As you digest
Lumière;Cogsworth : Tonight you'll prop your feet up But for now let's eat up Be our guest
Lumière;Cogsworth : Be our guest
Lumière;Cogsworth : Please be our
Lumière : guest
Lumière : Pudding
Belle : I don't understand why you're all being so kind to me
Belle : Surely you're as trapped here as I am
Belle : Don't you ever want to escape
Mrs. Potts : The master's not as terrible as he appears
Mrs. Potts : Somewhere deep in his soul there's a prince
Mrs. Potts : of a fellow who just waiting to be set free
Belle : Lumière mentioned something about the west wing
Mrs. Potts : Never you mind about that
Mrs. Potts : Off to bed with you poppet
Belle : Good night
Mrs. Potts : Nightynight
Mrs. Potts : Straight to bed
Beast(Prince Adam) : What are you doing here What did you do to it
Belle : Nothing
Beast(Prince Adam) : Do you realize what you could have done
Beast(Prince Adam) : You could have damned us all
Beast(Prince Adam) : Get out of here
Beast(Prince Adam) : Go
Lumière : Checkmate Again
Cogsworth : Wait No You cheated again
Lumière : Mademoiselle what are you doing
Belle : Getting out of here
Cogsworth : Stop
Lumière : Go Go Froufrou
Cogsworth : Yes Froufrou Stop her
Lumière : Don't let her leave
Mrs. Potts : Stop her
Mrs. Potts : No No Froufrou
Cogsworth : No No it's not play time
Lumière : Not now silly boy
Cogsworth : Bad dog Bad dog
Lumière : No No No
Lumière : Please don't go
Lumière : It's dangerous
Mrs. Potts : Oh my
Belle : You have to help me
Belle : You have to stand
Maurice : No I'm sure this is the way
Maurice : Do you hear those wolves
Maurice : That means we're getting very close to the castle
Gaston : Look enough is enough We have to turn back
Maurice : Stop
Maurice : That's it
Maurice : There it is
Maurice : That's the tree
Maurice : I'm sure of it
Maurice : It was downed by lightning at the time
Maurice : But now
Maurice : it's resumed an upright position through some sort of
Maurice : magic or other
LeFou : You really wanna marry into this family
Maurice : So that means that the castle is that
Maurice : No
Maurice : No it's
Maurice : That way Definitely that way
Gaston : I am done playing this game of yours
Gaston : Where is Belle
Maurice : The beast took her and she
Gaston : There are no such things as beasts
Gaston : Or talking teacups Or magic
Gaston : But there are wolves frostbite and starvation
LeFou : Deep breaths Gaston Deep breaths
Gaston : So why don't we just turn around Go back to Villeneuve
Gaston : I'm sure Belle is at home cooking up a lovely dinner
Maurice : If you think I've made all this up then why did you offer to help
Gaston : Because I want to marry your daughter
Gaston : Now let's go home
Maurice : Belle is not at home
Maurice : She is with the
Gaston : You say beast one more time
Gaston : I will feed you to the wolves
LeFou : Gaston Stop it Breathe
LeFou : Think happy thoughts Go back to the war Blood Explosions Countless widows
Gaston : Widows
LeFou : Yes Yes That's it
LeFou : That's it
Gaston : Maurice Please forgive me old bean
Gaston : That's no way to talk to my future fatherinlaw now is it
Maurice : Future fatherinlaw
Gaston : Yeah
Maurice : You will never marry my daughter
LeFou : I saw that coming
Gaston : If Maurice won't give me his blessing
Gaston : then he is in my way
Gaston : Once the wolves are finished with him Belle will have no one to take care of her but me
LeFou : For the sake of exhausting all of our options do we maybe wanna consider a slightly less gruesome alternative
Gaston : Are you coming
Gaston : Yah
Beast(Prince Adam) : That hurts
Belle : If you held still it wouldn't hurt as much
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well if you hadn't run away none of this would have happened
Belle : Well if you hadn't frightened me I wouldn't have run away
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well you shouldn't have been in the west wing
Belle : Well you should learn to control your temper
Belle : Try to get some rest
Mrs. Potts : Thank you miss
Lumière : We are eternally grateful
Belle : Why do you care about him so much
Mrs. Potts : We've looked after him all his life
Belle : But he's cursed you somehow Why
Belle : You did nothing
Mrs. Potts : You're quite right there dear
Mrs. Potts : You see when the master lost his mother
Mrs. Potts : and his cruel father took that sweet innocent lad
Mrs. Potts : and twisted him up to be just like him
Mrs. Potts : we did nothing
Lumière : Let him sleep
Young Prince : Days in the sun
Young Prince : When my life has barely begun
Young Prince : Not until my whole life is done
Young Prince : Will I ever leave you
Maestro Cadenza : Will I tremble again
Maestro Cadenza : To my dear one's gorgeous refrain
Plumette;Lumière : Will you now forever remain
Plumette;Lumière : Out of reach of my arms
Mrs. Potts : Oh those days in the sun
Mrs. Potts : What I'd give to relive just one
Chip : Night Mama
Mrs. Potts : Undo what's done
Mrs. Potts : And bring back the light
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Oh I could sing
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Of the pain these dark days bring
Madame de la Grande Bouche : The spell we're under
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Still it's the wonder of us I sing of tonight
Belle : How in the midst of all this sorrow
Belle : Can so much hope and love endure
Belle : I was innocent and certain
Belle : Now I'm wiser but unsure
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Days in the past
Belle : I can't go back into my childhood
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Oh those precious days couldn't last
Belle : One that my father made secure
Belle : I can feel a change in me
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Oh hold me closer
Belle : I'm stronger now but still not free
Belle;Madame de la Grande Bouche : Days in the sun Will return we must believe
Belle;Madame de la Grande Bouche;Lumière : As lovers do
Belle;Lumière;Madame de la Grande Bouche : That days in the sun
Belle;Lumière;Madame de la Grande Bouche : Will come shining
Belle;Lumière;Madame de la Grande Bouche : through
Belle : What happens when the last petal falls
Lumière : The master remains a beast forever
Lumière : And we become
Mrs. Potts : Antiques
Lumière : Knickknacks
Plumette : Lightlyused
Chip : houseware
Cogsworth : Rubbish
Cogsworth : We become rubbish
Belle : I want to help you
Belle : There must be some way to break the curse
Cogsworth : Well there is one
Mrs. Potts : It's not for you to worry about lamb
Mrs. Potts : We've made our bed and we must lie in it
Agathe : Drink
Maurice : Thank you Agathe
Belle : Love can transpose to form and dignity
Belle : Love looks not with the eyes but with the mind and therefore
Belle;Beast(Prince Adam) : And therefore is winged Cupid painted blind
Belle : You know Shakespeare
Beast(Prince Adam) : I had an expensive education
Belle : Actually Romeo and Juliet's my favorite play
Beast(Prince Adam) : Why is that not a surprise
Belle : I'm sorry
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well all that heartache and pining and
Beast(Prince Adam) : So many better things to read
Belle : Like what
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well there are a couple of things in here you could start with
Beast(Prince Adam) : Are you all right
Belle : It's wonderful
Beast(Prince Adam) : Yes I suppose it is
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well if you like it so much then it's yours
Belle : Have you really read every one of these books
Beast(Prince Adam) : What
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well not all of them
Beast(Prince Adam) : Some of them are in Greek
Belle : Was that a joke
Belle : Are you making jokes now
Beast(Prince Adam) : Maybe
Belle : The air is blue and keen and cold and in a frozen sheath enrolled
Belle : Each branch each twig each blade of grass seems clad miraculously with
Belle : glass
Beast(Prince Adam) : I feel as if I'm seeing it for the first time
Beast(Prince Adam) : Is there any more
Belle : Um
Belle : But in that solemn silence is heard the whisper of every sleeping thing
Belle : Look Look at me
Belle : Come wake me up
Belle : For still here I be
Belle : There's something sweet and almost kind
Belle : But he was mean and he was coarse and unrefined
Belle : And now he's dear and so unsure
Belle : I wonder why I didn't see it there before
Beast(Prince Adam) : She glanced this way I thought I saw
Beast(Prince Adam) : And when we touched She didn't shudder at my paw
Beast(Prince Adam) : No it can't be I'll just ignore
Beast(Prince Adam) : But then she's never looked at me That way before
Belle : New and a bit alarming
Belle : Who'd have ever thought that this could be
Belle : True that he's no Prince Charming
Belle : But there's something in him That I simply didn't see
Plumette : Well who'd have thought
Mrs. Potts : Well bless my soul
Cogsworth : Well who'd have known
Lumière : Well who indeed
Lumière : And who'd have guessed They'd come together on their own
Mrs. Potts : It's so peculiar Wait and see
All : We'll wait and see A few days more
All : There may be something there That wasn't there before
Cogsworth : And here's a thought
Cogsworth : Perhaps there's something there That wasn't there before
Chip : What Mama
Mrs. Potts : There may be something there That wasn't there before
Chip : What is it What's there
Mrs. Potts : I'll tell you when you're older
Chip : Okay I'm older
Mrs. Potts : Chip
Mrs. Potts : You are a one
Belle : What are you reading
Beast(Prince Adam) : Nothing
Belle : Guinevere and Lancelot
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well actually
Beast(Prince Adam) : King Arthur and the Round Table
Beast(Prince Adam) : Knights and men and swords and things
Belle : Mmm
Belle : Still
Belle : it's a romance
Beast(Prince Adam) : All right
Belle : I never thanked you for saving my life
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well I never thanked you for not leaving me to be eaten by wolves
Belle : They know how to have a good time
Beast(Prince Adam) : Yes But when I enter the room laughter dies
Belle : Me too
Belle : The villagers say that I'm a funny girl
Belle : but I'm not sure they mean it as a compliment
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'm sorry
Beast(Prince Adam) : Your village sounds terrible
Belle : Almost as lonely as your castle
Beast(Prince Adam) : What do you say we run away
Beast(Prince Adam) : Another little gift from the enchantress
Beast(Prince Adam) : A book that truly allows you to escape
Belle : How amazing
Beast(Prince Adam) : It was her cruelest trick of all
Beast(Prince Adam) : It was just another curse
Beast(Prince Adam) : The outside world has no place for a creature like me
Beast(Prince Adam) : but it can for you
Beast(Prince Adam) : Think of the one place you've always wanted to see
Beast(Prince Adam) : Now find it in your mind's eye
Beast(Prince Adam) : Then feel it in your heart
Beast(Prince Adam) : Where did you take us
Belle : Paris
Beast(Prince Adam) : Oh I love Paris
Beast(Prince Adam) : What would you like to see first
Beast(Prince Adam) : Notre Dame
Beast(Prince Adam) : The ChampsÉlysées
Beast(Prince Adam) : No
Beast(Prince Adam) : Too touristy
Belle : It's so much smaller than I imagined
Belle : This is the Paris of my childhood
Belle : These were the borders of my life
Belle : In this crumbling dusty attic
Belle : Where an artist loved his wife
Belle : Easy to remember
Belle : Harder to move on
Belle : Knowing the Paris of my childhood
Belle : Is gone
Beast(Prince Adam) : What happened to your mother
Belle : It was the one story Papa could never bring himself to tell
Belle : I knew better than to ask
Beast(Prince Adam) : Oh A doctor's mask
Beast(Prince Adam) : Plague
Plague Doctor : You must leave now
Belle's Mother : Quickly before it takes her too
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'm sorry I ever called your father a thief
Belle : Let's go home
LeFou : This is some storm huh
LeFou : At least we're not tied to a tree in the middle of nowhere surrounded by bloodthirsty wolves
LeFou : You know it's not too late We could always turn back
LeFou : It's just every time I close my eyes
LeFou : I picture Maurice stranded alone And then when I open them
LeFou : he's
LeFou : Maurice
Tavern Keeper : Gaston
Tavern Keeper : did you try to kill Maurice
Gaston : Maurice
Gaston : Thank heavens
Gaston : I've spent the last five days trying to find you
Maurice : You tried to kill me You left me to the wolves
Gaston : Wolves
Gaston : It's one thing to rave about your delusions It's another to accuse me of attempted murder
Man1 : Maurice
Man1 : do you have any proof of what you're saying
Maurice : Ask Agathe She rescued me
Gaston : Agathe
Gaston : You'd hang your accusations on the testimony of a filthy hag
Gaston : No offense Agathe
Maurice : Monsieur LeFou
Maurice : He was there He saw it all
LeFou : Me
Gaston : You're right
Gaston : Don't take my word for it
Gaston : LeFou
Gaston : my dearest companion
Gaston : did I
Gaston : your oldest friend and most loyal compatriot
Gaston : try to kill the father of the only woman I've ever loved
LeFou : Well it's a complicated question on a number of accounts
LeFou : But no
Gaston : No he did not
Maurice : You
Gaston : Maurice
Gaston : it pains me to say this but you've become a danger to yourself and others
Gaston : No wonder Belle ran away
Gaston : You need help sir
Gaston : A place to heal your troubled mind
Gaston : Everything's going to be fine
Gaston : Just fine
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well I saw her in the ballroom and said You're making everything look so beautiful We should have a dance tonight
Beast(Prince Adam) : I never imagined she'd actually say yes
Beast(Prince Adam) : What was I thinking
Lumière : No Master It's perfect
Lumière : The rose has only four petals left which means tonight
Lumière : you can tell her how you feel
Beast(Prince Adam) : I feel like a fool
Beast(Prince Adam) : She will never love me
Lumière : Do not be discouraged
Lumière : She is the one
Beast(Prince Adam) : I wish you'd stop saying that
Beast(Prince Adam) : There is no one
Lumière : You care for her don't you
Lumière : Well then woo her with beautiful music and romantic candlelight
Plumette : Yes and when the moment's just right
Beast(Prince Adam) : Well how will I know
Cogsworth : You will feel slightly nauseous
Lumière : Don't worry Master You'll do fine
Mrs. Potts : Just stop being so nervous and tell Belle how you feel
Mrs. Potts : Because if you don't I promise you'll be drinking cold tea for the rest of your days
Lumière : In the dark
Plumette : Covered in dust
Lumière : Dark and very very dusty
Lumière : Start with the hair
Lumière : Women love nice hair
Mrs. Potts : I'll take the fingers and toes
Beast(Prince Adam) : Chapeau brush those teeth They need it
Lumière : Dip dip
Lumière : Snip snip
Lumière : Polish the nails
Lumière : Shine the horns
Plumette : Eyes closed Poof poof
Lumière : And to top it all off
Lumière : Voilà
Lumière : Okay I can fix this
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Oh Beautiful
Madame de la Grande Bouche : But something is missing
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Oh yes
Madame de la Grande Bouche : The finishing touch
Mrs. Potts : Tale as old as time
Mrs. Potts : True as it can be
Mrs. Potts : Barely even friends
Mrs. Potts : Then somebody bends unexpectedly
Mrs. Potts : Just a little change
Mrs. Potts : Small to say the least
Mrs. Potts : Both a little scared
Mrs. Potts : Neither one prepared
Mrs. Potts : Beauty and the Beast
Mrs. Potts : Ever just the same
Mrs. Potts : Ever a surprise
Mrs. Potts : Ever as before
Mrs. Potts : Ever just as sure
Mrs. Potts : As the sun will rise
Mrs. Potts : Tale as old as time
Mrs. Potts : Tune as old as song
Mrs. Potts : Bittersweet and strange Finding you can change
Mrs. Potts : Learning you were wrong
Mrs. Potts : Certain as the sun
Mrs. Potts : Rising in the east
Mrs. Potts : Tale as old as time
Mrs. Potts : Song as old as rhyme
Mrs. Potts : Beauty and the Beast
Mrs. Potts : Tale as old as time
Mrs. Potts : Song as old as rhyme
Mrs. Potts : Beauty and the Beast
Beast(Prince Adam) : I haven't danced in years
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'd almost forgotten the feeling
Beast(Prince Adam) : It's foolish I suppose
Beast(Prince Adam) : for a creature like me to hope that one day he might earn your affection
Belle : I don't know
Beast(Prince Adam) : Really
Beast(Prince Adam) : You think you could be happy here
Belle : Can anybody be happy if they aren't free
Belle : My father taught me to dance
Belle : I used to step on his toes a lot
Beast(Prince Adam) : You must miss him
Belle : Very much
Beast(Prince Adam) : Would you like to see him
Belle : I'd like to see my father
Belle : Papa
Belle : What are they doing to him
Belle : He's in trouble
Beast(Prince Adam) : Then you must go to him
Belle : What did you say
Beast(Prince Adam) : You must go to him
Beast(Prince Adam) : No time to waste
Beast(Prince Adam) : No
Beast(Prince Adam) : you keep it with you
Beast(Prince Adam) : Then you'll always have a way to look back on me
Belle : Thank you
Mrs. Potts : Oh
Cogsworth : Well Master I have had my doubts but everything is moving like clockwork
Cogsworth : True love really does win the day
Beast(Prince Adam) : I let her go
Cogsworth : You what
Lumière : Master how could you do that
Beast(Prince Adam) : I had to
Cogsworth : But why
Mrs. Potts : Because he loves her
Lumière : Then why are we not human
Cogsworth : Because she doesn't love him And now it's too late
Plumette : But she might still come back
Beast(Prince Adam) : No
Beast(Prince Adam) : I set her free
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'm sorry I couldn't do the same for all of you
Beast(Prince Adam) : Now go
Beast(Prince Adam) : Our time is almost past
Lumière : Come my love
Beast(Prince Adam) : I was the one who had it all
Beast(Prince Adam) : I was the master of my fate
Beast(Prince Adam) : I never needed anybody in my life
Beast(Prince Adam) : I learned the truth too late
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'll never shake away the pain
Beast(Prince Adam) : I close my eyes but she's still there
Beast(Prince Adam) : I let her steal into my melancholy heart
Beast(Prince Adam) : It's more than I can bear
Beast(Prince Adam) : Now I know she'll never leave me
Beast(Prince Adam) : Even as she runs away
Beast(Prince Adam) : She will still torment me Calm me hurt me
Beast(Prince Adam) : Move me come what may
Beast(Prince Adam) : Wasting in my lonely tower
Beast(Prince Adam) : Waiting by an open door
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'll fool myself she'll walk right in
Beast(Prince Adam) : And be with me for evermore
Beast(Prince Adam) : I rage against the trials of love
Beast(Prince Adam) : I curse the fading of the light
Beast(Prince Adam) : Though she's already flown So far beyond my reach
Beast(Prince Adam) : She's never out of sight
Beast(Prince Adam) : Now I know she'll never leave me
Beast(Prince Adam) : Even as she fades from view
Beast(Prince Adam) : She will still inspire me
Beast(Prince Adam) : Be a part of everything I do
Beast(Prince Adam) : Wasting in my lonely tower
Beast(Prince Adam) : Waiting by an open door
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'll fool myself she'll walk right in
Beast(Prince Adam) : And as the long long nights begin
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'll think of all that might have been
Beast(Prince Adam) : Waiting here
Beast(Prince Adam) : for evermore
Tom : This man is weak
Tom : Please
Tom : He needs a hospital
Tom : not an asylum
Gaston : Have you ever seen the inside of a mad house Maurice
Gaston : You wouldn't last a week
Gaston : Just give me your daughter's hand and I'll set you free
Maurice : Never
Gaston : Take him away
Belle : Stop
Belle : Papa
Maurice : Oh Belle I thought I'd lost you
Belle : Let him out He's hurt
Guard : We can't do that miss But we'll take very good care of him
Belle : My father's not crazy
Belle : Gaston tell him
Gaston : You know how loyal I am to your family but your father's been making some unbelievable claims
Man1 : It's true Belle
Man1 : He's been raving about a beast in a castle
Belle : I've just come from the castle and there is a beast
Gaston : You'd say anything to set him free Your word is hardly proof
Belle : You want proof
Belle : Show me the Beast
Belle : There's your proof
Gaston : This is sorcery
Gaston : Look at this beast
Gaston : Look at his fangs
Gaston : His claws
Belle : No Don't be afraid
Belle : He's gentle and kind
Gaston : The monster has her under his spell
Gaston : If I didn't know better I'd say she even cared for him
Belle : He's not a monster Gaston
Belle : You are
Belle : The Beast wouldn't hurt anyone
Gaston : I've heard of the effects of dark magic but I've never before seen it with my own eyes
Gaston : This is a threat to our very existence
Gaston : We can't have her running off to warn the beast
Gaston : Lock her up too
Belle : No
Tom : TOMCome here
Tom : Shut up
Belle : You won't get away with this Gaston
Maurice : Oh Belle
LeFou : Gaston with all due respect
Gaston : Do you want to be next
Gaston : Fetch my horse
Gaston : Stand guard
Gaston : Don't let them escape
Gaston : This creature will curse us all if we don't stop him
Gaston : Well I say we kill the beast
All : Kill the beast
Tom : We're not safe until he's dead
Man2 : He'll come stalking us at night
Man1 : Set to sacrifice our children To his monstrous appetite
Woman1 : He'll wreak havoc on our village If we let him wander free
Gaston : So it's time to take some action boys
Gaston : It's time to follow me
Gaston : Through the mist through the wood Through the darkness and the shadows
Gaston : It's a nightmare But it's one exciting ride
Gaston : Say a prayer then we're there At the drawbridge of a castle
Gaston : And there's something truly terrible inside
Gaston : It's a beast He's got fangs razor sharp ones
Gaston : Massive paws killer claws for the feast
Gaston : Hear him roar see him foam
Gaston : But we're not coming home Til he's dead
Gaston : Good and dead
Gaston : Kill the beast
All : Light your torch mount your horse
Gaston : Screw your courage to the sticking place
All : We're counting on Gaston to lead the way
Gaston : Call it war call it threat You can bet they all will follow
Gaston : For in times like this They'll do just as I say
LeFou : There's a beast running wild There's no question
LeFou : But I fear the wrong monster's released
All : Sally forth tally ho Grab your sword grab your bow
All : Praise the Lord and here we go
Gaston : Show me the castle
Lumière : At least he has finally learned to love
Cogsworth : A lot of good that does us if she doesn't love him in return
Plumette : No This is the first time I've had any real hope she would
Chip : Did you hear that Mama
Chip : Is it her Is she coming back
Lumière : Could it be
Plumette : I told you
Lumière : Sacré bleu
Lumière : Invaders
Mrs. Potts : Ruffians
Cogsworth : Well there you go
Cogsworth : So much for true love
Lumière : Man the barricades
Lumière : and hold fast
Maestro Cadenza : Move aside
Maestro Cadenza;Lumière;Cogsworth;Mrs. Potts;Plumette : Hearts ablaze banners high We go marching into battle Unafraid although the danger's just increased
All : Raise the flag sing the song Here we come we're fifty strong And fifty Frenchmen can't be wrong
All : Let's kill the beast
Cogsworth : We need help
Belle : I have to warn the Beast
Maurice : Warn him
Maurice : How did you get away from him
Belle : He let me go Papa
Belle : He sent me back to you
Maurice : I don't understand
Maurice : Where did you
Belle : He took me there
Belle : I know what happened to Maman
Maurice : Then you know why I had to leave her there
Maurice : I had to protect you I've always tried to protect my little girl
Maurice : Probably too much
Belle : I understand
Belle : Will you help me now
Maurice : It's dangerous
Belle : Yes
Belle : Yes it is
Maurice : I could try to pick the lock
Maurice : After all
Maurice : it's only gears and springs
Maurice : But I would need
Maurice : something long and sharp
Maurice : Like that
Maurice : Perfect
Cogsworth : Oh excuse me Master
Cogsworth : I'm so sorry to disturb you
Beast(Prince Adam) : She's not coming back
Cogsworth : No
Cogsworth : They're breaking down the doors
Beast(Prince Adam) : Doesn't matter now
Beast(Prince Adam) : Just let them come
All : Kill the beast Kill the beast
Mrs. Potts : This isn't working
Lumière : I know what to do
All : Kill the beast Kill the beast
All : Kill the beast
LeFou : Are you not the least bit concerned that this castle might be haunted
Gaston : Don't lose your nerve LeFou
LeFou : Where are we
Man1 : This place seems familiar
Man1 : Like I've been here before
LeFou : Oh hello there
LeFou : You must be the talking tea cup
LeFou : And you must be his grandmother
Mrs. Potts : Grandmother Attack
Lumière : Oh hello
LeFou : Gaston
LeFou : Help
Gaston : Sorry old friend
Gaston : It's hero time
Maestro Cadenza : Ooh ouch
Maurice : Hello
Maurice : Oh uh I believe this is yours
Maurice : She's very headstrong
Maurice : Do you have children
Plumette : No one to protect you now huh
Chip : One two three four five six seven eight
Cogsworth : Good show Chip my boy
Cogsworth : Excellent
Cogsworth : The infantry's arrived
Cogsworth : Now go and teach them a lesson Go
Cogsworth : Yes those are called books you third rate musketeers
Cogsworth : Oh I'm off
Man1 : Just a clock
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Come here
Madame de la Grande Bouche : little boys
Madame de la Grande Bouche : I spin you this way I put it on Yes pretty little boys Yes
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Beautiful
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Go be free Be free Be free
Mrs. Potts : How do you like your tea
Mrs. Potts : Piping hot
Mrs. Potts : Or boiling
Mrs. Potts : Oh
Plumette : Mr Potts
Chip : Mama
Mrs. Potts : Thank you
Mrs. Potts : Take that
Mrs. Potts : Nicely handled
LeFou : Well I used to be on Gaston's side but we are so in a bad place right now
Mrs. Potts : You're too good for him anyway
LeFou : Yeah
Mrs. Potts : Should we get back to it then
Maestro Cadenza : Such sweet music
Woman1 : Stand back Silence that harpsichord
Maestro Cadenza : What Uhoh
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Maestro
Maestro Cadenza : Darling At last
Madame de la Grande Bouche : I'm coming my love
Madame de la Grande Bouche : This is it
Madame de la Grande Bouche : The fat lady is singing
Maestro Cadenza : Bravissima
Lumière : Watch your toes
Lumière : That's it Go Go
Lumière : Bon voyage
Lumière : Safe trip home
Cogsworth : And stay out
Gaston : Hello beast
Gaston : I'm Gaston
Gaston : Belle sent me
Gaston : Are you in love with her
Gaston : Did you honestly think she'd want you
Gaston : Belle
Belle : Where is he
Gaston : When we return to the village you will marry me
Gaston : And that beast's head will hang on our wall
Belle : Never
Gaston : I'm coming for you beast
Belle : No
Beast(Prince Adam) : Belle
Beast(Prince Adam) : You came back
Belle : I tried to stop them
Beast(Prince Adam) : Stay there
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'm coming
Belle : Gaston
Belle : No
Gaston : Don't let me go
Gaston : Please
Gaston : I'll do anything
Gaston : Don't hurt me beast
Beast(Prince Adam) : I am not a beast
Beast(Prince Adam) : Go
Beast(Prince Adam) : Get out
Belle : Don't
Belle : It's too far
Belle : Please
Belle : Come on
Beast(Prince Adam) : You came back
Belle : Of course I came back
Belle : I'll never leave you again
Beast(Prince Adam) : I'm afraid it's my turn to leave
Belle : We're together now
Belle : It's gonna be fine
Beast(Prince Adam) : At least I got to see you
Beast(Prince Adam) : One last time
Belle : No Please no
Belle : Come back
Lumière : We did it Plumette Victory is ours
Plumette : Oh...
Lumière : Plumette
Lumière : Oh my darling Plumette
Lumière : Oh no
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Maestro you were so brave
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Goodbye my love
Maestro Cadenza : Amore
Maestro Cadenza : No Don't leave me
Mrs. Potts : Chip
Mrs. Potts : Have you seen Chip He ran off
Mrs. Potts : Where is my little boy
Chip : Mama
Cogsworth : Oh no
Chip : Mom
Cogsworth : Lumière I can't speak
Lumière : It's all right Cogsworth
Cogsworth : I can't
Cogsworth : Lumière my friend
Cogsworth : It was an honor to serve with you
Lumière : The honor was mine
Belle : Come back
Belle : Please don't leave me
Belle : I love you
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Oh Maestro
Maestro Cadenza : Madame
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Maestro
Cogsworth : Ooh
Cogsworth : Lumière
Lumière : Ah
Lumière : Cogsworth we beat the clock
Cogsworth : Mon ami
Lumière : Plumette
Lumière : Oh Mon amour
Lumière : Oh
Lumière : Oh Oh
Mrs. Potts : Chip Look at you
Mrs. Potts : You're a little boy again
Mrs. Potts : What did I tell you darling You smell so good
Maestro Cadenza : Froufrou finalmente
Man1 : Darling
Mrs. Potts : Oh Mr Potts
Man1 : Beatrice I remember
Man1 : I do
Man2 : Henry
Cogsworth : Oh Oh dear
Woman1 : Oh
Woman1 : I've been so lonely
Cogsworth : Turn back into a clock
Plumette : Lumière look
Lumière : Oh my Prince
Beast(Prince Adam) : Hello old friend
Lumière : Oh It's so good to see you
Plumette : You saved our lives mademoiselle
Chip : Belle It's me
Chip : It's Chip
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Tale as old as time
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Tune as old as song
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Bittersweet and strange Finding you can change
Madame de la Grande Bouche : Learning you were wrong
Mrs. Potts : Winter turns to spring
Mrs. Potts : Famine turns to feast
Mrs. Potts : Nature points the way
Mrs. Potts : Nothing left to say
Mrs. Potts : Beauty and the Beast
Beast(Prince Adam) : What What is it
Belle : How would you feel about growing a beard
Madame de la Grande Bouche;All : Certain as the sun
Madame de la Grande Bouche;All : Rising in the east
Madame de la Grande Bouche;All : Tale as old as time
Madame de la Grande Bouche;All : Song as old as rhyme
Madame de la Grande Bouche;All : Beauty and the Beast
Madame de la Grande Bouche;All : Tale as old as time
Madame de la Grande Bouche;All : Song as old as rhyme
Madame de la Grande Bouche;All : Beauty and the Beast
How does a moment last forever
How can a story never die
It is love we must hold on to
Never easy but we try
Sometimes our happiness is captured
Somehow a time and place stand still
Love lives on inside our hearts
And always will
Minutes turn to hours
Days to years then gone
But when all else has been forgotten
Still our song lives on
Maybe some moments weren't so perfect
Maybe some memories not so sweet
But we have to know some bad times
Or our lives are incomplete
Then when shadows overtake us
Just when we feel all hope is gone
We'll hear our song and know once more
Our love lives on
Oh oh
How does a moment last forever
How does our happiness endure
Through the darkest of our troubles
Love is beauty love is pure
Love pays no mind to desolation
It flows like a river through the soul
Protects proceeds and perseveres
And makes us whole
Minutes turn to hours
Days to years then gone
But when all else has been forgotten
Still our song lives on
How does a moment last forever
When our song lives on
Ah
Tale as old as time
True as it can be
Barely even friends
Then somebody bends unexpectedly
Just a little change
Small to say the least
Both a little scared
Neither one prepared
Beauty and the Beast
Ever just the same
Ever a surprise
Ever as before
And ever just as sure
As the sun will rise
Oh
Hey
Ah
Ooh
Uhhuh
Ever just the same
And ever a surprise
Ever as before
And ever just as sure
As the sun will rise
Oh oh oh
Tale as old as time
Tune as old as song
Oh
Bittersweet and strange
Finding you can change
Learning you were wrong
Certain as the sun
Rising in the east
Tale as old as time
Song as old as rhyme
Beauty and the Beast
Tale as old as time
Song as old as rhyme
Beauty and the Beast
I was the one who had it all
I was the master of my fate
I never needed anybody in my life
I learned the truth too late
I'll never shake away the pain
I close my eyes but she's still there
I let her steal into my melancholy heart
It's more than I can bear
Now I know she'll never leave me
Even as she runs away
She will still torment me Calm me hurt me
Move me come what may
Wasting in my lonely tower
Waiting by an open door
I'll fool myself she'll walk right in
And be with me for evermore
I rage against the trials of love
I curse the fading of the light
Though she's already flown So far beyond my reach
She's never out of sight
Now I know she'll never leave me
Even as she fades from view
She will still inspire me
Be a part of everything I do
Wasting in my lonely tower
Waiting by an open door
I'll fool myself she'll walk right in
And as the long long nights begin
I'll think of all that might have been
Waiting here for evermore