Munkustrap : Are you blind when you're born
Demeter : Can you see in the dark
Skimbleshanks : Can you look at a king
Asparagus : Would you sit on his throne
Rum Tum Tugger : Can you say of your bite That it's worse than your bark
Munkustrap;Alonzo : Are you cock of the walk
Chorus Cat : When you're walking alone
All Cats : Because Jellicles are And Jellicles do
All Cats : Jellicles do and Jellicles would
All Cats : Jellicles would and Jellicles can
All Cats : Jellicles can and Jellicles do
Jellylorum : When you fall on your head Do you land on your feet
Coricopat : Are you tense when you sense There's a storm in the air
Jemima : Can you find your way blind When you're lost in the street
Old Deuteronomy : Do you know how to go To the Heaviside Layer
All Cats : Because Jellicles can And Jellicles do
All Cats : Jellicles do and Jellicles can
All Cats : Jellicles can and Jellicles do
Tantomile : Can you ride on a broomstick To places far distant
Jennyanydots;Victoria : Familiar with candle
Electra : With book and with bell
Bombalurina : Were you Whittington's friend
Mistoffelees : The Pied Piper's assistant
Tumblebrutus : Have you been an alumnus Of heaven and hell
Mungojerrie : Are you mean like a minx
Rumpleteazer : Are you lean like a lynx
Etcetera : Are you keen to be seen When you're smelling a rat
Cassandra : Were you there when the pharaohs Commissioned the Sphinx
All Cats : If you were and you are You're a Jellicle Cat
All Cats : Jellicle Songs for Jellicle Cats
All Cats : Jellicle Songs for Jellicle Cats Jellicle Songs for Jellicle Cats
All Cats : We can dive through the air
All Cats : Like a flying trapeze
All Cats : We can turn double somersaults Bounce on a tyre
All Cats : We can run up a wall We can swing through the trees
All Cats : We can balance on bars We can walk on a wire
All Cats : Jellicles can and Jellicles do
All Cats : Jellicle Songs for Jellicle Cats
Queens : Can you sing at the same time In more than one key
Queens : Duets by Rossini
Toms : And waltzes by Strauss
Toms : And can you as cats do Begin with a C
All Cats : That always triumphantly Brings down the house
All Cats : Jellicle Cats Are queens of the night
All Cats : Singing at astronomical heights
All Cats : Handling pieces from The Messiah
All Cats : Hallelujah angelical choir
All Cats : Jellicle Cats Are queens of the night
All Cats : Singing at astronomical heights
All Cats : Handling pieces from The Messiah
All Cats : Hallelujah angelical choir
All Cats : The mystical divinity
All Cats : Of unashamed felinity
All Cats : Round the cathedral
All Cats : Rang vivat
All Cats : Life to
All Cats : The everlasting cat
All Cats : Feline fearless
All Cats : Faithful and true
All Cats : To others who do what
All Cats : Jellicles do and Jellicles can
All Cats : Jellicles can and Jellicles do
All Cats : Jellicle Cats sing Jellicle Chants
All Cats : Jellicles old and Jellicles new
All Cats : Jellicle Song and Jellicle Dance
All Cats : Jellicle Songs for Jellicle Cats
All Cats : Practical cats dramatical cats
All Cats : Pragmatical cats fanatical cats
All Cats : Oratorical cats DelphicOracle cats
All Cats : Sceptical cats dyspeptical cats
All Cats : Romantical cats pedantical cats
All Cats : Critical and parasitical cats
All Cats : Allegorical cats metaphorical cats
All Cats : Statistical cats and mystical cats
All Cats : Political cats hypocritical cats
All Cats : Clerical cats hysterical cats
All Cats : Cynical cats rabbinical cats
All Cats : Jellicle Songs for Jellicle Cats
All Cats : Jellicle Songs for Jellicle Cats Jellicle Songs for Jellicle Cats
Asparagus : There's a man over there With a look of surprise
Asparagus : As much as to say Well now how about that
Munkustrap : Do I actually see With my own very eyes
Munkustrap : A man who's not heard Of a Jellicle Cat
Munkustrap : What's a Jellicle Cat
All Cats : What's a Jellicle Cat
All Cats : The naming of cats Is a difficult matter
All Cats : It isn't just one Of your holiday games
All Cats : You may think at first I'm as mad as a hatter
All Cats : When I tell you a cat Must have three different names
All Cats : First of all there's the name That the family use daily
All Cats : Such as Peter Augustus Alonzo or James
All Cats : Such as Victor or Jonathan George or Bill Bailey
All Cats : All of them Sensible everyday names
All Cats : There are fancier names If you think they sound sweeter
All Cats : Some for the gentlemen Some for the dames
All Cats : Such as Plato Admetus Electra Demeter
All Cats : But all of them Sensible everyday names
All Cats : But I tell you A cat needs a name that's particular
All Cats : A name that's peculiar And more dignified
All Cats : Else how can he keep up His tail perpendicular
All Cats : Or spread out his whiskers Or cherish his pride
All Cats : Of names of this kind I can give you a quorum
All Cats : Such as Munkustrap Quaxo Or Coricopat
All Cats : Such as Bombalurina Or else Jellylorum
All Cats : Names that never belong To more than one cat
All Cats : But above and beyond There's still one name left over
All Cats : And that is the name That you never will guess
All Cats : The name that no human research Can discover
All Cats : But the cat himself knows And will never confess
All Cats : When you notice a cat In profound meditation
All Cats : The reason I tell you Is always the same
All Cats : His mind is engaged In a rapt contemplation
All Cats : Of the thought of the thought
All Cats : Of the thought of his name
All Cats : His ineffable
All Cats : Effable
All Cats : Effanineffable
All Cats : Deep and inscrutable
All Cats : Singular
All Cats : Name Name Name Name
Mr. Mistoffelees : Jellicle Cats come out tonight
Mr. Mistoffelees : Jellicle Cats come one come all
Mr. Mistoffelees : The Jellicle Moon is shining bright
Mr. Mistoffelees : Jellicles come to the Jellicle Ball
Mr. Mistoffelees : Jellicle Cats come out tonight
Munkustrap : Jellicle Cats meet once a year
Munkustrap : At the Jellicle Ball Where we all rejoice
Munkustrap : And the Jellicle Leader Will soon appear
Munkustrap : And make what is known As the Jellicle Choice
Munkustrap : When Old Deuteronomy Just before dawn
Munkustrap : Through a silence you feel You could cut with a knife
Munkustrap : Announces the cat Who can now be reborn
Munkustrap : And come back to a different Jellicle Life
Munkustrap : For waiting up there Is the Heaviside Layer
Munkustrap : Full of wonders One Jellicle only will see
Munkustrap : And Jellicles ask Because Jellicles dare
Munkustrap : Who will it be
All Cats : Who will it be
Munkustrap : I have a Gumbie Cat in mind
Munkustrap : Her name is Jennyanydots
Munkustrap : Her coat is of the tabby kind
Munkustrap : With tiger stripes And leopard spots
Munkustrap : All day she sits beneath the stair
Munkustrap : Or on the steps or on the mat
Munkustrap : She sits and sits and sits and sits
Munkustrap : And that's what makes a Gumbie Cat
Munkustrap : That's what makes a Gumbie Cat
Demeter;Bombalurina;Jellylorum : But when the day's hustle And bustle is done
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : Then the Gumbie Cat's work Is but hardly begun
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : And when all the family's In bed and asleep
Jellylorum;Demeter;Bombalurina : She tucks up her skirts To the basement to creep
Jellylorum;Bombalurina;Demeter : She is deeply concerned With the ways of the mice
Jennyanydots : Their behaviour's not good And their manners not nice
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : So when she has got them Lined up on the matting
Jellylorum;Demeter;Bombalurina : She teaches them
Jennyanydots : Music crocheting and tatting
Munkustrap : I have a Gumbie Cat in mind
Munkustrap : Her name is Jennyanydots
Munkustrap : The curtain cord she likes to wind
Munkustrap : And tie it into sailor knots
She sits upon the windowsill
Munkustrap : Or anything that's smooth and flat
Munkustrap : She sits and sits and sits and sits
Munkustrap : And that's what makes a Gumbie Cat
Munkustrap : That's what makes a Gumbie Cat
Demeter;Bombalurina;Jellylorum : But when the day's hustle And bustle is done
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : Then the Gumbie Cat's work Is but hardly begun
Demeter;Bombalurina;Jellylorum;Jennyanydots : She thinks that the cockroaches Just need employment
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : To prevent them from
Jennyanydots : Idle and wanton destroyment
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : So she's formed from that lot Of disorderly louts
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : A troop of welldisciplined Helpful Boy Scouts
Jennyanydots : With a purpose in life And a good deed to do
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : And she's even created
Bombalurina;Demeter;Jellylorum : A beetles tattoo
Jennyanydots : Squad salute
All Cats : For she's a jolly good fellow
Jennyanydots : Thank you my dears
All Cats : The Rum Tum Tugger is a curious cat
Rum Tum Tugger : If you offer me pheasant I'd rather have grouse
Rum Tum Tugger : If you put me in a house I would much prefer a flat
Rum Tum Tugger : If you put me in a flat Then I'd rather have a house
Rum Tum Tugger : If you set me on a mouse Then I only want a rat
Rum Tum Tugger : If you set me on a rat Then I'd rather chase a mouse
All Cats : The Rum Tum Tugger is a curious cat
Rum Tum Tugger : And there isn't any call For me to shout it
All Cats : For he will do as he do do
Rum Tum Tugger : And there's no doing Anything about it
Mr. Mistoffelees : The Rum Tum Tugger Is a terrible bore
Rum Tum Tugger : When you let me in Then I want to go out
Rum Tum Tugger : I'm always on the wrong side Of every door
Rum Tum Tugger : And as soon as I get home Then I'd like to get about
Rum Tum Tugger : I like to lie in a bureau drawer
Rum Tum Tugger : But I make such a fuss If I can't get out
All Cats : The Rum Tum Tugger is a curious cat
Rum Tum Tugger : And there isn't any use For you to doubt it
All Cats : For he will do as he do do
Rum Tum Tugger : And there's no doing Anything about it
Bombalurina : The Rum Tum Tugger Is a curious beast
Rum Tum Tugger : My disobliging ways Are a matter of habit
Rum Tum Tugger : Now if you offer me fish Then I always want a feast
Rum Tum Tugger : And if there isn't any fish Then I won't eat rabbit
Rum Tum Tugger : If you offer me cream Then I sniff and sneer
Rum Tum Tugger : For I only like What I find for myself
Rum Tum Tugger : No
Rum Tum Tugger : So you catch me in it right up to my ears And you put it away on the larder shelf
All Cats : The Rum Tum Tugger Is artful and knowing
All Cats;Rum Tum Tugger : The Rum Tum Tugger Doesn't care for a cuddle
Rum Tum Tugger : So I'll leap up on your lap In the middle of your sewing Cause there's nothing I enjoy like a horrible muddle
All Cats : The Rum Tum Tugger is a curious cat
All Cats : The Rum Tum Tugger Doesn't care for a cuddle
Rum Tum Tugger : And there isn't any need For me to spout it
All Cats : For he will do as he do do
Rum Tum Tugger : And there's no
Rum Tum Tugger : Doing anything
Rum Tum Tugger : About
Rum Tum Tugger : About it
Grizabella : Remark the cat
Grizabella : Who hesitates towards you
Grizabella : In the light of the door
Grizabella : Which opens on her
Grizabella : Like a grin
Grizabella : You see the border
Grizabella : Of her coat is torn
Grizabella : And stained with sand
Grizabella : And you see the corner of her eye
Grizabella : Twist like a crooked pin
Demeter : She haunted many a low resort
Demeter : Near the grimy road Of Tottenham Court
Demeter : She flitted about the no man's land
Demeter : From The Rising Sun To The Friend at Hand
Demeter : And the postman sighed As he scratched his head
Demeter : You'd really have thought She'd ought to be dead
Demeter : And who would ever suppose
Demeter : That that
Demeter : Was Grizabella
Demeter : The Glamour Cat
Bombalurina : Grizabella the Glamour Cat
Bombalurina;Demeter : Grizabella the Glamour Cat
All Cats : Who would have ever supposed
All Cats : That that
All Cats : Was Grizabella
All Cats : The Glamour Cat
Jennyanydots : Bustopher Jones Is not skin and bones
Bombalurina : In fact he's remarkably fat
Jellylorum;Jennyanydots : He doesn't haunt pubs He has eight or nine clubs
Jennyanydots;Bombalurina;Jellylorum : For he's the St James's Street Cat
Jennyanydots : He's the cat we all greet As he walks down the street
Jennyanydots : In his coat of fastidious black
Bombalurina : No commonplace mousers Have such wellcut trousers
Jellylorum : Or such an impeccable back
Jennyanydots : In the whole of St James's The smartest of names is
Jennyanydots : The name of this Brummell of cats
Jennyanydots;Bombalurina;Jellylorum : And we're all of us proud To be nodded or bowed to
Jennyanydots;Bombalurina;Jellylorum : By Bustopher Jones in white spats
Toms : In the whole of St James's The smartest of names
Toms : is The name of this Brummell of cats
Toms : And we're all of us proud To be nodded or bowed to
Toms : By Bustopher Jones In white spats
Bustopher Jones : My visits are occasional To the Senior Educational
Bustopher Jones : And it is against the rules
Bustopher Jones : For any one cat To belong both to that
Bustopher Jones : And the Joint Superior Schools
Bustopher Jones : For a similar reason When game is in season
Bustopher Jones : I'm found not at Fox's but Blimp's
Bustopher Jones : I am frequently seen At the gay Stage and Screen
Bustopher Jones : Which is famous For winkles and shrimps
Bustopher Jones : In the season of venison I give my ben'son
Bustopher Jones : To the Pothunter's succulent bones
Bustopher Jones : And just before noon's Not a moment too soon
Bustopher Jones : To drop in for a drink
Bustopher Jones : At the Drones
Bustopher Jones : When I'm seen in a hurry There's probably curry
Bustopher Jones : At the Siamese or at the Glutton
Bustopher Jones : If I look full of gloom Then I've lunched at the Tomb
Bustopher Jones : On cabbage rice pudding
Bustopher Jones : And mutton
All Cats : In the whole of St James's The smartest of names is
All Cats : The name of this Brummell of cats
All Cats : And we're all of us proud To be nodded or bowed to
All Cats : By Bustopher Jones in white
All Cats : Bustopher Jones in white
All Cats : Bustopher Jones in white spats
Jennyanydots : So much in this way Passes Bustopher's day
Jennyanydots : At one club or another he's found
Jennyanydots : It can be no surprise That under our eyes
Jennyanydots : He has grown unmistakably round
Jennyanydots : He's a 25pounder
Bustopher Jones : Or I am a bounder
Jennyanydots : And he's putting on weight Every day
Bustopher Jones : But I'm so wellpreserved Because I've observed
Bustopher Jones : All me life a routine and I'd say
Bustopher Jones : I am still in me prime I shall last out me time
Jennyanydots : That's the word From this stoutest of cats
All Cats : It must and it shall Be spring in Pall Mall
All Cats : While Bustopher Jones wears white
All Cats : Bustopher Jones wears white
All Cats : Bustopher Jones Wears white spats
Bustopher Jones : Toodlepip
Demeter : Macavity
Mungojerrie : Mungojerrie
Rumpleteazer : And Rumpleteazer
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : We're a notorious couple of cats
Rumpleteazer : As knockabout clowns Quickchange comedians
Rumpleteazer : Tightrope walkers and acrobats
Mungojerrie : We have an extensive reputation
Mungojerrie : We make our home in Victoria Grove
Mungojerrie : This is merely our centre of operation
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : For we are incurably given to rove
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : When the family assembles For Sunday dinner
Rumpleteazer : Their minds made up That they won't get thinner
Mungojerrie : On Argentine joint
Rumpleteazer : Potatoes and greens
Rumpleteazer : And the cook would appear From behind the scenes
Mungojerrie : And say in a voice That is broken with sorrow
Mungojerrie : I'm afraid you must wait And have dinner tomorrow
Mungojerrie : The joint has gone from the oven like that
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Then the family will say It's that horrible cat
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Was it Mungojerrie Or Rumpleteazer
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : And most of the time They leave it at that
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Mungojerrie and Rumpleteazer
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Have a wonderful way Of working together
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : And some of the time You would say it was luck
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : And some of the time You would say it was weather
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : We'd go through the house Like a hurricane
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : And no sober person Could take his oath
Mungojerrie : Was it Mungojerrie
Rumpleteazer : Or Rumpleteazer
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Or could you have sworn That it might have been both
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : And when you hear A dining room smash
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Or up from the pantry There comes a loud crash
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Or down from the library Came a loud ping
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : From a vase which was commonly
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Said to be Ming
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : Then the family will say Now which was which cat
Mungojerrie : It was Mungojerrie
Rumpleteazer : And Rumpleteazer
Mungojerrie;Rumpleteazer : And there's nothing at all To be done about that
All Cats : And there's nothing at all To be done about that
Mr. Mistoffelees : Old Deuteronomy
Tantomile;Coricopat : I believe it is Old Deuteronomy
All Cats : Well of all things
All Cats : Can it be really
All Cats : Yes No Ho Hi Oh my eye
All Cats : My mind may be wandering But I confess
All Cats : I believe it is Old Deuteronomy
Munkustrap : Old Deuteronomy's lived a long time
Munkustrap : He's a cat who has lived Many lives in succession
Munkustrap : He was famous in proverb And famous in rhyme
Munkustrap : A long while before Queen Victoria's accession
Rum Tum Tugger : Old Deuteronomy's buried nine wives
Rum Tum Tugger : And more I am tempted To say ninetynine
Rum Tum Tugger : And his numerous progeny Prospers and thrives
Rum Tum Tugger : And the village is proud of him In his decline
Munkustrap : At the sight of that placid And bland physiognomy
Munkustrap : When he sits in the sun
Munkustrap : On the vicarage wall
Munkustrap : The oldest inhabitant croaks
Rum Tum Tugger;Munkustrap : Well of all things
Rum Tum Tugger;Munkustrap : Can it be really
Rum Tum Tugger;Munkustrap : Yes No Ho Hi Oh my eye
Rum Tum Tugger;Munkustrap : My mind may be wandering But I confess
Rum Tum Tugger;Munkustrap : I believe it is Old Deuteronomy
All Cats : Well of all things
All Cats : Can it be really
All Cats : Yes No Ho Hi Oh my eye
All Cats : My mind may be wandering But I confess
All Cats : I believe it is Old Deuteronomy
All Cats : Well of all things Can it be really
All Cats : Yes No Ho Hi Oh my eye
All Cats : My mind may be wandering But I confess
All Cats : I believe it is Old Deuteronomy
All Cats : Well of all things
All Cats : Can it be really
All Cats : Yes No Ho Hi Oh my eye
Old Deuteronomy : My legs may be tottery I must go slow
Old Deuteronomy : And be careful
Old Deuteronomy : Of Old Deuteronomy
Munkustrap : Jellicle Cats meet once a year
Munkustrap : On the night we make The Jellicle Choice
Munkustrap : And now that the Jellicle Leader is here
Munkustrap : Jellicle Cats can all rejoice
Munkustrap : Of the awefull battle of the Pekes And the Pollicles
Munkustrap : Together with some account
Munkustrap : Of the participation Of the Pugs and the Poms
Munkustrap : And the intervention
Munkustrap : Of the Great
Munkustrap : Rumpus Cat
Munkustrap : The Pekes and the Pollicles Everyone knows
Munkustrap : Are proud and implacable Passionate foes
Munkustrap : It is always the same Wherever one goes
Munkustrap : And the Pugs and the Poms Are the most people say
Munkustrap : That they do not like fighting Yet once in a way
Munkustrap : They now and again Join into the fray and they
All Cats : Bark Bark Bark Bark Bark Bark Bark Bark
Munkustrap : Until you can hear them All over the park
Munkustrap : Now on the occasion Of which I shall speak
Munkustrap : Almost nothing had happened For nearly a week
Munkustrap : And that's a long time For a Pol or a Peke
Munkustrap : The big Police Dog Was away from his beat
Munkustrap : I don't know the reason But most people think
Munkustrap : He slipped into the Wellington Arms for a drink
Munkustrap : And no one at all Was about on the street
Munkustrap : When a Peke and a Pollicle Happened to meet
Munkustrap : They did not advance Or exactly retreat
Munkustrap : But they glared at each other And scraped their hind feet
Munkustrap : And started to
Peke : Bark
Pollicle : Bark
Munkustrap : Until you could hear them All over the park and they'd
Pekes : Bark
Pollicles;All Cats : Bark
Pollicles : Bark
Pekes : Bark
Munkustrap : Until you could hear them All over the park
Munkustrap : Now the Peke although people May say what they please
Munkustrap : Is no British dog But a heathen Chinese
Munkustrap : And so all the Pekes When they heard the uproar
Munkustrap : Some came to the window Some came to the door
Munkustrap : There were surely a dozen More likely a score
Munkustrap : And together they started To grumble and wheeze
Munkustrap : In their hufferysnuffery Heathen Chinese
Munkustrap : But a terrible din Is what Pollicles like
Munkustrap : For your Pollicle dog Is a dour Yorkshire tyke
All Cats : There are dogs out of every nation The Irish the Welsh and the Dane
All Cats : The Russian the Dutch and Dalmatian And even from China and Spain
All Cats : From the Poodle the Pom The Alsatian
All Cats : And the Mastiff Who walks on a chain
Munkustrap : And to those that are frisky And frolicle
Munkustrap : That my meaning be perfectly plain
All Cats : That my name is just Little Tom Pollicle And you better not do it again
Munkustrap : And his braw Scottish cousins Are snappers and biters
Munkustrap : And every dogjack of them Notable fighters
Munkustrap : And so they stepped out With their pipers in order
Munkustrap : Playin When the Blue Bonnets Come Over the Border
Munkustrap : Then the Pugs and the Poms Held no longer aloof
Munkustrap : But some from the balcony Some from the roof
Munkustrap : Joined into the din with a
All Cats : Bark
Munkustrap : Until you could hear them All over the park
All Cats : Hufferysnuffery hufferysnuffery
All Cats : Hufferysnuffery hufferysnuff
Munkustrap : Until you could hear them All over the park
Munkustrap : Now
Munkustrap : When these bold heroes Together assembled
Munkustrap : The traffic all stopped And the Underground trembled
Munkustrap : And some of the neighbours Were so much afraid
Munkustrap : That they started to ring up The fire brigade
Munkustrap : When suddenly up From a small basement flat
Munkustrap : Why who should stalk out
All Cats : But the Great Rumpus Cat
Munkustrap : His eyes were like fireballs
Munkustrap : Fearfully blazing
Munkustrap : He gave a great yawn
Munkustrap : And his jaws were amazing
Munkustrap : And when he looked out Through the bars of the area
Munkustrap : You never saw anything
Munkustrap : Fiercer
Munkustrap : Or hairier
Munkustrap : And what with the glare Of his eyes and his yawning
Munkustrap : The Pekes and the Pollicles Quickly took warning
Munkustrap : He looked to the sky And he gave a great leap
Munkustrap : And they every last one of them Scattered like sheep
Munkustrap : And when the Police Dog Returned to his beat
Munkustrap : There wasn't a single one Left on the street
All Cats : All hail and all bow to
All Cats : The Great Rumpus Cat
Old Deuteronomy : Jellicle Cats and dogs all must
Old Deuteronomy : Pollicle Dogs and cats all must
Old Deuteronomy : Like undertakers come to dust
Demeter : Macavity
Old Deuteronomy : Jellicle Cats come out tonight
Old Deuteronomy : Jellicle Cats come one come all
Old Deuteronomy;Victoria;Jemima;Munkustrap : The Jellicle Moon is shining bright
Old Deuteronomy;Munkustrap;Jemima;Victoria : Jellicles come to the Jellicle Ball
Alonzo : Jellicle Cats are black and white
Alonzo : Jellicle Cats are rather small
Alonzo : Jellicle Cats are merry And bright
Victoria;Jemima : And pleasant to hear When we caterwaul
Skimbleshanks : Jellicle Cats have cheerful faces
Tumblebrutus : Jellicle Cats Have bright black eyes
Mr. Mistoffelees : We like to practise Our airs and graces
All Cats : And wait for the Jellicle Moon to rise
Munkustrap;Plato;Admetus : Jellicle Cats develop slowly
Tumblebrutus : Jellicle Cats are not too big
Asparagus : Jellicle Cats are rolypoly
Mr. Mistoffelees;Skimbleshanks : We know how to dance A gavotte and a jig
Demeter : Until the Jellicle Moon appears
Bombalurina : We make our toilette And take our repose
Jennyanydots : Jellicles wash behind their ears
Jellylorum : Jellicles dry between their toes
Coricopat;Tantomile : Jellicle Cats are white and black
Rumpleteazer;Mungojerrie : Jellicle Cats are of moderate size
Tumblebrutus;Skimbleshanks;Pouncival : Jellicles jump like a jumping jack
Cassandra : Jellicle Cats have moonlit eyes
All Cats : We're quiet enough In the morning hours
All Cats : We're quiet enough In the afternoon
Munkustrap;Mr. Mistoffelees : Reserving our terpsichorean powers
All Cats : To dance by the light Of the Jellicle Moon
Alonzo;Victoria;Electra;Rumpleteazer : Jellicle Cats are black And white
Tumblebrutus;Skimbleshanks;Mr. Mistoffelees : Jellicle Cats As we said are small
Admetus;Munkustrap;Plato : If it happens to be a stormy night
Tumblebrutus;Skimbleshanks;Mr. Mistoffelees : We will practise a caper Or two in the hall
All Cats : If it happens the sun Is shining bright
Rum Tum Tugger : You would say we had Nothing to do at all
All Cats : We are resting and saving Ourselves to be right
All Cats : For the Jellicle Moon And the Jellicle Ball
All Cats : Jellicle Cats come out tonight
All Cats : Jellicle Cats come one come all
All Cats : The Jellicle Moon is shining bright
All Cats : Jellicles come to the Jellicle Ball
All Cats : Jellicle Cats come out tonight
All Cats : Jellicle Cats come one come all
All Cats : The Jellicle Moon is shining bright
All Cats : Jellicles come to the Jellicle Ball
Jellylorum : You see the border of her coat
Jellylorum : Is torn and stained with sand
Jemima : And you see
Jemima : The corner of her eye
Jemima : Twist like a crooked pin
Grizabella : Midnight
Jellylorum;Grizabella : Not a sound from the pavement
Grizabella : Has the moon lost her memory
Grizabella : She is smiling alone
Grizabella : In the lamplight
Grizabella : The withered leaves Collect at my feet
Grizabella : And the wind
Grizabella : Begins to moan
Grizabella : Every street lamp
Grizabella : Seems to beat
Grizabella : A fatalistic warning
Grizabella : Someone mutters
Grizabella : And the street lamp gutters
Grizabella : And soon it will be morning
Grizabella : Memory
Grizabella : All alone in the moonlight
Grizabella : I can smile at the old days
Grizabella : I was beautiful then
Grizabella : I remember the time I knew
Grizabella : What happiness was
Grizabella : Let the memory
Grizabella : Live again
Old Deuteronomy : The moments of happiness
Old Deuteronomy : We had the experience
Old Deuteronomy : But missed the meaning
Old Deuteronomy : And approach to the meaning
Old Deuteronomy : Restores the experience In a different form
Old Deuteronomy : Beyond any meaning
Old Deuteronomy : We can assign to happiness
Old Deuteronomy : The past experience
Old Deuteronomy : Revived in the meaning
Old Deuteronomy : Is not the experience
Old Deuteronomy : Of one life only
Old Deuteronomy : But of many generations
Old Deuteronomy : Not forgetting
Old Deuteronomy : Something that is
Old Deuteronomy : Probably quite ineffable
Jemima : Moonlight
Jemima : Turn your face to the moonlight
Jemima : Let your memory lead you
Jemima : Open up enter in
Jemima : If you find there
Jemima : The meaning of what happiness is
Jemima : Then a new life
Jemima : Will begin
Moonlight
All Cats : Turn your face to the moonlight
All Cats : Let your memory lead you
All Cats : Open up enter in
All Cats : If you find there
All Cats : The meaning of what happiness is
All Cats : Then a new life
All Cats : Will begin
Jellylorum : Gus is the cat At the theatre door
Jellylorum : His name as I ought to Have told you before
Jellylorum : Is really Asparagus
Jellylorum : But that's such a fuss to pronounce
Jellylorum : That we usually call him just Gus
Jellylorum : His coat's very shabby He's thin as a rake
Jellylorum : And he suffers from palsy That makes his paws shake
Jellylorum : Yet he was in his youth Quite the smartest of cats
Jellylorum : But no longer a terror To mice or to rats
Jellylorum : For he isn't the cat That he was in his prime
Jellylorum : Though his name was quite famous
Jellylorum : He says in his time
Jellylorum : And whenever he joins His friends at their club
Jellylorum : Which takes place at the back Of the neighbouring pub
Jellylorum : He loves to regale them If someone else pays
Jellylorum : With anecdotes drawn From his palmiest days
Jellylorum : For he once was a star Of the highest degree
Jellylorum : He has acted with Irving He has acted with Tree
Jellylorum : And he likes to relate His success on the halls
Jellylorum : Where the gallery once gave him
Jellylorum : Seven cat calls
Jellylorum : But his grandest creation
Jellylorum : As he loves to tell
Jellylorum : Was Firefrorefiddle
Jellylorum : The Fiend of the Fell
Gus : I have played in my time
Gus : Every possible part
Gus : And I used to know seventy Speeches by heart
Gus : I'd extemporise backchat
Gus : I knew how to gag
Gus : And I knew how to let the cat Out of the bag
Gus : I knew how to act With my back and my tail
Gus : With an hour of rehearsal I never could fail
Gus : I'd a voice that would soften The hardest of hearts
Gus : Whether I took the lead Or in character parts
Gus : I have sat by the bedside Of poor little Nell
Gus : When the curfew was rung Then I swung on the bell
Gus : In the pantomime season I never fell flat
Gus : And I once understudied Dick Whittington's Cat
Gus : But my grandest creation
Gus : As history will tell
Gus : Was Firefrorefiddle
Gus : The Fiend of the Fell
Jellylorum : Then if someone will give him A toothful of gin
Jellylorum : He will tell how he once played A part in East Lynne
Jellylorum : At a Shakespeare performance He once walked on pat
Jellylorum : When some actor suggested The need for a cat
Gus : And I say that these kittens They do not get trained
Gus : As we did in the days When Victoria reigned
Gus : They never get drilled In a regular troupe
Gus : And they think they are smart Just to jump through a hoop
Jellylorum : And he says as he scratches himself With his claws
Gus : Well the theatre is certainly Not what it was
Gus : These modern productions Are all very well
Gus : But there's nothing to equal From what I hear tell
Gus : That moment of mystery
Gus : When I made history
Gus : As Firefrorefiddle
Gus : The Fiend of the Fell
Gus : These modern productions
Gus : Are all very well
Gus : But there's nothing to equal
Gus : From what I hear tell
Gus : That moment of mystery
Gus : When I
All Cats : Skimbleshanks the Railway Cat
All Cats : The cat of the railway train
All Cats : There's a whisper down the line At 1139
All Cats : When the Night Mail's Ready to depart
All Cats : Saying Skimble where is Skimble Has he gone to hunt the thimble
All Cats : We must find him Or the train can't start
Skimbleshanks : All the guards and all the porters And the stationmaster's daughters
Skimbleshanks : Would be searching high and low
Skimbleshanks : Saying Skimble where is Skimble For unless he's very nimble
Skimbleshanks : Then the Night Mail just can't go
Skimbleshanks : At 1142 With the signal overdue
Skimbleshanks : And the passengers All frantic to a man
Skimbleshanks : That's when I would appear And I'd saunter to the rear
Skimbleshanks : I'd been busy in the luggage van
All Cats : Then he gave one flash Of his glassgreen eyes
All Cats : And the signal went all clear
Skimbleshanks : They'd be off at last For the northern part
Skimbleshanks : Of the Northern Hemisphere
All Cats : Skimbleshanks the Railway Cat
All Cats : The cat of the railway train
Skimbleshanks : You could say that by and large It was me who was in charge
Skimbleshanks : Of the Sleeping Car Express
Skimbleshanks : From the driver and the guards To the bagmen playing cards
Skimbleshanks : I'd supervise them all More or less
All Cats : Down the corridor he paces And examines all the faces Of the travellers In the First and the Third
All Cats : He establishes control By a regular patrol
All Cats : And he'd know at once If anything occurred
All Cats : He would watch you without winking And he saw what you were thinking
All Cats : And it's certain That he didn't approve
All Cats : Of hilarity and riot So that folk were very quiet
All Cats : When Skimble was about And on the move
All Cats : You could play no pranks With Skimbleshanks
All Cats : He's a cat that cannot be ignored
All Cats : So nothing went wrong On the Northern Mail
All Cats : When Skimbleshanks was aboard
Skimbleshanks : It was very pleasant When they found their little den
Skimbleshanks : With their name Written up on the door
Skimbleshanks : And the berth was very neat With a newly folded sheet
Skimbleshanks : And not a speck of dust On the floor
Skimbleshanks : There was every sort of light You could make it dark or bright
Skimbleshanks : And a button you could turn To make a breeze
Skimbleshanks : And a funny little basin You're supposed to wash your face in
Skimbleshanks : And a crank to shut The window should you sneeze
Skimbleshanks : Then the guard looked in politely And would ask you very brightly
Skimbleshanks : Do you like your morning tea
All Cats : Weak or strong
Skimbleshanks : But I was just behind him And was ready to remind him
Skimbleshanks : For Skimble won't let Anything go wrong
All Cats : When they crept into Their cosy berths
All Cats : And pulled down the counterpane
All Cats : They ought to reflect It was very nice
All Cats : To know that they wouldn't Be bothered by mice
All Cats : They would leave all that To the Railway Cat
All Cats : The cat of the railway train
All Cats : Skimbleshanks the Railway Cat
Skimbleshanks : In the watches of the night I was always fresh and bright
Skimbleshanks : Every now and then I'd have a cup of tea
Skimbleshanks : With perhaps a drop of Scotch When I was keeping on the watch
Skimbleshanks : Only stopping here and there To catch a flea
Skimbleshanks : They were fast asleep at Crewe And so they never knew
Skimbleshanks : That I was walking Up and down the station
Skimbleshanks : They were sleeping all the while I was busy at Carlisle
Skimbleshanks : Where I met the station master With elation
Skimbleshanks : They might see me at Dumfries If I summoned the police
Skimbleshanks : If there was anything They ought to know about
All Cats : When they got to Gallowgate There they did not have to wait
All Cats : For Skimbleshanks will help them To get out
All Cats : And he
All Cats : Gives you a wave Of his long brown tail
All Cats : Which says I'll see you again
All Cats : You will meet without fail On the Midnight Mail
All Cats : The cat of the railway train
All Cats : The cat of the railway
All Cats : Train
Demeter : Macavity
Demeter : Macavity's a mystery cat
Demeter : He's called the Hidden Paw
Demeter : For he's the master criminal
Demeter : Who can defy the law
Demeter : He's the bafflement Of Scotland Yard
Demeter : The Flying Squad's despair
Demeter : For when they reach The scene of crime
Demeter : Macavity's not there
Demeter : Macavity Macavity
Demeter : There's no one like Macavity
Demeter : He's broken every human law
Demeter : He breaks the law of gravity
Demeter : His powers of levitation
Demeter : Would make a fakir stare
Demeter : And when you reach the scene of crime
Demeter : Macavity's not there
Demeter : You may seek him in the basement
Demeter : You may look up in the air
Demeter : But I tell you once and once again Macavity's not there
Bombalurina : Macavity's a ginger cat
Bombalurina : He's very tall and thin
Bombalurina : You would know him if you saw him
Bombalurina : For his eyes are sunken in
Bombalurina : His brow is deeply Lined with thought
Bombalurina : His head is highly domed
Bombalurina : His coat is dusty from neglect
Bombalurina : His whiskers are uncombed
Bombalurina : He sways his head from side to side
Bombalurina : With movements like a snake
Bombalurina : And when you think he's half asleep
Bombalurina : He's always wide awake
Bombalurina : Macavity Macavity
Bombalurina : There's no one like Macavity
Bombalurina : For he's a fiend in feline shape
Bombalurina : A monster of depravity
Bombalurina : You may meet him in a bystreet
Bombalurina : You may see him in the square
Bombalurina : But when a crime's discovered
Bombalurina : Then Macavity's not there
Demeter : He's outwardly respectable
Bombalurina : I know he cheats at cards
Demeter : And his footprints are not found in
Demeter : Any files of Scotland Yard's
Bombalurina : And when the larder's looted
Demeter : Or the jewel case is rifled
Bombalurina : Or when the milk is missing
Demeter : Or another Peke's been stifled
Bombalurina : Or the greenhouse glass is broken
Demeter : And the trellis past repair
Bombalurina;Demeter : There's the wonder of the thing
Bombalurina;Demeter : Macavity's not there
Bombalurina;Demeter : Macavity Macavity
Bombalurina;Demeter : There's no one like Macavity
Bombalurina;Demeter : There never was a cat
Bombalurina;Demeter : Of such deceitfulness and suavity
Bombalurina;Demeter : He always has an alibi
Bombalurina;Demeter : And one or two to spare
Bombalurina;Demeter : Whatever time the deed took place Macavity wasn't there
Bombalurina;Demeter : And they say that all the cats
Bombalurina;Demeter : Whose wicked deeds are widely known
Demeter : I might mention Mungojerrie
Bombalurina : I might mention Griddlebone
Bombalurina;Demeter : Are nothing more than agents
Bombalurina;Demeter : For the cat who all the time
Bombalurina;Demeter : Just controls the operations
Bombalurina;Demeter : The Napoleon of Crime
Queens : Macavity Macavity
Queens : There's no one like Macavity
Queens : He's a fiend in feline shape
Queens : A monster of depravity
Queens : You may meet him in a bystreet
Queens : You may see him in the square
Queens : But when a crime's discovered
Queens : Then Macavity
Queens : Macavity
Queens : When a crime's discovered
Bombalurina;Demeter : Then Macavity's not there
All Cats : Macavity
All Cats : Macavity's not there
All Cats : We have to find
All Cats : Old Deuteronomy
Rum Tum Tugger : You ought to ask Magical Mr Mistoffelees
Rum Tum Tugger : The original Conjuring Cat there can be no doubt about that
Rum Tum Tugger : Please listen to me and don't scoff
Rum Tum Tugger : All his inventions are off his own bat
Rum Tum Tugger : There's no such cat in the metropolis He holds all the patent monopolies
Rum Tum Tugger : for performing surprising illusions
Rum Tum Tugger : and creating eccentric confusions
Rum Tum Tugger : The greatest magicians Have something to learn
Rum Tum Tugger : From Mr Mistoffelees Conjuring turn
Rum Tum Tugger : And we all say
Rum Tum Tugger : Oh Well I never Was there ever a cat so clever
Rum Tum Tugger : As Magical Mr Mistoffelees
Rum Tum Tugger : He is quiet he is small He is black
Rum Tum Tugger : From his ears To the tip of his tail
Rum Tum Tugger : He can creep Through the tiniest crack
Rum Tum Tugger : He can walk on the narrowest rail
Rum Tum Tugger : He can pick any card from the pack
Rum Tum Tugger : He's equally cunning with dice
Rum Tum Tugger : He's always deceiving you Into believing
Rum Tum Tugger : That he's only hunting for mice
Rum Tum Tugger : He can play any trick with a cork
Rum Tum Tugger : Or a spoon and a bit of fish paste
Rum Tum Tugger : If you look for a knife or a fork
Rum Tum Tugger : And you think That it's merely misplaced
Rum Tum Tugger : You have seen it one moment But then it is gone
Rum Tum Tugger : But you'll find it next week Laying out on the lawn
Rum Tum Tugger : And we all say
Rum Tum Tugger : Oh Well I never Was there ever a cat so clever
Rum Tum Tugger : As Magical Mr Mistoffelees
Mr. Mistoffelees : Presto
All Cats : Oh Well I never Was there ever a cat so clever
All Cats : As Magical Mr Mistoffelees
Rum Tum Tugger : His manner is vague and aloof
Rum Tum Tugger : And you would think There was nobody shyer
Rum Tum Tugger : But his voice can be Heard on the roof
Rum Tum Tugger : While he was curled up by the fire
Rum Tum Tugger : And he's sometimes Been heard by the fire
Rum Tum Tugger : While he was about on the roof
Rum Tum Tugger : At least we all heard That somebody purred
Rum Tum Tugger : Which is incontestable proof
Rum Tum Tugger : And of his singular magical powers
Rum Tum Tugger : I've known the family to call
Rum Tum Tugger : Him in from the garden for hours
Rum Tum Tugger : While he was asleep in the hall
Rum Tum Tugger : And not long ago This phenomenal cat
Rum Tum Tugger : Produced seven kittens
Rum Tum Tugger : Right out of a hat
Rum Tum Tugger : And we all say
All Cats : Oh Well I never Was there ever a cat so clever
All Cats : As Magical Mr Mistoffelees
Rum Tum Tugger : Magical
Rum Tum Tugger : And not long ago This phenomenal cat
Rum Tum Tugger : Produced seven kittens
Rum Tum Tugger : Right out of a hat
Rum Tum Tugger : And we all say
Rum Tum Tugger : Oh Well I never
Rum Tum Tugger : Was there ever a cat so clever
Rum Tum Tugger : As Magical Mr Mistoffelees
All Cats : Oh Well I never Was there ever a cat so clever
All Cats : As Magical Mr Mistoffelees
All Cats : Mystical
All Cats : Oh Well I never Was there ever a cat so clever
All Cats : As Magical Mr Mistoffelees Magical
All Cats : Mystical
All Cats : Oh Well I never Was there ever a cat so clever
All Cats : As Magical Mr Mistoffelees
Rum Tum Tugger : I give you the Magical
Rum Tum Tugger : The Marvellous
Rum Tum Tugger : Mr Mistoffelees
Jemima : Daylight
Jemima : See the dew on a sunflower
Jemima : And a rose that is fading
Jemima : Roses wither away
Jemima : Like the sunflower
Jemima : I yearn to turn my face to the dawn
Jemima : I am waiting
Jemima : For the day
Munkustrap : Now Old Deuteronomy just before dawn
Munkustrap : through a silence you feel you could cut with a knife
Munkustrap : announces the cat who can now be reborn
Munkustrap : and come back to a different Jellicle Life
Grizabella : Memory
Grizabella : Turn your face to the moonlight
Grizabella : Let your memory lead you
Grizabella : Open up enter in
Grizabella : If you find there
Grizabella : The meaning of what happiness is
Grizabella : Then a new life
Grizabella : Will begin
Grizabella : Memory
Grizabella : All alone in the moonlight
Grizabella : I can smile at the old days
Grizabella : I was beautiful then
Grizabella : I remember
Grizabella : A time I knew what happiness was
Grizabella : Let the memory
Grizabella : Live again
Grizabella : Burnt out ends of smoky days
Grizabella : The stale cold smell Of morning
Grizabella : The street lamp dies
Grizabella : Another night is over
Grizabella : Another day
Grizabella : Is dawning
Grizabella : Daylight
Grizabella : I must wait for the sunrise
Grizabella : I must think of the new life
Grizabella : And I mustn't give in
Grizabella : When the dawn comes
Grizabella : Tonight will be a memory too
Grizabella : And the new day
Grizabella : Will begin
Jemima : Sunlight through the trees In summer
Jemima : Endless masquerading
Grizabella;Jemima : Like a flower As the dawn is breaking
Grizabella : The memory
Grizabella : Is fading
Grizabella : Touch me
Grizabella : It's so easy to leave me
Grizabella : All alone with the memory
Grizabella : Of my days in the sun
Grizabella : If you touch me
Grizabella : You'll understand what happiness is
Grizabella : Look a new day
Grizabella : Has begun
All Cats : Up up up Past the Russell Hotel
All Cats : Up up up up To the Heaviside Layer
All Cats : Up up up Past the Jellicle Moon
All Cats : The mystical divinity
All Cats : Of unashamed felinity
All Cats : Round the cathedral
All Cats : Rang vivat
All Cats : Life to
All Cats : The everlasting
All Cats : Cat
Old Deuteronomy : You've heard of Several kinds of cat
Old Deuteronomy : And my opinion now is that
Old Deuteronomy : You should need no interpreter
Old Deuteronomy : To understand our character
Old Deuteronomy : You've learned enough To take the view
Old Deuteronomy : That cats are very much like you
Old Deuteronomy : You've seen us both At work and games
Old Deuteronomy : And learnt about our proper names
Old Deuteronomy : Our habits and our habitat
Old Deuteronomy : But how would you
Old Deuteronomy : Address a cat
Old Deuteronomy : So first
Old Deuteronomy : Your memory I'll jog
Old Deuteronomy : And say a cat
Old Deuteronomy : Is not a dog
All Cats : So first
All Cats : Your memory I'll jog
All Cats : And say a cat
All Cats : Is not a dog
Old Deuteronomy : With cats
Old Deuteronomy : Some say one rule is true
Old Deuteronomy : Don't speak till you
Old Deuteronomy : Are spoken to
Old Deuteronomy : Myself I do not hold with that
Old Deuteronomy : I say you should address a cat
Old Deuteronomy : But always keep in mind that he
Old Deuteronomy : Resents familiarity
Old Deuteronomy : You bow
Old Deuteronomy : And taking off your hat
Old Deuteronomy : Address him in
Old Deuteronomy : This form
Old Deuteronomy : Oh Cat
Old Deuteronomy : Before a cat will condescend
Old Deuteronomy : To treat you as a trusted friend
Old Deuteronomy : Some little token of esteem
Old Deuteronomy : Is needed like a dish of cream
Old Deuteronomy : And you might now and then supply
Old Deuteronomy : Some caviar or Strassburg Pie
Old Deuteronomy : Some potted grouse or salmon paste
Old Deuteronomy : He's sure to have His personal taste
Old Deuteronomy : And so in time you reach your aim
Old Deuteronomy : And call him
Old Deuteronomy : By his name
All Cats : A cat's entitled to expect
All Cats : These evidences of respect
All Cats : So this is this
All Cats : And that is that
All Cats : And there's how you address a cat
All Cats : A cat's entitled to expect
All Cats : These evidences of respect
All Cats : So this is this
All Cats : And that is that
All Cats : And there's how you address
All Cats : A Cat