Stage Manager : Five six seven eight
Stage Manager : Anybody seen the Kelly Sisters
Stage Manager : You You're up in five
Velma Kelly : Keep the change Charlie
Charlie : Thanks
Stage Manager : Velma where you been
Stage Manager : And where's Veronica
Velma Kelly : She's not herself tonight
Stage Manager : But they paid to see a sister act
Velma Kelly : Don't sweat it I can do it alone
Velma Kelly : Shit
Stage Manager : Come on Velma Move it move it Hurry up
Stage Manager : You're killing me here
Narrator : Ladies and gentlemen
Narrator : the Onyx Club is proud to present
Narrator : Chicago's hottest dancing duo
Narrator : Two jazz babes moving as one
Narrator : The Kelly Sisters
Velma Kelly : Come on babe Why don't we paint the town
Velma Kelly : And all that jazz
Velma Kelly : I'm gonna rouge my knees And roll my stockings down
Velma Kelly : Start the car I know a whoopee spot
Velma Kelly : Where the gin is cold But the piano's hot
Velma Kelly : It's just a noisy hall Where there's a nightly brawl
Velma Kelly : And all
Velma Kelly : That
Velma Kelly : Jazz
Velma Kelly : Skidoo
Velma Kelly : And all that jazz
Woman Ensemble : Hotcha
Woman Ensemble : Whoopee
Velma Kelly : And all that jazz
Velma Kelly : Slick your hair And wear your buckle shoes
Velma Kelly : I hear that Father Dip Is gonna blow the blues
Velma Kelly : And all that jazz
Velma Kelly : Hold on hon We're gonna bunny hug
Velma Kelly : I bought some aspirin Down at United Drug
Velma Kelly : In case you shake apart
Velma Kelly : And want a brandnew start
Velma Kelly : To do
That
Roxie Hart : Jazz
Fred Casely : Let's go babe
Roxie Hart : But I didn't even meet your friend
Roxie Hart : That manager guy
Fred Casely : Don't worry Roxie
Fred Casely : It's all taken care of
Roxie Hart : You told him about me
Fred Casely : Yeah kid it's all arranged
Velma Kelly : Find a flask We're playing fast and loose
Velma Kelly : And all that jazz
Velma Kelly : Right up here Is where I store the juice
Velma Kelly : Come on babe We're gonna brush the sky
Velma Kelly : I betcha Lucky Lindy Never flew so high
Velma Kelly : Cause in the stratosphere How could he lend an ear
Velma Kelly : To all
Velma Kelly : That
Velma Kelly : Jazz
Velma Kelly : Oh you're gonna see Your sheba shimmyshake
Velma Kelly : And all that jazz
Velma Kelly : Oh she's gonna shimmy Till her garters break
Velma Kelly : Show her where to park her girdle
Velma Kelly : Oh her mother's blood will curdle
Velma Kelly : If she'd hear her baby's queer
Velma Kelly : For all
Velma Kelly : That
Velma Kelly : Jazz
Roxie Hart : Oh
Roxie Hart : Hello Miss Borusewicz
Ms Borusewicz : Mrs Hart
Roxie Hart : This is Fred
Roxie Hart : He's my brother
Velma Kelly : All
Velma Kelly : That
Velma Kelly : Jazz
Velma Kelly : Come on babe Why don't we paint the town
Velma Kelly : And all that jazz
Velma Kelly : I'm gonna rouge my knees And roll my stockings down
Velma Kelly : Start the car I know a whoopee spot
Velma Kelly : Where the gin is cold But the piano's hot
Velma Kelly : It's just a noisy hall Where there's a nightly brawl
Velma Kelly : And all
Velma Kelly : That
Velma Kelly : Jazz
Roxie Hart : Say it again Fred
Fred Casely : You're a star kid
Fred Casely : My little shootin star
Velma Kelly : No I'm no one's wife
Velma Kelly : But oh I love my life
Velma Kelly : And all
Velma Kelly : That
Velma Kelly : Jazz
Velma Kelly : That jazz
Roxie Hart : Say it again Fred
Roxie Hart : Hey
Roxie Hart : Where's the fire huh
Roxie Hart : Amos ain't home till midnight
Roxie Hart : Freddy
Roxie Hart : Fred
Roxie Hart : Hey you know I don't want you to feel
Roxie Hart : like I'm nagging at you or anything but don't you think it's about time I met your friend down at the Onyx
Roxie Hart : I mean it's been a month since you told him about me
Roxie Hart : And I know cause that was the night
Roxie Hart : Velma Kelly plugged her husband and her sister
Roxie Hart : You know they say that she found em in the kip together
Roxie Hart : Gosh if I ever found Amos slipping it to somebody else
Roxie Hart : boy I'd throw him a party
Roxie Hart : a great big goingaway party
Fred Casely : It's getting late
Roxie Hart : I have been thinking a lot about my act though
Roxie Hart : Whenever I get a really good idea
Roxie Hart : I write it down in my diary before it goes out of my head
Roxie Hart : And you know what occurred to me the other day
Roxie Hart : That all the really really knockout acts
Roxie Hart : have something a little different going on you know
Roxie Hart : Like a signature bit
Roxie Hart : And I thought that my thing could be aloof you know
Roxie Hart : Give em just enough to get em good and hungry
Roxie Hart : but always leave em wantin more
Roxie Hart : Hey and once I get a name for myself maybe
Roxie Hart : maybe we could open up a club of our own you know
Roxie Hart : You could run it and I could be the headliner
Roxie Hart : What's the idea
Fred Casely : Wake up kiddo You ain't never gonna have an act
Roxie Hart : Says who
Fred Casely : Face it Roxie You're a twobit talent with skinny legs
Fred Casely : And I'm just a furniture salesman
Roxie Hart : Yeah but you got connections
Roxie Hart : You know that guy at the club
Fred Casely : There is no guy
Roxie Hart : Yeah but that night
Fred Casely : It was the first time I set foot in that joint
Fred Casely : I was collecting on a bet from the trombone player
Roxie Hart : So you never told anyone about me
Fred Casely : Sugar you were hot stuff I would have said anything to get a piece of that
Roxie Hart : And now Now
Fred Casely : We had some laughs Let's just leave it at that
Roxie Hart : Fred
Roxie Hart : You can't do this to me
Fred Casely : Would you get off
Fred Casely : You touch me again I'll put your lights out
Roxie Hart : Wait
Fred Casely : Your husband will be home soon Why don't you wash yourself before you go hitting those sheets again
Roxie Hart : You're a liar Fred
Fred Casely : Yeah yeah so what
Roxie Hart : You lied to me
Roxie Hart : You lied to me you son of a bitch
Roxie Hart : That's life sweetheart That's life
Roxie Hart : You son of a bitch You son of a bitch
Roxie Hart : You're a son of a bitch
Woman Ensemble : Whoopee
Reporter : Why are you bothering Sal This one's all wrapped up
Reporter : I hear it's a new city record
Reporter : From killin to confession in an hour flat
Sergeant Fogarty : Where did you get the murder weapon
Amos Hart : I keep a gun in the underwear drawer
Amos Hart : Just in case of trouble you know
Police : That's just fine Sign right there Mr Hart
Amos Hart : Freely and gladly Freely and gladly
Police : And mind you don't say we beat it out of you when you get on the witness stand
Amos Hart : No I gave myself up Surrendered of my own free will
Police : Isn't he the cheerful murderer
Roxie Hart : Shootin a burglar ain't murder
Roxie Hart : Just last week a jury thanked a man
Sergeant Fogarty : I'm always grateful for citizens who know the law
Sergeant Fogarty : Get in there
Sergeant Fogarty : You too
Sergeant Fogarty : Sit down
Sergeant Fogarty : Okay From the top
Amos Hart : A man's got a right to protect his home and loved ones right
Sergeant Fogarty : Of course he has
Amos Hart : Well I come home from the garage and I see him climbing through the window
Amos Hart : with my wife Roxie laying there
Amos Hart : sleeping like an angel
Sergeant Fogarty : That true Mrs Hart
Amos Hart : I'm tellin you it's the God's honest truth My wife had nothing to do with it
Amos Hart : She wouldn't hurt a worm not even a worm
Amos Hart : It wasn't till I fired the first shot she even opened her eyes
Amos Hart : Boy she's some heavy sleeper I always said she could sleep through the St Paddy's Day Parade
Amos Hart : When I think of what would've happened if I went out for a beer with the guys instead of coming straight home It makes you sick even thinking about it
Narrator : For her first number Miss Roxie Hart would like to sing a song of love and devotion
Narrator : dedicated to her dear husband Amos
Roxie Hart : Sometimes I'm right
Roxie Hart : Sometimes I'm wrong
Roxie Hart : But he doesn't care
Roxie Hart : He'll string along
Roxie Hart : He loves me so
Roxie Hart : That funny honey of mine
Roxie Hart : Sometimes I'm down Sometimes I'm up
Roxie Hart : But he follows round Like some droopyeyed pup
Roxie Hart : He loves me so
Roxie Hart : That funny honey of mine
Amos Hart : Like I said even after I shot him
Amos Hart : he kept coming at me so I had to pull the trigger again
Roxie Hart : He ain't no sheik
Roxie Hart : That's no great physique
Roxie Hart : And Lord knows He ain't got the smarts
Roxie Hart : But look at that soul
Roxie Hart : I tell you that whole
Roxie Hart : Is a whole lot greater Than the sum of his parts
Roxie Hart : And if you knew him like me
Roxie Hart : I know you'd agree
Roxie Hart : What if the world slandered my name
Roxie Hart : Why he'd be right there Taking the blame
Roxie Hart : He loves me so
Roxie Hart : And it all suits me fine
Roxie Hart : That funny sunny honey
Roxie Hart : Hubby of mine
Amos Hart : Just supposing he had violated her or something
Amos Hart : You know what I mean violated
Sergeant Fogarty : I know what you mean
Amos Hart : Or something Think how terrible that would've been
Amos Hart : It's a good thing I got home from work on time
Roxie Hart : He loves me so
Amos Hart : I say I'm telling you that
Roxie Hart : funny honey of mine
Sergeant Fogarty : The name of deceased is Fred Casely
Amos Hart : Fred Casely? How could he be a burglar? My wife knows him He sold us our furniture
Amos Hart : He gave us 10 off
Roxie Hart : Lord knows He ain't got the smarts
Amos Hart : You told me he was a burglar
Sergeant Fogarty : You mean he was dead when you got home
Amos Hart : She had him covered in a sheet and she's telling me some cockandbull story about this burglar
Amos Hart : and how I ought to say I did it cause I was sure to get off
Amos Hart : Help me Amos she says It's my goddamn hour of need
Roxie Hart : Now he shot off his trap
Roxie Hart : I can't stand that sap
Roxie Hart : Look at him go Rattin on me With just one
more brain What a halfwit He'd be
Amos Hart : And I believed her That cheap little tramp She was twotiming me huh I'm through protecting her She can swing for all I care
Roxie Hart : If they String me up
Amos Hart : Boy I'm down at the garage working my butt off 14 hours a day
Roxie Hart : I'll know who
brought the twine
Amos Hart : and she's up here munching on bonbons
and tramping around like
Amos Hart : some goddamn floozy
Amos Hart : Thought she could pull
the wool over my eyes huh Well I wasn't born yesterday!
There's some things a man can't take
Roxie Hart : That scummy crummy Dummy!
Roxie Hart : Hubby Of mine
Amos Hart : And this time she pushed me too far  That little chiseler Boy what a sap I was
Roxie Hart : You doublecrosser You big blabbermouth
Roxie Hart : You promised you'd stick
Amos Hart : What you talkin about you You been stringin me Roxanne
Roxie Hart : Stop
Amos Hart : You told me he was a burglar
Roxie Hart : God Damn it The whole time you been up here jazzin him
Roxie Hart : You are a disloyal husband
Roxie Hart : Look it's true I shot him
Roxie Hart : But it was selfdefense He was trying to burgle me
Sergeant Fogarty : From what I hear he's been burgling you three times a week for the last month
Sergeant Fogarty : So what do you say missus
Ms Borusewicz : That's him all right
Sergeant Fogarty : Thank you
Sergeant Fogarty : Your story doesn't wash Mrs Hart so try this on for size
Sergeant Fogarty : Fred Casely was a good time on the side with Goofy here as a meal ticket
Roxie Hart : Meal ticket He couldn't buy my liquor
Sergeant Fogarty : And Fred Casely could With a wife and five little Caselys Or did he forget to mention them
Roxie Hart : What
Sergeant Fogarty : All his
Roxie Hart : That bastard That bastard
Roxie Hart : Yeah I killed him and I would kill him again
Sergeant Fogarty : Once was enough dearie Take her downtown Come on
Reporter : This is it 26412
Reporter : Here they come This way honey
Reporter : Come on it's a shame to hide such a beautiful face
Reporter2 : Why'd you shoot him hon
Reporter : Won't you give us a profile with a little smile like the girl from the toothpaste ad
Sergeant Fogarty : Enjoy it while you can Take this down
Sergeant Fogarty : Assistant District Attorney Harrison says this is a hanging case
Sergeant Fogarty : I'm ready to go to the jury tomorrow
Roxie Hart : Hanging What do you mean hanging
Sergeant Fogarty : Not so tough anymore are you Take her down to the Cook County Jail
Reporter : We need a headline Why'd you shoot him Was he cruel Did he beat you
Roxie Hart : Hey what do you mean hanging
Prison Officer : Morphine opium cocaine
Prison Officer2 : Arm length 31 inches
Prison Officer : Arm length 31 inches
Prison Officer2 : Height 66 inches
Prison Officer : The Matron's on her way so don't get too cozy
Prison Officer : Put out that cigarette
Velma Kelly;Prisoner : Ever had Morton before
Prisoner : She's fine Long as you keep her happy
Narrator : And now ladies and gentlemen
Narrator : the keeper of the keys the countess of the clink
Narrator : the mistress of murderess row
Narrator : Matron Mama Morton
Matron Mama Morton : Ask any of the chickies in my pen
Matron Mama Morton : They'll tell you I'm the biggest mother hen
Matron Mama Morton : I love them all And all of them love me
Matron Mama Morton : Because the system works The system called
Matron Mama Morton : Reciprocity
Prison Officer : On your feet
Matron Mama Morton : Welcome ladies
Matron Mama Morton : Got a little motto Always sees me through
Matron Mama Morton : When you're good to Mama
Matron Mama Morton : Mama's good to you
Matron Mama Morton : You might think I'm here to make your life a living hell
Matron Mama Morton : but it's just not true
Matron Mama Morton : There's a lot of favors
Matron Mama Morton : I'm prepared to do
Matron Mama Morton : You do one for Mama
Matron Mama Morton : She'll do one for you
Matron Mama Morton : I'd like to be your friend if you let me
Matron Mama Morton : So if there's something that upsets you or makes you unhappy in any way
Matron Mama Morton : don't shoot your fatass mouth off to me cause I don't give a shit Now move it out
Matron Mama Morton : They say that life is tit for tat And that's the way I live
Matron Mama Morton : So I deserve a lot of tat
Matron Mama Morton : For what I've got to give Don't you know that this hand
Matron Mama Morton : Washes that one too
Matron Mama Morton : When you're good to Mama
Matron Mama Morton : Mama's good to you
Prison Officer : Let's go
Matron Mama Morton : You must be Hart
Matron Mama Morton : Ain't you the pretty one
Roxie Hart : Thank you ma'am
Matron Mama Morton : Oh no call me Mama
Matron Mama Morton : I'm here to take care of you
Matron Mama Morton : Now you'll be habitatin down in the east block
Matron Mama Morton : Murderess Row we call it
Roxie Hart : Oh
Roxie Hart : Is that nicer
Roxie Hart : You know I don't think I really belong in here I didn't actually do anything wrong
Matron Mama Morton : No need to tell me honey I never heard of a man getting killed
Matron Mama Morton : when he didn't get just what was coming to him
Velma Kelly : Hey Mama Come here Come here
Roxie Hart : Velma Kelly
Roxie Hart : You're the Velma Kelly
Roxie Hart : You know I was there that night I was there the night you got arrested
Velma Kelly : Yeah You and half of Chicago
Velma Kelly : Look at this Mama
Velma Kelly : An editorial denouncing me in Redbook magazine
Velma Kelly : Not in memory do we recall so fiendish and horrible a double homicide
Matron Mama Morton : Baby you couldn't buy that kind of publicity
Velma Kelly : Couldn't buy it
Velma Kelly : I guess I can keep this then
Matron Mama Morton : Nice try
Matron Mama Morton : If you want my gravy
Matron Mama Morton : Pepper my ragout
Matron Mama Morton : Spice it up for Mama
Matron Mama Morton : She'll get hot for you
Matron Mama Morton : When they pass that basket
Matron Mama Morton : Folks contribute to You put in for Mama
Matron Mama Morton : She'll put out for you
Matron Mama Morton : The folks atop the ladder
Matron Mama Morton : Are the ones the world adores
Matron Mama Morton : So boost me up my ladder kid
Matron Mama Morton : And I'll boost you up yours
Matron Mama Morton : Let's all stroke together
Matron Mama Morton : Like the Princeton crew
Matron Mama Morton : When you're strokin Mama
Matron Mama Morton : Mama's strokin you
Matron Mama Morton : So what's the one conclusion I can bring this number to
Matron Mama Morton : When you're good to Mama
Matron Mama Morton : Mama's good
Matron Mama Morton : To you
Matron Mama Morton : Ah yes
Roxie Hart : Mama Um
Roxie Hart : It's kind of uh freezing in here
Roxie Hart : You don't think maybe there's something wrong with the heat
Roxie Hart : Not that I'm complaining mind you but but you know if you got a couple extra blankets tucked away
Matron Mama Morton : Lights out ladies
Roxie Hart : Okay
Liz : Pop
Annie : Six
June : Squish
Hunyak : Uhuh
Velma Kelly : Cicero
Mona : Lipschitz
Narrator : And now the six merry murderesses of the Cook County Jail
Narrator : in their rendition of the Cell Block Tango
Mona : Lipschitz
Liz : Pop
Annie : Six
June : Squish
Hunyak : Uhuh
Velma Kelly : Cicero
Mona : Lipschitz
Liz : Pop
Annie : Six
June : Squish
Hunyak : Uhuh
Velma Kelly : Cicero
Mona : Lipschitz
Murderesses : Pop Six Squish Uhuh Cicero Lipschitz
Liz : Pop
Annie : Six
June : Squish
Hunyak : Uhuh
Velma Kelly : Cicero
Mona : Lipschitz
Murderesses : He had it coming
Murderesses : He only had himself to blame
Murderesses : If you'd have been there
Murderesses : If you'd have seen it
Velma Kelly : I betcha You would have done the same
Liz : Pop
Annie : Six
June : Squish
Hunyak : Uhuh
Velma Kelly : Cicero
Mona : Lipschitz
Liz : Pop
Annie : Six
June : Squish
Hunyak : Uhuh
Velma Kelly : Cicero
Mona : Lipschitz
Liz : You know how people have these Little habits that get you down
Liz : Like Bernie Bernie liked to chew gum
Liz : No not chew
Liz : Pop
Liz : So I came home this one day And I'm really irritated And I'm looking For a little bit of sympathy
Liz : And there's Bernie lyin on the couch Drinkin a beer and chewin
Liz : No not chewin Poppin
Liz : So I said to him You pop that gum one more time
Liz : And he did
Liz : So I took the shotgun off the wall And I fired two warning shots
Liz : Into his head
Murderesses : He had it coming
Murderesses : He only had himself to blame
Murderesses : If you'd have been there If you'd have heard it
Murderesses : I betcha You would have done the same
Annie : I met Ezekial Young from Salt Lake City About two years ago
Annie : And he told me he was single And we hit it off right away
Annie : So we started living together He'd go to work he'd come home
Annie : I'd fix him a drink we'd have dinner
Annie : And then I found out
Annie : Single he told me Single my ass
Annie : Not only was he married
Annie : Oh no he had six wives
Annie : One of those Mormons you know
Annie : So that night When he came home from work
Annie : I fixed him his drink as usual
Annie : You know some guys Just can't hold their arsenic
Murderesses : He had it coming Pop six He had it coming Cicero Lipschitz He took a flower in its prime
Murderesses : And then he used it Pop And he abused it Six It was a murder but not a crime Cicero Lipschitz
June : Now I'm standing in the kitchen Carving up the chicken for dinner
June : Minding my own business In storms my husband Wilbur In a jealous rage
June : You been screwin the milkman He says
June : He was crazy And he kept on screamin You been screwin the milkman
June : And then he ran into my knife
June : He ran into my knife ten times
Murderesses : If you'd have been there
Murderesses : If you'd have seen it I betcha You would have done the same
Roxie Hart : Yeah but did you do it
Hunyak : Uhuh not guilty
Murderesses : He had it comin
Velma Kelly : My sister Veronica And I had this double act
Velma Kelly : And my husband Charlie traveled around with us
Velma Kelly : Now for the last number in our act We did these 20 acrobatic tricks In a row
Velma Kelly : One two three four five
Velma Kelly : Splits spread eagles Backflips flipflops One right after the other
Velma Kelly : So this one night before the show we're down at the Hotel Cicero
Velma Kelly : The three of us boozin and havin a few laughs
Velma Kelly : We run out of ice So I go out to get some
Velma Kelly : I come back open the door
Velma Kelly : And there's Veronica and Charlie Doing number seventeen
Velma Kelly : The spread eagle
Velma Kelly : Well I was in such a state of shock I completely blacked out I can't remember a thing
Velma Kelly : It wasn't until later
Velma Kelly : When I was washing the blood off my hands I even knew they were dead
Murderesses : They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming all along
Murderesses : I didn't do it She didn't do it But if I'd done it But if she'd done it
Velma Kelly : How could you tell me That I was wrong
Murderesses : They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming all along I didn't do it
Murderesses : But if I'd done it How could you tell me That I was wrong
Mona : I loved Al Lipschitz More than I could possibly say
Mona : He was a real artistic guy
Mona : Sensitive a painter
Mona : But he was always trying To find himself
Mona : He'd go out every night Looking for himself and on the way
Mona : He found Ruth Gladys Rosemary and Irving
Mona : I guess you could say we broke up Because of artistic differences
Mona : He saw himself as alive
Mona : And I saw him dead
Murderesses : The dirty bum bum bum bum bum The dirty bum bum bum bum bum
Murderesses : They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming They had it coming all along
Murderesses : And if they used us And if they used us Then they abused us Then they abused us Could you tell us That we were wrong
Murderesses : He had it coming He had it coming He had it coming He had it coming He only had himself to blame
Murderesses : If you'd have been there If you'd have been there If you'd have seen it If you'd have seen it I betcha You would have done the same
Liz : You pop that gum one more time
Annie : Single my ass
June : Ten times
Number seventeen the spread eagle
Mona : Artistic differences
Liz : Pop
Annie : Six
June : Squish
Hunyak : Uhuh
Velma Kelly : Cicero
Mona : Lipschitz
Roxie Hart : Who belongs to them
Prisoner : What's it to you
Roxie Hart : Nothing Heard they were Velma's
Annie : Yeah The Hunyak does all her laundry for a buck a week
Roxie Hart : Fresh towels for the can
Prison Officer : Make it quick
Matron Mama Morton : I'm gonna take care of you now I know a couple of things Now hear me out on this
Matron Mama Morton : Now Billy Flynn's set your trial date for March 5th
Matron Mama Morton : March 7th you'll be acquitted
Matron Mama Morton : On March 8th you know what Mama is gonna do for you
Matron Mama Morton : Mama is gonna put you back on the vaudeville circuit
Velma Kelly : So now you're an agent too
Matron Mama Morton : Well dearie until Ma Bell installs a private line in your cell all the calls have gotta go through me
Velma Kelly : What kind of dough are we talking about
Matron Mama Morton : You know it's a crazy world
Matron Mama Morton : I mean Babe Ruth is wearing rouge and playing the Palace for 5000 a week
Velma Kelly : Yeah What about someone with real talent
Matron Mama Morton : Well I been talking to the boys over at William Morris
Matron Mama Morton : Due to your recent sensational activities they think they can get you 2500 Twentyfive hundred
Velma Kelly : Jeez the most me and Veronica made was 350
Matron Mama Morton : Well that's what happens when you have the right representation
Velma Kelly : You know what Mama I always wanted to play Big Jim Colosimo's
Velma Kelly : Do you think you can get me that
Matron Mama Morton : Big Jim's
Velma Kelly : Yeah
Matron Mama Morton : Jeez I don't know
Matron Mama Morton : That's gonna take another phone call
Velma Kelly : How much is that gonna cost
Matron Mama Morton : Come on Vel
Matron Mama Morton : You know how I feel about you You're like family to me You're like one of my own
Velma Kelly : Oh yeah
Matron Mama Morton : I'll do it for 50 bucks
Velma Kelly : Fifty
bucks for a phone call
Velma Kelly : You must get a lot of wrong numbers Mama
Roxie Hart : Oh Miss Kelly
Roxie Hart : Got your personals Freshly pressed by yours truly
Roxie Hart : No no it's my pleasure
Roxie Hart : Hey listen um can I ask you something
Roxie Hart : You know that Harrison guy
Roxie Hart : Well he said that what I done is a hanging case and that he's prepared to ask for the maximum penalty
Velma Kelly : Yeah so
Roxie Hart : So  I'm scared
Roxie Hart : I sure would appreciate some advice Especially from someone I admire as much as you
Roxie Hart : Since I can remember I have wanted to be on the stage
Velma Kelly : Really What's your talent Washing and drying
Roxie Hart : No no I danced in the chorus
Roxie Hart : That was before I met my husband Amos
Velma Kelly : Look honey you want some advice
Velma Kelly : Here it is Direct from me to you
Velma Kelly : Keep your paws off my underwear okay
Roxie Hart : Yeah okay
Roxie Hart : Thanks
Roxie Hart : For nothin
Matron Mama Morton : She's something ain't she
Matron Mama Morton : I'll tell you no matter how big she gets she's still as common as ever
Matron Mama Morton : I'd like to help you dearie
Matron Mama Morton : Take a load off
Matron Mama Morton : So what do you figure on using for grounds
Matron Mama Morton : What are you gonna tell the jury
Roxie Hart : I just figured I'd tell them the truth
Matron Mama Morton : The truth
Roxie Hart : Yeah
Matron Mama Morton : That's a oneway ticket to the death house of God
Roxie Hart : Holy Mother
Matron Mama Morton : Oh Relax
Matron Mama Morton : I mean in this town murder's a form of entertainment
Matron Mama Morton : Besides in 47 years Cook County ain't never hung a woman yet
Matron Mama Morton : So the odds are 47 to one that they won't hang you
Roxie Hart : Jesus Mary and Joseph
Matron Mama Morton : You're talking to the wrong people What you need is Billy Flynn
Roxie Hart : Who Billy Flynn
Matron Mama Morton : He's only the best criminal lawyer in all of Illinois
Matron Mama Morton : I tell you what he don't know about juries and women
Roxie Hart : How do you get this Billy Flynn
Matron Mama Morton : Well not by praying dearie
Matron Mama Morton : First you give me 100 Then I make a phone call
Roxie Hart : A hundred dollars Well you just
Roxie Hart : I mean it seems pretty steep for a phone call
Matron Mama Morton : Oh but he's worth every cent
Matron Mama Morton : I mean he's never lost a case for a female client yet
Woman Ensemble : We want Billy
Matron Mama Morton : With a sweet little puss like yours well
Matron Mama Morton : let's just say justice ain't so blind in Chicago
Roxie Hart : He's never lost a case
Matron Mama Morton : Never
Matron Mama Morton : Every girl in this place would kill to have Billy Flynn represent her
Woman Ensemble : Billy
Woman Ensemble : We want Billy
Woman Ensemble : B I Double L Y
Woman Ensemble : We're all his
Woman Ensemble : He's our kind of a guy
Woman Ensemble : And ooh what luck
Woman Ensemble : Cause here he is
Narrator : Ladies and gentlemen presenting the silvertongued prince of the courtroom
Narrator : The one the only Billy Flynn
Billy Flynn : I don't care about expensive things
Billy Flynn : Cashmere coats diamond rings
Billy Flynn : Don't mean a thing
Billy Flynn : All I care about is love
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : That's what he's here for That's what I'm here for
Billy Flynn : I don't care for wearing silk cravats
Billy Flynn : Ruby studs satin spats
Billy Flynn : Don't mean a thing
Billy Flynn : All I care about is love
Woman Ensemble : All he cares about is love
Billy Flynn : Give me two eyes of blue
Billy Flynn : Softly saying I need you
Billy Flynn : Let me see her standing there And honest mister I'm a millionaire
Billy Flynn : I don't care for any fine attire
Billy Flynn : Vanderbilt might admire
Billy Flynn : No no not me
Billy Flynn : All I care about is love
Woman Ensemble : All he cares about is love
Prisoner : What about my trial day
Billy Flynn : Good morning ladies
Hunyak : Not guilty
Billy Flynn : You tell em sweetheart
Woman Ensemble : That's what he's here for
Mary Sunshine : Excuse me gentlemen
Mary Sunshine : Miss Kelly do you remember anything at all about that night
Velma Kelly : I passed out completely Miss Sunshine I can't remember a thing
Velma Kelly : Only that I didn't do it
Mary Sunshine : Any idea who did dear
Billy Flynn : No but my client is offering a substantial reward to anyone with information about this crime
Mary Sunshine : How much is the reward Miss Kelly
Velma Kelly : I don't know How much
Billy Flynn : We'll work it out after the trial
Billy Flynn : Now if there are no more questions Miss Kelly and I have a lot of work to do
Velma Kelly : What's all this about a reward
Billy Flynn : Awfully dumb reporters They'll write it up wrong You deny the whole thing later on
Billy Flynn : Thank you
Reporter : Just one more question please
Woman Ensemble : All he cares about is love
Roxie Hart : Mr Flynn I'm Roxie Hart
Billy Flynn : Who
Roxie Hart : Mama talked to you about me
Billy Flynn : Oh yeah right The cute one
Roxie Hart : I was hoping that you might represent me
Billy Flynn : You got 5000
Roxie Hart : Gee that's a lot of money
Roxie Hart : Mama didn't say anything about 5000
Roxie Hart : Look here Mr Flynn
Roxie Hart : I'm not very good at this sort of thing but maybe we could make some sort of arrangement between us
Roxie Hart : I can be an awfully good sport
Billy Flynn : Good you got that out of your system Now listen
Billy Flynn : You mean just one thing to me
Billy Flynn : You call me when you got 5000
Roxie Hart : All he cares about is love
Billy Flynn : Show me long raven hair
Billy Flynn : Flowin down about to there
Billy Flynn : When I see her runnin free
Billy Flynn : Keep your money that's enough for me
Billy Flynn : I don't care for drivin Packard cars
Billy Flynn : Or smoking long buck cigars
Billy Flynn : No no not me
Billy Flynn : All I care about is doin the guy in
Billy Flynn : Who's pickin on you
Billy Flynn : Twistin the wrist That's turnin the screw
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : All he cares about All I care about
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : Is
Billy Flynn : Love
Flynn's Secretary : Oh he'll see you now
Billy Flynn : Well hello Andy
Amos Hart : My name is Amos
Billy Flynn : That's right Take a seat
Billy Flynn : You know you're a remarkable man
Billy Flynn : Your wife twotimes you plugs the guy then tries to pin it on you
Billy Flynn : Most men would let a dame like that swing But no you're sticking by her
Billy Flynn : Makes you a hero in my eyes
Amos Hart : That's right I'm a hero
Billy Flynn : Did you bring the money
Amos Hart : I didn't do as well as I hoped
Amos Hart : But I will Mr Flynn I will
Billy Flynn : This is only a thousand
Amos Hart : Plus there's 300 I borrowed from the guys down at the garage
Amos Hart : And then there's 700 from the buildingandloan fund
Billy Flynn : Two thousand
Amos Hart : And that's all I got so far
Amos Hart : But I'll give you 20 off my salary every week
Amos Hart : I'll give you notes with interest
Amos Hart : Double Triple Till every cent is paid I promise
Billy Flynn : When you came to me yesterday
Billy Flynn : I didn't ask if she was guilty I didn't ask if she was innocent
Billy Flynn : I didn't ask if she was a drunk or a dope fiend No
Billy Flynn : All I said was Do you have 5000 You said yes
Billy Flynn : But you don't have 5000 So I figure you're a dirty liar And I don't waste my time with dirty liars
Amos Hart : Look
Amos Hart : I'm real sorry Mr Flynn
Billy Flynn : On the other hand
Billy Flynn : your devotion to your wife is really very very touching
Billy Flynn : I took your wife's case and I'll keep it
Billy Flynn : because I play square
Billy Flynn : Now look Hart
Billy Flynn : I don't like to blow my own horn but believe me if Jesus Christ had lived in Chicago today and if he had 5000 and he'd come to me
Billy Flynn : things would've turned out differently
Billy Flynn : All right this is what we're gonna do
Billy Flynn : By the end of the week I'm gonna have Roxie's name on the front page of every newspaper in town
Billy Flynn : Sweetest little jazz killer ever to hit Chicago
Billy Flynn : That's the angle I'm after
Billy Flynn : You make an announcement we're gonna have an auction
Billy Flynn : Tell them we gotta raise some money for her defense
Billy Flynn : They'll buy everything she's ever touched Everything
Billy Flynn : Your shoes your dresses your perfume your underwear
Roxie Hart : And Victrola records
Roxie Hart : Like the one I was playing when I shot the bastard
Billy Flynn : I didn't hear that Not that I didn't have grounds mind you
Roxie Hart : Hey what are they
Billy Flynn : That's for when we go to trial Look nobody nobody's gonna care a lick what your defense is unless they care about you
Billy Flynn : So the first thing that we gotta do is work up some sympathy from the press And they're not all pushovers like Mary Sunshine
Billy Flynn : But there's one thing that they can never resist And that is a reformed sinner
Billy Flynn : Alright So tell me what was your favorite subject in school
Roxie Hart : I was a real dummy
Billy Flynn : Come on There must've been something you were really good at
Roxie Hart : Oh I got high marks on courtesy and hygiene
Billy Flynn : Perfect You wanted to be a nun
Roxie Hart : A nun
Billy Flynn : Where were you born
Roxie Hart : On a chicken farm outside of Lubbock
Billy Flynn : Beautiful southern home filled with every luxury and refinement
Billy Flynn : Where are your parents now
Roxie Hart : Probably on the front porch in their rocking chairs
Billy Flynn : Parents dead
Billy Flynn : Family fortune swept away You were educated at the Sacred Heart
Billy Flynn : Then you fell into a runaway marriage Left you miserable alone unhappy And of course you got all swept up in the mad whirl of the city
Billy Flynn : Jazz cabarets liquor You were drawn like a moth to the flame
Roxie Hart : A moth
Billy Flynn : Now the mad whirl has ceased
Billy Flynn : And you are a butterfly crushed on the wheel
Roxie Hart : So which is it Is it the moth or the butterfly
Billy Flynn : You have sinned and you are sorry
Roxie Hart : God that's beautiful
Billy Flynn : Cut out God Stay where you're better acquainted
Billy Flynn : Kid when I'm through with you not only will you be acquitted
Billy Flynn : every man on that jury will want to take you home to meet his mother
Roxie Hart : I was born on a beautiful Southern convent
Billy Flynn : What
Roxie Hart : Holy shit I'm never gonna get this straight
Billy Flynn : Pipe down the swearing Look from here on in
Billy Flynn : you say nothing rougher than Oh dear Now try again
Roxie Hart : I was born on a
Billy Flynn : Come on Come on come on
Velma Kelly : I came up with some more things to do on the witness stand
Velma Kelly : I thought I'd get all tearyeyed and ask to borrow your handkerchief
Velma Kelly : Then I thought I'd take a peek at the jury like this
Velma Kelly : Flash em a bit of thigh huh What do you think
Billy Flynn : Sounds great
Velma Kelly : Don't you want to hear the rest
Billy Flynn : Tomorrow kiddo
Billy Flynn : You're at the top of my list
Billy Flynn : Well well well
Roxie Hart : Sorry to be late Mr Flynn
Roxie Hart : Hope you weren't too bored
Billy Flynn : I like it
Velma Kelly : Hey Pollyanna
Velma Kelly : I heard your press conference is tomorrow
Roxie Hart : Yeah what's it to you
Velma Kelly : Well you wanted my advice right
Velma Kelly : Well here it is
Velma Kelly : Don't forget Billy Flynn's numberone client is Billy Flynn
Roxie Hart : Meaning what
Velma Kelly : Meaning don't let him hog the spotlight
Velma Kelly : You're the one they pay to see
Billy Flynn : Now remember we can only sell them one idea at a time
Roxie Hart : Yeah I can still see him coming at me with that awful look in his eyes
Billy Flynn : And
Roxie Hart : And we both reached for the gun
Billy Flynn : That's right You both reached for the gun
Billy Flynn : You ready
Roxie Hart : Yeah
Reporter : Miss Hart
Billy Flynn : Good day gentlemen Gentlemen Miss Sunshine
Billy Flynn : My client has just entered a plea of not guilty
Billy Flynn : We look forward to a trial at the earliest possible date Now are there any questions
Mary Sunshine : Miss Sunshine As you know my paper is dry
Mary Sunshine : Do you have any advice for young girls seeking to avoid a life of jazz and drink
Billy Flynn : Absolutely yes Mrs Hart feels that it was the tragic combination of liquor and jazz which led to her downfall
Billy Flynn : Next question please
Roxie Hart : Ladies and gentlemen
Roxie Hart : I would just like to say how flattered I am that y'all came to see me
Billy Flynn : Mrs Hart is very pleased...
Roxie Hart : You see I was a moth crushed on the wheel
Roxie Hart : You know a butterfly drawn to the to the
Roxie Hart : I bet you want to know why I shot the bastard
Billy Flynn : Shut up dummy
Narrator : Mr Billy Flynn in The Press Conference Rag
Narrator : Notice how his mouth never moves
Narrator : Almost
Reporter : Where'd you come from
Billy Flynn : Mississippi
Reporter2 : And your parents
Billy Flynn : Very wealthy
Reporter3 : Where are they now
Billy Flynn : Six feet under
Billy Flynn : But she was granted one more start The Convent of the Sacred Heart
Reporter : When'd you get here
Reporter2 : How old were you
Billy Flynn : Don't remember
Reporter3 : Then what happened
Billy Flynn : I met Amos And he stole my heart away Convinced me to elope one day
Mary Sunshine : Oh you poor dear I can't believe what you've been through
Mary Sunshine : A convent girl a runaway marriage
Mary Sunshine : Now tell us Roxie
Mary Sunshine : Who's Fred Casely
Billy Flynn : My exboyfriend
Reporters : Why'd you shoot him
Billy Flynn : I was leavin
Reporters : Was he angry
Billy Flynn : Like a madman Still I said Fred move along
Billy Flynn : She knew that she was doing wrong
Reporters : Then describe it
Billy Flynn : He came toward me
Reporters : With the pistol
Billy Flynn : From my bureau
Reporters : Did you fight him
Billy Flynn : Like a tiger
Billy Flynn : He had strength that she had none
Billy Flynn : And yet we both reached for the gun
Billy Flynn : Oh yes oh yes Oh yes we both oh yes we both Oh yes we both reached For the gun the gun the gun the gun Oh yes we both Reached for the gun for the gun
Reporters : Oh yes oh yes oh yes they both Oh yes they both Oh yes they both reached for The gun the gun the gun the gun Oh yes they both Reached for the gun for the gun
Billy Flynn : Understandable
Billy Flynn : Yes it's perfectly understandable
Billy Flynn : Comprehensible
Billy Flynn : Not a bit reprehensible
Billy Flynn : It's so defensible
Reporters : How you feelin
Billy Flynn : Very frightened
Mary Sunshine : Are you sorry
Roxie Hart : Are you kidding
Reporters : What's your statement
Billy Flynn : All I'd say is
Billy Flynn : Though my choochoo jumped the track I'd give my life to bring him back
Reporters : And?
Roxie Hart : Stay away from What Jazz and liquor
Reporters : And
Billy Flynn : And the men who
Reporters : What
Billy Flynn : What Play for fun
Reporters : And what
Billy Flynn : That's the thought that
Billy Flynn : Yeah Came upon me
Billy Flynn : When When we both reached for the gun
Mary Sunshine : Understandable Understandable
Billy Flynn;Mary Sunshine : Yes it's perfectly understandable
Billy Flynn;Mary Sunshine : Comprehensible Comprehensible Not a bit reprehensible
Billy Flynn;Mary Sunshine : It's so defensible
Reporters : Oh yes oh yes oh yes they both
Reporters : Oh yes they both Oh yes they both reached for
Billy Flynn : Let me hear it
Reporters : The gun the gun the gun the gun
Reporters : Oh yes they both reached For the gun for the gun
Billy Flynn : A little louder
Reporters : Oh yes oh yes oh yes they both Oh yes they both oh yes They both reached for Oh yeah The gun the gun the gun the gun Oh yeah The gun the gun the gun the gun
Billy Flynn : Oh yes oh yes oh yes they both
Billy Flynn : Oh yes they both Oh yes they both reached for
Billy Flynn : The gun the gun the gun the gun
Billy Flynn : Oh yes they both Reached for the gun for the gun
Billy Flynn;Reporters : Oh yes oh yes oh yes they both Oh yes they both Oh yes they both reached for
Billy Flynn;Reporters : The gun the gun the gun the gun The gun the gun the gun the gun The gun the gun the gun the gun The gun the gun the gun the gun
Billy Flynn : Both reached for the
Billy Flynn : Gun
Reporter : Move over AI Capone
Reporter : The Windy City has taken a new criminal to its heart
Reporter : The name on everybody's lips is Roxie Hart The sweetest little lady ever accused of murder in Chicago
Reporter : Women want to look like her Fellas want to go out with her
Reporter : Some little girls even want to take her home
Reporter : Don't get any ideas little lady
Reporter : On the other side of town the assistant D. A promises the game little sharpshooter will swing before the year is up
Sergeant Fogarty : She'll swing before the year is up
Reporter : Who knows If he lives up to his word Assistant D. A Harrison might become Governor Harrison someday
Reporter : Back at the scene of the crime
Reporter : everybody wants a little piece of Roxie Hart
Reporter : This jar of cold cream set her husband back 20
Reporter : Maybe this pretty little lady will get some of that famous Roxie style
Reporter : It seems everybody these days is rooting for Roxie Hart
Matron Mama Morton : Take those wilting flowers over to the orphanage and make sure they know who sent them
Matron Mama Morton : So kiddo given any thought to what you want to do after Billy gets you off
Roxie Hart : Yeah I think I'd like to go on the stage
Matron Mama Morton : Yeah I figured as much
Matron Mama Morton : I already called the Morris office
Roxie Hart : Really
Roxie Hart : How much is that gonna cost me
Matron Mama Morton : My standard deal Ten percent of all your takings
Roxie Hart : Yeah well we'll see Mama
Roxie Hart : Besides I don't even have an act yet
Matron Mama Morton : Killing Fred Casely was your act
Matron Mama Morton : I mean that's all those stiffs in the audience want to say they saw somebody famous
Roxie Hart : That's a freak act
Roxie Hart : And besides I am better than that
Matron Mama Morton : Well of course you are cupcake
Matron Mama Morton : I mean you can be as big as Sophie Tucker
Roxie Hart : You really think so
Matron Mama Morton : Bigger than Cantor and Jolson combined
Roxie Hart : You know I've always wanted to have my name in all the papers
Roxie Hart : You know before I met Amos I used to date this welltodo ugly bootlegger
Roxie Hart : He used to like to take me out and show me off
Roxie Hart : Ugly guys like to do that
Roxie Hart : Once it said in the paper
Roxie Hart : Gangland's Al Capelli seen at Chez Vito with cute blond chorine
Roxie Hart : That was me
Roxie Hart : I clipped it and I saved it
Roxie Hart : You know all my life I wanted to have my own act
Roxie Hart : But no no no no always no They always turned me down
Roxie Hart : One big world full of no
Roxie Hart : And then Amos came along
Roxie Hart : Aw
Roxie Hart : Safe sweet Amos
Roxie Hart : who never says no
Roxie Hart : Oh yeah
Roxie Hart : I've never done this before
Roxie Hart : But you know it is such a special night And you are such a great audience
Roxie Hart : And And I just
Roxie Hart : I really feel like I can talk to you you know
Roxie Hart : So forget what you've read in the papers
Roxie Hart : And forget what you've heard on the radio because... because...
Roxie Hart : Because I'm gonna tell you the truth
Roxie Hart : Not that the truth really matters
Roxie Hart : But I'm gonna tell you anyway
Roxie Hart : In the bed department
Roxie Hart : Amos was zero
Roxie Hart : I mean when he made love to me
Roxie Hart : it was like he was fixing a carburetor or something
Roxie Hart : I love ya honey I love ya
Roxie Hart : Anyway I started fooling around
Roxie Hart : Then I started screwing around
Roxie Hart : which is fooling around without dinner
Roxie Hart : Then I met Fred Casely
Roxie Hart : who said that he could get me into vaudeville
Roxie Hart : But that didn't quite work out like I planned
Roxie Hart : I guess it didn't really work out too great for Fred either
Roxie Hart : So I gave up on the whole vaudeville idea
Roxie Hart : because you kinda figure after all those years
Roxie Hart : opportunity's just passed you by
Roxie Hart : But it ain't
Roxie Hart : Oh no no no no but it ain't
Roxie Hart : And now
Roxie Hart : Well if this Flynn guy gets me off
Roxie Hart : with all this publicity I got me a world full of yes
Roxie Hart : The name on everybody's lips Is gonna be Roxie
Roxie Hart : The lady rakin in the chips Is gonna be Roxie
Roxie Hart : I'm gonna be a celebrity That means somebody everyone knows
Roxie Hart : They're gonna recognize my eyes My hair my teeth my boobs my nose
Roxie Hart : From just some dumb mechanic's wife I'm gonna be Roxie
Roxie Hart : Who says that murder's not an art
Roxie Hart : And who in case she doesn't hang
Roxie Hart : Can say she started with a bang
Roxie Hart
Roxie Hart : Boys
Man Ensemble : They're gonna wait outside in line To get to see Roxie Roxie
Roxie Hart : Think of those autographs I'll sign Good luck to you
Man Ensemble : Roxie
Roxie Hart : And I'll appear in a lavaliere That goes all the way Down to my waist
Man Ensemble : Here a ring there a ring Everywhere a ringaling
Roxie Hart : But always in the best of taste
Roxie Hart : I'm a star
Roxie Hart : And the audience loves me And I love them
Roxie Hart : And they love me for loving them And I love them for loving me
Roxie Hart : And we love each other
Roxie Hart : And that's cause none of us got enough love in our childhoods
Roxie Hart : And that's showbiz
Roxie Hart : kid
Man Ensemble : She's givin up her humdrum life
Roxie Hart : I'm gonna be Sing it
Man Ensemble : Roxie
Man Ensemble : She made a scandal and a start
Roxie Hart : And Sophie Tucker will shit I know
Roxie Hart : To see her name get billed below
Roxie Hart : Roxie Hart
Man Ensemble : Roxie
Velma Kelly : I just can't take it anymore You can't go anywhere without hearing about that dumb tomato
Velma Kelly : Oh no Mama not you too
Matron Mama Morton : I have some bad news kid The tour has been canceled
Velma Kelly : What
Matron Mama Morton : Your name's been out of the papers too long
Matron Mama Morton : All you read about today is that Hart kid
Matron Mama Morton : She's hot
Velma Kelly : And what am I supposed to do huh
Velma Kelly : Suck up to her like everybody else
Matron Mama Morton : It couldn't hurt
Velma Kelly : Over my dead body
Velma Kelly : Mind if I join you
Prison Officer : Lights out ten minutes
Velma Kelly : Smoke
Velma Kelly : Look what some Johnny sent me
Velma Kelly : Triplecream caramels all the way from San Francisco
Roxie Hart : Oh
Roxie Hart : I'm watching my figure You know the trial
Velma Kelly : Hey great mention of you in the Trib today huh
Roxie Hart : You know there have been so many I just can't keep track
Velma Kelly : Hey did I ever tell you you are exactly the same size as my sister
Velma Kelly : I mean you'd fit into her costumes perfectly
Roxie Hart : Really?
Velma Kelly : Yeah And I was thinking you know with all the publicity that's piled up between us and when Billy gets us off
Velma Kelly : we'd be a natural to do an act together You think so huh
Narrator : Ladies and gentlemen
Narrator : Miss Velma Kelly in an act of desperation
Velma Kelly : My sister and I had an act That couldn't flop
Velma Kelly : My sister and I were headed Straight for the top
Velma Kelly : My sister and I earned a thou A week at least
Velma Kelly : Oh yeah
Velma Kelly : But my sister is now Unfortunately deceased
Velma Kelly : I know it's sad of course But a fact is still a fact
Velma Kelly : And now all that remains
Velma Kelly : Is the remains of a perfect
Velma Kelly : Double act
Velma Kelly : Watch this
Velma Kelly : Now you have to imagine it with two people
Velma Kelly : It's swell with two people
Velma Kelly : First I'd
Velma Kelly : Then she'd
Velma Kelly : Then we'd
Velma Kelly : But I can't do it alone
Velma Kelly : Then she'd
Velma Kelly : Then I'd
Velma Kelly : Then we'd
Velma Kelly : But I can't do it alone
Velma Kelly : She'd say What's your sister like
Velma Kelly : I'd say Men
Velma Kelly : She'd say You're the cat's meow Then we'd wow the crowd again When she'd go
Velma Kelly : I'd go
Velma Kelly : We'd go
Velma Kelly : Then those dingdong daddies Started to roar
Velma Kelly : Whistled stomped Stamped on the floor
Velma Kelly : Yelling screaming Begging for more And we'd say Okay fellas keep your socks up
Velma Kelly : cause you ain't seen nothin yet
Velma Kelly : But I simply cannot do it
Velma Kelly : Alone
Velma Kelly : So what do you think huh
Velma Kelly : Come on you can say
Velma Kelly : I know You're right The first part's shit
Velma Kelly : But the second part the second part is really nifty
Velma Kelly : Okay
Velma Kelly : She'd go
Velma Kelly : I'd go
Velma Kelly : We'd go
Velma Kelly : And then those twobit Johnnies Did it up brown
Velma Kelly : To cheer the best attraction in town
Velma Kelly : They nearly tore the balcony down And we'd say Okay boys we're going home
Velma Kelly : But before we go here's a few more partin shots
Velma Kelly : And this this we did in perfect unison
Velma Kelly : Now you've seen me going through it
Velma Kelly : You may think there's nothing to it
Velma Kelly : But I simply cannot do it
Velma Kelly : Alone
Roxie Hart : So where was the part where you blew her brains out
Velma Kelly : Okay Roxie I'll level with you
Roxie Hart : Oh no no no Don't bother
Roxie Hart : You think you're fooling me
Roxie Hart : You're all washed up and it's me they want now
Roxie Hart : And I'm a big star
Roxie Hart : Single
Roxie Hart : Oh I almost forgot You were in the paper today too
Roxie Hart : In the back with the obituaries
Roxie Hart : Velma Kelly's trial has been postponed indefinitely
Roxie Hart : Seven words Wow
Roxie Hart : Oh And here's a little piece of advice
Roxie Hart : Direct from me to you
Roxie Hart : Lay off the caramels
Narrator : And now for all you Chicago stayuplaters You night owls who only come alive after dark
Narrator : We dedicate this tune
Narrator : Chicago After Midnight
Billy Flynn : This all took place on Lakeshore Drive
Billy Flynn : Incredible Incredible
Billy Flynn : All right Yeah Thanks Tom
Billy Flynn : Oh God They just arrested this woman for a triple homicide
Man1 : Really
Billy Flynn : Yeah And get this She's an heiress
Women : What
Billy Flynn : Yeah All the family's in
Billy Flynn : pineapples grapefruits Some kind of fruit I don't know
Billy Flynn : So anyhow this dame Kitty what'shername something
Billy Flynn : she's playing house on the North Side
Billy Flynn : in an apartment with a guy named Harry
Billy Flynn : What Harry does for a living no one's quite sure but it doesn't really matter because she's footing all the bills
Billy Flynn : Anyhow Kitty comes home tonight
Billy Flynn : Harry's already in bed which is par for the course for Harry
Billy Flynn : She goes to change When she returns
Billy Flynn : she notices something rather odd
Billy Flynn : Extremely odd
Billy Flynn : Kitty disappears for a second Cool as a cucumber
Billy Flynn : When she returns she gently wakes up Harry
Billy Flynn : Harry says What I'm alone
Billy Flynn : She says Alone You got two other women in bed with you
Billy Flynn : So get this Harry says Come on doll
Billy Flynn : You gonna believe what you see or what I tell you
Narrator : Good night folks
Reporters : Give us the line
Mary Sunshine : Miss Sunshine from the Evening Star
Mary Sunshine : I wonder if you wouldn't mind saying a word or two
Kitty Baxter : Sure I'll say three Go to hell
Billy Flynn : Please direct your questions to her counsel
Kitty Baxter : You're not my counsel and I want my money back
Billy Flynn : It's not your money It's your mother's money
Mary Sunshine : Are you sorry dear
Kitty Baxter : Sure I'm sorry
Kitty Baxter : Sorry I got caught
Roxie Hart : Hey Miss Sunshine
Mary Sunshine : Not now Roxie
Roxie Hart : I got a letter from a guy He says he's going on a hunger strike until I'm freed
Mary Sunshine : That's nice dear
Reporter : Miss Baxter please Miss Baxter did you know these two ladies personally
Kitty Baxter : Did I know these two ladies personally Was that your question
Reporter2 : Yeah that's my que
Matron Mama Morton : She's very highspirited isn't she
Mary Sunshine : Miss Baxter
Roxie Hart : Hey Mr Flynn
Roxie Hart : Mr Flynn
Billy Flynn : Yeah hi Trixie
Roxie Hart : It's Roxie
Billy Flynn : Yeah sure I was just kidding
Roxie Hart : Hey did you get my trial date yet
Billy Flynn : Listen kid
Roxie Hart : Yeah I'm at the top
of your list right
Kitty Baxter : Go to hell
Billy Flynn : Boy what a hellion huh
Billy Flynn : She's a socialite too
Billy Flynn : Her mother owns all the pineapples in Hawaii
Roxie Hart : What the hell do I care about pineapples
Billy Flynn : All right All right
Roxie Hart : Hey Hey hey hey
Billy Flynn : Miss Baxter will answer all of your questions And afterwards I'll be happy to give you an interview myself
Reporter : Billy
Man Ensemble : Roxie
Velma Kelly : How's it feel kid
Velma Kelly : J Edgar Hoover couldn't find your name in the papers
Roxie Hart : Mr Flynn
Billy Flynn : Someone open this door immediately
Mary Sunshine : Oh my God Roxie What is it dear
Roxie Hart : Oh oh Oh no no no Don't worry about me
Roxie Hart : Oh I only hope the fall didn't hurt the baby
Matron Mama Morton : Baby
Velma Kelly : Shit
Mary Sunshine : What
Mary Sunshine : Roxie when did this happen darling
Billy Flynn : Well doc is she or isn't she
Doctor : She is
Billy Flynn : Would you swear to that statement in court
Doctor : Yes
Billy Flynn : Good
Billy Flynn : Button your fly
Roxie Hart : I would I would just like to say that
Roxie Hart : Well my own life doesn't matter now just that of my unborn child
Mary Sunshine : You poor dear to have your baby born in jail
Mary Sunshine : My readers won't stand for it
Reporter : I can assure you that won't happen
Billy Flynn : She'll come to trial at the earliest possible moment Please quote me on that
Matron Mama Morton : Well I think it's sweet
Matron Mama Morton : First time we ever had one of our girls knocked up
Reporter : When is the baby due
Amos Hart : Roxie Roxie Hey Roxie Roxie
Amos Hart : Roxie I just heard the good news
Amos Hart : I'm the father I'm the father
Reporter2 : Roxie who's the father
Billy Flynn : That question is completely out of line
Billy Flynn : How dare you insult this brave young woman
Billy Flynn : That's enough we're out of here
Amos Hart : Roxie Roxie honey
Amos Hart : It's me Daddy It's Daddy
Amos Hart : Roxie I came as soon as I could
Amos Hart : Rox
Amos Hart : If someone stood up in a crowd
Amos Hart : And raised his voice up way out loud
Amos Hart : And waved his arm And shook his leg
Amos Hart : You'd notice him
Amos Hart : If someone in the movie show
Amos Hart : Yelled Fire in the second row
Amos Hart : This whole place is a powder keg
Amos Hart : You'd notice him
Amos Hart : And even without clucking like a hen
Amos Hart : Everyone gets noticed now and then
Amos Hart : Unless of course That personage should be
Amos Hart : Invisible
Amos Hart : Inconsequential
Amos Hart : Me
Amos Hart : Cellophane Mister Cellophane
Amos Hart : Shoulda been my name Mister Cellophane
Amos Hart : Cause you can look right through me
Amos Hart : Walk right by me
Amos Hart : And never know I'm there
Amos Hart : I tell ya
Amos Hart : Cellophane Mister Cellophane
Amos Hart : Shoulda been my name Mister Cellophane
Amos Hart : Cause you can look right through me
Amos Hart : Walk right by me
Amos Hart : And never know I'm there
Billy Flynn : Oh I didn't see you Sit down Sit down Sit down
Billy Flynn : Look Andy I'm afraid I got to hit you hard
Billy Flynn : And I can only hope that you'll be big about it
Amos Hart : Amos My name is Amos
Billy Flynn : Who said it wasn't
Billy Flynn : It was the kid The kid s name I was thinking about yeah
Billy Flynn : You know when she's due September
Billy Flynn : Now but But pass out those cigars anyway I don't want you to give a damn when people
Amos Hart : People what
Billy Flynn : Laugh
Amos Hart : Laugh Why would they laugh
Billy Flynn : Cause they can count
Billy Flynn : Can you count September
Billy Flynn : Here's a copy of Roxie's first statement from the D. A. s office
Billy Flynn : It says she hadn't copulated with you for four months prior to the incident
Amos Hart : Well she would know
Amos Hart : Yeah I guess we hadn't done no copulating since
Amos Hart : Wait a minute That don't figure out right I
Amos Hart : I couldn't be the father
Billy Flynn : Well forget about that now My client needs your support
Amos Hart : You mean she needs a meal ticket
Amos Hart : That's all I ever been But this time she's gone too far
Billy Flynn : What are you gonna do
Billy Flynn : Divorce her
Amos Hart : You're damn right
Amos Hart : I'll divorce her
Amos Hart : She probably won't even notice
Billy Flynn : Yeah Yeah put him through
Amos Hart : A human being's made of more than air
Amos Hart : With all that bulk You're bound to see him there
Amos Hart : Unless that human being next to you
Amos Hart : Is unimpressive
Amos Hart : Undistinguished
Amos Hart : You
Amos Hart : Know
Amos Hart : Who
Billy Flynn : You still here Andy
Amos Hart : Yeah I'm still here
Amos Hart : I think
Amos Hart : Shoulda been my name
Amos Hart : Mister Cellophane
Amos Hart : Cause you can look right through me
Amos Hart : Walk right by me
Amos Hart : And never know I'm there
Amos Hart : I tell you
Amos Hart : Cellophane Mister Cellophane
Amos Hart : Shoulda been my name Mister Cellophane
Amos Hart : Cause you can look right through me
Amos Hart : Walk right by me
Amos Hart : And never know I'm there
Amos Hart : Never even
Amos Hart : Know
Amos Hart : I'm there
Amos Hart : I hope I didn't take up too much of your time
Billy Flynn : I've been waiting here for ten minutes Don't do that again
Roxie Hart : This dress makes me look like a Woolworth's lampshade I'm not wearing this
Billy Flynn : You're wearing it cause I tell you to wear it
Roxie Hart : I'm not wearing this dress
Billy Flynn : And when Andy's on the stand I want you to be knitting
Roxie Hart : Knitting
Roxie Hart : For Christ's sake
Billy Flynn : A baby garment
Roxie Hart : I don't know how to knit
Billy Flynn : Then learn
Roxie Hart : That is no way to win a jury's sympathy
Billy Flynn : You don't need advice anymore
Roxie Hart : Lookit here Mr Mouthpiece
Roxie Hart : it seems to me I am the one who's coming up with the good ideas
Roxie Hart : I am sick of everybody telling me what to do You treat me like dirt
Roxie Hart : You know that You treat me like I'm some dumb common criminal
Billy Flynn : But you are some dumb common criminal
Roxie Hart : Well it's better than being a greasy Mick lawyer
Billy Flynn : Who happens to be saving your ass
Roxie Hart : Who's out for all he can steal
Billy Flynn : Maybe you'd like to appear in court without me
Roxie Hart : Well maybe I could Have you read the morning papers
Roxie Hart : They love me
Billy Flynn : Wise up
Billy Flynn : They'd love you a lot more if you were hanged You know why Cause they'd sell more papers
Roxie Hart : You're fired
Billy Flynn : I quit
Roxie Hart : Any lawyer in this town would die to have my case
Billy Flynn : You are a phony celebrity You're a flash in the pan In a couple of weeks no one's gonna give a shit about you
Billy Flynn : That's Chicago
Hunyak : No No no Not guilty
Roxie Hart : What happened It's the Hunyak
Velma Kelly : She lost her last appeal
Roxie Hart : So what's that mean
Velma Kelly : Well that means that next week she's gonna
Mary Sunshine : This is Mary Sunshine coming to you from the Cook County Jail
Mary Sunshine : where history will be made today
Mary Sunshine : Katalin Helinski will become the first woman in the state of Illinois to be executed
Mary Sunshine : And so ladies and gentlemen
Narrator : And now ladies and gentlemen for your pleasure and your entertainment
Narrator : we proudly present Katalin Helinski and her famous Hungarian disappearing act
Roxie Hart : You know it's really not that bad
Billy Flynn : You clear about everything we agreed on
Roxie Hart : Yep I've been up all night rehearsing
Billy Flynn : What do you do when Harrison starts coming after you
Roxie Hart : I sit still and look straight ahead never at the jury
Billy Flynn : And And I look modest
Billy Flynn : And
Roxie Hart : And
Billy Flynn : And say nothing
Roxie Hart : That's right
Billy Flynn : That was the deal right
Roxie Hart : Right
Billy Flynn : Right You asked me back I do all the talking this time
Roxie Hart : Absolutely Billy Whatever you say
Man2 : Mr Flynn His Honor's here
Billy Flynn : Thank you
Billy Flynn : You ready
Roxie Hart : Yeah
Roxie Hart : Billy
Billy Flynn : Hm
Roxie Hart : I'm scared
Billy Flynn : Nah don't be I've been around a long time Believe me You got nothing to worry about
Billy Flynn : It's all a circus
Billy Flynn : A threering circus
Billy Flynn : These trials the whole world
Billy Flynn : It's all just show business
Billy Flynn : But kid
Billy Flynn : you're working with a star
Billy Flynn : Give em the old razzle dazzle
Billy Flynn : Razzle dazzle em
Billy Flynn : Give em an act With lots of flash in it
Billy Flynn : And the reaction will be passionate
Billy Flynn : Give em the old hocus pocus
Billy Flynn : Bead and feather em
Billy Flynn : How can they see With sequins in their eyes
Billy Flynn : What if your hinges all are rusting
Billy Flynn : What if in fact You're just disgusting
Billy Flynn : Razzle dazzle em
Billy Flynn : And they'll never catch wise
Billy Flynn : Give em the old razzle dazzle
Billy Flynn : Razzle dazzle em
Billy Flynn : Give em a show That's so splendiferous
Billy Flynn : Row after row will grow vociferous
Billy Flynn : Give em the old flimflam flummox
Billy Flynn : Fool and fracture em
Billy Flynn : How can they hear the truth Above the roar
Woman Ensemble : Roar roar roar
Billy Flynn : Throw em a fake and a finagle
Billy Flynn : They'll never know you're just a bagel
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : Razzle dazzle em
Billy Flynn : And they'll beg you for more
Billy Flynn : I object
Jury : Sustained
Martin Harrison : Your Honor I haven't even asked the question yet
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : Give em the old double whammy
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : Daze and dizzy em
Billy Flynn : Back since the days of old Methuselah
Billy Flynn : Everyone loves the big bamboozler
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : Give em the old threering circus
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : Stun and stagger em
Billy Flynn : When you're in trouble Go into your dance
Billy Flynn : Though you are stiffer than a girder
Billy Flynn : They'll let you get away
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : With murder
Billy Flynn : Razzle dazzle em
Billy Flynn : And you got a romance
Billy Flynn : Hello Amos
Amos Hart : Amos That's right Mr Flynn, Amos
Billy Flynn : Amos
Billy Flynn : When did you file suit for divorce
Amos Hart : A month ago
Billy Flynn : Was there any reason for filing it at this particular time
Amos Hart : I'll say
Amos Hart : The newspapers said Roxie was expecting a little stranger
Billy Flynn : Well That's hardly grounds for divorce isnt it
Amos Hart : A little too much of a stranger
Billy Flynn : Oh
Billy Flynn : By that you mean you doubted the paternity of the child
Amos Hart : Well sure
Billy Flynn : Tell me something Amos
Billy Flynn : You share a bed with your wife
Amos Hart : Yes sir every night
Billy Flynn : And you expect this jury to believe that you slept  next to this woman every night without exercising your rights as a husband
Amos Hart : Well I could've if I wanted to
Billy Flynn : Oh but you didn't
Amos Hart : No I did
Billy Flynn : Did what
Amos Hart : Want to
Billy Flynn : But you didn't
Amos Hart : Didn't what
Billy Flynn : What you wanted
Amos Hart : Wait a minute I'm getting confused here
Billy Flynn : Now you tell me did you ever question Roxie herself Did you even bother to ask her if you were the father of her child
Amos Hart : No sir
Billy Flynn : No No But if you became convinced that you were wrong you'd be man enough to admit it wouldn't you
Billy Flynn : You'd even be willing to take her back if Roxie swore that you were the father of her child Which she does
Amos Hart : She does
Billy Flynn : She does She does
Billy Flynn : No more questions You can step down now
Billy Flynn : Well done Andy
Amos Hart : Roxie I'm so sorry
Billy Flynn : Give em the old razzle dazzle
Billy Flynn : Razzle dazzle em
Billy Flynn : Show em the firstrate sorcerer You are
Billy Flynn : Long as you keep em way off balance
Billy Flynn : How can they spot You got no talents
Billy Flynn : Razzle dazzle em
Woman Ensemble : Razzle dazzle em
Narrator2 : This is the moment we've been waiting for
Narrator2 : Roxie Hart finally takes the stand in her own defense
Billy Flynn;Woman Ensemble : And they'll make you a star
Jury : Order Order Order
Jury : Proceed Mr Flynn
Billy Flynn : Roxie I have here a statement in which you admit to having
Billy Flynn : illicit relations with the deceased Fred Casely Is this statement true or false
Roxie Hart : I'm afraid that's true
Billy Flynn : You're an honest girl Roxie
Billy Flynn : When did you first meet Fred Casely
Roxie Hart : When he sold Amos and me our furniture
Billy Flynn : Your personal relationship with him
Billy Flynn : could you tell the jury when that began
Roxie Hart : When I permitted him to escort me home one night
Roxie Hart : I don't think I would've gone with him if Mr Hart and me hadn't quarreled that very morning
Billy Flynn : Quarreled
Roxie Hart : Yes sir
Billy Flynn : Well I suppose it was his fault
Roxie Hart : Oh no sir It was my fault
Roxie Hart : I suppose I just couldn't stop pestering him
Billy Flynn : Pestering him About what
Roxie Hart : I didn't like him working those long hours at the garage I wanted him home with me
Roxie Hart : to darn his socks and iron his shirts
Roxie Hart : I wanted a real home and a child
Billy Flynn : So you drifted into this illicit relationship because you were unhappy at home
Roxie Hart : Yes
Roxie Hart : I was most unhappy
Billy Flynn : Roxie Hart
Billy Flynn : The state has accused you of the murder of Fred Casely
Billy Flynn : Are you guilty or not guilty
Roxie Hart : I'm not guilty
Roxie Hart : I'm not guilty I killed him I did but I'm not a criminal
Roxie Hart : I'm not a criminal
Billy Flynn : There
Billy Flynn : Roxie
Roxie Hart : Uhhuh
Billy Flynn : Yeah
Billy Flynn : Do you recall the night of January 14
Roxie Hart : Uhhuh
Billy Flynn : Could you tell the jury in your own words the happenings of that night
Roxie Hart : Well when Fred came over I told him my good news
Billy Flynn : And what was that
Roxie Hart : That me and Amos were gonna have a baby
Roxie Hart : And that it was all over between us
Billy Flynn : What happened then
Roxie Hart : Well then
Roxie Hart : um
Roxie Hart : Then
Billy Flynn : Did he threaten you Roxie
Martin Harrison : Objection Your Honor Counsel is leading the witness
Jury : Sustained
Billy Flynn : What did Casely say when you told him the news
Roxie Hart : I'll kill you before I'll see you have another man's child
Billy Flynn : Could you tell the audience the jury what happened next
Roxie Hart : Well in his passion he tore off my robe and he threw me on the bed
Roxie Hart : And Mr Hart's pistol was lying there between us
Billy Flynn : And then?
Roxie Hart : And then we both reached for the gun but I got it first
Roxie Hart : And then he came toward me with this funny
look in his eyes He was angry and wild
Billy Flynn : Wild
Roxie Hart : Wild
Billy Flynn : Did you think he meant to kill you
Roxie Hart : Oh yes sir Yes sir
Billy Flynn : So it was his life or yours
Roxie Hart : And not just mine
Roxie Hart : I closed my eyes and I shot
Billy Flynn : In defense of your life
Roxie Hart : To save my husband's innocent unborn child
Billy Flynn : Roxie
Jury : Order
Roxie Hart : What a bull'seye huh
Jury : Order in this court
Amos Hart : Roxie
Jury : I'll clear this court if necessary
Mary Sunshine : There's pandemonium here in the courtroom
Jury : Order
Jury : Bailiff
Mary Sunshine : Mrs Hart's behavior throughout this ordeal has been truly extraordinary
Velma Kelly : Yeah I bet it has
Mary Sunshine : Opening her eyes she fans herself with her attorney's handkerchief
Velma Kelly : Handkerchief
Mary Sunshine : Poor child has had no relief
Mary Sunshine : She looks around now bewildered seeming to want something
Mary Sunshine : Oh it's a glass of water
Velma Kelly : Mama that was my bit I told Billy I was gonna do that at my trial
Mary Sunshine : But now her eyes flutter wildly and she
Mary Sunshine : Mrs Hart has fainted again
Velma Kelly : Oh jeez
Mary Sunshine : She slumps over her chiffon dress up around her knees
Mary Sunshine : revealing a glimpse of a blue garter with a rhinestone buckle
Velma Kelly : Mama she stole my garter
Velma Kelly : She stole my garter
Matron Mama Morton : Don't break my radio
Velma Kelly : God First the slob steals my publicity Then she steals my lawyer my trial date Now she stole my goddamn garter
Matron Mama Morton : What do you expect
Matron Mama Morton : I mean these days you get a little success
Matron Mama Morton : and it's good riddance to the people who put you there
Velma Kelly : There ain't no justice in the world
Velma Kelly : And there ain't nothing you can do about it
Matron Mama Morton : Nerts to that You think I got you up here just so you can listen to my radio
Matron Mama Morton : People write some pretty interesting things when they think no one's looking
Velma Kelly : Oh Mama
Martin Harrison : Ooh The state calls a rebuttal witness
Martin Harrison : Left hand on the Bible raise your right hand You swear to tell the truth the whole truth nothing but the truth so help you God
Velma Kelly : And then some
Martin Harrison : Have a seat
Martin Harrison : Would you state your name for the record please
Velma Kelly : Velma Kelly
Martin Harrison : Miss Kelly
Martin Harrison : will you please tell the court if the object I am holding is the one you happened to come upon in the defendant's jail cell Yes it is
Martin Harrison : I submit this as Exhibit X
Martin Harrison : Roxie Hart's diary
Billy Flynn : I object
Billy Flynn : My client has never kept a diary And even if she did
Billy Flynn : this would be invasion of privacy in violation of the Fourth Amendment
Billy Flynn : and illegal search without a warrant
Roxie Hart : Yeah And she broke the lock
Jury : Order Order
Jury : Well that settles that I'll allow it
Roxie Hart : What's the big deal It's just a bunch of doodlings
Billy Flynn : Shh
Martin Harrison : If you would read for us please Miss Kelly
Velma Kelly : I haven't worked in a while
Velma Kelly : What a laugh plugging Fred Casely
Velma Kelly : What The big baboon had it coming
Velma Kelly : I'm just sorry I only got to kill him once
Roxie Hart : I never wrote that You Hey she made that up
Jury : Order
Roxie Hart : She made that up She made that up
Jury : Please Mr Flynn get control of your client
Billy Flynn : I'm sorry Your Honor It won't happen again
Billy Flynn : Sit down Shut up It's only making it worse
Martin Harrison : I have no more questions
Jury : Your witness Mr Flynn
Narrator : Ladies and gentlemen a tap dance
Billy Flynn : Tell me Miss Kelly did you make a deal with Mr Harrison
Billy Flynn : Maybe to drop all charges against you in exchange for testifying here today
Velma Kelly : Well sure I'm not a complete idiot
Billy Flynn : Good Good
Billy Flynn : Since you gave such an impressive performance for Mr Harrison
Billy Flynn : maybe you'd do me the same honor
Velma Kelly : I'd be delighted Thank you
Velma Kelly : Fred Casely assured me he'd get me an audition down at the Onyx
Velma Kelly : Then he reneged on his pledge and that was my motive for attacking him
Billy Flynn : Pretty fancy way of saying He's a big fat liar who welshed on a deal so I shot him
Billy Flynn : Amos accused me of having an affair
Billy Flynn : so I told him that the charge was erroneous
Martin Harrison : Objection Your Honor
Martin Harrison : Mr Flynn is twisting this evidence to draw conclusions that are specious and
Billy Flynn : Erroneous
Martin Harrison : Exactly
Jury : Order Order
Billy Flynn : Miss Kelly do you know the meaning of the word perjury
Velma Kelly : Yes I do
Billy Flynn : You also know that it's a crime
Velma Kelly : Yes
Billy Flynn : I mean for example if it turns out that you knew that this diary was a fake
Billy Flynn : I'd hate to think of you rotting in prison for the next ten years especially since you just won your freedom
Velma Kelly : Look all I know is what I was told
Billy Flynn : Oh So All right
Billy Flynn : So you didn't find this diary in Roxie's cell
Velma Kelly : No
Velma Kelly : Mama Miss Morton gave it to me She said someone sent it to her
Billy Flynn : Someone Any idea who this mysterious benefactor might be
Velma Kelly : No She didn't know
Billy Flynn : All right let's see if we can work this out
Billy Flynn : Someone who writes about reneging on pledges and erroneous charges
Billy Flynn : Call me crazy Doesn't that sound like a lawyer to you? A lawyer!
Billy Flynn : A lawyer who obviously had a sample of my client's handwriting
Billy Flynn : Mr Harrison didn't you ask Roxie to write out a confession for you
Martin Harrison : Yes But you're not suggesting I tampered with evidence are you
Billy Flynn : No no no no no I wouldn't Don't be ridiculous No
Billy Flynn : That's thoroughly and utterly absurd
Billy Flynn : But now that you mention it
Martin Harrison : Your Honor this is outrageous
Billy Flynn : It's outrageous I know I agree To even suggest that the prosecutor would make a thieves bargain with the notorious Velma Kelly
Billy Flynn : and then fabricate the very evidence that set her free just so you can win another case Your Honor and move one step closer to the Governor's Mansion
Billy Flynn : Why it's simply beyond all imagining
Jury : I'll hold you in contempt
Billy Flynn : No it is not even conceivable
Billy Flynn : But if it were wouldn't it be time to say
Billy Flynn : Come clean Mr Harrison Come clean
Billy Flynn : Even in Chicago this kind of corruption cannot stand
Billy Flynn : Will not stand
Jury : That's enough Mr Flynn
Billy Flynn : I agree Your Honor It is enough
Billy Flynn : The defense rests
Mary Sunshine : Ladies and gentlemen this is Mary Sunshine reporting live from the Cook County Courthouse
Mary Sunshine : The city of Chicago has come to a complete standstill
Mary Sunshine : as the trial of the century finally draws to a close
Mary Sunshine : Mrs Hart sits quietly at the defense table hands folded
Mary Sunshine : wondering what fate has in store for her
Mary Sunshine : And now a hush falls over the courtroom as the 12 men of the jury file slowly back to their seats
Jury : Gentlemen of the jury have you reached a verdict
Gentleman of the Jury : We have Your Honor
Mary Sunshine : The jury has reached a verdict
Jury : Will the defendant please rise
Jury : What is your verdict
Gentleman of the Jury : We the jury find the defendant
Paper boy : Roxie Hart is innocent She's innocent  Get your paper Roxie Hart is free She's free
Reporter : Come on Move it!
Reporter2 : First she shoots the husband then she plugs the lawyer
Roxie Hart : Hey Hey Don't you want to take my picture
Roxie Hart : Hey I'm the famous Roxie Hart
Roxie Hart : Hey what happened
Billy Flynn : Billy what the hell happened
Billy Flynn : This is Chicago kid You can't beat fresh blood on the walls
Roxie Hart : But my publicity Billy My name in the papers
Roxie Hart : I was counting on that
Billy Flynn : Your gratitude is overwhelming kid
Billy Flynn : I just
saved your life
Roxie Hart : Yeah and you got 5000 And what do I get I get nothing
Billy Flynn : Five Actually it's ten once I collect from Velma
Roxie Hart : I get nothing
Billy Flynn : Alright Don't forget your blessed diary
Billy Flynn : Hope you don't mind I added a few erroneous phrases in there
Billy Flynn : Sorry I couldn't tell you
Billy Flynn : Couldn't take a chance
Billy Flynn : I never lost a case
Billy Flynn : You're a free woman Roxie Hart
Billy Flynn : And God save Illinois
Amos Hart : Roxie
Roxie Hart : What do you want
Amos Hart : I want you to come home
Amos Hart : You said you still wanted to
Amos Hart : And the baby
Roxie Hart : Baby What baby
Roxie Hart : Oh Jesus
Roxie Hart : What do you take me for
Roxie Hart : There ain't no baby
Amos Hart : There ain't no baby
Roxie Hart : They didn't even want my picture
Roxie Hart : I just I can't understand that
Roxie Hart : Why didn't they even want my picture
Roxie Hart : It's good
Roxie Hart : Isn't it grand
Roxie Hart : Isn't it great
Roxie Hart : Isn't it swell
Roxie Hart : Isn't it fun Isn't it
Roxie Hart : Nowadays
Narrator : Ladies and gentlemen
Narrator : Miss Roxie Hart says Good night
Roxie Hart : There's men everywhere
Roxie Hart : Jazz everywhere Booze everywhere
Roxie Hart : Life everywhere
Roxie Hart : Joy everywhere
Roxie Hart : Nowadays
Roxie Hart : You can like the life you're livin
Roxie Hart : You can live the life you like
Roxie Hart : You can even marry Harry
Roxie Hart : But mess around with Ike
Roxie Hart : And that's good
Roxie Hart : Isn't it grand
Roxie Hart : Isn't it great
Roxie Hart : Isn't it swell Isn't it fun Isn't it
Roxie Hart : But nothing
Roxie Hart : Stays
Roxie Hart : You can like the life you're living
Roxie Hart : You can live the life you like
Roxie Hart;Producer1 : Didn't she kill a guy a while back
Producer2 : Eh who can keep them straight anymore
Roxie Hart : But mess around with Ike
Roxie Hart : And that's good
Roxie Hart : Isn't it grand
Roxie Hart : Isn't it great
Roxie Hart : Isn't it swell
Producer2 : That's great
Producer2 : We'll be in touch
Roxie Hart : You know I'm not quite finished yet I have uh I have
Roxie Hart : Wait wait wait One more
Roxie Hart : Um I could
Roxie Hart : Just a second I'm not
Roxie Hart : Goddamnit
Roxie Hart : Thank you
Piano Player : Here's the music hon
Roxie Hart : Thanks
Roxie Hart : Goddamnit
Velma Kelly : You know you're really pretty good
Roxie Hart : Yeah that and a dime
Roxie Hart : What are you doing here
Velma Kelly : I heard you been making the rounds
Roxie Hart : Yeah well if it was up to you I'd be swinging by now
Velma Kelly : Come on I always knew Billy would get you off
Velma Kelly : You should learn how to put things behind you
Roxie Hart : Thank you I'll put that at the top of my list
Roxie Hart : Right after finding a job and an apartment with a john
Velma Kelly : Just shut up and listen to me
Roxie Hart : You really are something
Roxie Hart : Coming in here like some goddamn queen bee
Roxie Hart : All full of advice for a poor slob like me
Roxie Hart : Let me tell you something Miss Velma Kelly
Roxie Hart : I got a new life now
Roxie Hart : And one of the best things about it is it don't include you
Velma Kelly : Fine I just thought we could help each other out
Roxie Hart : You thought wrong didn't you
Velma Kelly : Listen to me
Velma Kelly : Look I talked to this guy downtown
Velma Kelly : He said one jazz killer is nothing these days
Velma Kelly : But two
Velma Kelly : We could make a couple of hundred a week
Velma Kelly : Think about it Roxie
Velma Kelly : Our faces back in the papers Our names on the marquee
Velma Kelly : Velma Kelly and Roxie Hart
Roxie Hart : Shouldn't it be alphabetical
Velma Kelly : That could work
Roxie Hart : Couple hundred Maybe we could ask for a thou
Velma Kelly : We're worth it
Roxie Hart : Forget it
Roxie Hart : It'll never work
Velma Kelly : Why not
Roxie Hart : Cause I hate you
Velma Kelly : There's only one business in the world where that's no problem at all
Narrator : Ladies and gentlemen the Chicago Theater  is proud to announce a first
Narrator : The first time anywhere there's been an act of this nature
Narrator : Not only one little lady But two
Narrator : You've read about them in the papers
Narrator : And now here they are
Narrator : Chicago's own killerdillers Those scintillating sinners
Narrator : Roxie Hart and Velma Kelly
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : You can like the life you're livin
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : You can live the life you like
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : You can even marry Harry
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : But mess around with Ike
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : And that's good
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : Isn't it grand
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : Isn't it great
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : Isn't it swell
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : Isn't it fun Isn't it
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : But nothing stays
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : In 50 years or so
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : It's gonna change you know
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : But oh it's heaven
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : Nowadays
Narrator : Okay you babes of jazz let's pick up the pace
Narrator : Let's make the parties longer let's make the skirts shorter
Narrator : Let's all go to hell in a fast car and keep it hot
Matron Mama Morton : Yeah
Velma Kelly : Me and Roxie we'd just like to say thank you
Roxie Hart : Thank you
Roxie Hart : Believe us we could not have done it without you
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : And all
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : That
Velma Kelly;Roxie Hart : Jazz
Roxie Hart : That jazz
Narrator : Five six seven eight