Elsa : Okay, okay, here we go.
Elsa : So lonely.
Elsa : Stiff.
Elsa : I can't do that.
Elsa : Come on, Elsa. Elsa : This is for Anna. You can do this.
Kristoff : Relax! Kristoff : It looks great!
Elsa : I just want it to be perfect.
Kristoff : Speaking of "perfect..."
Kristoff : Check this out.
Kristoff, are you sure I can leave you in charge here?
Absolutely.
Elsa : Because I don't want anything to happen to this courtyard.
Kristoff : What could happen?
Kristoff : It's all set.
Elsa : Olaf, what are you doing?
Olaf : I'm not eating cake.
Elsa : Olaf...
Olaf : But it's an ice cream cake.
Elsa : And it's for Anna.
Olaf : And it's for Anna.
Elsa : Oh, it's time!
Olaf : It's time!
Olaf : For what?
Elsa : Okay, you sure you got this?
Kristoff : I'm sure.
Elsa : Don't let anyone in before we're ready.
Kristoff : I won't.
Elsa : And don't touch anything.
Kristoff : I'm just gonna stand here.
Olaf : I'm probably gonna walk around a little.
Elsa : And keep an eye on that cake!
Sven : She thinks you're an idiot.
Kristoff : Well, clearly she's wrong.
Kristoff : Ooh! Ooh! Whoops. Whoa.
Kristoff : What? It's fine.
Olaf : I can't read. Olaf : Or spell.
Elsa : Psst. Anna?
Anna : Yeah?
Elsa : Happy birthday.
Anna : ...to you
Elsa : It's your birthday.
Anna : ...to me
Anna : It's my birthday.
Elsa : Come on!
Anna : It's my birthday?
Elsa : Mmm-hmm.
Elsa : And it's going to be perfect because...
Elsa : You've never had a real birthday before
Elsa : Except of course the ones you spent Outside my locked door
Elsa : So I'm here way too late to help you celebrate
Elsa : And be your birthday date
Elsa : If I may
Anna : Elsa, I'm thinkin' ya might have a cold
Elsa : I don't get colds. Besides...
Elsa : A cold never bothered me anyway
Anna : Whoa.
Anna : Fancy.
Elsa : Just follow the string.
Anna : Wait, what?
Elsa : I've got big plans I've got surprises for today
Elsa : Nothin' but nothin's gonna get in our way
Elsa : I've worked for weeks
Elsa : Planned everything within my power
Elsa : I even got Kristoff and Sven to take a shower
Elsa : If someone wants to hold me back
Elsa : I'd like to see them try
Olaf : Summer!
Elsa : I'm on the birthday plan attack
Elsa : I'm givin' you the sun the moon, and the sky
Olaf : Little brothers!
Elsa : I'm makin' today a perfect day for you
Anna : Ooh, sandwich.
Elsa : I'm makin' today a blast If it's the last thing I do
Elsa : For everything you are to me And all you've been through
Elsa : I'm makin' today... A perfect day for you
Anna : They come in threes.
Elsa : I'm fine.
Kristoff : Hey!
Elsa : Surprise, surprise this one is specially...
Anna : Wow, you've got me reeling But I'm still concerned for you
Anna : I think it's time that you go home and get some rest
Elsa : We are not stopping 'Cause the next one is the be...
Elsa : Ah-ah...
Elsa : Achoo!
Anna : Elsa, you gotta go lie down
Elsa : No way, we have to paint the town
Anna : But you need medical attention
Oaken : Are you sick? How about a cold remedy...
Oaken : Of my own invention?
Elsa : No, thanks.
Anna : We'll take it.
Children : We're making today a perfect day for you
Elsa : We're making today a special day
Children : We're singing a birthday song... To make your wishes come true
Elsa : Wishes come true
Elsa : And I love you too
Children : So we're making today a perfect day
Children : A fabulous day in every way
Children : Yes, we are making today a perfect day
Olaf : I can fix it.
Kristoff : No, no!
Olaf : All fixed.
Olaf : "Dry Banana Hippy Hat"?
Elsa : Come on. Now we climb!
Anna : Elsa, that's too much. You need to rest.
Elsa : We need to get to our birthday chills.
Elsa : I mean thrills.
Elsa : Making dreams!
Elsa : Making plans!
Elsa : Go, go, go, go!
Anna : Follow the string to the end You are my very best friend
Anna : Elsa?
Elsa : What? I'm fine
Elsa : We're gonna climb
Elsa : We're gonna sing
Elsa : Follow the string
Elsa : To the thing
Elsa : Happy, happy, happy
Elsa : Merry, merry, merry...
Elsa : Hot, cold...
Elsa : Hot birthday
Anna : Elsa, look at you, you've got a fever.
Anna : -You're burning up.
Anna : All right we can't go on like this
Anna : Let's put this day on hold
Anna : Come on admit it to yourself
Elsa : Okay...
Elsa : I have a cold
Elsa : I'm sorry, Anna.
Elsa : I just wanted to give you one perfect birthday.
Elsa : But I ruined it. Again.
Anna : You didn't ruin anything.
Anna : Let's just get you to bed.
Kristoff : Oh, no, please, please stop!
All : Surprise!
Anna : Wow!
Elsa : Wow.
All : We're making today a perfect day...
Olaf : For you
All : We're making today a smiley face All shiny and new
Kristoff : There's a fine line between chaos
Olaf : And a hullabaloo
All : So we're makin' today a perfect day
All : Makin' today a perfect day
All : A-N-N-A!
All : Makin' today a perfect day for you
Kristoff : Happy birthday.
All : Makin' today a happy day
All : And no feelin' blue
Kristoff : I love you, baby!
All : For everything you are to us...
All : And all that you do
Kristoff : I do.
All : We're makin' today a perfect day
All : Makin' today a perfect day
Elsa : A perfect day!
Anna : Okay, to bed with you.
Elsa : No, wait. Wait. Anna: Oh!
Elsa : All that's left to do is for the Queen to blow the birthday bukkehorn.
Anna : Oh, no, no, no.
Hans : Ah!
Anna : Best birthday present ever.
Elsa : Which one?
Anna : You letting me take care of you.
Olaf : This way, Sludge and Slush and Slide and Ansel... and Flake and Fridge and Flurry and Powder... and Crystal and Squalor and Pat and Sphere...
Olaf : and William.
Kristoff : Don't ask.