Agnarr : Anna Elsa
Iduna : Bedtime soon
Baby Anna : Uhoh The princess is trapped in the snow goblin's evil spell
Baby Anna : Quick Elsa Make a prince A fancy one
Baby Anna : Oh no The prince is trapped too
Baby Anna : Who cares about danger when there's love
Baby Elsa : Ugh Anna Bleugh
Baby Elsa : Kissing won't save the Forest
Baby Elsa : The lost fairies cry out
Baby Elsa : What sound does a giraffe make
Baby Elsa : Never mind They wake the fairy queen who breaks the spell and saves everyone
Baby Anna : And they all get married
Agnarr : What are you playing
Baby Anna : Enchanted Forest The prince and the princess
Agnarr : That's like no enchanted forest I've ever seen
Baby Elsa : You've seen an enchanted forest
Baby Anna : Wait what
Agnarr : I have Once
Baby Anna : And you've never told us this before
Agnarr : Well I could tell you now if you
Baby Elsa : Okay Now Tell us now
Iduna : Are you sure about this
Agnarr : It's time they know
Baby Anna : Let's make a big snowman later
Agnarr : If they can settle and listen
Agnarr : Far away as north as we can go stood a very old and very enchanted forest
Agnarr : But its magic wasn't that of goblin spells and lost fairies
Agnarr : It was protected by the most powerful spirits of all
Agnarr : those of air of fire of water and earth
Agnarr : But it was also home to the mysterious Northuldra people
Baby Elsa : Were the Northuldra magical like me
Agnarr : No Elsa They were not magical
Agnarr : They just took advantage of the Forest's gifts
Agnarr : Their ways were so different from ours but still they promised us friendship
Agnarr : In honor of that your grandfather King Runeard built them a mighty dam to strengthen their waters
Agnarr : It was a gift of peace
Baby Anna : That's a big gift of peace
Agnarr : And I was so honored to get to go to the Forest to celebrate it
Runeard : Stand tall Agnarr
Agnarr : I wasn't at all prepared for what the day would bring
Agnarr : We let down our guard
Agnarr : We were charmed
Agnarr : Whoa Whoa
Agnarr : It felt so magical
Agnarr : But something went wrong
Agnarr : They were attacking us
Mattias : Get behind me
Agnarr : It was a brutal battle
Agnarr : Your grandfather
Young Agnarr : Father
Agnarr : was lost
Young Agnarr : Aah
Agnarr : The fighting enraged the spirits
Soldier : Look out
Agnarr : They turned their magic against us all
Agnarr : There was this voice
Agnarr : and someone saved me
Agnarr : I'm told the spirits then vanished
Agnarr : And a powerful mist covered the Forest
Agnarr : Locking everyone out
Agnarr : And that night I came home King of Arendelle
Baby Anna : Whoa Papa that was epic
Baby Anna : Whoever saved you I love them
Agnarr : I wish I knew who it was
Baby Elsa : What happened to the spirits
Baby Elsa : What's in the Forest now
Agnarr : I don't know
Agnarr : The mist still stands
Agnarr : No one can get in
Agnarr : And no one has since come out
Iduna : So we're safe
Agnarr : Yes
Agnarr : But the Forest could wake again
Agnarr : And we must be prepared for whatever danger it may bring
Iduna : And on that note how about we say good night to your father
Baby Anna : But I still have so many questions
Agnarr : Save them for another night Anna
Baby Anna : You know I don't have that kind of patience
Baby Anna : Why did Northuldra attack us anyway
Baby Anna : Who attacks people who give them gifts
Baby Elsa : Do you think the Forest will wake again
Iduna : Only Ahtohallan knows
Baby Anna : Octawhowhat
Iduna : When I was little my mother would sing a song about a special river called Ahtohallan
Iduna : that was said to hold all the answers about the past
Iduna : About what we are a part of
Baby Anna : Wow
Baby Elsa : Will you sing it for us Please
Iduna : Okay
Iduna : Cuddle close
Iduna : Scooch in
Iduna : Where the Northwind
Iduna : Meets the sea
Iduna : There's a river
Iduna : Full of memory
Iduna : Sleep my darling safe and sound
Iduna : For in this river all is found
Iduna : In her waters
Iduna : Deep and true
Iduna : Lie the answers
Iduna : And a path for you
Iduna : Dive down deep into her sound
Iduna : But not too far or you'll be drowned
Iduna : Yes she will sing to those who hear
Iduna : And in her song all magic flows
Iduna : But can you brave what you most fear
Iduna : Can you face what the river knows
Iduna : Where the Northwind Meets the sea
Iduna : There's a mother Full of memory
Iduna : Come my darling homeward bound
Iduna : When all is lost
Iduna : Then all is found
Kai : Your Majesty
Elsa : Oh
Kai : They're ready
Elsa : Excuse me
Elsa : I'm coming
Elsa : Do you hear that
Kai : What
Elsa : Never mind
Anna : Enjoying your new permafrost Olaf
Olaf : I'm just living the dream Anna
Olaf : Ah How I wish this could last forever
Olaf : And yet change mocks us with her beauty
Anna : What's that
Olaf : Forgive me Maturity is making me poetic
Olaf : Tell me you're older and thus allknowing
Olaf : do you ever worry about the notion that nothing is permanent
Anna : Uh No
Olaf : Really
Olaf : Wow I can't wait until I'm ancient like you so I don't have to worry about important things
Anna : That's not what I mean
Anna : I don't worry because well I have you and Elsa and Kristoff and Sven
Anna : and the gates are open wide and I'm not alone anymore
Anna : Yes the wind blows a little bit colder
Anna : And we're all getting older
Anna : And the clouds are moving on With every autumn breeze
Anna : Peter Pumpkin just became fertilizer
Olaf : And my leaf's a little sadder and wiser
Anna : That's why I rely on certain certainties
Anna : Yes some things never change
Anna : Like the feel of your hand in mine
Anna : Some things stay the same
Anna;Olaf : Like how we get along just fine
Anna : Like an old stone wall that'll never fall
Anna : Some things are always true
Anna : Some things never change
Anna : Like how I'm holding on tight to you
Kristoff : The leaves are already falling
Kristoff : Sven it feels like the future is calling
Sven : Are you telling me tonight You're gonna get down on one knee
Kristoff : Yeah but I'm really bad at planning these things out
Kristoff : Like candlelight and pulling of rings out
Sven : Maybe you should leave all the romantic stuff to me
Kristoff : Yeah some things never change
Kristoff : Like the love that I feel for her
Kristoff : Some things stay the same
Kristoff : Like how reindeers are easier
Kristoff : But if I commit and I go for it
Kristoff : I'll know what to say and do
Kristoff : Right
Sven : Some things never change
Kristoff : Sven the pressure is all on you
Elsa : The winds are restless
Elsa : Could that be why I'm hearing this call
Elsa : Is something coming
Elsa : I'm not sure I want things to change at all
Elsa : These days are precious
Elsa : Can't let them slip away
Elsa : I can't freeze this moment
Elsa : But I can still go out and seize this day
Anna : Oh
All : The wind blows a little bit colder
Olaf : And you all look a little bit older
Anna : It's time to count our blessings
Anna;Kristoff : Beneath an autumn sky
All : We'll always live in a kingdom of plenty
All : That stands for the good of the many
Elsa : And I promise you the flag of Arendelle will always fly
Anna : Our flag will always fly
All : Our flag will always fly Our flag will always fly
Anna;Olaf : Some things never change
Anna;Olaf : Turn around and the time has flown
Anna;Olaf : Some things stay the same
Anna;Olaf : Though the future remains unknown
Anna;Olaf : May our good luck last May our past be past
Anna;Olaf : Time's moving fast it's true
Anna;Olaf : Some things never change
Anna : And I'm holding on tight to you
Elsa : Holding on tight to you
Olaf : Holding on tight to
Kristoff : Holding on tight to you
Anna : I'm holding on tight to you
Kristoff : Uh okay Um lion
Olaf : Grizzly bear
Kristoff : Uh monster
Olaf : Brown bear
Kristoff : Angry face
Olaf : Black bear
Kristoff : Uh
Olaf : Hans
Elsa : Unredeemable monster
Kristoff : Greatest mistake of your life
Olaf : Wouldn't even kiss you
Anna : Villain
Elsa;Kristoff : Oh
Olaf : We all kind of got it
Kristoff : Okay Olaf you're up
Olaf : Okay
Olaf : So much easier now that I can read
Sven : Mm
Olaf : Lightning round boys against girls
Kristoff : Okay I'm ready I'm ready Go
Kristoff : Unicorn
Kristoff : Ice cream
Kristoff : Castle Oaken
Kristoff : Teapot Mouse
Kristoff : Oh Elsa
Anna : I don't think Olaf should get to rearrange
Anna : Doesn't matter This is gonna be a cinch
Anna : Two sisters one mind
Elsa : Thank you
Anna : Okay
Anna : Here we go
Anna : You got this Elsa
Anna : Anytime Just just do it with your body
Anna : Uh nothing Air Tree People
Anna : Treeple Oh that's not a word
Anna : Oh shovel boy
Anna : Teeth
Anna : Oh Doing the dishes
Olaf : Polar bear
Anna : Hey
Olaf : Sorry
Elsa : Uh Ugh
Anna : You gotta give me something
Elsa : Um
Anna : Oh Uh
Anna : Alarmed Distracted
Anna : Um worried Panicking Disturbed
Anna : Oh come on you definitely look disturbed
Kristoff : We won
Anna : Rematch
Elsa : Oh you know what I think I'll turn in
Anna : Are you okay
Elsa : Just Just tired
Elsa : Good night
Olaf : Yeah I'm tired too
Olaf : And Sven promised to read me a bedtime story
Olaf : Didn't you Sven
Sven : Did I
Olaf : Oh you do the best voices
Olaf : Like when you pretend to be Kristoff and you're like
Olaf : I just need to go talk to some rocks about my childhood and stuff
Kristoff : Um how about you guys start without me
Kristoff : Ugh
Anna : Did Elsa seem weird to you
Kristoff : She seemed like Elsa
Anna : That last word really seemed to throw her What was it
Kristoff : I don't know I don't know but
Anna : Ah Ice
Anna : Oh come on
Anna : She couldn't act out ice
Anna : I better go check on her
Anna : Thanks honey Love you
Kristoff : Love you too
Kristoff : It's fine
Elsa : Come in
Anna : Yep Something's wrong
Elsa : With you
Anna : No with you You're wearing Mother's scarf
Anna : You do that when something's wrong
Anna : Did we hurt your feelings
Anna : I'm so sorry if we did
Anna : You know very few people are actually good at family games
Anna : That's just a fact
Elsa : No that's not it
Anna : Then what is it
Elsa : There's this
Elsa : I just don't wanna mess things up
Anna : What things You're doing great
Anna : Oh Elsa when are you going to see yourself the way I see you
Elsa : What would I do without you
Anna : You'll always have me
Anna : I know what you need
Anna : Come on come here
Elsa : What
Anna : In Mama's words
Anna : cuddle close scooch in
Elsa : Mmhmm
Anna : Where the Northwind
Anna : Meets the sea
Anna : There's a river
Anna;Elsa : Full of memory
Elsa : I know what you're doing
Elsa;Anna : Sleep my darling safe and sound
Elsa;Anna : For in this river all is found
Elsa : I can hear you
Elsa : But I won't
Elsa : Some look for trouble
Elsa : While others don't
Elsa : There's a thousand reasons I should go about my day
Elsa : And ignore your whispers which I wish would go away oh
Elsa : Oh
Elsa : You're not a voice
Elsa : You're just a ringing in my ear
Elsa : And if I heard you
Elsa : Which I don't
Elsa : I'm spoken for I fear
Elsa : Everyone I've ever loved is here within these walls
Elsa : I'm sorry Secret Siren But I'm blocking out your calls
Elsa : I've had my adventure I don't need something new
Elsa : I'm afraid of what I'm risking if I follow you
Elsa : Into the unknown
Elsa : What do you want
Elsa : Cause you've been keeping me awake
Elsa : Are you here to distract me
Elsa : So I make a big mistake
Elsa : Or are you someone out there
Elsa : Who's a little bit like me
Elsa : Who knows deep down
Elsa : I'm not where I'm meant to be
Elsa : Every day's a little harder
Elsa : As I feel my power grow
Elsa : Don't you know there's part of me that longs to go
Elsa : Into the unknown
Elsa : Whoaohoh
Elsa : Are you out there Do you know me
Elsa : Can you feel me Can you show me
Elsa : Where are you going Don't leave me alone
Elsa : How do I follow you
Elsa : Into the unknown
Elsa : Air fire water earth
Elsa : The water
Elsa : The air rages no fire no water
Elsa : The earth is next We have to get out
Elsa : It'll be okay Evacuate to the cliffs
Olaf : Oh no I'm gonna blow
Kristoff : I've got you
Kristoff : Yes Everyone's out and safe
Kristoff : Here Take one of these
Sven : Huh
Kristoff : You okay there Olaf
Olaf : Oh yeah We're calling this controlling what you can when things feel out of control
Anna : Okay I don't understand
Anna : You've been hearing a voice and you didn't think to tell me
Elsa : I didn't want to worry you
Anna : We made a promise not to shut each other out
Anna : Just tell me what's going on
Elsa : I woke the magical spirits at the Enchanted Forest
Anna : Okay that's definitely not what I thought you were gonna say
Anna : Wait The Enchanted Forest
Anna : The one Father warned us about
Elsa : Yes
Anna : Why would you do that
Elsa : Because of the voice
Elsa : I know it sounds crazy
Elsa : but I believe whoever is calling me is good
Anna : How can you say that Look at our kingdom
Elsa : I know It's just that my magic can feel it
Elsa : I can feel it
Anna : Okay
Elsa : Oh no What now
Kristoff : The Trolls
Bulda : Kristoff
Kristoff : oh
Bulda : We missed you
Elsa : Pabbie
Grand Pabbie : Well never a dull moment with you two
Grand Pabbie : I hope you're prepared for what you have done Elsa
Grand Pabbie : Angry magical spirits are not for the faint of heart
Anna : Why are they still angry
Anna : What does all of this have to do with Arendelle
Grand Pabbie : Let me see what I can see
Grand Pabbie : The past is not what it seems
Grand Pabbie : A wrong demands to be righted
Grand Pabbie : Arendelle is not safe
Grand Pabbie : The truth must be found
Grand Pabbie : Without it
Grand Pabbie : I see no future
Anna : No future
Grand Pabbie : When one can see no future all one can do is the next right thing
Elsa : The next right thing is for me to go to the Enchanted Forest and find that voice
Elsa : Kristoff can I borrow your wagon and Sven
Kristoff : I'm not very comfortable with the idea of that
Anna : You are not going alone
Elsa : Anna no I have my powers to protect me You don't
Anna : Excuse me I climbed the North Mountain survived a frozen heart and saved you from my exboyfriend and I did it all without powers
Anna : so you know I'm coming
Kristoff : Me too I'll drive
Olaf : I'll bring the snacks
Grand Pabbie : I will look after your people
Anna : Please make sure they stay out of the kingdom until we return
Grand Pabbie : Of course
Elsa : Let's let them know
Grand Pabbie : Anna I am worried for her
Grand Pabbie : We have always feared Elsa's powers were too much for this world
Grand Pabbie : Now we must pray they are enough
Anna : I won't let anything happen to her
Olaf : Who's into trivia
Olaf : I am Okay
Olaf : Did you know that water has memory True fact
Olaf : It's disputed by many but it's true
Olaf : Did you know men are six times more likely to be struck by lightning
Olaf : Did you know gorillas burp when they're happy
Olaf : Did you know we blink four million times a day
Olaf : Did you know wombats poop squares
Kristoff : Did you know sleeping quietly on long journeys prevents insanity
Olaf : Yeah that's not true
Kristoff : It is
Anna : It's true
Elsa : Definitely true
Anna : No it's the truth
Olaf : Well that was unanimous
Olaf : But I will look it up when we get home
Anna : They're both asleep
Anna : So what do you wanna do
Kristoff : Sven keep us steady will ya
Anna : Hmm
Kristoff : Anna Ahem Anna
Anna : Mmhmm
Kristoff : Remember our first trip like this when I said you'd have to be crazy to want to marry a man you just met
Anna : Wait what Crazy
Anna : You didn't say I was crazy You think I'm crazy
Kristoff : No I did
Kristoff : You were not crazy
Kristoff : Clearly Just naive
Kristoff : Not naive Just uh new to love Like I was
Kristoff : And when you're new you're bound to get it wrong
Anna : So you're saying I'm wrong for you
Kristoff : What No no I'm not saying
Kristoff : you're wrong or crazy
Elsa : Kristoff stop Please
Kristoff : Good idea
Elsa : I hear it I hear the voice
Anna : You do
Anna : Olaf wake up
Kristoff : Whoa
Anna : Wow
Kristoff : Whoa What the
Elsa : Whoa
Anna : Promise me we do this together okay
Elsa : I promise
Kristoff : It's okay
Olaf : Did you know that an enchanted forest is a place of transformation
Olaf : I have no idea what that means
Olaf : but I can't wait to see what it's gonna do to each one of us
All : Hey
Kristoff : What is this
Anna : No pushing
Kristoff : Whoa whoa whoa
Anna : It's too fast
Kristoff : What was that
Elsa : No No no no
Anna : And we're locked in
Anna : Probably should have seen that one coming
Elsa : This forest is beautiful
Olaf : Ooh
Anna : The dam It still stands
Anna : It was in Grand Pabbie's visions
Anna : But why
Kristoff : I don't know but it's still in good shape Thank goodness
Anna : What do you mean
Kristoff : Well if that dam broke it would send a tidal wave so big it would wash away everything on this fjord
Anna : Everything
Anna : But Arendelle's on this fjord
Kristoff : Nothing's gonna happen to Arendelle Anna It's gonna be fine
Kristoff : Come here
Kristoff : You know under different circumstances this would be a uh pretty romantic place
Kristoff : Don't you think
Anna : Different circumstances
Anna : You mean like with someone else
Kristoff : What No No
Kristoff : I'm saying
Kristoff : Just in case we don't make it out of here
Anna : Wait what You don't think we're gonna make it out of here
Kristoff : No No I mean no we will make it out of here
Kristoff : Well technically the odds are kind of complicated but my point is
Kristoff : In case we die
Anna : You think we're gonna die
Kristoff : No No no no
Kristoff : We will die at some point
Anna : I swore that I wouldn't leave her side
Kristoff : But way far in the future we will die
Kristoff : Don't patronize me
Anna : Elsa
Anna : There you are
Anna : You okay
Elsa : I'm fine
Anna : Okay good
Anna : Where's Olaf
Olaf : Um Anna Elsa Sven
Olaf : Samantha
Olaf : I don't even know a Samantha
Olaf : Whoa
Olaf : Mm
Olaf : That's normal
Olaf : What was that
Olaf : Samantha
Olaf : This will all make sense when I am older
Olaf : Someday I will see that this makes sense
Olaf : One day when I'm old and wise I'll think back and realize
Olaf : That these were all completely normal events
Olaf : I'll have all the answers when I'm older
Olaf : Like why we're in this dark enchanted wood
Olaf : I know in a couple years
Olaf : These will seem like childish fears
Olaf : And so I know this isn't bad it's good
Olaf : Excuse me
Olaf : Growing up means adapting
Olaf : Puzzling out your world and your place
Olaf : When I'm more mature I'll feel totally secure
Olaf : Being watched by something with a creepy creepy face
Olaf : See that will all make sense when I am older
Olaf : So there's no need to be terrified or tense
Olaf : I'll just dream about a time
Olaf : When I'm in my agèd prime
Olaf : Cause when you're older
Olaf : Absolutely everything makes sense
Olaf : This is fine
Anna : Olaf
Olaf : Hey guys
Olaf : Meet the Wind Spirit
Olaf : Coming through
Anna : Ooh I think I'm gonna be sick
Olaf : I'd hold your hair back but I can't find my arms
Elsa : Hey Stop
Anna : Elsa
Anna : Let her go
Kristoff : Anna be careful
Anna : That's my sister
Mattias : Prince Agnarr
Runeard : For Arendelle
Mattias : Look out
Young Agnarr : Father
Anna : Are you okay
Elsa : I'm fine
Kristoff : What are these
Elsa : Oh they look like moments in time
Anna : What's that thing you say Olaf
Olaf : The thing Oh
Olaf : My theory about advancing technologies as both our savior and our doom
Anna : No not that one The one about
Olaf : The one about cucumbers
Anna : No The thing about water
Olaf : Oh Yeah Water has memory
Olaf : The water that makes up you and me has passed through at least four humans andor animals before us
Anna : Hmm
Olaf : And remembers everything
Olaf : The wind's back
Olaf : Delicious
Olaf : I think I'll name you Gale
Kristoff : Get out of there Whoa
Anna : Oh Hi Aren't you curious
Elsa : You in a better mood now
Anna : Father That's Father
Elsa : This girl
Olaf : She's saving him
Kristoff : She's Northuldra
Anna : What is that
Elsa : Olaf get behind me
Kristoff : What are you gonna do with that
Anna : I have no idea
Honeymaren : Lower your weapon
Mattias : And you lower yours
Anna : Arendellian soldiers
Yelena : Threatening my people Lieutenant
Mattias : Invading my dance space Yelena
Anna : Why does that soldier look so familiar
Arendellian Soldier : Lieutenant
Mattias : Get the sword
Mattias : That was magic
Mattias : Did you see that
Yelena : Of course I saw it
Anna : You chose a nice cold greeting
Kristoff : They've been trapped in here this whole time
Anna : Yeah
Elsa : What do we do now
Olaf : I got this
Olaf : Hi I'm Olaf
Olaf : Oh sorry Yeah I just find clothes restricting
Olaf : Bet you're wondering who we are and why we're here
Olaf : It's really quite simple
Olaf : It began with two sisters
Olaf : One born with magical powers
Olaf : One born powerless
Olaf : Their love of snowmen infinite
Olaf : Anna no Too high
Olaf : Blast
Olaf : Mama Papa Help
Olaf : Slam Doors shutting everywhere
Olaf : Sisters torn apart
Olaf : Well at least they have their parents
Olaf : Their parents are dead
Olaf : Oh Oh hi I'm Anna
Olaf : I'll marry a man I just met
Olaf : Elsa's gonna blow
Olaf : Snow Snow Aah run
Olaf : Magic pulses through my snowflakes
Olaf : I live
Olaf : Ice palace for one Ice palace for one
Olaf : Get out Anna
Olaf : Pew Pew
Olaf : My heart
Mattias : Oh my goodness
Olaf : Only an act of true love can save you
Olaf : Here's a true love's kiss
Olaf : You're not worth it
Olaf : Guess what I'm the bad guy
Mattias : What
Olaf : And Anna freezes to death forever
Mattias : Oh Anna
Olaf : Then she unfreezes
Olaf : Oh and then Elsa woke up the magical spirits and we were forced out of our kingdom
Olaf : Now our only hope is to find the truth about the past but we don't have a clue how to do that except Elsa's hearing voices so we got that going for us
Olaf : Any questions
Olaf : I think they got it
Mattias : Are you really Queen of Arendelle
Elsa : I am
Yelena : Why would nature reward a person of Arendelle with magic
Mattias : Perhaps to make up for the actions of your people
Yelena : My people are innocent
Yelena : We would have never attacked first
Mattias : May the truth be found
Anna : Mm
Mattias : Hi I'm sorry
Mattias : Uh what's happening
Anna : That's it Lieutenant Mattias
Anna : Library second portrait on the left
Anna : You were our father's official guard
Mattias : Agnarr
Mattias : What did happen to your parents
Anna : Our parents ship went down in the Southern Sea six years ago
Mattias : I see him I see him in your faces
Anna : Really
Mattias : Soldiers
Mattias : We may be getting on in years but we're still strong
Mattias : And proud to serve Arendelle
Elsa : Wait Please
Elsa : Someone has called me here
Elsa : If I can just find them
Elsa : I believe they have the answers that may help us free this forest
Elsa : Trust me I just want to help
Yelena : We only trust nature
Yelena : When nature speaks
Yelena : we listen
Olaf : This will all make sense when I'm older
Man1 : Fire Spirit
Ryder : No No No The reindeer That's a dead end
Kristoff : Come on Sven
Kristoff : We'll get them
Anna : Elsa Get out of there
Anna : No no no
Anna : Elsa
Kristoff : Come on buddy we can do this
Kristoff : Hyah
Kristoff : Anna
Anna : Oh
Elsa : Get her out of here
Anna : No Elsa
Elsa : They're all looking at us aren't they
Elsa : Got any advice
Elsa : Nothing
Elsa : Hmm Should I know what that means
Elsa : You hear it too
Elsa : Somebody's calling us
Elsa : Who is it What do we do
Elsa : Okay keep going north
Anna : Elsa
Anna : Oh thank goodness
Elsa : Anna
Anna : Are you okay
Elsa : What were you doing
Elsa : You could've been killed
Elsa : You can't just follow me into fire
Anna : You don't want me to follow you into fire then don't run into fire
Anna : You're not being careful Elsa
Elsa : I'm sorry Are you okay
Anna : I've been better
Elsa : Hmm I know what you need
Yelena : Where did you get that scarf
Ryder : That's a Northuldra scarf
Anna : What
Honeymaren : This is from one of our oldest families
Anna : It was our mother's
Anna : Elsa
Elsa : I see it
Elsa : It's Mother
Anna : Mother saved Father's life that day
Elsa : Our mother was Northuldra
Yelena : We are called Northuldra
Yelena : We are the people of the sun
Elsa : I promise you I will free this forest
Elsa : and restore Arendelle
Anna : That's a pretty big promise Elsa
Ryder : Free the Forest Wow
Ryder : I'm sorry It's just uh some of us were born in here we've never even seen a clear sky
Kristoff : I get it
Ryder : The name's Ryder
Kristoff : Kristoff
Elsa : I heard the voice again
Elsa : We need to go north
Honeymaren : But the Earth Giants now roam the north at night
Yelena : You can leave in the morning
Honeymaren : I'm Honeymaren
Anna : Honeymaren we'll do all we can
Olaf : Hey let me ask you
Olaf : How do you guys cope with the everincreasing complexity of thought that comes with maturity
Olaf : Brilliant
Olaf : Oh
Olaf : It's so refreshing to talk to the youth of today
Olaf : Our future's in bright hands
Olaf : Oh no no Don't chew that
Olaf : You don't know what I've stepped in
Kristoff : I can't seem to get her attention Or even say the right thing
Ryder : Well you're in luck
Ryder : I know nothing about women
Ryder : But I do know that we have the most amazing way of proposing
Ryder : If we start now we'll be ready by dawn
Kristoff : Really
Ryder : Best part
Ryder : it involves a lot of reindeer
Kristoff : Whoa
Mattias : Hey back at home Halima still over at Hudson's Hearth
Anna : She is
Mattias : Really She married
Anna : Mmmm
Mattias : Oh wow Why didn't that make me feel better
Anna : What else do you miss
Mattias : My father He passed long before all this
Mattias : He was a great man
Mattias : Built us a good life in Arendelle But taught me to never take the good for granted
Mattias : He'd say Be prepared
Mattias : Just when you think you've found your way life will throw you onto a new path
Anna : What do you do when it does
Mattias : Don't give up
Mattias : Take it one step at a time and
Anna : Just do the next right thing
Mattias : Yeah
Mattias : You got it
Honeymaren : I wanna show you something May I
Honeymaren : You know air fire water and earth
Elsa : Yes
Honeymaren : But look there's a fifth spirit said to be a bridge between us and the magic of nature
Elsa : A fifth spirit
Honeymaren : Some say
Honeymaren : they heard it call out the day the Forest fell
Elsa : My father heard it
Elsa : Do you think that is who's calling me
Honeymaren : Maybe Alas only Ahtohallan knows
Elsa : Ahtohallan
Elsa : Dive down deep into her sound
Elsa;Honeymaren : But not too far or you'll be drowned
Honeymaren : Why do lullabies always have to have some terrible warning in them
Elsa : I wonder that all the time
Honeymaren : Earth Giants
Yelena : What are they doing down here
Mattias : Shh
Elsa : Hide
Olaf : They're coming
Olaf : This is why we don't play with fire
Olaf : Oh I can't stay mad at you Why are you so cute
Anna : Please tell me you were not about to follow them
Elsa : What if I can settle them like I did the wind and fire
Anna : Or what if they can crush you before you even get the chance
Anna : Remember the goal is to find the voice find the truth and get us home
Olaf : Hey guys That was close
Elsa : I know
Elsa : The giants sensed me They may come back here I don't want to put anyone at risk again
Elsa : And you're right Anna We've got to find the voice
Elsa : We're going now
Anna : Okay We're going Let me just
Anna : Wait Where are Kristoff and Sven
Olaf : Oh yeah I think they took off with that Ryder guy and a bunch of reindeer
Anna : They left
Olaf : Mmhmm
Anna : Just left without saying anything
Olaf : Who knows the ways of men
Kristoff : Am I supposed to feel this ridiculous
Ryder : Oh yeah Definitely
Kristoff : Everyone ready
Ryder : Ready
Ryder : Uh I could use a rehearsal
Ryder : I love love
Kristoff : Wait You talk for them too
Ryder : I do
Kristoff : It's like you can actually hear what they're thinking
Ryder : Yeah And then you just say it
Kristoff : And then you just say it
Ryder : Okay Here she comes
Kristoff : Princess Anna of Arendelle
Kristoff : my feisty fearless gingersweet love
Kristoff : Will you marry me
Yelena : Um
Yelena : No
Yelena : The princess left with the queen
Kristoff : What Wait what What
Yelena : I wouldn't try to follow They're long gone
Kristoff : Long gone
Yelena : So yeah
Yelena : Um we're heading west to the Lichen Meadows You can come with us if you want
Ryder : Hey Um I'm really sorry that
Kristoff : No it's fine
Ryder : Yeah Yep
Ryder : Okay I better go pack You coming with
Kristoff : I'll just Yeah I'll meet you there
Ryder : Okay uh you know where you're going
Kristoff : Yeap
Ryder : right
Kristoff : Yeah
Ryder : Yep
Kristoff : I know the woods
Kristoff : Reindeers are better than people
Kristoff : Sven why is love so hard
Sven : You feel what you feel
Sven : And those feelings are real
Sven : Come on Kristoff
Sven : Let down your guard
Kristoff : Again you're gone
Kristoff : Off on a diff'rent path than mine
Kristoff : I'm left behind
Kristoff : Wondering if I should follow
Kristoff : You had to go
Kristoff : And of course it's always fine
Kristoff : I prob'ly could catch up with you tomorrow
Kristoff : But is this what it feels like to be growing apart
Kristoff : When did I become the one Who's always chasing your heart
Kristoff;Sven : Now I turn around and find
Kristoff;Sven : I am lost in the woods
Kristoff;Sven : North is South Right is left
Kristoff;Sven : When you're gone
Kristoff;Sven : I'm the one who sees you home
Kristoff;Sven : But now I'm lost in the woods
Kristoff;Sven : And I don't know what path you are on
Kristoff : I'm lost in the woods
Kristoff : Up till now
Kristoff : The next step was a question of how
Kristoff : I never thought it was a question of whether
Kristoff : Who am I
Kristoff : If I'm not your guy
Kristoff : Where am I if we're not together
Kristoff : Forever
Kristoff;Sven : Now I know you're my true North
Sven;Kristoff : Cause I am lost in the woods
Kristoff;Sven : Up is down Day is night
Kristoff;Sven : When you're not there
Kristoff;Sven : Oh you're my only landmark
Kristoff;Sven : So I'm lost in the woods
Kristoff;Sven : Wondering if you still care
Kristoff : But I'll wait
Kristoff : For a sign
Kristoff;Sven : For a sign That I'm your path
Kristoff : Cause you are mine
Sven : You are mine
Kristoff : Until then
Kristoff : I'm lost in the woods
Sven : lost in the woods
Sven : In the woods Lost in the woods
Kristoff : I'm lost in the woods
Sven : Lost in the woods I'm lost
Anna : Hey Olaf um maybe just one of you should do it
Olaf : I agree She's a little pitchy
Olaf : Hey Gale's back
Elsa : What
Anna : How can it be
Olaf : What is it
Elsa : Mother and Father's ship
Olaf : But this isn't the Southern Sea
Anna : No it isn't
Elsa : Why is their ship here
Elsa : How is it here
Anna : It must have been washed in from the Dark Sea
Elsa : What were they doing in the Dark Sea
Anna : I don't know
Olaf : How did the ship get through the mist
Olaf : I thought nobody could but us
Olaf : Unless nobody was on it
Anna : There's gotta be something here
Anna : Wait Wait Look around
Anna : Every Arendellian ship has a compartment
Anna : Waterproof
Olaf : That's very clever
Olaf : Although it does make me wonder why they don't just make the whole ship waterproof
Anna : Here
Anna : What language is this
Elsa : I don't know
Elsa : But look this is Mother's handwriting
Anna : The end of the ice age
Anna : The river found but lost
Anna : Magic's source Elsa's source
Anna : It's a map
Anna : They traveled north
Anna : and planned to cross the Dark Sea to
Elsa : Ahtohallan
Anna : It's real
Olaf : Octawhowhat
Anna : Ahtohallan
Anna : It's a magical river said to hold all the answers about the past
Olaf : Reinforcing my water has memory theory Mm
Elsa : Water has memory
Anna : Elsa
Elsa : I wanna know what happened to them
Iduna : Ahtohallan has to be the source of her magic
Agnarr : We keep going for Elsa
Iduna : The waves are too high
Agnarr : Iduna
Iduna : Agnarr
Anna : Elsa
Anna : Hey hey hey what are you doing
Elsa : This is my fault
Elsa : They were looking for answers about me
Anna : You are not responsible for their choices Elsa
Elsa : No Just their deaths
Anna : Stop No
Anna : Yelena asked why would the spirits reward Arendelle with a magical queen
Anna : Because our mother saved our father
Anna : She saved her enemy
Anna : Her good deed was rewarded with you
Anna : You are a gift
Elsa : For what
Anna : If anyone can resolve the past
Anna : if anyone can save Arendelle and free this forest it's you
Anna : I believe in you Elsa More than anyone or anything
Elsa : Honeymaren said there was a fifth spirit
Elsa : A bridge between the magic of nature and us
Anna : A fifth spirit
Elsa : That's who's been calling me from Ahtohallan
Elsa : The answers about the past are all there
Elsa : So we go to Ahtohallan
Elsa : Not we
Elsa : Me
Anna : What
Elsa : The Dark Sea is too dangerous for us both
Anna : No No We do this together
Anna : Remember the song
Anna : Go too far and you'll be drowned
Anna : Who will stop you from going too far
Elsa : You said you believed in me that this is what I was born to do
Anna : And I don't wanna stop you from that
Anna : I I don't wanna stop you from being whatever you need to be
Anna : I just don't want you dying trying to be everything for everyone else too
Anna : Don't do this alone
Anna : Let me help you please
Anna : I can't lose you Elsa
Elsa : I can't lose you either Anna
Olaf : Come on
Olaf : Mmm
Anna : Wait what
Anna : What are you doing
Anna : Elsa
Anna : No No
Anna : Olaf help me stop
Anna : Give me a hand
Anna : Hang on
Olaf : Whoa
Anna : Wait Wait No No No
Anna : Oh come on
Olaf : Anna this might sound crazy but I'm sensing some rising anger
Anna : Well I am angry Olaf
Anna : She promised me we'd do this together
Olaf : Yeah Uhhuh But what I mean is I'm sensing rising anger in me
Anna : Wait you're angry
Olaf : Um I I think so
Olaf : Elsa pushed me away too and didn't even say goodbye
Anna : And you have every right to be very very mad at her
Olaf : And you said some things never change
Olaf : But since then everything's done nothing but change
Anna : I know
Anna : But look I'm still here holding your hand
Olaf : Yeah that's a good point Anna
Olaf : I feel better You're such a good listener
Olaf : Don't shush me That's rude
Anna : No No
Olaf : Oh The Giants
Olaf : They're huge
Anna : Hang on Olaf
Olaf : Huh
Anna : Try not to scream
Anna : Found it
Olaf : Thank you
Olaf : Where are we
Anna : In a pit with no way out
Olaf : But with a spooky pitchblack way in
Olaf : Come on it'll be fun
Olaf : Assuming we don't get stuck here forever no one ever finds us and you starve and I give up
Olaf : But bright side Elsa's gotta be doing a whole lot better than we are
Elsa : Okay
Elsa : Whoa
Elsa : No
Elsa : Of course
Elsa : Glaciers are rivers of ice
Elsa : Ahtohallan is frozen
Elsa : I hear you
Elsa : And I'm coming
Elsa : Every inch of me is trembling
Elsa : But not from the cold
Elsa : Something is familiar
Elsa : Like a dream I can reach but not quite hold
Elsa : I can sense you there
Elsa : Like a friend I've always known
Elsa : I'm arriving
Elsa : And it feels like I am home
Elsa : I have always been a fortress
Elsa : Cold secrets deep inside
Elsa : You have secrets too
Elsa : But you don't have to hide
Elsa : Show yourself
Elsa : I'm dying to meet you
Elsa : It's your turn
Elsa : Are you the one I've been looking for all of my life
Elsa : Show yourself
Elsa : I'm ready to learn
Elsa : I've never felt so certain
Elsa : All my life I've been torn
Elsa : But I'm here for a reason
Elsa : Could it be the reason I was born
Elsa : I have always been so different
Elsa : Normal rules did not apply
Elsa : Is this the day Are you the way
Elsa : I finally find out why
Elsa : Show yourself
Elsa : I'm no longer trembling
Elsa : Here I am
Elsa : I've come so far
Elsa : You are the answer I've waited for
Elsa : All of my life
Elsa : Oh show yourself
Elsa : Let me see who you are
Elsa : Come to me now
Elsa : Open your door
Elsa : Don't make me wait
Elsa : One moment more oh
Elsa : Come to me now
Elsa : Open your door
Elsa : Don't make me wait
Elsa : One moment more
Elsa;Women Ensemble : Where the Northwind
Elsa;Women Ensemble : Meets the sea
Women Ensemble : There's a river
Women Ensemble : Full of memory
Elsa : Mother
Iduna : Come my darling homeward bound
Elsa : I am found
Elsa;Iduna : Show yourself
Elsa;Iduna : Step into your power
Elsa;Iduna : Grow yourself
Elsa;Iduna : Into something new
Iduna : You are the one you've been waiting for
Elsa : All of my life
Iduna : All of your life
Elsa : Oh show yourself
Baby Elsa : Hi I'm Olaf And I like warm hugs
Baby Anna : I love you Olaf
Elsa : Come on you can do it
Elsa : Here I stand
Elsa : Oh
Duke of Weselton : Oh Like a chicken with the face of a monkey
Anna : I just wasn't looking where I was going But I'm great actually
Hans : Prince Hans of the Southern Isles
Agnarr : I love you
Iduna : I need to tell you about my past
Iduna : And where I'm from
Agnarr : I'm listening
Young Agnarr : Iduna
Young Iduna : What are you reading Your Majesty
Young Agnarr : Oh some new Danish author
Elsa : Grandfather
Runeard : We bring Arendelle's full guard
Servant : But they have given us no reason not to trust them
Runeard : The Northuldra follow magic
Runeard : Which means we can never trust them
Elsa : Grandfather
Runeard : Magic makes people feel too powerful Too entitled
Runeard : It makes them think they can defy the will of a king
Elsa : That is not what magic does
Elsa : That's just your fear
Elsa : Fear is what can't be trusted
Runeard : You see the dam will weaken their lands so they will have to turn to me
Iduna : Dive down deep into her sound
Iduna : But not too far or you'll be drowned
Runeard : They will come in celebration
Runeard : And then we will know their size and strength
Runeard : As you have welcomed us we welcome you
Runeard : our neighbors our friends
Servant : King Runeard the dam isn't strengthening our waters
Servant : It's hurting the Forest It's cutting off the North
Runeard : Let Let's not discuss this here Let's meet on the fjord Have tea
Runeard : Find a solution
Elsa : No
Elsa : Anna
Olaf : Hmm Which lucky tunnel do we choose
Runeard : You see the dam will
weaken their lands so they will have to turn to me
Northuldra Leader : King
Runeard the dam it's hurting the Forest
Anna : Elsa's found it
Olaf : What is it
Anna : The truth about the past
Anna : That's my grandfather attacking the Northuldra leader who wields no weapon
Anna : The dam wasn't a gift of peace
Anna : It was a trick
Olaf : But that goes against everything Arendelle stands for
Anna : It does doesn't it
Anna : I know how to free the Forest
Anna : I know what we have to do to set things right
Olaf : Why do you say that so sadly
Anna : We have to break the dam
Olaf : But Arendelle will be flooded
Anna : That's why everyone was forced out
Anna : To protect them from what has to be done
Olaf : Oh Oh
Olaf : Are you okay
Anna : I could really use a bright side Olaf
Olaf : Bright side Um Turtles can breathe through their butts
Anna : Huh
Olaf : And I see a way out
Anna : I knew I could count on you
Anna : Come on Olaf Elsa's probably on her way back right now
Anna : We can meet her and
Olaf : Olaf
Olaf : What's this
Anna : Are you okay
Olaf : I'm flurrying
Olaf : Wait No That's That's not it
Olaf : I'm flurrying away
Olaf : The magic in me is fading
Anna : What
Olaf : I don't think Elsa's okay
Olaf : I think
Olaf : she may have gone too far
Anna : No No
Olaf : Anna
Olaf : I'm sorry
Olaf : You're gonna have to do this next part on your own
Olaf : Okay
Anna : Wait Come here
Anna : I've got you Oh
Olaf : Oh That's good
Olaf : Hey Anna
Olaf : I just thought of one thing that's permanent
Anna : What's that
Olaf : Love
Anna : Warm hugs
Olaf : I like warm hugs
Anna : I love you
Anna : Olaf Elsa
Anna : What do I do now
Anna : I've seen dark before
Anna : But not like this
Anna : This is cold this is empty This is numb
Anna : The life I knew is over
Anna : The lights are out
Anna : Hello darkness
Anna : I'm ready to succumb
Anna : I follow you around
Anna : I always have
Anna : But you've gone to a place I cannot find
Anna : This grief has a gravity It pulls me down
Anna : But a tiny voice Whispers in my mind
Anna : You are lost Hope is gone
Anna : But you must go on
Anna : And do the next right thing
Anna : Can there be a day beyond this night
Anna : I don't know anymore what is true
Anna : I can't find my direction I'm all alone
Anna : The only star that guided me was you
Anna : How to rise from the floor
Anna : When it's not you I'm rising for
Anna : Just do the next right thing
Anna : Take a step
Anna : Step again
Anna : It is all that I can
Anna : To do the next right thing
Anna : I won't look too far ahead
Anna : It's too much for me to take
Anna : But break it down to this next breath
Anna : This next step
Anna : This next choice is one that I can make
Anna : So I'll walk through this night
Anna : Stumbling blindly toward the light
Anna : And do the next right thing
Anna : And with the dawn
Anna : What comes then
Anna : When it's clear that everything Will never be the same again
Anna : Then I'll make the choice
Anna : To hear that voice
Anna : And do
Anna : The next right thing
Anna : Wake up
Anna : That's it
Anna : Come and get me Come on
Anna : Over here
Anna : That's right Keep coming Keep coming
Anna : That'll work
Anna : This way guys
Mattias : What
Mattias : No no no no She's leading them to the dam
Anna : Kristoff
Kristoff : I'm here What do you need
Anna : To get to the dam
Kristoff : You got it
Anna : Thank you
Kristoff : Come on
Anna : Help me up
Kristoff : We'll meet you around
Anna : Lieutenant Mattias
Mattias : Your Highness what are you doing
Anna : The dam must fall
Anna : It's the only way to break the mist and free the Forest
Mattias : But we've sworn to protect Arendelle at all costs
Anna : Arendelle has no future until we make this right
Anna : King Runeard betrayed everyone
Anna : How do you know that
Anna : My sister gave her life for the truth
Anna : Please
Anna : Before we lose anyone else
Mattias : Look out
Anna : Destroy the dam! Come on! Throw your boulders!
Anna : That's it
Mattias : I've got her
Kristoff : Anna!
Mattias : Hang on
Anna : I'm sorry I left you behind
Anna : I was just so desperate to protect her
Kristoff : I know I know It's okay
Kristoff : My love is not fragile
Ryder : Wow
Ryder : Look at the sky
Ryder : I just didn't realize there was so much of it
Mattias : 34 years
Yelena : Five months
Mattias : And 23 days
Anna : Is it really you
Elsa : Anna
Anna : I thought I'd lost you
Elsa : Lost me
Elsa : You saved me Again
Anna : I did
Elsa : And Anna Arendelle did not fall
Anna : It didn't
Elsa : The spirits all agreed
Elsa : Arendelle deserves to stand with you
Anna : Me
Elsa : You did what was right For everyone
Anna : Did you find the fifth spirit
Anna : You are the fifth spirit
Anna : You're the bridge
Elsa : Well actually a bridge has two sides
Elsa : And Mother had two daughters
Elsa : We did this together
Elsa : And we'll continue to do this together
Anna : Together
Kristoff : Elsa You're okay
Kristoff : You look different
Kristoff : Did you cut your hair or something
Elsa : Or something
Kristoff : Oh
Elsa : Anna I need to ask you a question
Anna : Okay
Elsa : Do you want to build a snowman
Anna : What
Elsa : Thank goodness water has memory
Olaf : Anna
Olaf : Elsa
Olaf : Kristoff And Sven
Olaf : You all came back
Olaf : Oh I love happy endings
Olaf : I mean I presume we're done Or is this putting us in mortal danger situation gonna be a regular thing
Elsa : No We're done
Kristoff : Actually there is one more thing
Kristoff : Anna you are the most extraordinary person I've ever known
Kristoff : I love you with all I am
Kristoff : Will you marry me
Anna : Oh Yes
Kristoff : Ah
Kristoff : Aw
Anna : Arendelle's okay
Mattias : What
Elsa : Ahtohallan is beautiful
Elsa : Oh
Elsa : Hello
Elsa : You know you belong up here
Elsa : I took an oath to always do what's best for Arendelle
Elsa : Luckily I know just what that is
Olaf : While I still don't know what transformation means
Olaf : I feel like this Forest has really changed us all
Kai : Presenting Her Majesty Queen Anna of Arendelle
Anna : Oh Hello Hi
Anna : Sven don't you look nice
Anna : Oh my goodness Olaf
Olaf : Charmed I'm sure
Anna : Charming
Kristoff : Your Majesty
Anna : Kristoff
Anna : Aw did you boys get all dressed up for me
Olaf : It was Sven's idea
Kristoff : One hour You get this for one hour
Anna : That's okay
Anna : I prefer you in leather anyway
Olaf : I'm shocked you can last an hour That was brutal
Olaf : The things we do for love
Mattias : What is this crazy magic called again
Halima : A photograph
Mattias : Photograph Huh
Mattias : We look good
Anna : Halima General Mattias
Mattias : Uh Your Majesty I'll be right back
Mattias : You can look at our photograph while I'm gone
Mattias : I'm just kidding
Mattias : How am I doing
Anna : Fantastic
Anna : Our lands and people now connected by love
Anna : Hi Gale You like it
Anna : Oh do you mind I've got a message for my sister
Elsa : Thank you
Elsa : Charades Friday night Don't be late
Elsa : And don't worry Arendelle's doing just fine
Elsa : Keep looking after the Forest
Elsa : I love you
Elsa : I love you too sis
Elsa : Hey Gale We're going for a ride wanna come
Elsa : You ready
Ah ah oh oh oh
Ah ah oh oh oh oh oh oh
Into the unknown
Ah ah oh oh oh
I can hear you but I won't
Some look for trouble while others don't
There's a thousand reasons I should go about my day
And ignore your whispers Which I wish would go away
Oh oh oh
Whoa oh
You're not a voice
You're just a ringing in my ear
And if I heard you which I don't
I'm spoken for I fear
Everyone I've ever loved is here within these walls
I'm sorry secret siren But I'm blocking out your calls
I've had my adventure
I don't need something new
I'm afraid of what I'm risking if I follow you
Into the unknown
Ah ah oh oh oh
Ah ah oh oh oh oh oh oh
What do you want
Cause you've been keeping me awake
Are you here to distract me so I make a big mistake
Or are you someone out there who's a little bit like me
Who knows deep down I'm not where I'm meant to be
Every day's a little harder
As I feel your power grow
Don't you know there's a part of me That longs to go
Into the unknown
Whoa oh oh
Are you out there Do you know me Can you feel me Can you show me
Ah ah oh oh
Where are you going Don't leave me alone
How do I follow you
Into the unknown
Whoo
Where the Northwind
Meets the sea
There's a river
Full of memory
Sleep my darling Safe and sound
For in this river all is found
All is found
When all is lost then all is found
In her waters
Deep and true
Lie the answers and a path for you
Dive down deep into her sound
But not too far or you'll be drowned
She will sing to those who hear
And in her song all magic flows
But can you brave what you most fear
Can you face what the river knows
Until the river's finally crossed
You'll never feel the solid ground
You have to get a little lost
On your way
To being found
Where the Northwind
Meets the sea
There's a mother
Full of memory
Come my darling homeward bound
Where all is lost
Then all is found
All is found
Again you're gone
Off on a diff'rent path than mine
I'm left behind
Wondering if I should follow
You had to go
And of course it's always fine
I prob'ly could catch up with you tomorrow
But is this what it feels like to be growing apart
When did I become the one Who's always chasing your heart
Now I turn around and find
I am lost in the woods
North is South Right is left
When you're gone
I'm the one who sees you home
But now I'm lost in the woods
And I don't know what path you are on
I'm lost in the woods
Up till now
The next step was a question of how
I never thought it was a question of whether
Who am I
If I'm not your guy
Where am I if we're not together
Forever
Now I know you're my true North
Cause I am lost in the woods
Up is down Day is night
When you're not there
Oh you're my only landmark
So I'm lost in the woods
Wondering if you still care
But I'll wait
For a sign
For a sign That I'm your path
Cause you are mine You are mine
Until then
I'm lost in the woods Lost in the woods
I'm lost in the woods
Show yourself right now
Elsa be who you are
Oh I will Mama I will
Elsa's dead Olaf's dead
Anna cries
And then a bunch of important things happen that I forgot But all that matters is I was right
And water has memory and thus
I live
And so do you
Whoa
We live
We live Oh
Good story