As around 20000 people took part in a protest against
Meanwhile hundreds of anticapitalist protestors
REPORTER 1 Society continues to generate waste and squander resources
REPORTER 2 This is a global issue
REPORTER 3 John what's your view on the oil market's reaction
I mean earlier today we were
Hundreds of antiwar activists
REPORTER 4 Spain and Greece and right across Europe
resorted to using gas stun grenades and
rubber bullets to disperse the angry crowd
MALE PROTESTOR Hey stop filming The police can use it
Stay back Stay back
REPORTER 5 But the tough economy is pushing people to the brink
The question remains are their voices being heard
My mind is clearer now
At last all too well
I can see
Where we all soon will be
If you strip away
The myth from the man
You will see
Where we all soon will be
Jesus
You've started to believe the things they say of you
You really do believe this talk of God is true
And all the good you've done will soon get swept away
You've begun to matter more
Than the things you say
Listen Jesus I don't like what I see
All I ask is that you listen to me
And remember
I've been your righthand man all along
You have set them all on fire
They think they've found the new messiah
And they'll hurt you when they find they're wrong
I remember when this whole thing began
No talk of God then We called you a man
And believe me
My admiration for you hasn't died
But every word you say today
Just gets twisted round some other way
And they'll hurt you if they think you've lied
Nazareth your famous son should have stayed a great
unknown Like his father carving wood he'd have made good
Tables chairs and oaken
chests would have suited Jesus best He'd have caused
nobody harm
No one alarm
Listen Jesus do you care for your race
Can't you see we must keep in our place
We are occupied
Have you forgotten how far down we are
I am frightened by the crowd
For we are getting much too loud
And they will crush us if we go too far
If we go too far
Listen Jesus to the warning I give
Please remember that I want us to live
But it's sad to see our chances
Weakening with every hour
All of your followers are blind
They've too much heaven on their minds
It was beautiful but now it's sour
Yes it's all gone sour
Listen Jesus to the warning I give
Please remember that I want us to live
Come on come on
He won't listen to me
So it's all
Gone
Sour
What's the buzz Tell me what's ahappening
Why should you want to know
Don't you mind about the future
Don't you try to think ahead
Save tomorrow for tomorrow
Think about today instead
What's the buzz Tell me what's ahappening
Oh yeah
I could give you facts and figures
What's the buzz Tell me what's ahappening
I could give you plans and forecasts
When do we ride to Jerusalem
Even tell you where I'm going
Why should you want to know
Why are you obsessed with fighting
Times and fates you can't defy
If you knew the path we're riding
You'd understand it less than I
What's the buzz Tell me what's ahappening
Let me try to cool down your face a bit Let me try to cool down your face a bit
Let me try let me try Try to cool down your face a bit
Let me try let me try Let me try to cool down your face a bit
Mary ooh that is good
While you prattle through your supper
Where and when and who and how
She alone has tried to give me
What I need right here and now
What's the buzz Tell me what's ahappening
It seems to me a strange thing
Mystifying
That a man like you should waste his time
On women of her kind
Yes I can understand that
She amuses
But to let her stroke you and kiss your hair
It's hardly in your line
It's not that I object to her profession
But she doesn't fit in well with what we teach and say
It doesn't help us if you're inconsistent
They only need a small excuse
To put us all away
Who are you to criticise her
Who are you to despise her
Leave her leave her Let her be now
Leave her leave her She's with me now
If your slate is clean then you can throw stones
If your slate is not then leave her alone
I'm amazed that men like you
Can be so shallow thick and slow
There is not a man among you who knows or cares if I come or go
No you're wrong You're very wrong
How can you say that
Not one of you
Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto
Problems that upset you
Oh
Don't you know everything's all right
Yes everything's fine
And we want you to sleep well tonight
Let the world turn without you tonight
If we try we'll get by so forget all about us tonight
Everything's all right yes
Sleep and I shall soothe you
Calm you and anoint you
Myrrh for your hot forehead
Oh
Then you'll feel everything's all right
Yes everything's fine
And it's cool and the ointment's sweet
For the fire in your head and feet
Close your eyes close your eyes
And relax think of nothing tonight
Everything's all right yes
Woman your fine ointment Brandnew and expensive
Could have been saved for the poor
Why has it been wasted
We could have raised maybe
300 silver pieces or more
People who are hungry
People who are starving
Matter more than your
Feet and hair
Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto
Problems that upset you
Oh
Don't you know everything's all right
Yes everything's fine
And we want you to sleep well tonight
Let the world turn without you tonight
If we try we'll get by so forget all about us tonight
Everything's all right yes
Surely you're not saying
We have the resources
To save the poor from their lot
There will be poor always pathetically struggling
Look at the good things you've got
Think while you still have me
Move while you still see me
You'll be lost and you'll be so so sorry
When I'm gone
Sleep and I shall soothe you
Calm you and anoint you
Myrrh for your hot forehead
Oh
Then you'll feel everything's all right yes
Everything's fine
And it's cool and the ointment's sweet
For the fire in your head and feet
Close your eyes Close your eyes and relax
Think of nothing Tonight
Close your eyes close your eyes and relax
Think of nothing
Close your eyes close your eyes and relax Everything's all right yes
Good Caiaphas
The Council waits for you
The Pharisees
And priests are here for you
Ah gentlemen
You know why we are here
We've not much time
And quite a problem here
Hosanna Superstar
Listen to that howling mob
Of blockheads in the street
A trick or two with lepers
And the whole town's on its feet
He is dangerous
Jesus Christ Superstar
Tell us that you're who they say you are
The man is in town right now
To whip up some support
A rabblerousing mission
That I think we must abort
He is dangerous
Jesus Christ
Superstar
He is dangerous
Look Caiaphas They're right outside our yard
Quick Caiaphas Go call the Roman guard
No wait
We need a more permanent solution to our problem
What then to do about Jesus of Nazareth
Miracle wonder man hero of fools
No riots no army
No fighting no slogans
Infantile sermons the multitude drools
We dare not leave him to his own devices
His halfwitted fans will get out of control
But how do we stop him His glamour increases
By leaps every minute
He's top of the pole
I see bad things arising
The crowd crown him king which the Romans would ban
I see blood and destruction
Our elimination because of one man
Blood and destruction because of one man
Because because because of one man
Our elimination because of one man
Because because because of one
Cause of one cause of one man
What then to do about this Jesus mania
How do we deal with the carpenter king
Where do we start with a man who is bigger
Than John was when John did his baptism thing
Fools you have no perception
The stakes we are gambling are frighteningly high
We must crush him completely
So like John before him this Jesus must die
For the sake of the nation this Jesus must die
Must die must die this Jesus must die
So like John before him this Jesus must die
Must die must die This Jesus must Jesus must
Jesus must
Die
Hosanna heysanna sanna sanna ho
Sanna heysanna hosanna
Hey J. C J. C
Won't you fight for me
Sanna hosanna hey superstar
Tell the rabble to be quiet
We anticipate a riot
This common crowd
Is much too loud
Tell the mob who sing your song
That they are fools and they are wrong
They are a curse
They should disperse
Hosanna heysanna sanna sanna ho
Sanna heysanna hosanna
Hey J. C J. C
You're all right by me
Sanna hosanna hey superstar
Why waste your breath moaning at the crowd
Nothing can be done to stop the shouting
If every tongue were still
The noise would still continue
The rocks and stones themselves
Would start to sing
Hosanna heysanna sanna sanna ho
Sanna heysanna hosanna
Whoohoo
Hey J. C J. C
Won't you fight for me
Sanna hosanna hey superstar
Sing me a song but not for me alone
Yes yes
Sing out for yourselves
For you are blessed
There is not one of you
Who cannot win the Kingdom
The slow the suffering
The quick the dead
Hosanna heysanna sanna sanna ho
Sanna heysanna hosanna
Hey J. C J. C
Won't you die for me
Sanna hosanna hey superstar
Superstar
Christ you know I love you Did you see I waved
I believe in you and God so tell me that I'm saved
Jesus I am with you Touch me touch me Jesus
Jesus I am on your side Kiss me kiss me Jesus
Christ what more do you need to convince you
That you've made it and you're easily as strong
As the filth from Rome who rape our country
And who've terrorised our people for so long
Christ you know I love you Did you see I waved
They love you
I believe in you and God so tell me that I'm saved
Christ you know I love you Did you see I waved
Jesus I am with you Touch me touch me Jesus
Jesus I am on your side Kiss me kiss me Jesus
There must be over 50000
Screaming love and more for you
Every one of 50000
Would do whatever you asked them to
But keep them yelling their devotion
Add a touch of hate at Rome
You will rise to a greater power
We will win ourselves a home
You'll get the power and the glory
You'll get the glory
Forever and ever and ever
You'll get the power
You'll get the power and the glory
You'll get the glory
Forever and ever and ever
And the power
Forever
You'll get the glory
You'll get the power and the glory
And the power
Forever and ever and ever
You'll get the glory
You'll get the power and the glory
Forever amen
Forever and ever
Neither you Simon
Nor the 50000
Nor the Romans
Nor the Jews
Nor Judas
Nor the 12
Nor the priests nor the scribes
Nor doomed Jerusalem itself
Understand what power is
Understand what glory is
Understand at all
If you knew
All that I knew
My poor Jerusalem
You'd see the truth
But you'd close your eyes
While you live
Your troubles are many
Poor Jerusalem
To conquer death
You only have to die
I dreamed I met a Galilean
A most amazing man
He had that look
You very rarely find
The haunting hunted kind
I asked him
To say what had happened
How it all began
I asked again
He never said a word
As if he hadn't heard
And next
The room was full
Of wild and angry men
They seemed to hate this man
They fell on him and then
They disappeared again
Then I saw
Thousands of millions
Crying for this man
And then I heard them
Mentioning my name
And leaving me the blame
Roll on up for my price is down Come on in for the best in town
Take your pick of the finest wine Lay your bets on this bird of mine
Name your price I got everything
Come and buy it's all going fast
Borrow cash on the finest terms
Hurry now while stocks still last
Roll on up Jerusalem
Here it isn't us and them
While our temples still survive
We at least are still alive
Come all classes come all creeds
I can fix your wildest needs
Name your pleasure I will sell
I got heaven I got hell
What you see is what you get
No one's been disappointed yet
Don't be scared give me a try
There is nothing you can't buy
Roll on up for my price is down Come on in for the best in town
Take your pick of the finest wine Lay your bets on this bird of mine
My temple should be
A house of prayer
But you have made it
A den of thieves
Get out
My time
Is almost through
Little left to do
After all
I've tried for three years
Seems like 30
See my eyes I can hardly see
See me stand I can hardly walk
I believe you can make me whole
See his tongue he can hardly talk
See my skin I'm a mass of blood
Change my life oh I know you can
I believe you can make me well
See my purse I'm a poor poor man
Will you touch will you mend me Christ
Won't you touch will you heal me Christ
Will you kiss you can cure me Christ
Won't you kiss won't you pay me Christ
See our eyes we can hardly see
See us stand we can hardly walk
We believe you can make us whole
See the tongues that can hardly talk
See our skin we're a mass of blood
Change our lives oh we know you can
We believe you can make us well
You're the hope of the poor poor man
Will you touch will you mend me Christ
Won't you touch will you heal me Christ
Will you kiss you can cure me Christ
Won't you kiss won't you pay me Christ
See our eyes we can hardly see
See us stand we can hardly walk
We believe you can make us whole
See the tongues that can hardly talk
See our skin we're a mass of blood
Change our lives oh we know you can
We believe you can make us well
You're the hope of the poor poor man
Will you touch will you mend me Christ
Won't you touch will you heal me Christ
Will you kiss you can cure me Christ
Won't you kiss won't you pay me Christ
See my eyes I can hardly see
There's too
See me stand I can hardly walk
too many of you
I believe you can make me whole
Don't
See my tongue I can hardly talk
crowd me
See my skin I'm a mass of blood
Don't crowd me
See my legs I can hardly stand
We believe you can make us well
See my purse I'm a poor poor man
Will you touch will you mend me Christ
Won't you touch will you heal me Christ
Will you kiss you can cure me Christ
Won't you kiss won't you pay me Christ
Heal yourselves
Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto
Problems that upset you
Oh don't you know everything's all right
Yes everything's fine
And I think I shall sleep well tonight
Let the world turn without me tonight
If we try we'll get by so forget all about us tonight
I don't know how to love him
What to do
How to move him
I've been changed
Yes really changed
In these past few days
When I've seen myself
I seem like someone else
I don't know how to take this
I don't see why he moves me
He's a man
He's just a man
And I've had so many men before
In very many ways
He's just one more
Should I bring him down
Should I scream and shout
Should I speak of love
Let my feelings out
I never thought I'd come to this
What's it all about
Don't you think it's rather funny
I should be in this position
I'm the one
Who's always been
So calm so cool
No lover's fool
Running every show
He scares me so
I never thought
I'd come to this
What's it all about
Yet if he said he loved me
I'd be lost
I'd be frightened
I couldn't cope
Just couldn't cope
I'd turn my head
I'd back away
I wouldn't want to know
He scares me so
I want him so
I love him
So
Now if I help you it matters that you see
These sordid kind of things are coming hard to me
It's taken me some time to work out what to do
I weighed the whole thing up before I came to you
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned for all time
I came because I had to I'm the one who saw
Jesus can't control it like he did before
And furthermore I know that Jesus thinks so too
Jesus wouldn't mind that I'm here with you
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned for all time
Annas you're a friend a worldly man and wise
Caiaphas my friend I know you sympathise
Why are we the prophets Why are we the ones
We see the sad solution Know what must be done
I have no thought at all about my own reward
I really didn't come here of my own accord
Just don't say I'm
Damned
For all time
Cut the protesting
Forget the excuses
We want information
Get up off the floor
We have the papers
We need to arrest him
You know his movements
We know the law
Your help in this matter won't go unrewarded
We'll pay you in silver Cash on the nail
We just need to know where our soldiers can find him
With no crowd round him
Then we can't fail
I don't need your blood money
That doesn't matter our expenses are good
I don't want your blood money
But you might as well take it We think that you should
Think of the things you could do with that money
Choose any charity give to the poor
We've noted your motives We've noted your feelings
This isn't blood money it's a fee
Just a fee
It's a fee nothing more
On Thursday night
You'll find him where you want him
Far from the crowds
In the Garden Of
Gethsemane
Well done Judas
Good old Judas
Look at all my trials and tribulations
Sinking in a gentle pool of wine
Pool of wine
Don't disturb me now
I can see the answers
Till this evening is this morning
Life is fine
Always hoped that I'd be an apostle
Knew that I would make it if I tried
Then when we retire
We can write the gospels
So they'll still talk about us when we've died
The end
Is just a little harder When
brought about
By friends
For all you care
This wine could be my blood
This bread
Could be my body
The end
This is my blood you drink
This is my body you eat
If you would remember me
When you eat and drink
I must be mad thinking I'll be remembered
Yes I must be out of my head
Look at your blank faces
My name will mean nothing
Ten minutes after I'm dead
One of you denies me
One of you betrays me
Peter will deny me in just a few hours
Three times will deny me
And that's not all I see
One of you here dining One of my 12 chosen
Will leave to betray me
Cut out the dramatics You know very well who
Why don't you go do it
You want me to do it
Hurry they are waiting
If you knew why I do it
I don't care why you do it
To think I admired you Well now I despise you
You liar you Judas
You wanted me to do it
What if I just stayed here and ruined your ambition
Christ you deserve it
Hurry you fool Hurry and go
Save me your speeches I don't want to know
Go
Look at all my trials and tribulations
Sinking in a gentle pool of wine
What's that in the bread
It's gone to my head
Till this morning is this evening
Life is fine
Always hoped that I'd be an apostle
Knew that I would make it if I tried
Then when we retire
We can write the gospels
So they'll all talk about us when we've died
You sad pathetic man
Look what you've brought us to
Our ideals die around us
And all because of you
And now the saddest cut of all
Is someone had to turn you in
Like a common criminal
Like a wounded animal
A jaded mandarin
Like a jaded mandarin
Like a faded jaded jaded faded faded mandarin
Get out They're waiting
Get out
They're waiting
Oh they're waiting for you
Every time I look at you
I don't understand
Why you let the things you did get so out of hand
You'd have managed better
If you'd had it planned
Why
Look at all my trials and tribulations
Sinking in a gentle pool of wine
Don't disturb me now
I can see the answers
Till this evening is this morning
Life is fine
Always hoped that I'd be an apostle
Knew that I would make it if I tried
Then when we retire
We can write the gospels
So they'll still talk about us when we've died
Will no one stay awake with me
Peter
John
James
Will none of you wait with me
Peter
John
James
I only want to say
If there is a way
Take this cup away from me
For I don't want to taste its poison
Feel it burn me
I have changed
I'm not as sure
As when we started
Then I was inspired
Now
I'm sad and tired
Listen
Surely I've exceeded expectations
I tried for three years
Seems like 30
Could you ask as much
From any other man
But if I die
See the saga through
And do the things you ask of me
Let them hate me hit me hurt me
Nail me to their tree
I'd want to know I'd want to know my God
I'd want to see I'd want to see my God
Why I should die
Would I be more noticed
Than I ever was before
Would the things I've said and done
Matter any more
I'd have to know I'd have to know my Lord
I'd have to see I'd have to see my Lord
If I die what would be my reward
Have to know Have to know my Lord
Why
Should I die
Can you show me now
That I would not be killed in vain
Show me just a little
Of your omnipresent brain
Show me there's a reason
For your wanting me to die
You're far too keen on where and how
And not so hot on why
All right
I'll die
Just watch me die
See how I die
Then
I was inspired
Now
I'm sad and tired
After all
I've tried for three years
Seems like 90
Why then am I scared to finish
What I started
What you started
I didn't start it
God thy will be done
Take your only son
I will drink your cup of poison
Nail me to your cross
And break me
Bleed me
Beat me kill me
Take me now
Before I change my mind
Now
There he is
They're all asleep the fools
Judas must you betray me
With a kiss
What's the buzz Tell me what's happening
Tell me what's happening
Hang on Lord We're gonna fight for you
You hang on Lord We're gonna fight for you
Put away your sword
Don't you know that it's all over
It was nice but now it's gone
Why are you obsessed with fighting
Stick to fishing from now on
Tell me Christ how you feel tonight
Do you plan to put up a fight
Do you feel that you've had the breaks
What would you say were your big mistakes
How do you view your coming trial
Have your men proved at all worthwhile
Did you pick an efficient team
Is that it for the Jewish dream
Come with us to see Caiaphas
You'll just love the high priest's house
You'll just love seeing Caiaphas
You'll just die in the high priest's house
Come on God this is not like you
Let us know what you're gonna do
You know what your supporters feel
You'll escape in the final reel
Tell me Christ how you feel tonight
Do you plan to put up a fight
Do you feel that you had the breaks
What would you say were your big mistakes
Come with us to see Caiaphas
You'll just love the high priest's house
You'll just love seeing Caiaphas
You'll just die in the high priest's house
Now we have him now we've got him
Now we have him now We have got him now
Jesus you must realise
The serious charges facing you
You say you're the son of God in all your handouts
Well is it true
That's what you say You say that I am
There you have it gentlemen
What more evidence do you need
Judas thank you for the victim
Stay a while
and you'll see him bleed
Now we have him now we've got him
Take him to Pilate take him to Pilate
I think I've seen you somewhere
I remember
You were with that man they took away
I recognise your face
You've got the wrong man lady
I don't know him
And I wasn't where he was tonight
Never near the place
That's strange for I am sure I saw you with him
You were right by his side and yet you denied
I tell you I was never ever with him
But I saw you too He looked just like you
I don't know him
Peter
Don't you know what you have said
You've gone and cut him dead
I had to do it
Don't you see
Or else they'd go for me
It's what he told us you would do
I wonder how he knew
Who is
This broken man
Cluttering up
My hallway
Who is this unfortunate
Someone Christ King of the Jews
Oh so this is Jesus Christ
I am really quite surprised
You look so small
Not a king at all
We all know that you are news
But are you King
King of the Jews
That's what you say
What do
You mean by that
That is not an answer
You're deep
In trouble friend
Someone Christ King of the Jews
How can someone in your state
Be so cool about his fate
An amazing thing
This silent king
Since you come from Galilee
Then you need not come to me
You're Herod's race
He's Herod's case
Hosanna heysanna
Sanna sanna ho
Sanna heysanna hosanna
Hey J. C J. C
Please explain to me
You had everything
Where is it now
Jesus
I am overjoyed
To meet you facetoface
You've been getting quite a name
All around the place
Healing cripples
Ooh
Raising from the dead
Ah
That's pretty good
And now I understand you're God
At least that's what he said
So
You are the Christ
You're the great Jesus Christ
Prove to me that you're divine
Change my water into wine
That's all you need do
And I'll know it's all true
Come on King of the Jews
Jesus you just won't believe the hit you've made around here
You're all we talk about The wonder of the year
But oh what a pity if it's all a lie
Still I'm sure that you can rock the cynics if you try
So if you are the Christ
Yes the great Jesus Christ
Prove to me that you're no fool
Walk across my swimming pool
If you do that for me
Then I'll let you go free
Come on King of the Jews
So you decide
Is he the Lord or is he a fraud
Text our number now We'll see you after the break
I only ask things I'd ask any superstar
What is it that you've got that puts you where you are
Oh I am waiting
Yes I'm a captive fan
I'm dying to be shown that you are not just any man
So if you are the Christ
Yes the great Jesus Christ
Feed my household with this bread
You can do it on your head Or has something
gone wrong Why do you take so long
Come on King of the Jews
Hey aren't you
Scared of me Christ
Mr Wonderful Christ
You're a joke You're not the Lord You are nothing but a fraud
Take him away
He's got nothing to say
Get out you King of the
Get out you King of the Jews
Thank you for watching the show tonight
Join me tomorrow when I'll be interviewing One Direction
Thank you Birmingham and good night
I've been living to see you
Dying to see you but it shouldn't be like this
This was unexpected
What do I do now
Could we start again please
I've been very hopeful so far
Now for the first time
I think we're going wrong
Hurry up and tell me
This is all a dream
Or could we start again please
Could we start again please
I think you've made your point now
You've even gone a bit too far
To get your message home
Before it gets too frightening
We ought to call a halt
could we start again please
Could we start again please
I've been living to see you
Dying to see you but it shouldn't be like this
This was unexpected
What do I do now
Could we start again please
I think you've made your point now
You've even gone a bit too far to get your message home
Before it gets too frightening
We ought to call a halt
So could we start again please
Could we start again please
Could we start again
Guards
My God I saw him
He looked threequarters dead and he was so bad I had to turn my head
They beat him so hard that he was bent and lame
And I know who everybody's gonna blame
I don't believe he knows I acted for our good
I'd save him all this suffering if I could
Don't believe Our good
I'd save him if I could
Cut the confession forget the excuses
I don't understand why you're filled with remorse
All that you've said has come true with a vengeance
The mob turned against him You backed the right horse
What you have done will be the saving of Israel
You'll be remembered forever for this
And not only that You've been paid for your efforts
Pretty good wages for one little kiss
Christ I know you can't hear me
But I only did what you wanted me to
Christ I'd sell out the nation
For I have been saddled with the murder of you
I have been spattered with innocent blood
I shall be dragged through the slime and the mud
I shall be dragged through the slime
and the slime and the Slime and the mud
I
Don't know how to love him
I don't know why he moves me
He's a man
He's just a man
He is not a king
He's just the same
As anyone I know
He scares me so
When he's cold and dead
Will he let me be Does he love
Does he love me too
Does he care for me
My mind is in darkness now
Oh God I am sick
I've been used
And you knew all the time
God I will never ever know
Why you chose me
For your crime
For your bloody crime
You have murdered me
You have murdered me Murdered me
Murdered me Murdered me
Jesus
Poor old Judas
So long Judas
And so the King
Is once again my guest
And why is this
Was Herod unimpressed
We turn to Rome
To sentence Nazareth
We have no law
To put a man to death
We need him crucified
It's all you have to do
Talk to me Jesus Christ You have been brought here
Manacled beaten by your own people Do
you have the first idea why you deserve it
Listen King of the Jews Where is your kingdom
Look at me Am I a Jew
I have got no kingdom In this
world I'm through Through through
Talk to me Jesus Christ
There may be a kingdom for me somewhere
If I only knew
Then you are a king
That's what you say I am
I look for truth and find that I get damned
But what is truth Not easy to define We
both have truths Are yours the same as mine
Crucify him Crucify him
What do you mean You'd crucify your king
We have no king but Caesar
He's done no wrong No not the slightest thing
We have no king but Caesar Crucify him
Well this is new Respect for Caesar
Till now this has been noticeably lacking
Who is this Jesus Why is he different
You Jews produce messiahs by the sackful
We need him crucified It's all you have to do
Talk to me Jesus Christ
Look at your Jesus Christ
I'll agree he's mad
Ought to be locked up
But that is not a reason to destroy him
He's a sad little man not a king or God
Not a thief I need a crime
Kill him he says he's God He's a blasphemer
He'll conquer you and us and even Caesar
Do it Kill him
Crucify him Crucify him
Behold the man behold your shattered king
We have no king but Caesar
You hypocrites you hate us more than him
We have no king but Caesar Crucify him
I find no reason I see no evil
This man is harmless so why does he upset you
He's just misguided thinks he's important
But to keep you vultures happy I shall flog him
Crucify Crucify
Crucify him Crucify him
Crucify Crucify Crucify Crucify
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
Fourteen
Fifteen
Sixteen
Seventeen
Eighteen
Nineteen
Twenty
Twentyone
Twentytwo
Twentythree
Twentyfour
Twentyfive
Twentysix
Twentyseven
Twentyeight
Twentynine
Thirty
Thirtyone
Thirtytwo
Thirtythree
Thirtyfour
Thirtyfive
Thirtysix
Thirtyseven
Thirtyeight
Thirtynine
Where are you from Jesus
What do you want Jesus
Tell me
You've got to be careful
You could be dead soon
Could well be
Why do you not speak
When I have your life in my hands
How can you stay quiet
I don't believe you understand
You have nothing in your hands
Any power you have comes to you from far beyond
Everything is fixed and you can't change it
You're a fool Jesus Christ
How can I help you
Pilate crucify him Crucify
Remember Caesar
You have a duty to keep the peace
So crucify him
Remember Caesar
You'll be demoted you'll be deported
Crucify him
Remember Caesar
You have a duty to keep the peace So crucify him
You'll be demoted you'll be deported
Crucify him
Remember Caesar
You have a duty to keep the peace So crucify him
You'll be demoted you'll be deported
Crucify him
Don't let me stop
Your great selfdestruction
Die if you want to
You misguided martyr
I wash my hands
Of your demolition
Die if you want to
You innocent puppet
Every time I look at you I don't understand
Why you let the things you did get so out of hand
You'd have managed better if you'd had it planned
Why'd you choose such a backwards time and such a strange land
If you'd come today you would have reached a whole nation
Israel in 4 B. C had no mass communication
Don't you get me wrong
Don't you get me wrong now
Only wanna know
Only wanna know now
Only wanna know Only wanna know
I only wanna know
Jesus Christ
Who are you What have you sacrificed
Jesus Jesus
Jesus Christ
Superstar
Do you think you're what they say you are
Jesus Christ
Superstar
Do you think you're what they say you are
Hey let's go
Tell me what you think about your friends at the top
Who do you think besides yourself's the pick of the crop
Buddha was he where it's at Is he where you are
Could Muhammad move a mountain baby or did he just have good PR
Did you mean to die like that Was that a mistake
Or did you know that your messy death would be a record breaker
Don't you get me wrong
Don't you get me wrong now
Only wanna know
Only wanna know now
I only wanna know
Jesus Christ
Who are you What have you sacrificed
Jesus Christ Superstar Superstar
Do you think you're
what they say you are
Jesus Christ Superstar
Do you think you're
Do you think you're what they say you are
I only wanna know
I only wanna only wanna only wanna know I only wanna know now
Tell me tell me Won't you tell me Jesus
Don't you get me wrong Don't you get me wrong
Only wanna only wanna only wanna know Only wanna know now
Only wanna know Won't you tell me Jesus
Only wanna only wanna only wanna know now
Tell me tell me
Won't you tell me Jesus
Don't you get me wrong
Only wanna only wanna only wanna know now
Only wanna know
I only wanna know
Only wanna only wanna only wanna know Only wanna only wanna only wanna know
Tell me tell me Won't you tell me Jesus
Don't you get me wrong
Only wanna only wanna only wanna know now
Only wanna know
Yeah
Only wanna only wanna only wanna know now
Tell me tell me
Don't you get me wrong
Only wanna only wanna only wanna know Only wanna know
Are you what they
Say you are
God forgive them
They don't know what they're doing
Where is my mother
My God
My God why have you forsaken me
I'm thirsty I'm thirsty
It is finished
Father
into your hands
I commend
my spirit
Thank you Thanks again
Oh my gosh
I
I just don't know really what to say
Thank you to everybody
I mean what an extraordinary thing for me to see this brought back
to where I'd hoped it would always be in a rock and roll arena
And with this fabulous fabulous cast
One of the problems about being in a rock venue is
Tim will tell you and Mel will tell you
is that what happens is that about this time of night
the set gets moved so we could be here
And if I talked for hours and I said thank you to everybody
bits and pieces of the scenery would start to be removed from underneath me
and all of us
So I'm gonna keep it very very simple and I'd like to say
thank you to our fantastic cast
And
And Laurence Connor who directed the show so brilliantly
And our wonderful live rock band
We are live remember that
And just before they clear the set away
this may sound very very strange
I would like to dedicate this performance to one person
who was with me when Superstar was written
Her name was Sarah and I'd like to say
if you're in the audience Sarah thank you for coming
Thank you all of you
Jesus Christ
Who are you What have you sacrificed
Superstar
Do you think you're what they say you are
Jesus Christ
Superstar
Do you think you're what they say you are
Only wanna know
Only wanna only wanna Only wanna know now
Tell me tell me
Don't you get me wrong
Only wanna only wanna Only wanna know now
Only wanna know
Tell me tell me
Don't you get me wrong
Only wanna only wanna Only wanna know now