Factory Workers : Trust your feet in Price Son Our work is tried and true
Factory Workers : Practical pragmatical Steadfast and steady too
Factory Workers : If you stroll or saunter amble walk jog hop or run
Factory Workers : The prudent shoe for you to choose is Price and Son
Mr.Price : You might think beauty comes in spring and sparrow
Mr.Price : Or when the sunrise hits the morning dew
Mr.Price : But if you walk the straight and narrow
Mr.Price : You'll find the elegance and comfort is a
Mr.Price : Do you know what the most beautiful thing in the world is Charlie
Young Charlie : A shoe
Mr.Price : A shoe
Mr.Price : The most beautiful thing in the world
Mr.Price : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie That I know
Mr.Price : Sing it Charlie
Young Charlie;Mr.Price : The most beautiful thing in the world
Young Charlie;Mr.Price : the most beautiful thing in the world
Mr.Price : Charlie It's beautiful
Mr.Price : Four generations have paved the way before you
Mr.Price : You'll be next in line when my time is through
Mr.Price : And there's a saying handed down I've found of value
Mr.Price : That you can tell about a fella from his
Young Charlie : Shoe
Mr.Price;Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world
Mr.Price;Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie That I know I know
Mr.Price;Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie It's beautiful it's beautiful
Young Charlie : But what if I don't want to make shoes
Mr.Price : You're a right funny kid you are
Factory Workers : Ooh
Factory Workers : Ah
Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world
Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie That I know I know
Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie It's beautiful it's beautiful
Young Lola : Feels like I'm dancing across the high wire
Young Lola : Or bravely soaring off into the blue
Young Lola : Just like a rocket lifts with sparks and fire
Young Lola : Feels like the magic never ends inside these
Simon Sr. : Take those things off your feet and get inside here stupid boy
Nicola : Charlie here are the shoes I told you about Come have a look
Nicola : Aren't they the most necessary things ever
Nicola : If you want to slip a ring on my finger you'll first slip these shoes on my feet
Charlie Price : A tad posh for life in Northampton wouldn't you say
Nicola : Then good thing we're moving to London
Nicola : And won't they make a fitting farewell to the stink of cattle farms and tanning leather
Nicola : We may have been born in a small factory town but we sure as hell don't have to die there
Charlie Price : You see the price There's three months rent
Nicola : Pinch em or pay for em that's up to you
Nicola : but these shoes are in my future
Nicola : To new beginnings Hello to sunny days
Nicola : We're upward mobile now Goodbye to smalltown ways
Nicola : Till it's impossible to find A trace of what we left behind
Nicola : And the defining element is in these shoes
Nicola : The most beautiful thing in the world
Nicola : Charlie That I know I know
Nicola : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie It's beautiful it's beautiful
Mr.Price : Your life your future is right here in this factory You belong here
Charlie Price : No I belong with Nicola in London
Mr.Price : No you belong here
Charlie Price : Will you toast my journey
Mr.Price : But to leave your family and home for a job shopping in London
Charlie Price : Marketing
Charlie Price : Dad Richard Bailey has offered Nicola and me positions marketing real estate
Mr.Price : You're breaking me heart Charlie
Charlie Price : Oi to you Dad
Mr.Price : Shoes can protect a man's journey but only his heart can choose the path
Mr.Price : And so a toast to our own Charlie
Mr.Price : May you never fail to point your shoes back home
Factory Workers : To Charlie
Factory Workers : Beautiful it's beautiful
Mr.Price : These shoes are symbols of our family history
Nicola : These shoes will carry me to where I want to be
Young Lola : Feels like I'm dancing
Mr.Price : These shoes are symbols of our family history
Young Lola : Don't you go anywhere cause you belong to me
Charlie Price : You all do realize you're talking about shoes
Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world
Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie It's beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful
Factory Workers : Beautiful thing in the world
Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie
Factory Workers : That I know I know
Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world
Factory Workers : The most beautiful thing in the world Charlie
Factory Workers : It's beautiful it's beautiful it's beautiful
Factory Workers : It's beautiful
Nicola : God this flat is dirty and small and dreary and everything about it needs replacing except
Charlie Price : Me
Nicola : The address
Nicola : We're in London Charlie London
Nicola : London
Charlie Price : Where'd you say we were
Charlie Price : So you're happy Nic
Nicola : I'm ecstatic aren't you
Charlie Price : I'm happy if you're happy
Nicola : Oh is that really the best you can do
Charlie Price : I love you
Nicola : Well you can always go back and muck in with your dad
Charlie Price : And what make shoes
Charlie Price : That's not what I want
Nicola : What is it you want
Don : Sorry
Charlie Price : Hello
Charlie Price : Yes this is is his son
Charlie Price : When
Charlie Price : How
Woman : Trust your feet in Price Son Our work is tried and true
Woman : Practical pragmatical Steadfast and sturdy too
Woman : If you stroll or saunter amble walk jog hop or run
Woman : The prudent shoe for you to choose Is
Woman : Price and Son
George : Your father would be proud to see you standing here Mr Price
Charlie Price : Oh cripes George you've known me all my life
Charlie Price : Call me Charlie
George : Price Son must have a Mr Price Mr Price
Charlie Price : I'm glad you brought that up
Charlie Price : Now you see my father always assumed that one day I'd take over the factory but I never said I would
George : Excuse me sir if you could just they're waiting below
Charlie Price : Huh?
George : A word or two sir
George : They'd appreciate hearing from the new head of Price Son
Charlie Price : Oh that's not really necessary
Charlie Price : Just a word sir
Don : Oi oi quiet down
Don : The little prince got somethin to say
Charlie Price : Hello hi
Charlie Price : Cheers um
Charlie Price : Thanks for the flowers and the notes and whatnot
George : Perhaps a word of encouragement about the future
Charlie Price : Yes um
Charlie Price : Let's keep making shoes
Charlie Price : great shoes
Charlie Price : And good luck with that
Lauren : Wow that wanker's got a way with words
Pat : Mr Price come quick Chambers have sent back their entire shoe order
George : After you Mr Price
Delivery Man : Can someone sign so I can get the rest of these shoes off me truck
Charlie Price : Is there something wrong with them
Delivery Man : Ask someone who cares Sign all three copies
Charlie Price : All right Pat I guess we should put these in the store room
Pat : The Chambers winter shoe order is already in there
Charlie Price : What are these
Pat : The Chambers spring shoe order
Charlie Price : And we're currently manufacturing
Pat : The Chambers summer shoe order and it's a big one
Charlie Price : You telling me we have a year's worth of shoes and no one to buy them
Pat : It started some time back Chambers cut down orders but
Pat : cutting back production would have meant cutting back workers hours and your father wouldn't hear of it
George : I would have thought he'd told you
George : but then you were busy at university and with your girl
Charlie Price : Yeah but what's to be done with all these shoes
George : Once or twice your father sold overstock to the discount chains
Charlie Price : So it's happened before
Pat : Never as bad as this
George : Actually of late he seemed less concerned
George : He said he'd settled on some sort of plan
Charlie Price : Sort of plan
Charlie Price : What sort of plan
Factory Workers : Whoa
Harry;Ensemble : Singin whoa
Harry;Ensemble : Whoa
Harry : Ladies and gents band's on a break Back in five
Harry : Not bad for a discount shoe salesman eh
Charlie Price : Really terrific Harry To you
Harry : To your father yeah
Harry : He was a gent
Charlie Price : And to yours
Harry : Ooh
Harry : Well mate I assume you didn't come all the way to London just to buy me a drink
Charlie Price : Yeah seems like we find ourselves with 600 pairs of brogues and no buyer
Harry : Chambers finally canceled your orders completely yeah
Charlie Price : But then I remembered the time your father found his stock short and my dad at no small expense
Charlie Price : took on the task of filling the shortfall
Harry : No fair conjuring ancient history
Charlie Price : Look I'll give em to you at cost
Charlie Price : Cost Harry for old time's sake
Harry : You see these Charlie
Harry : I import them from Slovakia and sell them
Harry : at a fraction of your cost
Charlie Price : But they're shite
Charlie Price : A Price shoe will last a man a lifetime
Charlie Price : The poor sod who buys these will need new ones in a season
Harry : And I'll be right there to sell him a pair at a very affordable price
Charlie Price : Oi ever hear the saying poor people stay poor because they buy cheap shoes
Harry : You ever hear the saying no matter how far down the wrong road you've gone turn back
Harry : Selling off inventory's only gonna prolong the inevitable
Harry : But tell me Charlie is manufacturing shoes really what you had your cap set on
Charlie Price : Is selling cheap imports your aspiration
Harry : If my life was nothing more than shoes you'd find me swinging by my tie from a steam pipe
Harry : My guitar my mates and music are my escape
Harry : It ain't perfect but it's what I got
Harry : Remember the pub where our fathers went
Harry : To spend the end of their day
Charlie Price : Remember the yard behind the pub
Charlie Price : Where we'd run and play
Harry : Well the places we loved came down with a blast
Charlie Price : High rise flats rose up so fast
Harry : You can't go back
Harry : You can't make it last
Harry : You've got to take what you've got
Harry : Even when your life is in knots
Harry : You take aim take your shot
Harry : Sometimes you've gotta rewrite the plot
Harry : You got to take what you got
Charlie Price : You'd always say that one of these days
Charlie Price : You'd get out of Northampton town
Harry : You'd always say that you wouldn't stay
Harry : No you wouldn't stick around
Charlie Price : Never knew what I wanted before
Charlie Price : Now I'm even more unsure
Harry : You can't move on
Harry : If you're still in the past hehe Listen
Harry : You've gotta take what you've got
Harry : Even when your life is in knots
Harry : You take aim take your shot
Harry : Sometimes you gotta rewrite the plot
Harry : You've got to take what you got
Charlie Price : Everybody's telling me
Charlie Price : What I need to be
Charlie Price : Change with the times move to London town
Charlie Price : Or live out a legacy Well
Charlie Price : maybe this time I take a chance
Charlie Price : Leap into the vast expanse
Charlie Price : Maybe this time I seize my destiny
Charlie Price : My destiny
Harry : If you're on the wrong road turn back
Charlie Price : So you'll help me out
Charlie Price : Thank you Harry
Harry : Two three
Harry : You've got to take what you've got
Harry : Even when your life is in knots
Harry : You take aim take your shot
Harry : Sometimes you gotta rewrite the plot
Charlie Price : You got to take what you got
Harry : You've got to take what you got
Beggar : You have something to spare for a thirsty man eh
Charlie Price : Here here
Charlie Price : A Price Son shoe will last a man a lifetime
Beggar : Do I look like a man whose problem is shoes
Lola(Simon) : All right fellas let's go easy now
Bully : However you like it darling
Bully : We can start out easy and take it from there
Lola(Simon) : I'm all for progress
Charlie Price : Hey hey hey come now gents
Charlie Price : think maybe you've had your
Bully : And what if I said mind your own business
Charlie Price : Let the lady go on her way
Bully : You can take her place if you fancy
Lola(Simon) : Step aside sir I can handle the likes of these
Angels : Lola
Lola(Simon) : He's not the first man to fall for me and I promise he won't be the last
Lola(Simon) : Leave expectations at the door
Lola(Simon) : Just let your eyes explore
Lola(Simon) : My cinematic flair
Lola(Simon) : From my boot to derriere
Lola(Simon) : I got a lacy silken feel
Lola(Simon) : With arms as hard as steel
Lola(Simon) : I am freedom I'm constriction A potpourri of contradiction
Lola(Simon) : Leave that humdrum pace of glum behind
Lola(Simon) : Once you walk inside these doors
Lola(Simon) : You're mine
Lola(Simon) : Now let me blow your mind
Lola(Simon) : And like shazam and bam
Lola(Simon) : Here I am yes ma'am
Lola(Simon) : I am Lola
Lola(Simon) : And like je suis oohwee
Lola(Simon) : That's me ebony
Lola(Simon) : I am Lola
Lola(Simon) : Step in step in to a dream
Lola(Simon) : Where glam where glamor is extreme
Lola(Simon) : Welcome welcome to my fantasy
Lola(Simon) : We give good epiphany
Lola(Simon) : So come and take my hand and welcome to the land
Lola(Simon) : Of Loooo Lola
Lola(Simon) : No need to be embarrassed
Lola(Simon) : I like to be looked at and you like to look
Lola(Simon) : I know a way to make us both happy
Lola(Simon) : Lola oh
Lola(Simon) : Lola ooh yeah
Angels : Lola
Lola(Simon) : Got Ginger Rogers savoir faire
Lola(Simon) : With the moves of Fred Astaire
Lola(Simon) : I'm black Jesus I'm black Mary
Lola(Simon) : But this Mary's legs are hairy
Lola(Simon) : I'm your coco butter bitch
Lola(Simon) : Not just cookie cutter kitsch
Lola(Simon) : I provide the unexpected
Lola(Simon) : With a prize that's undetected
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Let Lola lift you to your highest highs
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Let's explore your flight of fancy tonight
Lola(Simon) : I am gonna treat you right
Lola(Simon) : And like shazam
Lola(Simon) : and bam Here I am yes ma'am
Lola(Simon) : I am Lola
Angels;Lola(Simon) : And like je suis oohwee
Lola(Simon) : That's me ebony
Lola(Simon) : I am hey Lo Lo Lo Lo Lo Lola
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Step in step in to a dream
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Where glam where glamor is extreme
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Welcome welcome to my fantasy
Lola(Simon) : We give good epiphany
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Step in step in to a dream
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Where glam where glamor is extreme
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Welcome welcome to my fantasy
Lola(Simon) : We give good epiphany
Lola(Simon) : So come and take my hand and welcome to the land
Lola(Simon) : Of Lo
Lola(Simon) : Lola
Lola(Simon) : Lola say my name
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Lola hey oh
Angels : Lola
Lola(Simon) : So come and take my hand and welcome to the land
Lola(Simon) : Of Lo
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Lola
Lola(Simon) : Oh
Lola(Simon) : He lives
Lola(Simon) : Hello
Lola(Simon) : They call me Lola because it's my name
Lola(Simon) : Very sweet you riding to my rescue
Lola(Simon) : Very Prince Charming
Charlie Price : You don't appear to be in much need of rescue
Lola(Simon) : A girl's got to know how to look after herself
Lola(Simon) : There are some very funny people out there
Lola(Simon) : How's your chin
Lola(Simon) : Ooh don't flatter yourself
Lola(Simon) : I will say one thing for you
Lola(Simon) : You're hardheaded
Lola(Simon) : Your jaw whacked my heel clean off
Charlie Price : Oh well I could fix these for ya
Charlie Price : but they're just cheap boots
Lola(Simon) : Very expensive boots but cheaply made
Lola(Simon) : I'd give my left tit for a shoe that could stand up to me
Lola(Simon) : Oh but it's my curse to love these things
Charlie Price : Oh here here please um
Charlie Price : Allow me
Lola(Simon) : Ooh
Lola(Simon) : Well thanks again mister
Lola(Simon) : Not to be presumptive
Lola(Simon) : but you are a mister
Charlie Price : Charlie from Northampton
Lola(Simon) : Well Charlie from Northampton
Lola(Simon) : if you'll excuse me I need to start the second show
Lola(Simon) : There's a room full of people waiting to feel normal by comparison
Lola(Simon) : But please feel free to join in the fun
Charlie Price : Oh very kind thank you but I must be getting back
Charlie Price : I've got a factory full of folk need firing tomorrow morning
Lola(Simon) : And they call me kinky
Lola(Simon) : Well as Oscar Wilde said Be yourself
Lola(Simon) : Everyone else is already taken
Angels : Lola
Lola(Simon) : Ladies gentlemen
Lola(Simon) : and those who have yet to make up their minds
Lola(Simon) : I invite you to look around
Lola(Simon) : You might see something you want
Charlie Price : Oh
Lola(Simon) : Did you catch that
Lola(Simon) : I just made a man disappear with one wink
Lola(Simon) : Oh what a shame
Lola(Simon) : My girls so wanted to meet him
Lola(Simon) : Isn't that right
Lola(Simon) : Now don't worry you're perfectly safe
Lola(Simon) : My girls are harmless
Lola(Simon) : But then again this is live theater so you never know
Lola(Simon) : Leave expectations at the door
Lola(Simon) : Just let your eyes explore
Lola(Simon) : My cinematic flair from my boot to derriere
Trish : A twoweek notice
Charlie Price : And then what
Charlie Price : As I've said I've found someone to buy our current stock
Charlie Price : but no orders for next season I'm afraid we'll have to shut down
Trish : Please Charlie me girl's just started school It's the uniforms love and me with no husband to help
Charlie Price : I'm sorry Trish
Charlie Price : but Chambers has canceled our contract What else can I do
Trish : Is that what all this is about
Trish : them Chambers shoe returns
Trish : All right so you've had some bad news but chin up me duck
Trish : As me mother used to say
Trish : Don't worry today because today ain't tomorrow
Trish : So thanks for the chat Charlie and good luck
Charlie Price : What
Charlie Price : Trish no it's not like that
Charlie Price : Trish I have to
Lola(Simon) : And like shazam
Lola(Simon) : and bam Here I am yes ma'am
Lola(Simon) : I am Lola
Charlie Price : So I'm giving everyone their twoweek notice We'll use the time to ratchet down production
Charlie Price : take inventory clean the machines
Don : Who are you kidding
Don : I've been workin here since you and me was kids
Don : I'm third generation Price Son
Charlie Price : Yeah well the fact is that nine out of 10 shoe manufacturers have shut down already
Charlie Price : And unless I can find a miracle buyer what else can I do
Don : Do what you like but you can't fire me
Don : Remember back at school when you tried to cut me off your rugby team
Don : Remember what happened
Charlie Price : You shoved me down a flight of stairs and got suspended
Don : Yeah but I stayed on the team
Lola(Simon) : And like je suis oohwee
Lola(Simon) : That's me ebony
Lola(Simon) : I am Lola
Charlie Price : But what else can I do We can't keep making things no one wants
Lauren : Then make something they do
Charlie Price : Make something they do what
Lauren : Make something they do want
Lauren : Change the product
Charlie Price : This is a shoe factory we make shoes
Lauren : Not ones anyone wants
Lauren : Over at the Whitcomb factory they noted a lack of allweather hiking shoes so
Lauren : They started making allweather hiking shoes and saved the factory
Lauren : Toby's has started making sandals
Lauren : All the sods who survived went out looking for an underserved niche market and aimed to fill the void
Lauren : They didn't sit up in their offices whining
Lauren : What else can I do
Nicola : Well my wedding shoes are still here but my fiance's nowhere in sight
Charlie Price : Sorry Nic I'm completely underwater
Nicola : You're saying you still haven't left
Nicola : Charlie we have an appointment
Nicola : If we lose this hall we'll wind up gettin married in a fish and chip shop
Charlie Price : Yeah now that sounds like fun
Nicola : Are you seriously standing me up
Charlie Price : Come on Nic do we really need a showy wedding
Charlie Price : In the end shouldn't it be about us
Nicola : A wedding announces to the world who you as a couple are going to be
Charlie Price : I've just given twoweek notices to George Don Maggie Trish
Nicola : Oh bloody hell
Nicola : I forgot to ask Maggie to be a bridesmaid
Nicola : She'd like that wouldn't she
Charlie Price : I think she'd like getting paid better
Charlie Price : Honestly Nic wouldn't saving all those people's jobs tell the world a little bit more about us
Charlie Price : than having a fancy party in a pair of 900quid shoes you're only gonna wear once
Charlie Price : Talk about your niche market
Nicola : Talk about what niche market
Charlie Price : Take what you've got change the product find an underserved nice market and they certainly are
Charlie Price : a completely underserved niche market
Nicola : Have you gone off your nut
Charlie Price : Nic I'll ring you back
Charlie Price : Lauren to the office Come see Mr Pri Charlie in his office
Charlie Price : now
Angels : Step in
Lola(Simon) : step in to a dream
Angels : Where glam
Lola(Simon) : where glamor is extreme
Angels : Welcome
Lola(Simon) : welcome to my fantasy
Lola(Simon) : We give good epiphany
Lola(Simon) : So come and take my hand and welcome to the land
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Lo
Lola(Simon);Angels : Lola
Charlie Price : Yes
Charlie Price : Yeah
Lola(Simon) : Oh
Lola(Simon) : You've returned
Lola(Simon) : You've got a dark horse in this boyfriend of yours
Charlie Price;Lauren : No no no no no no no
Charlie Price;Lauren : Nothing's going on here She's not my
Lauren : He's got another girl
Lauren : I just stuff his boxes
Lauren : At least for the next two weeks
Lola(Simon) : What are you staring at
Lauren : Oh you'll have to forgive him
Lauren : We don't get many transvestites in Northampton
Lola(Simon) : Ha don't kid yourself
Lola(Simon) : You're never more than 10 steps away from some sort of crossdresser
Lola(Simon) : In any case those are not transvestites
Lola(Simon) : They're drag queens
Lauren : There's a difference
Lola(Simon) : Yes
Lola(Simon) : A drag queen puts on a frock and suddenly she's Cleopatra
Lola(Simon) : A transvestite gets done up and often as not
Lola(Simon) : looks like Winston Churchill in his mother's knickers
Charlie Price : And so you are
Lola(Simon) : Insulted that you need to ask
Lola(Simon) : So you fired this lovely girl
Charlie Price : Things aren't very good in men's shoes
Lola(Simon) : Certainly I'm not
Charlie Price : How much do you weigh
Lola(Simon) : Exactly the right amount
Charlie Price : For a man but you're wearing women's boots
Lola(Simon) : And I thought you weren't paying attention
Charlie Price : Well it's all wrong
Lola(Simon) : Hasn't stopped me yet
Charlie Price : A heel made for a woman cannot possibly support a man's weight
Charlie Price : You need something special
Lola(Simon) : And I deserve something special
Charlie Price : Yes well if you transveterans
Charlie Price : are everywhere like you say
Charlie Price : then there must be a niche market
Charlie Price : for properly builttolast women's boots for women who are men
Charlie Price : Yes
Charlie Price : No
Charlie Price : The international shoe exhibition is in Milan next month
Charlie Price : If we had something new to show something no one else in the world has to offer it might just save the factory
Lauren : Oh
Charlie Price : I'd like to measure you up go back and make a sample pair
Lola(Simon) : First riddle me this
Lola(Simon) : Who gets to keep the boots
Lola(Simon) : And I'll give you a hint
Lola(Simon) : The correct answer is you do Lola
Charlie Price : You do Lola
Lola(Simon) : Ah and where do I pick them up
Lola(Simon) : Price's of Northampton is it
Charlie Price : Oh no no no no no no no I'll bring them to you I come to London all the time
Lola(Simon) : You don't want me to come to Northampton do you
Charlie Price : No
Lola(Simon) : I'm sorry but I have a terrible habit
Lola(Simon) : of doing exactly the opposite of what people ask
Lola(Simon) : which might explain why I'm wearing this frock today
Lola(Simon) : See you in Northampton
Lola(Simon) : Oh and make them
Lola(Simon) : red
Charlie Price : Do I belong here am I what's wrong here
Charlie Price : Know what I'm doin or am I a fraud
Charlie Price : Do I fit in where do I begin
Charlie Price : Same old Charlie frightened and flawed
Charlie Price : So I Pretend
Charlie Price : And keep my head up like I know
Charlie Price : How this Will end
Charlie Price : Maybe these pieces are fallin together
Charlie Price : Making me feel like I'm not alone
Charlie Price : Punching holes into this leather
Charlie Price : This kinda feels like I'm back home
Charlie Price : I'm watching myself
Charlie Price : And I know what to do
Charlie Price : Hey look at me now
Charlie Price : It's a shoe
Charlie Price : This is time for a shakeup Look at me wake up
Charlie Price : Taking control
Charlie Price : This is a new beginning My gears are spinning
Charlie Price : Let's rock and roll
Charlie Price : Just put
Charlie Price : One foot
Charlie Price : Onward and forward
Charlie Price : I used to be a zero but now I clearly feel
Charlie Price : That I may be the hero who reinvents the heel
Charlie Price : I may be facing the impossible
Charlie Price : I may be chasing after miracles
Charlie Price : And there may be the steepest mountain to overcome
Charlie Price : But this is step one
Charlie Price : This is step one
Charlie Price : Who knew I had it in me Let me begin see
Charlie Price : Where this could go
Charlie Price : I've got knowledge and knowhow Don't stop the show now
Charlie Price : Don't stop the flow
Charlie Price : Just put
Charlie Price : One foot
Charlie Price : Onward and forward yeah
Charlie Price : I used to live in limbo never dying to begin
Charlie Price : But now it's sink or swim so I better dive right in
Charlie Price : I may be facing the impossible
Charlie Price : I may be chasing after miracles
Charlie Price : And there may be the steepest mountain to overcome
Charlie Price : But this is step one
Charlie Price : It's not just a factory
Charlie Price : This is my family
Charlie Price : No one's gonna shut us down
Charlie Price : Not while Charlie Price is around
Charlie Price : We may be facing the impossible
Charlie Price : We may be chasing after miracles
Charlie Price : And there may be the steepest mountain to overcome
Charlie Price : We may be facing the impossible
Charlie Price : We may be chasing after miracles
Charlie Price : And there may be the steepest mountain to overcome
Charlie Price : But this is step one
Charlie Price : Look what Charlie boy has done
Charlie Price : This is step one
Lola(Simon) : What is this
Charlie Price : Your boot
Lola(Simon) : Burgundy
Charlie Price : Is something wrong
Lola(Simon) : Please Lord tell me I've not inspired something
Lola(Simon) : burgundy
Charlie Price : At the club you said
Lola(Simon) : Red You didn't specify
Lola(Simon) : Red
Charlie Price : Burgundy is a red
Lola(Simon) : Burgundy's the color of hot water bottles
Lola(Simon) : Red is the color of sex
Lola(Simon) : Burgundy's for cardigans and golF apparel
Lola(Simon) : Red is passion and danger and signs that say do not enter
Pat : I've always been partial to pink
Lola(Simon) : Pink is for playthings yellow for warnings
Lola(Simon) : purple for princes black is for wannabes
Lola(Simon) : Green is for pickles
Lola(Simon) : but red
Lola(Simon) : is for
Lola(Simon) : sex
Charlie Price : Well at least try them on
Charlie Price : I guarantee they're comfy
Lola(Simon) : Sex shouldn't be comfy
Trish : Oh good I thought it was just me
Lola(Simon) : Comfy's what's been putting you out of business
Lola(Simon) : You want to save this place
Charlie Price : Yeah
Lola(Simon) : Then you're going to have to start manufacturing sex
Lola(Simon) : two and a half feet of irresistible
Lola(Simon) : tubular
Lola(Simon) : sex
Charlie Price : But at least look at the heel
Charlie Price : You sort can dance all night and beat up a football team
Charlie Price : but this heel will still be whole
Charlie Price : Isn't that what you wanted
Lola(Simon) : Not if it means looking like a Ukrainian folk dancer
Lola(Simon) : Ladies
Lola(Simon) : Would you go out in something like this
Ladies : No
Don : But I say you'd look all right in em
Don : sweetheart
Lola(Simon) : And what's your name
Lola(Simon) : darling
Don : It's Don to you sweetheart
Lola(Simon) : Well
Lola(Simon) : Don
Lola(Simon) : if you can't get women to wear them
Lola(Simon) : you'll never get em on blokes like me
Lola(Simon) : And that's the color red you need
Lola(Simon) : And Charlie if you want to put them over the top
Lola(Simon) : look to the heel
Lola(Simon) : The sex is in the heel
Lola(Simon) : Even if you break it
Lola(Simon) : The sex is in the feel Honey you can't fake it
Lola(Simon) : Jack it up cause I'm no flat tire
Lola(Simon) : Mack it up six inches higher
Lola(Simon) : oh The sex is in the heel
Lola(Simon) : So just embrace it
Lola(Simon) : I hope you don't mind but I brought my own backup
Lola(Simon) : Ladies tell the man what you need
Angels : From London to Milan
Angels : Stilettos are an ism
Angels : In red and neon life
Angels : Gimme Jimmy Choo Choo Choo Choo Choo
Angels : Shoes in New York Paris Hong Kong
Angels : Live it like an ism
Angels : Seduction amplified
Angels : The heel is the transmission
Pat : Asserting actual scientific reason Heels tense the leg and the hindquarter region
Pat : Lifting the rear and making it appear Pert and ready for mating season
Lola(Simon) : That's the scientific view But you know what I say
Lola(Simon) : The sex is in the heel fierce as you can make it
Lola(Simon) : The sex is the appeal kinky boys can shake it
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Pump it up till it's ostentatious
Angels;Lola(Simon) : Funk it up it's contagious whoo
Angels;Lola(Simon) : The sex is in the heel so just embrace it
Lola(Simon) : Here we go
Angels : From London to Milan
Angels : Feed that chic hot feeling
Angels : In red and neon life
Angels : Won't go nowhere without my my my Manolos
Angels : New York Paris Hong Kong
Angels : Stilettos leave em reeling
Angels : Seduction amplified
Angels : The heel should hit the ceiling
Angels;Lola(Simon) : The heel should hit the
Lola(Simon) : The sex is in the heel heel
Lola(Simon);Angels : From London to Milan
Angels : Stilettos are an ism
Angels : In red and neon life
Angels : Got a lotta PPPPPPPrada
Angels : New York Paris Hong Kong
Angels : Live it like an ism
Angels : Seduction amplified
Angels : The heel is the transmission
Lauren : These are brilliant I'd wear any one of em
Charlie Price : You're not our niche market
George : There are some very interesting ideas here
Charlie Price : But they're all stiletto heels It's physically impossible to make a stiletto that can bear the weight of a fullgrown man
George : Not so fast
George : If we could mold the steel
George : One piece from ball to heel
George : We'd underpin it and remake it So not even Don could break it
Charlie Price : Sorry
George : I said
George : Underpin it and remake it So not even Don could break it
Charlie Price : Yeah you think
George : We can do it
Lauren : We can do it
Charlie Price : We can do it
Angels;Factory Workers : From London to Milan
Angels;Factory Workers : Stilettos are an ism
Angels;Factory Workers : In red and neon life
Angels;Factory Workers : Gimme big red bbbbbbboots
Angels;Factory Workers : New York Paris Hong Kong
Angels;Factory Workers : Watch out world watch out world
Angels;Factory Workers : Here we come
Charlie Price : Lola
Charlie Price : Lola did you hear me
Charlie Price : I said we can do it
Lola(Simon) : All right but you'll have to be quick We have an eight o'clock show
Charlie Price : No no no seriously we think we have a way to make the boots and if we can and if you're right
Charlie Price : about never being far from a cross customer
Charlie Price : we might just have something
Lola(Simon) : That there's cause for celebration
Charlie Price : Yes
Lola(Simon) : Yes
Lola(Simon) : I need a van to take seven to the train station
Charlie Price : You've got to stay
Lola(Simon) : I'll ring back
Lola(Simon) : Me
Lola(Simon) : Stay
Lola(Simon) : Here
Lola(Simon) : Yes
Lola(Simon) : No
Lola(Simon) : Charlie my boy I abandoned the provinces years ago
Lola(Simon) : and your fellow Don in there was a stellar reminder why
Charlie Price : Forget about Don he's just
Lola(Simon) : Just like every other man in Northampton
Lola(Simon) : Charlie
Lola(Simon) : I've lived this life once I'm not doing it again
Charlie Price : Oh so you head back to London and I'm here
Charlie Price : trying to save a factory that four generations of my family poured their life's blood into
Lola(Simon) : Get to the part that applies to me
Charlie Price : I'm willing to gamble the fate of this whole enterprise on you as a designer
Lola(Simon) : Me a designer
Lola(Simon) : Now who's kidding who
Lola(Simon) : Hand me glitter feathers and a hot glue gun and I can make the world a pretty place
Lola(Simon) : But me a designer
Charlie Price : I've been forcefed shoes since childhood
Charlie Price : but I never seen nothing like what you just drew
Lola(Simon) : They're drawings
Lola(Simon) : the silly scribblings of a braggarty sissy boy who doesn't know when to shut his gob
Lola(Simon) : Oh have a gander at me Charlie
Lola(Simon) : I wouldn't trust me to babysit a cactus
Charlie Price : You are passionate about shoes
Charlie Price : I haven't heard anyone talk about a heel that way since
Charlie Price : well not since my father
Charlie Price : You know how rare it is to feel that way about something You know how jealous I am
Charlie Price : I never been passionate about nothin
Charlie Price : Well maybe snoggin
Lola(Simon) : Ah but you're forgetting something
Lola(Simon) : I don't know how to make a shoe
Charlie Price : It just so happens I do
Charlie Price : If we're to succeed we'll need to produce a boot
Charlie Price : unlike anything anyone has ever seen before
Charlie Price : That's where you come in
Charlie Price : And if we don't want to be laughed out of Milan they'll have to be executed so impeccably
Charlie Price : that no one can deny we're comers to be reckoned with and that God help us is where I come in
Charlie Price : Three weeks
Charlie Price : Three weeks Lola that's all I'm asking
Lola(Simon) : Is that a taxi or a police car
Lola(Simon) : Guess I'll find out when I offer him money
Charlie Price : Opportunity has fallen into your lap
Charlie Price : The easy thing maybe even the sensible thing would be to walk off and have a laugh about the time some nutter offered you a job
Charlie Price : designing kinky boots
Charlie Price : But I promise if you do the rest of your life you'll wonder what if I'd said yes
Charlie Price : What if I'd stayed
Lola(Simon) : A designer
Lola(Simon) : I guess I could get used to the name Kinky Boots
Lola(Simon) : Or better yet
Lola(Simon) : Lola's Kinky Boots
Lola(Simon) : I hope you know you're going to have to make me a new sign
Lola(Simon) : And I warn you it had better be
Lola(Simon) : red
Factory Workers : If you stroll or saunter amble walk jog hop or run
Factory Workers : The prudent shoe for you to choose Is
Factory Workers : Price Son
Charlie Price : Price Son spent the last century making a range of shoes for men
Charlie Price : We will begin this century by making a range of shoes for a range of men
Charlie Price : There's no denying it's do or die but do we will
Charlie Price : Are there any questions
Charlie Price : All right let's make shoes boots
George : If I could just get your signature on these checks Mr Price
Charlie Price : George it's Charlie
George : Mr Price you've earned it
George : Today at least
Charlie Price : Mr Price eh
Charlie Price : Better than WhatElseCanIDoCharlie
Charlie Price : Oi I'm TakeChargeCharlie all the way now
Lauren : Very impressive
Charlie Price : Yeah well thanks to you
Lauren : Any time
Charlie Price : No I mean it
Charlie Price : Thanks to you
Charlie Price : Thank you
Marge : Charlie can I get your opinion here
Charlie Price : Excuse me
Lauren : Oh no
Lauren : Don't you dare
Lauren : Girl girl girl I'm warning you
Lauren : I think I've got a crush
Lauren : I can't
Lauren : I think I'm falling for him
Lauren : Oh no
Lauren : Why not
Lauren : Women have been making bad choices
Lauren : Since the beginning of time
Lauren : Are you gonna be another one of mine
Lauren : Oh
Charlie Price : Lauren
Charlie Price : I was thinkin that keepin you on the production line is a waste of your talents
Charlie Price : I'd like you to work with me on the Milan show
Lauren : You don't owe me a job
Charlie Price : No
Lauren : No
Charlie Price : Well all this started with you having a fit
Lauren : I had a fit but you had an idea
Lauren : And that's why some of us get our names on factories and the rest on punch cards
Charlie Price : Well as someone whose name is on a factory I am asking if I may please place your name
Charlie Price : on one of my executive punch cards
Charlie Price : Good
Charlie Price : What
Lauren : Have I got something in my teeth
Lauren : No it's just funny how you can know someone all your life and not really know em at all
Charlie Price : I guess I'll see you later
Lauren : Sure thing boss
Lauren : Used to think you were from outer space
Lauren : Who's this brighteyed guy in your place
Lauren : You're kind of cute
Lauren : When you're not so shy
Lauren : Oh
Lauren : But I've been here before
Lauren : Have I come back for more
Lauren : Another chapter in the history of wrong guys
Lauren : You used to be so meh
Lauren : A limp lackluster bore
Lauren : But now you're changing into someone I just can't ignore
Lauren : Charlie
Lauren : Honestly
Lauren : I've been hurt like this before
Lauren : Is there really more to you
Lauren : Than what I always thought
Lauren : How can you surprise me any more
Lauren : Oh
Lauren : Oh whoa
Lauren : He's got a girlfriend you knob
Lauren : Don't want to be another starcrossed lover
Lauren : We all know how that ends
Lauren : I'm better off without him we're better off as friends
Lauren : Yeah
Lauren : But I've been here before
Lauren : Have I come back for more
Lauren : Another chapter in the history of wrong guys
Lauren : Yesterday no spark
Lauren : No heartaching allure
Lauren : But today I'm feeling something I just can't ignore
Lauren : Charlie
Lauren : Honestly
Lauren : I've been hurt like this before
Lauren : Oh
Lauren : Oh whoa
Lauren : The history of wrong guys
Lauren : Chapter one he's a bum
Lauren : Two he's not into you Three he's a sleaze
Lauren : Four loves the girl next door Fives loves the boy next door
Lauren : Six don't love you no more Makes you insecure makes you so unsure
Lauren : Is so immature loves his mother more
Lauren : Or
Lauren : Has a girlfriend named Nicola
Charlie Price : Ready to get to work
Lauren : Charlie
Lauren : Honestly
Lauren : I've been hurt like this before
Lauren : I can see there's more to you
Lauren : Than what I always thought
Lauren : But I won't be burned anymore
Lauren : Oh
Lauren : Oh whoa
Trish : Where are you off to
Lauren : I've been executized
Don : Look at this
George : I didn't hear the tea trolley
George : Don't you boys have work needs doing
Don's friend : Oh what's the matter
Don's friend : Frettin that the mistress will slap you down
Don's friend : for not doin her biddin
George : You're as clever as you are rich
Don : Come on George
Don : He's gonna make Price Son the town joke and you know it
George : Happens I know no such thing
Don : At Fist'a Cuffs last night the fellas from Delaney Shoes was callin us slaves of the pouf
George : With Delaney's about to shutter one would think those boys would do better than to drink their money away
George : Meanwhile last time I looked you lot were still on the payroll here
George : So why don't you stifle your yaps and earn your keep
Don's friend : Ooh you've really been put in your place now haven't you Don
Don : Get stuffed the both of yous
Angels : Lola
Don : And here comes Her Royal Highness now
Don's friend : What the
Don's friend : Ha
Don's friend : Just when you were sure you'd seen it all eh
Angels : Lola
Lola(Simon) : Have you got any toilets down here
Don : Oh I'm sorry love
Don : I'm afraid all we've got is men's
Don : and women's
Lauren : Charlie quick
Lauren : Lola's gone and locked herself in the loo hurry
Charlie Price : All right I'll talk to her
Charlie Price : but I'm not going into the ladies room You go and get her to come out
Lauren : She's in the gents
Charlie Price : The what
Lauren : The men's room
Charlie Price : Well of course she is
Charlie Price : Lola
Charlie Price : Lola it's Charlie are you sick
Lola(Simon) : Depends who you ask
Charlie Price : No
Charlie Price : Did someone nick your frock
Lola(Simon) : I come up with the daft idea that maybe I should try to fit in
Charlie Price : Probably get a lot more work done this way
Charlie Price : Less bits and bobs to catch in the machines
Lola(Simon) : Thanks for your support
Lola(Simon) : God
Lola(Simon) : In a gown I can bellow Brunhilde in front of 500 drunks and have a laugh
Lola(Simon) : but put me in men's clothes and I can't sodding well say hello
Lola(Simon) : Oh what am I doing here Charlie
Charlie Price : Becoming a designer
Lola(Simon) : Did I ever ask to be one
Charlie Price : Well did you always want to be a performer
Charlie Price : I mean when you were a kid
Lola(Simon) : Whatever it was I wanted as a kid
Lola(Simon) : my father beat out of me
Charlie Price : Your dad hit you
Lola(Simon) : Not like that
Lola(Simon) : He was a boxer
Lola(Simon) : Yeah a proper prize fighter
Lola(Simon) : who never got the title match he wanted
Lola(Simon) : But presented with a baby boy
Lola(Simon) : Well if he couldn't raise a champion's belt over his head
Lola(Simon) : his son would
Charlie Price : He didn't know about
Lola(Simon) : Of course he knew
Lola(Simon) : But he figured if he pushed me trained me himself
Lola(Simon) : ah you heard right
Lola(Simon) : I am a professionally trained boxer
Lola(Simon) : with a dozen amateur bouts to my name so don't try me
Lola(Simon) : But when I appeared for a fight in a white cocktail dress
Lola(Simon) : he disowned me
Lola(Simon) : Refused to see me
Lola(Simon) : even when he came down with lung cancer
Lola(Simon) : It's ironic really
Lola(Simon) : Fags got him in the end
Lola(Simon) : And you
Lola(Simon) : You like making shoes
Charlie Price : On the day I was born my dad set me down next in line of Price Son
Charlie Price : For him a done deal but for me
Charlie Price : First opportunity I grabbed my childhood sweetheart and we jumped on the next train out of town
Lola(Simon) : What was it you ran off to do
Charlie Price : Anything but what he wanted
Lola(Simon) : And yet here you are
Charlie Price : Here I am
Lola(Simon) : When I was just a kid
Lola(Simon) : Everything I did
Lola(Simon) : Was to be like him
Lola(Simon) : Under my skin
Lola(Simon) : My father always thought
Lola(Simon) : If I was strong and fought
Lola(Simon) : Not like some albatross
Lola(Simon) : I'd begin
Lola(Simon) : To fit in
Lola(Simon) : Look at me powerless
Lola(Simon) : And holding my breath
Lola(Simon) : Trying hard to repress
Lola(Simon) : What scared him to death
Lola(Simon) : It was never easy
Lola(Simon) : To be his type of man
Lola(Simon) : To breathe freely
Lola(Simon) : Was not in his plan
Lola(Simon) : And the best part of me
Lola(Simon) : Is what he wouldn't See
Lola(Simon) : I'm not my father's son
Lola(Simon) : I'm not the image
Lola(Simon) : Of what he dreamed of
Lola(Simon) : With the strength of Sparta
Lola(Simon) : And the patience of Job
Lola(Simon) : Still couldn't be the one
Lola(Simon) : To echo what he'd done
Lola(Simon) : And mirror what was not
Lola(Simon) : In me
Lola(Simon) : So I jumped in my dreams
Lola(Simon) : And found an escape
Lola(Simon) : Maybe I went to extremes
Lola(Simon) : Of leather and lace
Lola(Simon) : But the world seemed brighter
Lola(Simon) : Six inches off the ground
Lola(Simon) : And the air seemed lighter
Lola(Simon) : I was profound
Lola(Simon) : And I felt so Proud
Lola(Simon) : Just to live out Loud
Lola(Simon) : I'm not my father's son
Lola(Simon) : I'm not the image
Lola(Simon) : Of what he dreamed of
Lola(Simon) : With the strength of Sparta
Lola(Simon) : And the patience of Job
Lola(Simon) : Still couldn't be the one
Lola(Simon) : To echo what he'd done
Lola(Simon) : And mirror what was not
Lola(Simon) : In me
Lola(Simon) : The endless torrent of expectation
Lola(Simon) : Swirling inside my mind
Lola(Simon) : Wore me down
Lola(Simon) : I came to a realization
Lola(Simon) : And I finally turned around
Lola(Simon) : To see
Lola(Simon) : That I
Lola(Simon) : Could just
Lola(Simon) : Be me
Charlie Price : I'm not my father's son
Charlie Price : I'm not the image
Charlie Price : Of what he dreamed of
Lola(Simon) : With the strength of Sparta
Lola(Simon);Charlie Price : And the patience of Job
Charlie Price;Lola(Simon) : Still couldn't be the one
Charlie Price;Lola(Simon) : To echo what he'd done
Charlie Price;Lola(Simon) : And mirror what was not
Charlie Price;Lola(Simon) : In me
Lola(Simon) : We're the same
Lola(Simon) : Charlie boy
Lola(Simon) : You and me
Lola(Simon) : Charlie from Northampton
Lola(Simon) : meet Simon from Clacton
Charlie Price : Let's make boots
Charlie Price : Sorry
Charlie Price : You wouldn't believe what's going on in there
Nicola : Hey stranger don't I get a kiss
Charlie Price : Sorry
Charlie Price : I'm just excited Nic
Charlie Price : I've found the craziest solution for the factory
Nicola : Slow down Charlie
Nicola : You said you'd hear us out yeah
Nicola : Like I told you on the phone some of this is gonna come as a shock but you promised you'd listen with an open mind
Nicola : Charlie you remember my boss Richard Bailey
Richard Bailey : I was almost your boss too eh mate
Richard Bailey : Sorry about your dad but I hope once the dust settles maybe you'll come back and work with us
Richard Bailey : In any event I have to say I am totally mad for this project
Richard Bailey : Not all buildings deserve a second life but yours is special
Charlie Price : Second life
Nicola : Let the man talk darling
Richard Bailey : Price Son
Richard Bailey : Riverside Apartments one two and threebedroom loftstyle homes with all the luxuries
Nicola : How exciting is that
Richard Bailey : Look at the detail It's not what you change about a building
Richard Bailey : it's what you preserve that marks a great conversion
Charlie Price : What makes you think we're up for conversion
Nicola : You promised to hear the man out
Charlie Price : Price Son is not for sale
Nicola : Actually it is unless you want to see it foreclosed
Charlie Price : No if you'd listen you know that I've found a solution
Lola(Simon) : Charlie
Charlie Price : To the factory
Nicola : Come quick
Lola(Simon) : the Angels train just pulled in the first pair of boots are on their final polish but we can't unveil them without you
Lola(Simon) : Oh hello
Lola(Simon) : I'm Lola I'm the one designing Charlie's new line of transvestite footwear
Lola(Simon) : Oh f
Lola(Simon) : Oh
Lola(Simon) : There's a slight chill in the air isn't there
Lola(Simon) : Yes
Charlie Price : Yes
Lola(Simon) : Maybe I should just
Lola(Simon) : go away
Charlie Price : That was
Charlie Price : You have to get to know him
Charlie Price : Listen Nic I haven't gone into this lightly
Charlie Price : There actually is a market out there
Nicola : Before you make a complete fool of yourself
Nicola : it's time you heard the truth
Nicola : Selling the building was your father's idea
Charlie Price : Oh
Nicola : Yes Your father's idea
Nicola : He approached Richard months ago
Nicola : Tell him
Richard Bailey : It's true your dad and I had several meetings
Nicola : You yourself told me that he had a plan remember
Nicola : Well this was it
Nicola : The contracts were almost done when he passed away
Nicola : We can show you the papers
Nicola : Look Richard came to me first lest you think your father doubted you could run the business
Nicola : But don't look so down
Nicola : This is all good news
Nicola : The deal Richard's put together will rid you of the factory
Nicola : settle your family's debts and ensure our future with a careerdefining selling opportunity
Nicola : We even get a model flat rentfree while we're selling
Charlie Price : I'm asking you to have a bit of faith in
Nicola : Stop
Nicola : Are you deaf
Nicola : Your father was cashing out you owe him nothing
Nicola : The prison door's open
Nicola : You're free Charlie
Nicola : All you need to do is walk away
Charlie Price : You were always telling me
Charlie Price : What I need to be
Charlie Price : But you never really had enough faith in me
Charlie Price : Dad you gave up the factory
Charlie Price : Well
Charlie Price : This time I'm gonna take that chance
Charlie Price : Leap into the vast expanse
Charlie Price : This time I'm gonna seize my destiny
Charlie Price : My destiny
Lola(Simon) : Well boss is this what you had in mind
Charlie Price : Yeah
Lola(Simon) : Yeah
Factory Workers : Come on
Factory Workers : Yeah
Factory Workers : Yes
Factory Workers : Charlie
Charlie Price : Let me hear you say yeah yeah
George : Yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Say yeah yeah
Factory Workers : Yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Say yeah
Factory Workers : Say yeah
Factory Workers : Yeah
Charlie Price : You can throw out the old way cause it's been done
Lola(Simon) : We're getting ready for the new
Charlie Price : Witness the future of Price Son
Lola(Simon) : Ow Papa's got a brand new shoe
Lola(Simon) : A life of broken heels got you down
Charlie Price : Well we've got your solution
Lola(Simon) : Get up
Charlie Price : Get it on and get in step
Charlie Price;Lola(Simon) : With our kinky revolution
Charlie Price : Let me hear you say yeah yeah
Lauren : Yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Say yeah yeah
Lola(Simon) : Yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Let me hear you say yeah yeah
Lauren : Yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Say yeah
Factory Workers : Yeah
Charlie Price : Welcome to our future
Charlie Price : No longer are we making shoes
Charlie Price : we are making 212feet of irresistible
Charlie Price : tubular sex
Charlie Price : So let's do it
Don's friend : I punched the holes
Factory Workers : I sewed the seams
Pat : And I pull the leather tight
George : I put the steel inside the heel
Factory Workers : Now we go off like dynamite
Charlie Price : Can you picture this
Charlie Price : A glamorous
Charlie Price : Fashion exhibition
Lola(Simon) : I see flashbulb lights and fashion heights
Charlie Price;Factory Workers : I see press and television
Charlie Price : Let me hear you say yeah yeah
Factory Workers : Yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Say yeah yeah
Lola(Simon) : He wants to hear you say yeah yeah
Factory Workers : Yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Say yeah
Factory Workers : Yeah
Trish;Pat : Synergy my pets
Pat;Trish : In patent leather red
Pat;Trish : Say whoa
Factory Workers : Whoa
Pat;Trish : Tell me is this kismet
Charlie Price : Now if you are with this
Charlie Price;Factory Workers : let's go
Charlie Price;Factory Workers : Everybody say yeah
Lola(Simon) : Ladies
Lola(Simon) : Gentlemen
Lola(Simon) : Help me welcome our niche market
Factory Workers : Oi oi oi oi
Trish : Charlie
Charlie Price : Somebody catch her
Trish : Charlie give me your hand No somebody
Factory Workers : Oi oi
Charlie Price : Everybody
Lola(Simon) : Everybody
Charlie Price : Everybody say yeah yeah
Factory Workers : Yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Say yeah yeah
Lola(Simon) : He wants to hear you say yeah yeah
Factory Workers : Yeah yeah
Lola(Simon) : Say yeah yeah yeah yeah
Charlie Price : Say yeah
Factory Workers : Say yeah
Lola(Simon);Charlie Price : Say yeah
Factory Workers : Say yeah yeah yeah yeah
Charlie Price;Factory Workers : Say yeah yeah
Lola(Simon);Charlie Price;Factory Workers : Say yeah yeah
Factory Workers : Everybody
Factory Workers : Everybody say yeah yeah yeah
Factory Workers : Trust your feet in Price Son Our work is tried and true
Factory Workers : Practical pragmatical Steadfast and sturdy sturdy too
Factory Workers : Whether you're high brow or pure Or posh or working class
Factory Workers : Get your mitts on kinky kicks
Factory Workers : And kick Some Ass
Charlie Price : Uh where do you think you're going with those
Lola(Simon) : Ah something's not quite right
Lola(Simon) : I want to see the colors in daylight
Charlie Price : What did we talk about the other day
Charlie Price : I thought we agreed what constitutes proper working attire
Lola(Simon) : Don't be so hard on yourself You look adorable
Charlie Price : Did you approve the lining fabrics and fittings for the bags
Lola(Simon) : Right after lunch
Charlie Price : And did you call the modeling agency
Charlie Price : They needed to start castin yesterday
Charlie Price : Get it done now
Lola(Simon) : Yes boss
Charlie Price : Right now
Charlie Price : I mean it
Lola(Simon) : Love you too
Don : Oh careful there big lady
Don : Or is it little man
Don : Need a hand or a boot
Don's friend : Yeah
Lola(Simon) : Tell me Dapper Don what can I do that will allow you
Lola(Simon) : to go on with your life undistracted by my sharing the planet
Don : Try dressing like a bloke for starters
Lola(Simon) : Jealous
Don : Me
Don : What have I got to be jealous of
Lola(Simon) : Of all the attention I get from the ladies
Don : You ladies
Lola(Simon) : Raise your hands if you look to see what I wear to work each day
Lola(Simon) : Now raise your hands if you care what Don wears
Don : You're telling me you ain't all tarted up to get blokes
Lola(Simon) : Why would I do that
Lola(Simon) : Blokes that fancy blokes fancy blokes
Don : You like women
Lola(Simon) : Ha I adore them I worship them
Lola(Simon) : My whole being is dedicated to loving them
Lola(Simon) : and they love me right back
Don : Then why don't all men wear dresses
Lola(Simon) : A question I've been asking all my life
Don : A woman wants a man what acts like a real man
Lola(Simon) : And what does a real man act like
Lola(Simon) : Ladies care to help Don out
Lola(Simon) : Tell him what you want
Marge : Me
Marge : I don't need much a bit of companionship a mate
Marge : a mate with benefits
Trish : I like big hands
Marge : And affection
Trish : I like to bite
Pat : I want sensitivity and compassion all right
Lola(Simon) : Companionship affection sensitivity and compassion
Lola(Simon) : traditionally female characteristics wouldn't you say
Don : You're off your trolley
Lola(Simon) : Really
Lola(Simon) : Stand back
Lola(Simon) : Let me tell you something
Lola(Simon) : What a woman
Lola(Simon) : Wants to see
Lola(Simon) : Stand back
Lola(Simon) : Mr IKnowEverything
Lola(Simon) : But it's what you
Lola(Simon) : Blindly see
Lola(Simon) : What a woman wants
Don : Masculinity
Pat : What a man
Lola(Simon) : sensitivity
Don : in a fantasy
Pat : What a man
Lola(Simon) : what a woman wants
Don : a muscle to clutch
Pat : What a man
Lola(Simon) : just a tender touch
Don : Well you don't get out too much
Lola(Simon) : To know the smoothness of her skin
Lola(Simon) : With a gentle caress
Lola(Simon) : Feel the feathery quality
Lola(Simon) : Of her dress
Lola(Simon) : What separates a man like you
Lola(Simon) : From a man like me
Lola(Simon) : I'm a reflection
Lola(Simon) : Her protection
Lola(Simon) : I'm her curious mystery
Pat : What a man
Lola(Simon) : what a woman
Marge : What a man what a man
Lola(Simon) : What a woman wants
Ladies : What a man what a man what a man
Trish : What a man
Lola(Simon) : what a woman
Ladies : What a man what a man
Lola(Simon) : What a woman wants
Ladies : what a man
Don : Oh come on we all know what a bird really wants
Don : is a rocksolid
Lola(Simon) : Uhhuh commitment
Lola(Simon) : Look at me
Lola(Simon) : Devilishly
Lola(Simon) : Debonair
Lola(Simon) : Look at you
Lola(Simon) : Divinely dull drab
Lola(Simon) : And dumpy
Don : A woman wants
Don : A man to give as much as she can take
Don : Just like me
Ladies : A libidinous Lothario on the make
Don : Piss off
Lola(Simon) : I have a challenge for you
Lola(Simon) : Write down what you think I need to do to be a real man
Lola(Simon) : and I'll do the same for you
Lola(Simon) : Whatever you tell me to do I will have to do
Lola(Simon) : But you will have to do the same for me
Lola(Simon) : Deal
Don : I ain't wearin no poufy dress
Lola(Simon) : Chickening out already
Woman : What a man what a man what a man what a man
Woman : What a man what a man
Lola(Simon) : what a woman wants
Ladies : What a man what a man what a man
Lola(Simon) : What a woman wants
Ladies : What a man what a man
Ladies : What a man what a man what a man
Lola(Simon) : What a woman what a man what a man
Lola(Simon) : What a woman what a woman wants
Lola(Simon) : Is me
Ladies : What a woman wants what a man what a man
Ladies;Lola(Simon) : What a man what a man what a woman wants
Lola(Simon) : You're on
Ladies : What a man
Charlie Price : Why didn't you warn me
Lauren : I thought you heard everyone else did
Charlie Price : Do you think I woulda let it go this far And why didn't you stop it
Lauren : Have you ever tried stopping Lola from doing anything
Lauren : Lola told Don he could give her any challenge at all and this is what he chose
Charlie Price : A boxing match between Lola and Don at Fist'a Cuffs
Charlie Price : It's gonna be a bloody slaughter
Lauren : Have some faith
Lauren : I'm sure Lola's got a few moves up her sleeve
Charlie Price : It's not her I'm worried about
Charlie Price : Lola is a professionallytrained fighter
Lauren : She's a what
Charlie Price : Come on
Don's friend : Oi oi looks like there's gonna be trouble
Angel : Oh he don't know who he's messing with all right
Angel : So shut your mouth
Angel : Ladies
Angel : Gentlemen
Angel : And those who've yet to make up their minds
Angel : In this corner
Angel : Lean and brown
Angel : Weighin in in a gold lame gown yeah yeah
Angel : In this corner
Angel : Here tonight
Angel : In the cradle of the bright white light
Factory Workers;Lola's Side : Hit him in his big mouth
Lola's Side : Hit him in his insecurity Yeah
Lola's Side : Hit him off his high horse
Lola's Side : Hit him so everyone can see
Lola's Side : Yeah
Trish : Who do you think you are coming to our town lookin like a penny sardine on a fivestar plate
Trish : You better watch your back
Angel : Whoa
Angel : In this corner
Angel : Heavyweight
Don : Come on
Angel : We mean heavy Like a buttermilk cake
Angel : Can a real man
Angel : Ever confess
Angel : He was beaten by a guy in a dress
Don's Side : Ooh hit him in the lipstick
Don's Side : Hit him in his feminine mystique
Don's Side : Yeah
Don's Side : Hit him off his high heels
Don's Side : Hit him in the cheek
Don's Side : And send him back to London town
Trish : Sequined freak
Pat : Hey you are gonna get slapped slapped slapped
Angel : All right all right listen up you two
Angel : I want a clean fair but artfully performed fight
Angel : I don't want to see any blows below the belt
Angel : or any hairs out of place
Angel : Oh hang on darling you've got a tick of lipstick on your teeth
Angel : All right then back to your corners and come out fighting
Don : Shut up
Trish : He ain't half the man Don is
Pat : You can say that again
Lola's Side : In this corner Wow the crowd
Lola's Side : Take him down and make us ladies proud
Don's Side : In this corner
Don's Side : Dominate
Don's Side : Set her up so we can set her straight
Angel : Round one
Lola's Side : Hit him in his big mouth
Lola's Side : Hit him in his insecurity Yeah
Lola's Side : Hit him off his high horse
Lola's Side : Hit him so everyone can see Ooh yeah
Lola(Simon) : Hiyah
Angel : Back to your corners you beasts
Angel : Fancy a Grasshopper darling
Angel : It'll keep you bouncy
Lola's Side : If you finish him off quick
Lola's Side : we can still get kimchi at the Korean's
Don : So you got a good shot but don't get cocky
Lola(Simon) : I'm as pretty as Ali and tough as Rocky
Don : If you're lucky I might let you off easy
Lola(Simon) : Don you know I get excited when you tease me
Trish : What's the matter Don you look a little pale
Lola(Simon) : I feel like a hammer
Don : I feel like the nail
Trish : Come on Don knock him black and blue
Pat : Here comes an uppercut a left hook
Pat : And a pirouette too
Angel : Round two
Lola's Side : Hit him in his big mouth
Lola's Side : Hit him in his insecurity Yeah
Don's Side : Hit him off his high horse
Don's Side : Hit him so everyone can everyone can Everyone can
Lola(Simon);Angel : Un deux trois
Don's Side : Hit him off his high horse
Don's Side : Don really let that big fist fly Yeah
Don's Side : He hit him with his brute force
Don's Side : Now he can hold his head up high Ooh yeah
Don's Side : Don Don champion Don Don champion
Don's Side : Don Don champion
Charlie Price : Less than a week till Milan and you somehow think a boxing match a good idea
Lola(Simon) : I thought watching Don slap me around might boost morale
Charlie Price : I suppose I should thank you for not crippling him
Lola(Simon) : Anything for the war effort
Don : Charlie
Don : Lola
Charlie Price : Congratulations
Don : Thanks
Charlie Price : Why don't I leave you two lovebirds to make up
Don : They say vodka's your preferred
Don : So why'd you do it
Don : Why'd you let me win
Lola(Simon) : Really
Don : Really
Lola(Simon) : Because I didn't want you to walk into the factory tomorrow and feel disrespected
Don : How bout you
Lola(Simon) : Ha compared to my challenge
Lola(Simon) : losing a fight is like a polka in the pansies
Don : Accept someone for who they are
Don : What's that mean
Lola(Simon) : Just what it says
Don : You lookin for me to say men in frocks is all right
Lola(Simon) : I ain't lookin for you to say anything
Don : Accept someone for who they are
Don : How's that make me a man
Lola(Simon) : Try it
Don : Anyone Anyone at all
Don : And that's it
Lola(Simon) : Good luck
Lauren : But you have no idea what you're doing either
Lauren : We're in the same hole
Charlie Price : Whoa whoa whoa everyone just stop talking
Charlie Price : Now one of you please cut to the chase
Pat : We miscalculated
Pat : The Milan trip is going to cost more than we budgeted
Charlie Price : No it can't cost more because we have no more
Lauren : It's me I'm the blunderer
Lauren : I never factored in land transport in Milan
Pat : Or the import taxes
Lauren : No I planned for the taxes on the samples
Lauren : but only one pair of each
Charlie Price : Oh
Lauren : I know stupid
Charlie Price : Not brilliant
Lauren : Well it's all your fault for putting me in charge
Lauren : What do I know about producing a bloody fashion show in bleedin Italy
Charlie Price : If we don't get our boots to Milan
Charlie Price : then all this work will have been for nothing
Pat : How about we call the bank
Pat : Maybe seeing how close we are they'd carry us
Charlie Price : Good day Mr Banker We've gone tits up making the best shoes in England
Charlie Price : but we've chucked all that to make boots for transgentries
Charlie Price : How'd you like to bunk in with us
Lauren : It would be an awful burden I know
Lauren : but how about a shortterm mortgage on your new flat
Charlie Price : I just did that That's how we got to today
Lola(Simon) : Charlie Charlie
Lola(Simon) : I was sitting on the loo when I was truck by lightning
Pat : Oh kitten you ought to close the window first
Lauren : I spoke to a nice chap down at the post office
Lauren : Let me see if he can give us any leeway on the taxes
Lola(Simon) : Will someone listen to me
Charlie Price : We're in crisis here
Lola(Simon) : Charlie you want me to hire Italian models and hair and makeup staff why
Charlie Price : At last one question to which I have an answer
Charlie Price : I want you to hire models hair and makeup because we are putting on a show
Lola(Simon) : But why are we using fashion models
Charlie Price : Oh I've got this one too Because we are putting on a fashion show
Lola(Simon) : But why are we using professional fashion models
Charlie Price : Oh this really is my day
Charlie Price : Because we are putting on a professional fashion show
Lola(Simon) : Let's take the girls from the club
Charlie Price : The Angels
Lola(Simon) : Who would be more fun to see on a runway
Lola(Simon) : a bunch of personalityfree pretty boys prancing about
Lola(Simon) : or a gaggle of fabulous drags who can demonstrate
Lola(Simon) : what these boots were born to do
Charlie Price : You're not serious you want me to gamble my family's business this building my home
Charlie Price : the very shirt on my back on a ramshackle bunch of brokendown
Lola(Simon) : There you go biting the hand that feeds
Charlie Price : I don't know which one is more daft
Charlie Price : what you're saying or what you're wearing
George : Want to have a look at these Mr Price
Charlie Price : No no the heel is wrong this isn't the design
George : True enough but up against the deadline we had to improvise
Charlie Price : Well it's nothing like the drawing
George : We had to put the heel on a different angle
Charlie Price : Why
George : Else we'd have to create an entirely new steel shank
Charlie Price : Then do it
Trish : We'll have no sewing time if we have to wait for a new heel
Lola(Simon) : I told them to go ahead like that
Charlie Price : But it's not what you drew
Lola(Simon) : One's a drawing one's a shoe
Charlie Price : I didn't give you approval
Lola(Simon) : No all you give me is deadlines
Charlie Price : Okay we're gonna do this right or not at all
Charlie Price : Let me see them
Charlie Price : No these seams aren't straight you're rushing
Charlie Price : Do it again Excuse me
Trish : And the zipper is set wrong
Charlie Price : People this is for Milan
Charlie Price : for the most sophisticated shoe buyers in the world
Trish : So
Charlie Price : So I don't want to be the laughing stock of the industry
Charlie Price : We're on thin ice puttin these out in the first place
Charlie Price : Everyone stop oi stop stop hold on the floor
Charlie Price : Marge Maggie George
Charlie Price : George Trish take a look at these
Charlie Price : Now they all have to be picked out and redone correctly
Charlie Price : They all have to be done again
Trish : It's Saturday
Charlie Price : And
Trish : I don't mind a bit of rahrahkumbaya for the sake of the team
Trish : but some of us have a life outside this factory
Charlie Price : And you'll have a bloody lot more of it if I fire you
Charlie Price : Now do it again
Charlie Price : please
Charlie Price : You have a problem
George : All right everyone back to work
Charlie Price : Here's what I don't understand
Charlie Price : why am I the only one who cares
Charlie Price : No not now Nic
Nicola : Don't even think about puttin me off Charlie
Charlie Price : Sorry Nic but I'm up against a bit of a crisis here
Nicola : You mortgaged our flat without even discussin it with me
Nicola : There I am havin my supper alone as usual
Nicola : and along comes a man to measure up the garden for the valuation
Charlie Price : Yeah I can explain
Nicola : No one can ever say I didn't stand by my man
Nicola : and I'll stand by you still if you give me but one reason
Charlie Price : The reason is right in front of you Isn't saving Price Son worth everything
Nicola : Where was this passion when I was trying to make us a new life in London
Charlie Price : London was for you
Nicola : For us
Charlie Price : For you you wanted London and I went along
Nicola : Really
Nicola : Well you could have fooled me
Nicola : And what about us
Nicola : Was gettin engaged just for me too
Nicola : And this who's this rubbish for
Nicola : Oh don't tell me it's for your father
Nicola : He's probably spinning in his grave over what you've turned his factory into
Nicola : So who's it for Charlie
Nicola : That fancy friend of yours Doing special favors for him
Nicola : Something going on there I should know about
Charlie Price : Oh don't be ridiculous
Nicola : Well how should I know who you've been sleeping with
Nicola : Certainly hasn't been with me
Charlie Price : I'm doing it for them
Nicola : Who
Charlie Price : Them our friends
Charlie Price : No
Charlie Price : We grew up with these people we've known them all our lives and now their whole livelihood is riding on this factory
Nicola : And this factory is riding straight off the cliff
Nicola : If your father was still here they'd already be out of work
Charlie Price : But he isn't I am
Nicola : So you're hankering to be a hero
Charlie Price : Nic
Nicola : Charlie to the rescue is it
Nicola : Well how do I get Charlie to rescue me
Charlie Price : You look nice all done up
Nicola : Richard's put me on a new project
Nicola : Big time stuff
Charlie Price : Yeah
Nicola : I'm headed back to London for good
Nicola : Are you coming
Charlie Price : Aren't those the shoes we saw
Nicola : How long was I supposed to wait
Nicola : So long Charlie
Charlie Price : Yeah
Lola(Simon) : If you're done making wedding plans
Lola(Simon) : can we finish discussing the Milan show
Charlie Price : There's no discussion to be had
Charlie Price : We're using professional models done
Lola(Simon) : Then you better get on the phone
Lola(Simon) : because I just called and canceled them
Charlie Price : I never told you that you could
Lola(Simon) : Think Charlie
Lola(Simon) : My girls don't need to be paid
Lola(Simon) : They'll do it for cocktails giggles and the chance to walk a professional runway
Lola(Simon) : and my girls do their own hair and makeup
Lola(Simon) : so there's the money we need to get us to Milan
Charlie Price : How do I get this into your head
Charlie Price : We are marketing to the world's most sophisticated buyers
Lola(Simon) : Half of whom probably watch the evening news
Lola(Simon) : wearing their wives brassieres
Charlie Price : News flash for Lola
Charlie Price : There are a whole lot of us who don't watch the evening news in brassieres
Lola(Simon) : Well bully for you but you ain't my buyers
Charlie Price : Then here's another news flash
Charlie Price : I am not flying all the way across Europe
Charlie Price : just to sell to your chums
Lola(Simon) : We won't be selling to anyone if we can't get to Milan
Charlie Price : Then there's no reason to go if all we've got to show is a bunch of Nancyboys stomping about in skirts
Charlie Price : We need to show these boots on women
Lola(Simon) : Women
Charlie Price : You heard me
Lola(Simon) : That was never the deal
Charlie Price : Well then the deal was wrong
Lola(Simon) : What did that girl say to you
Charlie Price : I am not embarrasin the name of Price Son by parading a planeload of misfits
Lola(Simon) : Misfits
Charlie Price : At the most influential footwear show in the world
Charlie Price : Listen to me Lola these boots can be mainstream
Lola(Simon) : Drag queens are mainstream
Lola(Simon) : Just this morning I was offered a gig singing
Lola(Simon) : at a nursing home
Lola(Simon) : A nursing home Charlie in Clacton
Charlie Price : And maybe that's just where you belong
Lola(Simon) : What
Charlie Price : Look at you
Charlie Price : You're meant to be a business person
Charlie Price : How many successful designers do you think go about camped up like the entertainment at a lowrent tea dance
Lola(Simon) : After all I've shared with you
Lola(Simon) : you still think I'm wearing this
Lola(Simon) : for a lack of a pair of trousers
Charlie Price : Look I get it I understand
Charlie Price : All of this froufrou it protects who you really are I heard you
Lola(Simon) : You heard nothing
Charlie Price : I'm telling you you don't have to hide
Charlie Price : Once the industry sees your work you'll be able to stop all of this and have a normal life
Lola(Simon) : You're a fool
Charlie Price : Am I
Charlie Price : I'd wager if we stood side by side and asked passersby which one of us is fooling himself
Charlie Price : most of the votes would swing your way
Lola(Simon) : Ha
Charlie Price : Why am I
Charlie Price : the only one in here who believes in you
Lola(Simon) : You believe in my shoes I am not my shoes
Charlie Price : No you're a joke
Charlie Price : You think you're being all mystical and deep representing the best of both sexes
Charlie Price : but I'm here to tell you that all you are is daft
Charlie Price : You say you want to be treated like a man then start acting like one
Charlie Price : I'm sorry but sometimes the truth hurts
Lola(Simon) : The truth
Lola(Simon) : We're done here
Charlie Price : And Simon
Charlie Price : Yes that's right Simon
Charlie Price : when you show up at the airport try to look somethin like your passport photo
Charlie Price : Yes
Charlie Price : For both our sakes
Trish : Here
Charlie Price : This is shite do it again
Trish : You're outta your bloody mind
Charlie Price : This is for Milan
Trish : Milan
Trish : Milan you don't even know what Milan is
Trish : You've never been there you're just guessin
Trish : And I'm goin home
Charlie Price : I don't have to guess to know what's good
Trish : They'd be good enough for your father
Charlie Price : Well I am not my father
Trish : Truer words
Trish : were never spoke
Charlie Price : Do it again
Trish : As the saying goes you want something done your way
Trish : have at it
Trish : What say we clear out
Trish : and leave the man from Milan to his stitching
Charlie Price : We have all these samples to make and no time
Charlie Price : If you all go home now what have we been working for
Charlie Price : Maggie Marge
Charlie Price : George
Charlie Price : Who was I kidding
Charlie Price : This scheme was skidding
Charlie Price : My fractured attempt at taking control
Charlie Price : I tried in vain now
Charlie Price : I'm to blame
Charlie Price : Now I'm left with
Charlie Price : A deep dark hole
Charlie Price : So confident
Charlie Price : So collected
Charlie Price : And so cool
Charlie Price : Hey look at me now
Charlie Price : I'm a fool
Charlie Price : I'm bad news a black and blueser
Charlie Price : Who's a loser
Charlie Price : A merrygoround spiralin down
Charlie Price : I'm all used up I'm chafed and chewed up
Charlie Price : Who's just screwed up
Charlie Price : The same old Charlie hitting the ground
Charlie Price : Cause I'll never be the soul of a man
Charlie Price : Noble and wise Like the soul of a man
Charlie Price : Who lifted me high
Charlie Price : Like the soul of a man
Charlie Price : Heroic and true
Charlie Price : Like a soul of a man that I looked up to
Charlie Price : What else could I do
Charlie Price : Stupid hubris
Charlie Price : No excuses
Charlie Price : I blew my fuses
Charlie Price : I guess I'm just a ruse in my father's shoes
Charlie Price : Not amusin
Charlie Price : No confusin This streak of losin
Charlie Price : Totally brutal and useless too
Charlie Price : How can I be the soul of a man
Charlie Price : Noble and wise
Charlie Price : Like the soul of a man
Charlie Price : Who lifted me high Like the soul of a man
Charlie Price : Heroic and true Like the soul of a man
Charlie Price : That I looked up to
Charlie Price : What else could I
Charlie Price : Just when I'm reaching for that run at the top
Charlie Price : I'm that broken heel unsteady ready ready to drop
Charlie Price : When will I be the soul of a man
Charlie Price : Noble and wise Like the soul of a man
Charlie Price : Who lifted me high Soul of a man
Charlie Price : Heroic and true Like the soul of a man
Charlie Price : That I looked up to
Charlie Price : What else could I
Charlie Price : Do
Charlie Price : Soul of a man
Charlie Price : I'll never be
Charlie Price : No I'll never be
Charlie Price : I have gone and let you down
Charlie Price : Oh
Charlie Price : Soul
Charlie Price : Soul of a man
Charlie Price : Here comes that familiar sound
Charlie Price : Same old Charlie
Charlie Price : hitting the ground
Charlie Price : Just keep walking
Charlie Price : You want no part of this
Lauren : Down doggie
Lauren : Like every mutt I've ever met you only growl because you're scared
Charlie Price : Dogs growl to protect something
Charlie Price : I've nothing left to growl over
Lauren : You're a funny one Charlie Price
Lauren : I always took you for a spoiled brat waitin to have the world handed to him
Charlie Price : Don't hand me nothin unless you want it destroyed
Lauren : Budge up
Lauren : Feelin sorry for ourselves eh
Lauren : I
Lauren : I felt the same way when my dad died
Charlie Price : Yeah
Lauren : Yeah
Lauren : I was so lost
Lauren : After the funeral
Lauren : the undertaker handed me a shoebox of his stuff
Lauren : and said That's what he left
Lauren : And I looked at him and I said no
Lauren : this is what he left
Lauren : What a body leaves behind ain't in his pocket
Lauren : Sometimes it's what he inspired in others
Lauren : Turn around Charlie
Charlie Price : What's going on
Charlie Price : Why's the factory all lit up
Lauren : Go and see for yourself
Charlie Price : Hey
Charlie Price : You did this
Lauren : Me No no no
Lauren : Don Don done it
Lauren : Lola challenged him to accept someone for who they are
Lauren : and I'd say he rather rose to the occasion
Charlie Price : What so Don got everyone back to work just by accepting Lola
Lauren : No Charlie
Lauren : You
Lauren : Don accepted you
Don : Oi
Don : I heard you was runnin low on funds
Don : Last week's payslips
Don : Who needs to eat
Trish : Here we go mates Should we see what he thinks
Trish : Well
Charlie Price : Wow
Trish : My God
Trish : The man from Milan says yes
Factory Workers : London to Milan
Factory Workers : Stilettos are an ism
Factory Workers : In red and neon life
Factory Workers : Gimme Kinky BBBBBBBBBoots
Lauren : That's the lot eh George We got it all
George : Yeah van should've been here by now
George : Maybe he's gone around to the loading bay I'll check
Charlie Price : Lola's not here she's not coming
Lauren : Ring her again
Charlie Price : I've rung a dozen times
Charlie Price : I can't even get Pat to answer my calls
Lauren : Maybe they're flying straight from London
Lauren : She wouldn't miss this
Charlie Price : After what I said
Lauren : Oh here comes the van
Lauren : I'll load the boots you try Lola again
Charlie Price : Hello Lola
Charlie Price : Guess who again
Charlie Price : We're on our way to the airport but there's a monumental hole where you should be
Charlie Price : which is no surprise
Charlie Price : Whenever you leave a room there's always a great big gap
Charlie Price : Just how life with you is
Charlie Price : Anyway I want you to know that I don't blame you for being angry
Charlie Price : The way I shot my gob off I'd walk out myself if I could
Charlie Price : Hey leave it to me to finally find my passion and use it to hurt someone I love
Charlie Price : But forget me forget Milan forget the boots and business
Charlie Price : What I wanted to say was
Charlie Price : if anyone ever tries to tell you you're something less than a man
Charlie Price : then you have them see me
Charlie Price : If being a man means being brave enough to take on the entire world
Charlie Price : then you're the only man I've ever known
Charlie Price : Certainly the best
Charlie Price : You challenged Don to change his mind
Charlie Price : but I'm the one who really needed that lesson
Charlie Price : So this is Charlie from Northampton telling Simon from Clacton
Charlie Price : he is so terribly sorry
Charlie Price : Goodbye Lola
Charlie Price : and thank you
Lola(Simon) : You don't want to see me Anymore
Lola(Simon) : You can't listen to me Laugh out loud
Lola(Simon) : You don't want to see me dance
Lola(Simon) : You can't even take the chance
Lola(Simon) : That it might reflect on You
Lola(Simon) : You missed out On the best part of me
Lola(Simon) : The part That made me who I am
Lola(Simon) : Today Oh
Lola(Simon) : But the best part of me
Lola(Simon) : Is standing in front of you
Lola(Simon) : And loves you anyway
Lola(Simon) : Hold me in your heart
Lola(Simon) : Till you understand
Lola(Simon) : Just the way that I am
Lola(Simon) : With all your faults I love you
Lola(Simon) : Don't give up On me
Lola(Simon) : I won't give up On you
Lola(Simon) : When you took my hand taught me how to be strong
Lola(Simon) : That's where I picked up where we went all wrong
Lola(Simon) : I know that I hurt you and you hurt me too
Lola(Simon) : But you mean more to me I must mean more to you
Lola(Simon) : Hold me in your heart
Lola(Simon) : Till you understand
Lola(Simon) : Just the way that I am
Lola(Simon) : With all your faults I love you
Lola(Simon) : I need you
Lola(Simon) : To love me that way
Lola(Simon) : Too
Lola(Simon) : Thank you for welcoming me to your lovely facility
Lola(Simon) : Believe it or not I grew up just down the road
Lola(Simon) : Anyway it was my pleasure to come
Lola(Simon) : You see you're not my usual audience and I'm probably not your usual entertainment
Lola(Simon) : and that is because I'm actually a man
Lola(Simon) : My name is Simon
Lola(Simon) : Thank you for listening
Lola(Simon) : It was good to see you Daddy
Lola(Simon) : Goodbye
Lola(Simon) : I love you
Milan Stage Manager : Hallo peoples can you hear me
Milan Stage Manager : This is a
Milan Stage Manager : Donatella
Milan Stage Manager : Kinky Boots
Milan Stage Manager : Can I see the exhibitors for Price Son
Charlie Price : Oh that's me
Milan Stage Manager : Aha and your dressers
Charlie Price : That's me
Milan Stage Manager : Aha and your models
Charlie Price : Me
Milan Stage Manager : Aha
Milan Stage Manager : Then you have everyone you need to proceed si
Charlie Price : Si
Milan Stage Manager : Si
Milan Stage Manager : Perfecto
Milan Stage Manager : Your presentation begins in
Lauren : No sign of anyone no one no one at all
Charlie Price : Go out front and sit with George
Charlie Price : I want at least two friendly faces in the crowd
Lauren : Charlie you're not really going to
Charlie Price : Now go go go shoo shoo shoo shoo shoo
Lauren : We're going we're going
George : Is he really going to
Lauren : It appears so yes
George : Oh
George : Does he look sexy
Lauren : To me
Lauren : Very
Lauren : No
Lauren : Charlie
Lauren : Honestly
Lauren : How can you surprise me Any more
Lauren : Oh
Lauren : Oh whoa
Lauren : Oh oh
Lauren : Come on Charlie you can do it
Lola(Simon) : Don't go thinking it was your sappy phone calls that brought me here
Lola(Simon) : I have come for one thing and one thing only
Lola(Simon) : adulation
Lola(Simon) : People of the world Price Son proudly presents Lola's Kinky Boots
Charlie Price : Thank you Lola
Lola(Simon) : Once I was afraid but then you came along
Lola(Simon) : You put your faith in me and I was challenged to be strong
Lola(Simon) : When I lost my way you were there to see me through
Lola(Simon) : Now let Lola lend some love and do the same for you
Angels : Feed your fire to take you higher
Angels : We'll light you up like a live wire
Angels : Celebrate you to elevate you
Angels : When you struggle to stand we'll take a helping hand
Lola(Simon) : If you hit the dust let me raise you up
Lola(Simon) : When your bubble busts let me raise you up
Lola(Simon) : If your glitter rusts let me raise you up
Lola(Simon) : And up
Angels : Raise you up
Lola(Simon) : Ooh
Charlie Price : Never put much heart in anything before
Charlie Price : You strut into my life and helped me go for something more
Charlie Price : Now I stand up for myself
Charlie Price : Now I stand out from the crowd
Charlie Price : Now I'm standing on high heels If Dad could see me now
Angels : Feed your fire to take you higher
Angels : We'll light you up like a live wire
Lola(Simon) : Celebrate you to elevate you
Angels : When you struggle to stand we'll take a helping hand
Lola(Simon);All : If you hit the dust let me raise you up
All : When your bubble busts let me raise you up
All : If your glitter rusts let me raise you up
Lola(Simon) : And up
All : Raise you up
All : Ooh raise you up
Lauren : I knew you had it in you I knew what you could do
Charlie Price : You believed in me let me be right for you
Lauren : Your stumbling days are done and now we're walkin on air
Charlie Price : I was a loose shoe but you need two to make a pair
Lauren : Wait wait wait hold it right there buster
Lauren : Are you saying you'd like to take me out
Charlie Price : Yes
Lauren : Are you saying that you and Nicola are through
Lauren : And that you're actually available
Charlie Price : Yes
Lauren : And you still like girls
Lauren : Carry on
All : Feed your fire to take you higher
All : We'll light you up like a live wire
All : Celebrate you to elevate you
All : When you struggle to stand we'll take a helping hand
Don : Look out Milan Here comes Don
Don : And Don has brought some friends along
Don : When you're stuck inside uncertainty
Don : The ones you love
Don : Are gonna set you free
Don : Yeah yeah
Don : Whoo
All : Feed your fire to take you higher
All : We'll light you up like a live wire
All : Celebrate you to elevate you
All : When you struggle to stand we'll take a helping hand
All : If you hit the dust let me raise you up
All : When your bubble busts let me raise you up
All : If your glitter rusts let me raise you up
All : And up
All : Raise you up
All : If you hit the dust let me raise you up
All : When your bubble busts let me raise you up
All : If your glitter rusts let me raise you up
All : And up
All : Raise you up
All : Just be raise you up
Lola(Simon) : We're the same Charlie boy
Lola(Simon) : You and me
All : Just be
All : Who you wanna be
All : Never let em tell you who you ought to be
All : Just be
All : With dignity
All : Celebrate yourself triumphantly
All : You'll see
All : Just be
All : Whoo
Lola(Simon) : Ladies
Charlie Price : Gentlemen
Lola(Simon);Charlie Price : And those who have yet to make up their minds
Charlie Price : As people all over the world clamor for Kinky Boots
Charlie Price : it is time for us to get back to work
Charlie Price : But before we go we'd like to leave you
Charlie Price : with the Price Simon secret to success
Lola(Simon) : All right now we've all heard of the 12Step Program have we not
Lola(Simon) : Yes
Lola(Simon) : Well whatever you can do in 12 let me tell you we can do in six
Lola(Simon) : Hey and it goes like this
All : One
Pat : pursue the truth
All : Two
Trish : learn something new
All : Three
Nicola : accept yourself and you'll accept others too
All : Four
Lauren : let love shine
All : Five
Charlie Price : let pride be your guide
All : Six
Don : change the world when you change your mind
All : Just be who you wanna be
All : Never let em tell you who you ought to be
All : Just be
All : With dignity
All : Celebrate your life triumphantly
All : You'll see it's beautiful
All : Just be it's beautiful
All : Just be
All : You'll see it's beautiful
All : Just be it's beautiful
All : Just be
All : Beautiful
All : Whoo feed your fire to take you higher
All : We'll light you up like a live wire
All : Celebrate you to elevate you
All : When you struggle to stand we'll take a helping hand
All : If you hit the dust let me raise you up
All : When your bubble busts let me raise you up
All : If your glitter rusts let me raise you up
All : And raise you up and up and up
All : And up
All : Beautiful