Radio : It's another hot sunny day today here in Southern California
Radio : Temperature is 84 for downtown Los Angeles overnight lows of 75
Girl1 : I think about that day I left him at a Greyhound station West of Santa Fe
Girl1 : We were 17 but he was sweet And it was true
Girl1 : Still I did what I had to do
Girl1 : Cause I just knew
Girl1 : Summer Sunday nights
Girl1 : We'd sink into our seats Right as they dimmed out all the lights
Girl1 : A Technicolor world Made out of music and machine
Girl1 : It called me to be on that screen
Girl1 : And live inside each scene
Girl1;Man1 : Without a nickel to my name Hopped a bus here I came
Girl1;Man1;Man2 : Could be brave or just insane We'll have to see
Girl1 : Cause maybe in that sleepy town He'll sit one day the lights are down
Girl1 : He'll see my face and think Of how he
Girl1;Man1 : used to know me
All : Climb these hills I'm reaching for the heights
All : And chasing all the lights that shine
All : And when they let you down
All : You get up off the ground
All : Cause morning rolls around And it's another day of sun
Man3 : I hear them every day
Man3 : The rhythms in the canyons That'll never fade away
Man3 : The ballads in the bar rooms Left by those who came before
Man3 : They say You gotta want it more
Man3 : So I bang on every door
Girl2 : And even when the answer's no Or when my money's running low
Girl2 : The dusty mic and neon glow are all I need
Man3 : And someday as I sing my song A smalltown kid'll come along
Man3;Girl2 : That'll be the thing to push him on And go go
All : Climb these hills I'm reaching for the heights
All : And chasing all the lights that shine
All : And when they let you down
All : You get up off the ground
All : Cause morning rolls around And it's another day of sun
Girl1 : And when they've let you down
Girl1 : The morning rolls around
All : It's another day of sun
All : It's another day of sun Sun sun sun sun sun
All : Just another day of sun
All : It's another day of sun
All : Another day has just begun
Radio : already has won three Oscars including for the 1998 film Shakespeare in Love
Mia Dolan : I mean we could not believe what was happening
Mia Dolan : No I swear to God she was wrecked
Mia Dolan : She was completely wrecked
Mia Dolan : I know I know It was pure insanity
Mia Dolan : It's insanity
Mia Dolan : Ah
Mia Dolan : Lunacy It was pure lunacy
Mia Dolan : What is his prob I should go
Customer : Cappuccino please
Cafe Manager : Right Of course On us
Customer : Oh no thank you I insist
Man1 : Did you see who that was
Mia Dolan : Shit
Cafe Manager : Mia where do you think you're going
Mia Dolan : Oh it's five after
Cafe Manager : Better be here early tomorrow
Mia Dolan : Okay
Mia Dolan : Have a good night
Mia Dolan : Oh
Mia Dolan : She was wrecked It was pure lunacy
Mia Dolan : It was so crazy and I just
Mia Dolan : Oh you would have died
Mia Dolan : No Turner's fine Turner's fine I just um
Mia Dolan : Are you gonna wait till Denver to tell her or
Mia Dolan : What
Mia Dolan : Okay
Mia Dolan : No I'm happy for you
Mia Dolan : I am I'm happy for you I just
Mia Dolan : I just thought
Mia Dolan : I don't know
Judge : One second
Mia Dolan : I guess I thought
Judge : What Ruby Jessica's on the phone
Judge2 : Um tell her I'll call her back
Judge : In two minutes
Judge2 : Less than two minutes
Judge : I'll go get your lunch
Judge2 : I'm almost done Thank you
Judge : Oh you know what
Judge2 : I think we're good Thanks for coming in
Tracy : Whoa Holy shit You wanna open a window
Mia Dolan : I was trying to give you an entrance
Tracy : Thank you
Alexis : Mia How'd the audition go
Mia Dolan : Eh Eh same here Was Jen there or Rachel
Mia Dolan : I don't know who Jen and Rachel are
Alexis : They're the worst Well
Mia Dolan : I don't know if they were there
Alexis : I bet they were
Caltin : Why is there a convention in the bathroom
Caltin : Two minutes people Mia you're coming right
Mia Dolan : I can't I'm working
Alexis : What
Alexis : Did she just say working
Alexis : I'm sorry it didn't go well today and there's four things in my inbox that you're perfect for and I will submit you But right now you're coming
Alexis : It'll be fun
Mia Dolan : It's not gonna be fun
Alexis : It could be
Mia Dolan : It's not It's gonna be a bunch of social climbers
Mia Dolan : all packed into one of those big glass houses
Alexis : This looks familiar
Mia Dolan : I was gonna give that back How long have you had this
Tracy : A long time Come on Mia
Tracy : When else are you gonna get to see every Hollywood cliche crammed into the same room We'll make fun of it together
Alexis : I'm disappointed in you Lex
Alexis : There's nothing to make fun of This party's gonna be humanity at its finest
Alexis : You got the invitation
Tracy : You got the right address
Alexis : You need some medication
Caltin : The answer's always yes
Alexis : A little chance encounter Could be the one you've waited for
Tracy : Just squeeze a bit more
Tracy : Tonight we're on a mission Tonight's the casting call
Caltin : If this is the real audition
Mia Dolan : Oh God help us all
Alexis : You make the right impression Then everybody knows your name
Alexis;Tracy;Caltin : We're in the fast lane
Tracy : Someone in the crowd could be the one you need to know
Tracy : The one to finally lift you off the ground
Alexis : Someone in the crowd could take you where you wanna go
Alexis : If you're the someone ready to be found
Tracy : If you're the
someone ready to be
Alexis;Tracy;Caltin : Do what you need to do
Till they discover you
Alexis;Tracy;Caltin : And make you more Than who you're seeing now
Alexis;Tracy;Caltin : So with the stars aligned
Mia Dolan : I think I'll stay behind
Alexis;Tracy;Caltin : You've got to go and find
Caltin : That someone in the crowd
Tracy : Hey girl
Alexis;Tracy;Caltin : That someone in the crowd
Mia Dolan : Is someone in the crowd
Mia Dolan : The only thing you really see
Mia Dolan : Watching while the world
Mia Dolan : Keeps spinning round
Mia Dolan : Somewhere there's a place
Mia Dolan : Where I find who I'm gonna be
Mia Dolan : A somewhere that's just waiting To be found
All : Someone in the crowd could be the one you need to know
All : The someone who can lift You off the ground
All : Someone in the crowd Could take you where you wanna go
All : Someone in the crowd could make you Someone in the crowd could take you
All : Flying off the ground If you're the someone
All : Ready to be
All : Found
Mia Dolan : No no
Mia Dolan : Oh come on What
Mia Dolan : Ah
Sebastian Wilder : Please stop sneaking into my home
Laura Wilder : You think Mom or Dad would call this a home
Sebastian Wilder : What are you doing
Sebastian Wilder : Please don't do that
Sebastian Wilder : Please don't sit on that
Laura Wilder : Are you kidding
Sebastian Wilder : Please don't sit on that Don't sit on that Don't sit on that
Sebastian Wilder : Hoagy Carmichael sat on that
Laura Wilder : Oh my God
Sebastian Wilder : The Baked Potato just threw it away
Laura Wilder : I can't imagine why
Sebastian Wilder : And now you're just sitting on it
Laura Wilder : I got you a throw rug
Sebastian Wilder : I don't need that
Laura Wilder : What if I said Miles Davis pissed on it
Sebastian Wilder : It's almost insulting Is it true
Laura Wilder : When are you gonna unpack these boxes
Sebastian Wilder : When I unpack them in my own club
Laura Wilder : Oh Sebastian It's like a girl broke up with you and you're stalking her You're not still going by there are you
Sebastian Wilder : That's
Sebastian Wilder : Can you believe that they turned it into a sambatapas place
Laura Wilder : Oh my God Sebastian
Sebastian Wilder : Samba Tapas
Sebastian Wilder : Pick one you know Do one right
Laura Wilder : I have someone I want you to meet
Sebastian Wilder : I don't wanna meet anyone
Sebastian Wilder : No no I don't wanna meet anyone
Laura Wilder : Dad gave you this
Sebastian Wilder : Yes
Laura Wilder : You'll like her
Sebastian Wilder : I don't think I'm gonna like her
Sebastian Wilder : Does she like jazz
Laura Wilder : Probably not
Sebastian Wilder : Then what are we gonna talk about
Laura Wilder : I don't know It doesn't matter Okay
Laura Wilder : Because you're living like a hermit
Laura Wilder : You're driving without insurance
Sebastian Wilder : It doesn't matter
Laura Wilder : Yeah it doesn't matter
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Laura Wilder : You need to get serious
Sebastian Wilder : Well I know a guy with a face tattoo that you should see
Laura Wilder : Okay low blow
Sebastian Wilder : With a heart of gold
Laura Wilder : Get serious
Sebastian Wilder : Get serious Laura
Sebastian Wilder : I had a very serious plan for my future I know It's not my fault I got shanghaied
Laura Wilder : You didn't get shanghaied You got ripped off
Sebastian Wilder : What's the difference
Laura Wilder : I don't know It's not as romantic as that
Sebastian Wilder : Don't sit
Laura Wilder : Everybody knew that guy was shady except for you
Sebastian Wilder : Why do you say romantic like it's a dirty word
Laura Wilder : Unpaid bills are not romantic Call her
Sebastian Wilder : I'm not gonna call her And the thing is you're acting like life's got me on the ropes
Sebastian Wilder : I want to be on the ropes Okay I'm letting life hit me till it gets tired
Laura Wilder : Oh
Sebastian Wilder : Then I'm gonna hit back It's a classic ropeadope
Laura Wilder : Okay Ali I love you Unpack the boxes
Sebastian Wilder : I'm gonna change the locks
Laura Wilder : You can't afford it
Sebastian Wilder : I'm a phoenix rising from the ashes
Bill : Hey
Sebastian Wilder : Bill Thanks for having me back
Bill : You're welcome
Sebastian Wilder : I want you to know you're looking at a new man
Bill : Good
Sebastian Wilder : A manthat's happy to be here
Bill : Excellent
Sebastian Wilder : Very easy to work with man
Bill : And you're going to play the set list
Sebastian Wilder : Happy to
Sebastian Wilder : Even though I don't think anyone cares what I play but yeah
Bill : Well if by anyone you mean anyone other than me that would be correct I care and I don't wanna hear the free jazz
Sebastian Wilder : Right Okay
Sebastian Wilder : Although I thought in this town it worked on a sort of one for you one for me type system
Sebastian Wilder : How about two for you one for me
Sebastian Wilder : How about all for you and none for me
Bill : That's perfect yes
Sebastian Wilder : Great Okay Mutual decision then
Bill : Right Made by me
Sebastian Wilder : Right And I sign off on it so
Bill : Whatever Tell yourself what you wanna know
Karen : Well Welcome back
Sebastian Wilder : There's a nice way to say that Karen
Bill : Seb
Sebastian Wilder : I hear what you're saying but I don't think you're saying what you mean
Bill : Yeah I don't think you hear what I'm saying You're fired
Sebastian Wilder : I think that's what you're saying but it's not what you mean What you mean is
Bill : You're fired
Sebastian Wilder : Play the set list
Bill : No I'm saying it's too late
Sebastian Wilder : It's a warning
Bill : What planet are you from
Sebastian Wilder : Don't fire me Bill
Bill : You're done
Sebastian Wilder : Don't fire me
Bill : I'm sorry Seb
Sebastian Wilder : It's Christmas
Bill : Yeah I see the decorations Good luck in the new year
Mia Dolan : I just heard you play and I wanted to
Mia Dolan : I don't like the fissure on the GT scan
Mia Dolan : Did you test for achromatopsia
Mia Dolan : DOA on 23rd Perp laughing his face off at the PD
Mia Dolan : Damn Miranda rights
Mia Dolan : This is my classroom
Mia Dolan : You don't like it the door's to my left
Judge3 : Lady why you be tripping like that
Mia Dolan : No Jamal You be trippin
Woman1 : Jump right here
Band Vocal : We're talking away
Band Vocal : I don't know what I'm to say I'll say it anyway
Tracy : Oh Mia
Mia Dolan;Tracy : Hi Hi
Tracy : I want you to meet my friend Carlo
Carlo : Hi
Mia Dolan : Hi Carlo
Tracy : Carlo this is Mia
Carlo : Nice to Mia
Mia : Yes Mia
Carlo : Hi How are you
Tracy : Carlo is a writer
Carlo : Yeah They say I have a knack for worldbuilding I got a lot of heat right now
Carlo : There's been a lot of buzz people talking about me which is exciting I mean you work so hard and then all that validation
Mia Dolan : I'm gonna grab a drink Okay
Carlo : It's really nice to meet you
Band Vocal : I'll be gone
Band Vocal : In a day or two
Band Vocal : So needless to say
Band Vocal : I'm odds and ends
Band Vocal : But I'll be stumbling away
Band Vocal : Slowly learning that life is okay
Band Vocal : Say after me
Band Vocal : It's no better to be safe than sorry
Band Vocal : Take on me
Band Vocal : Take me on
Band Vocal : I'll be gone
Band Vocal : In a day or two
Band Vocal : Thank you Any other requests
Band Vocal : Girl in the front
Mia Dolan : I Ran
Band Vocal : I Ran A fantastic suggestion
Band Vocal : All right Piano Man tickle those ivories Let's hit it
Band Vocal : One Two Three Four
Band Vocal : That's right
Band Vocal : I walk along the avenue
Band Vocal : I never thought I'd meet a girl like you
Band Vocal : Meet a girl like you
Band Vocal : With auburn hair and tawny eyes
Band Vocal : The kind of eyes that hypnotize me through
Band Vocal : You hypnotize me through
Band Vocal : And I ran I ran so far away
Band Vocal : I couldn't get away
Band Vocal : Sometimes I feel I've got to
Band Vocal : Run away I've got to
Band Vocal : Get away from the pain you drive into
Sebastian Wilder : All right I remember you And I'll admit I was a little curt that night
Mia Dolan : Curt
Sebastian Wilder : Okay I was an asshole I can admit that
Mia Dolan : Okay
Sebastian Wilder : But requesting I Ran from a serious musician it's just It's too far
Mia Dolan : My lord Did you just say a serious musician
Sebastian Wilder : I don't think so
Mia Dolan : Can I borrow what you're wearing
Sebastian Wilder : Why
Mia Dolan : Cause I have an audition next week
Mia Dolan : I'm playing a serious firefighter
Sebastian Wilder : So you're an actress
Sebastian Wilder : I thought you looked familiar Have I seen you in anything
Mia Dolan : Uh
Mia Dolan : Coffee shop on the Warner Brothers lot
Mia Dolan : That's a classic
Sebastian Wilder : Oh I see Yeah You're a barista
Sebastian Wilder : And I could see how you could then look down on me from all the way up there
Sebastian Wilder : Time for next set
Sebastian Wilder : He doesn't I don't
Sebastian Wilder : He doesn't tell me what to do
Mia Dolan : He just told you what to do
Sebastian Wilder : I know I let him
Sebastian Wilder : What's your name
Mia Dolan : Mia
Sebastian Wilder : Mia
Sebastian Wilder : Guess I'll see you in the movies
Carlo : You heard of Joseph Campbell
Mia Dolan : Uh yeah
Carlo : I have this idea to do a reimagine of Goldilocks and the Three Bears but from the perspective of the bears
Carlo : The Hero's Journey It could be like a franchise
Mia Dolan : Right
Carlo : There's a lot we don't know
Carlo : There could have been a fourth bear we don't know
Mia Dolan : George Michael
Sebastian Wilder : Hello
Mia Dolan : Sorry
Carlo : Yeah yeah
Mia Dolan : I know that guy Did you get your keys
Sebastian Wilder : Mmhmm yes
Mia Dolan : Can you grab mine
Sebastian Wilder : Can I what
Mia Dolan : Would you be able to grab mine My keys
Sebastian Wilder : I can't hear
Mia Dolan : Sorry
Mia Dolan : Can you grab my keys
Sebastian Wilder : Oh
Mia Dolan : Please
Sebastian Wilder : Oh there we go
Mia Dolan : Thank you
Sebastian Wilder : You're welcome
Sebastian Wilder : What kind
Mia Dolan : It's a Prius
Sebastian Wilder : That doesn't help me
Mia Dolan : With a green ribbon
Sebastian Wilder : All right
Sebastian Wilder : Those look uh comfortable
Mia Dolan : They are
Mia Dolan : Thank you for saving the day back there
Sebastian Wilder : Well you didn't really give me much of a choice
Mia Dolan : It's pretty strange that we keep running into each other
Sebastian Wilder : It is strange
Sebastian Wilder : Maybe it means something
Mia Dolan : I doubt it
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah I don't think so
Mia Dolan : Where's my car
Sebastian Wilder : You gotta put that thing to your chin
Mia Dolan : This
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah
Sebastian Wilder : It makes your head into an antenna so
Mia Dolan : Ooh
Sebastian Wilder : I think it gives you cancer but you find your car faster
Mia Dolan : What
Sebastian Wilder : You don't live as long but you get where you're going quicker so it all evens out
Mia Dolan : That sounds terrible
Sebastian Wilder : Just a suggestion
Mia Dolan : You're
Mia Dolan : You're a real um What's the word I'm looking for
Sebastian Wilder : Knight in shining armour
Mia Dolan : Weirdo
Mia Dolan : That was the word
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Sebastian Wilder : Not much to look at huh
Mia Dolan : I've seen better
Sebastian Wilder : The sun is nearly gone
Sebastian Wilder : The lights are turning on
Sebastian Wilder : A silver shine that stretches to the sea
Sebastian Wilder : We've stumbled on a view That's tailormade for two
Sebastian Wilder : What a shame those two are you and me
Sebastian Wilder : Some other girl and guy
Sebastian Wilder : Would love this swirling sky
Sebastian Wilder : But there's only you and I
Sebastian Wilder : And we've got no shot
Sebastian Wilder : This could never be
Sebastian Wilder : You're not the type for me
Mia Dolan : Really
Sebastian Wilder : And there's not a spark in sight
Sebastian Wilder : What a A waste of a lovely night
Mia Dolan : You say there's nothing here Well let's make something clear
Mia Dolan : I think I'll be the one to make that call
Sebastian Wilder : But you'll call
Mia Dolan : And though you looked so cute In your polyester suit
Sebastian Wilder : It's wool
Mia Dolan : You're right I'd never fall for you at all
Mia Dolan : And maybe this appeals
Mia Dolan : To someone not in heels
Mia Dolan : Or to any girl who feels
Mia Dolan : There's some chance for romance
Mia Dolan : But I'm frankly feeling nothing
Sebastian Wilder : Is that so
Mia Dolan : Or it could be less than nothing
Sebastian Wilder : Good to know So you agree
Mia Dolan : That's right
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : What a waste of a lovely night
Mia Dolan : Ah
Mia Dolan : Hi Greg Oh sorry I'm late
Mia Dolan : Yeah Be there soon Okay Bye
Mia Dolan : It was just right there
Sebastian Wilder : Just right here
Mia Dolan : Do you want a ride to your car
Sebastian Wilder : No I'm just right up here
Mia Dolan : Good night
Sebastian Wilder : Good night
Customer : Excuse me This is glutenfree right
Mia Dolan : No
Customer : What
Mia Dolan : Mmmm
Customer : Ugh I'd like a refund
Mia Dolan : Okay Let me check on that for you
Cafe Manager : Mia
Cafe Manager : Hi You're closing Friday
Mia Dolan : I can't close on Friday I have an audition Remember
Cafe Manager : Do I look like I care Reschedule it
Cafe Manager : Oh and we need to have a little talk tomorrow okay
Cafe Manager : Fix your apron please
Mia Dolan : Okay
Sebastian Wilder : You again
Mia Dolan : What are you doing here
Sebastian Wilder : Oh you know just meetings and studio heads and
Mia Dolan : How'd you get on the lot
Sebastian Wilder : I basically just hauled ass past the guard gates so I think I have 20 minutes until they find me
Sebastian Wilder : You don't have a break coming up do you
Mia Dolan : I'm off in 10 minutes
Sebastian Wilder : Can I hide in the bathroom
Mia Dolan : Yes
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Mia Dolan : Sorry
Mia Dolan : Um
Mia Dolan : I actually do have to check I'm sorry
Mia Dolan : That's the window that Humphrey Bogart and Ingrid Bergman looked out of in Casablanca
Sebastian Wilder : Wow
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Sebastian Wilder : I can't believe you work right across the street from that
Sebastian Wilder : That's amazing
Sebastian Wilder : What was your Bogart's name
Sebastian Wilder : What's his name Is it Greg
Mia Dolan : Yeah Greg
Sebastian Wilder : Right How long have you been
Mia Dolan : We've been seeing each other for about a month
Sebastian Wilder : Oh that's great
Mia Dolan : He's um He's sweet
Mia Dolan : Anyway I love being around this stuff you know
Sebastian Wilder : I know what you mean I get coffee five miles out of the way just so I can be near a jazz club
Mia Dolan : Really
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah the Van Beek
Sebastian Wilder : Do you know it
Mia Dolan : Mmmm
Sebastian Wilder : All the big swing bands used to play there Count Basie Chick Webb
Sebastian Wilder : Anyway it's a sambatapas place now so
Mia Dolan : What's a sambatapas place
Sebastian Wilder : It's just a samba place where they serve tapas
Mia Dolan : Oh
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah so the joke's on history
Sebastian Wilder : I don't know That's LA
Sebastian Wilder : They just worship everything and they value nothing
Filming Director : We're about to roll Stop please guys
Mia Dolan : Okay
Sebastian Wilder : You're rolling
Filming Director : Yeah
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah I know They shoot movies on my street all the time so I know about movies Come this way
Filming Director : Great
Sebastian Wilder : It's a lockdown
Mia Dolan : I love her
Filming Director : And here we go
Sebastian Wilder : Hey How'd you get into all this
Filming Director : And roll
Mia Dolan : Get into what
Filming Director : Sound speed
Sebastian Wilder : You know movies acting
Filming Director : Action
Mia Dolan : Oh um
Mia Dolan : My aunt was an actress
Sebastian Wilder : Oh okay
Mia Dolan : She was in a travelling theatre company I grew up in Boulder City Nevada
Mia Dolan : So across the street from my house there was this little library that had an old movie section
Mia Dolan : So she took me and we spent an entire day watching all these old movies
Mia Dolan : like Notorious and Bringing Up Baby and Casablanca
Mia Dolan : And
Filming Director : Cut it there Cut
Filming Director : Check the gate
Mia Dolan : So we can talk now
Sebastian Wilder : She sounds incredible
Mia Dolan : She was incredible
Mia Dolan : And I would put on all these plays in my bedroom
Mia Dolan : and it would basically just be she and I reenacting those scenes from the movies
Mia Dolan : And then I would write my own plays
Sebastian Wilder : Wow
Mia Dolan : Um Yeah
Mia Dolan : I love it
Mia Dolan : So anyway I left college after two years to come here
Mia Dolan : and um my last audition was for a teen show pitched as Dangerous Minds meets The O. C
Mia Dolan : So yeah should've been a lawyer
Sebastian Wilder : Cause the world needs more lawyers
Mia Dolan : It doesn't need more actresses
Sebastian Wilder : You're not just an actress
Mia Dolan : What do you mean just an actress
Sebastian Wilder : You said it yourself You're a child prodigy playwright
Mia Dolan : That is not what I said
Sebastian Wilder : Well you're too modest to say it but it's true
Sebastian Wilder : You could just write your own roles you know Write something that's as interesting as you are and you don't have to audition for this
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Sebastian Wilder : Uh pissy caca
Sebastian Wilder : Look at Louis Armstrong He could've just played the marching band charts that he was given
Sebastian Wilder : But he didn't do that What did he do
Mia Dolan : What did he do
Sebastian Wilder : Well he made history didn't he
Mia Dolan : Well I'm gonna stop auditioning and I'm gonna make history instead
Sebastian Wilder : Well my work is done here
Mia Dolan : I should probably tell you something now just to get it out of the way
Sebastian Wilder : Mmhmm
Mia Dolan : I hate jazz
Mia Dolan : Are you okay
Sebastian Wilder : What do you mean you hate jazz
Mia Dolan : It just means that when I listen to it I don't like it
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah but it's such a blanket statement you don't like jazz
Sebastian Wilder : What are you doing right now
Mia Dolan : Nothing
Sebastian Wilder : I just think that people when they say that they
Sebastian Wilder : you know hate jazz
Sebastian Wilder : They just They don't have context they don't know where it comes from
Sebastian Wilder : You know Jazz was born in a little flophouse in New Orleans
Sebastian Wilder : and it's just because people were crammed in there they spoke five different languages they couldn't talk to each other
Sebastian Wilder : The only way they could communicate was with jazz
Mia Dolan : You know what about Kenny G
Sebastian Wilder : What
Mia Dolan : What about Kenny G
Mia Dolan : I mean what about elevator music
Mia Dolan : You know jazz music that I know
Sebastian Wilder : What about it
Mia Dolan : From my life
Sebastian Wilder : Mmhmm I just find it relaxing
Sebastian Wilder : It's not relaxing It's not It's not
Sebastian Wilder : Sidney Bechet shot somebody because they told him he played a wrong note
Sebastian Wilder : That's hardly relaxing
Mia Dolan : Yeah but where I grew up there was this station called KJAZZ 103
Mia Dolan : And people would just put on that station when they had a cocktail party
Sebastian Wilder : Right
Mia Dolan : And everyone would kind of just talk over it
Sebastian Wilder : I know
Mia Dolan : Cause it was
Sebastian Wilder : That's the prob Okay okay So I think that's part of the problem is that you can't hear it you know
Sebastian Wilder : You have to see it You have to see what's at stake I mean look at these fellas
Sebastian Wilder : Look at the sax player right now He just hijacked the song He's on his own trip
Sebastian Wilder : Every one of these guys is composing they're rearranging they're writing
Sebastian Wilder : and they're playing the melody They're just
Sebastian Wilder : And now look the trumpet player
Sebastian Wilder : He's got his own idea
Sebastian Wilder : And so it's conflict and it's compromise and it's just
Sebastian Wilder : It's new every time It's brandnew every night
Sebastian Wilder : It's very very exciting
Sebastian Wilder : And it's dying It's dying Mia
Sebastian Wilder : It's dying on the vine
Sebastian Wilder : And the world says Let it die It had its time
Sebastian Wilder : Well not on my watch
Mia Dolan : What are you gonna do
Sebastian Wilder : I'm gonna have my own club
Mia Dolan : Really
Sebastian Wilder : Yes
Sebastian Wilder : We're gonna play whatever we want whenever we want
Sebastian Wilder : however we want as long as it's pure jazz
Mia Dolan : Hi this is Mia Dolan
Mia Dolan : Yeah I just missed a call
Mia Dolan : I got a callback
Sebastian Wilder : What Come on
Sebastian Wilder : For what
Mia Dolan : For a TV show The one I was telling you about earlier
Sebastian Wilder : The Dangerous Minds meets The O. C
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Sebastian Wilder : Congratulations That's incredible
Mia Dolan : It's really exciting
Mia Dolan : I feel like I said negative stuff about it before
Mia Dolan : What
Mia Dolan : It's like Rebel Without A Cause sort of
Sebastian Wilder : I got the bullets
Mia Dolan : Yes
Sebastian Wilder : You've never seen it
Mia Dolan : I've never seen it
Sebastian Wilder : Oh my You know it's playing at the Rialto
Mia Dolan : Really
Mia Dolan : Yes
Sebastian Wilder : You should go I mean I can take you
Mia Dolan : Okay
Sebastian Wilder : You know for research
Mia Dolan : For research
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Sebastian Wilder : Um Monday night 10 O'clock
Mia Dolan : Yeah Great
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Mia Dolan : For research
Sebastian Wilder : City of Stars
Sebastian Wilder : Are you shining just for me
Sebastian Wilder : There's so much that I can't see
Sebastian Wilder : Who knows
Sebastian Wilder : Is this the start Of something wonderful and new
Sebastian Wilder : Or one more dream
Sebastian Wilder : That I cannot make true
Sebastian Wilder;Woman : Stand right there please
Mia Dolan : Okay Nice to meet you
Mia Dolan : Hi
Judge : Hi
Judge : In your own time
Mia Dolan : Okay
Mia Dolan : Two options
Mia Dolan : You either follow my rules or follow my rules Capisce
Judge : Thank you
Mia Dolan : Oh
Judge : Thanks
Mia Dolan : I can do it a different way
Judge : No that's fine Thank you very much Thank you
Mia Dolan : That was fun Thanks
Judge : Bye
Tracy : Oh hey Mia
Mia Dolan : Hey
Tracy : Greg's here
Mia Dolan : What do you mean
Greg : Hey babe Got a space out front
Mia Dolan : Great
Greg : We should get going
Greg : Okay My brother landed really early
Greg : Did you forget
Mia Dolan : Shit
Greg : You forgot
Mia Dolan : That's tonight
Greg : That's okay
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Greg : Yeah
Mia Dolan : Okay
Mia Dolan : All right so then I'll just get changed
Greg : Okay
Mia Dolan : Okay
Greg : Great
Mia Dolan : Great
Greg : Yeah that's him
Mia Dolan : Um
Greg : Hey Josh yeah Uh
Greg : Just picking up Mia We'll be there in like
Josh : But now we've got this surround sound setup so it's like
Josh's Fiance : It's like being in a movie theatre
Greg : Wow
Josh : But better than being in a theatre really I can't wait You know theatres these days
Greg : Yeah They're so dirty
Josh : Yeah I know And so smelly
Greg : And they're either too hot or too cold
Josh : I know The quality's really fallen off
Greg : The quality's terrible And there's always people talking
Josh : Cause of all of the people Which is just
Greg : Oh it's the worst Oh I'm sorry Hold on one
second
Josh : The texting
Josh : Hello
Josh's Fiance : Probably work
Greg : Mm
Josh : Sorry So yeah we love it
Josh's Fiance : Oh it's so nice
Josh : Well we have to come
Greg : Maybe
Josh : You should Come by
Josh : I got one word for you man
Greg : Mmhmm
Josh : Indo, nesia.
Greg : I've never heard anyone say that
Josh : I don't even know I can't keep track of it but honestly it was lifechanging
Greg : Really Yeah
Josh : It affected me
Josh : It was incredible
Greg : Is it amazing
Josh : Yes A fivestar jungle ecoresort
Josh : you would not believe
Josh's Fiance : Amazing
Greg : We were thinking about Nicaragua the thing about Nicaragua
Greg : is it's less developed It's a little underdeveloped
Josh : Right
Greg : I think there's a little more
Greg : Yeah then I just I don't know I don't know if it's safe
Josh : Yeah yeah It's
Greg : You know
Josh's Fiance : Yeah you don't want to explore too far Kind of a natives are restless sort of thing
Greg : Actually China's going to build a Panama Canal
Mia Dolan : I'm sorry
Movie Sound : And immensity of our universe
Movie Sound : For many days before the end of our Earth
Movie Sound : people will look into the night sky and notice a star
Movie Sound : increasingly bright and increasingly near
Movie Sound : As this star approaches us
Movie Sound : Jim Stark
Movie Sound : I'll go find a place I'm sorry
Movie Sound : As this star approaches us
Movie Sound : the weather will change
Movie Sound : The great polar fields of the north and south will rot and divide
Movie Sound : and the seas will turn warm
Movie Sound : The last of us search the heavens and stand amazed
Movie Sound : for the stars will still be there and will be
Sebastian Wilder : Mm
Mia Dolan : I have an idea
Alexis : What is that Is it a script
Mia Dolan : It's a play
Tracy : A play You better give us all roles
Mia Dolan : Actually it's a onewoman show
Mia Dolan : So I can't
Alexis : Wow Is that gonna happen every time
Mia Dolan : I think so
Woman : Ah It's oneway
Mia Dolan : I love you
Sebastian Wilder : I love you too
Mia Dolan : Oh
Keith : Sebastian
Sebastian Wilder : Keith
Keith : Come here man
Sebastian Wilder : How are you
Keith : I've been good man
Sebastian Wilder : This is Mia Mia Keith
Keith : Hi Mia Nice to meet you
Mia Dolan : Nice to meet you
Keith : I used to play with this guy
Sebastian Wilder : Went to school together
Keith : So how you been brother
Sebastian Wilder : Great
Sebastian Wilder : Never been better How about you
Keith : I've been really good Been very busy
Keith : I got a new combo
Sebastian Wilder : Okay Cool
Keith : We're looking for keys
Sebastian Wilder : Are you kidding me
Keith : No I'm not kidding you
Keith : No I'm good Are you sure It pays
Sebastian Wilder : I'm good
Keith : Let's just grab a drink then It's been too long
Keith : Okay Nice to meet you Mia
Mia Dolan : Nice to meet you
Mia Dolan : The End
Sebastian Wilder : Genius
Mia Dolan : Really
Sebastian Wilder : Yes
Mia Dolan : It feels really nostalgic to me Is it too nostalgic
Sebastian Wilder : That's the point
Mia Dolan : Are people gonna like it
Sebastian Wilder : Fuck em
Mia Dolan : You always say that
Sebastian Wilder : Well I truly believe it
Mia Dolan : I made you something
Sebastian Wilder : For what
Mia Dolan : For your club
Sebastian Wilder : Why does it say Seb's
Mia Dolan : Cause I think you should call it Seb's
Sebastian Wilder : What
Mia Dolan : Cause no one's gonna come to Chicken On A Stick
Sebastian Wilder : Is that a music note as an apostrophe
Mia Dolan : Yes
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah That's pretty cool
Sebastian Wilder : It's gotta be Chicken On A Stick
Sebastian Wilder : Because Charlie Parker got his nickname
Mia Dolan : I know because he loved chicken
Sebastian Wilder : That's why they called him Bird
Sebastian Wilder : So I'm gonna have chicken beer jazz Chicken On A Stick
Mia Dolan : I know You should drop the chicken and just have drinks and jazz and also
Sebastian Wilder : I'm not dropping the chicken
Mia Dolan : You could maybe do it somewhere else
Sebastian Wilder : What are you talk
Mia Dolan : Find a new spot
Sebastian Wilder : It's gotta be the Van Beek
Mia Dolan : Well it doesn't have to be the Van Beek
Sebastian Wilder : I can't let them samba all over its history
Sebastian Wilder : I can't do it
Mia Dolan : You can let them but you refuse to Your play's incredible
Sebastian Wilder : You know the whole world from your bedroom
Sebastian Wilder : What else do they want Who's doing that
Mia Dolan : I'm doing that
Sebastian Wilder : You're doing that
Mia Dolan : Who was that guy at The Lighthouse
Mia Dolan : The guy that offered you the gig
Sebastian Wilder : Keith
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Mia Dolan : Why was it so weird between you two
Sebastian Wilder : It's always weird with him
Mia Dolan : Really
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah
Mia Dolan : But he seemed kind of nice cause he did offer you a job
Mia Dolan : Are you gonna call him
Sebastian Wilder : No No
Mia Dolan : All right
Sebastian Wilder : So Here's what we know
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Sebastian Wilder : It's definitely Chicken On A Stick
Sebastian Wilder : and your play is gonna be a triumph
Mia Dolan : It's a onewoman show so it's just me No I mean I'm acting in it too
Mia Dolan : No Mom I'm not getting paid I'm paying to do it
Mia Dolan : He's great He's gonna open his own jazz club
Mia Dolan : Yeah it's gonna be incredible
Mia Dolan : No he hasn't he hasn't opened it yet He needs some
Mia Dolan : He's saving up I think
Mia Dolan : No he doesn't have a steady gig
Mia Dolan : But he's figuring it out It's just been a little tricky lately
Mia Dolan : Mom he's gonna find a way to open it and you're gonna love it okay
Mia Dolan : How's Dad
Keith : Sebastian
Keith : Come on in man
Keith : Thanks for coming
Sebastian Wilder : Thanks for having me
Keith : Wasn't sure I'd see you today
Keith : So here's the deal
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Keith : We got distribution with Universal We've got our own imprint
Keith : About to go on the road
Keith : Uh we can pay you 1000 bucks a week plus a cut of the ticket revenue and merchandising
Keith : Sound good
Keith : Sebastian
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah All right
Keith : Let's play
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Keith : Tonight
Keith : I know It's different
Keith : But you say you wanna save jazz
Keith : How you gonna save jazz if no one's listening
Keith : Jazz is dying because of people like you
Keith : You're playing to 90yearolds at The Lighthouse
Keith : Where are the kids Where are the young people
Keith : You're so obsessed with Kenny Clarke and Thelonious Monk
Keith : These guys were revolutionaries
Keith : How are you gonna be a revolutionary
Keith : if you're such a traditionalist
Keith : You're holding onto the past but jazz is about the future
Keith : I know
Keith : The other guy he wasn't as good as you
Keith : But you're a pain in the ass man
Sebastian Wilder : City of Stars
Sebastian Wilder : Are you shining just for me
Sebastian Wilder : There's so much that I can't see
Sebastian Wilder : Who knows
Sebastian Wilder : I felt it from the first embrace I shared with you
Mia Dolan : That now our dreams
Mia Dolan : May finally come true
Mia Dolan : City of Stars
Mia Dolan : Just one thing everybody wants
Mia Dolan : There in the bars
Mia Dolan : Or through the smokescreen of the crowded restaurants
Mia Dolan : It's love
Mia Dolan : Yes all we're looking for is love
Mia Dolan : From someone else
Sebastian Wilder : A rush
Mia Dolan : A glance
Sebastian Wilder : A touch
Mia Dolan : A dance
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : A look in somebody's eyes
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : To light up the skies
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : To open the world and send it reeling
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : A voice that says I'll be here
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : And you'll be all right
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : I don't care if I know
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : Just where I will go
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : Cause all that I need's This crazy feeling
Mia Dolan;Sebastian Wilder : A rattattat on my heart
Sebastian Wilder : Think I want it to stay
Sebastian Wilder : City of Stars
Sebastian Wilder : Are you shining just for me
Mia Dolan : You never shined so brightly
Keith : I don't know Why I keep moving my body
Keith : I don't know if this is wrong Or if it's right
Keith : I don't know if it's the beat
Keith : But something's taken over me
Keith : And I just know I feel so good tonight
Keith : I don't know what your name is But I like it
Keith : I've been thinking About some things I wanna try
Keith : I don't know what you came to do
Keith : But I wanna do it with you
Keith : And I just know I feel so good tonight
Keith : Oh if we keep on dancing
Keith : Take our rhythm to new heights
Keith : Feel the heat of passion baby
Keith : Light up the night
Keith : Come on let it burn baby
Keith : Let the tables turn baby
Keith : I just know I feel so good
Keith : Don't you know I feel so good
Keith : Tonight
Keith : I don't care if this turns into a riot
Keith : Let's get reckless Tear this place down to the floor
Keith : Turn the music way up loud
Keith : Can't nobody stop us now
Keith : I just know I feel so good tonight
Keith : Come on let it burn baby
Keith : Let the tables turn baby
Keith : Oh I just know I feel so good
Keith : Don't you know I feel so good
Keith : Don't you know Don't you know
Keith : Tonight
Mia Dolan : Hey it's me
Mia Dolan : Uh I'm not sure where you are right now I think Boston
Mia Dolan : Maybe Dallas I don't know
Mia Dolan : Uh
Mia Dolan : I haven't heard from you in a little while
Mia Dolan : and I miss you
Mia Dolan : All right bye
Sebastian Wilder : I thought
Sebastian Wilder : Surprise
Sebastian Wilder : Gotta leave first thing in the morning but I just had to see you
Sebastian Wilder : It's so nice to be home
Mia Dolan : I'm so glad you're home
Sebastian Wilder : How's the play going
Mia Dolan : Um I'm nervous
Sebastian Wilder : You are
Mia Dolan : Mmhmm
Sebastian Wilder : Why
Mia Dolan : Because what if people show up
Sebastian Wilder : Pissy caca
Sebastian Wilder : You're nervous about what they think
Mia Dolan : I'm nervous to do it I'm nervous to get up
Mia Dolan : on a stage and perform for people I mean I don't need to say that to you
Sebastian Wilder :
It's gonna be incredible
Mia Dolan : You don't get it
but I'm terrified
Sebastian Wilder : They should be so lucky to see it
Sebastian Wilder : I can't wait
Mia Dolan : I can
Mia Dolan : When do you leave the morning
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah six fortyfive
Mia Dolan : Ooh
Sebastian Wilder : Boise
Mia Dolan : Boyhe
Sebastian Wilder : Boyden
Mia Dolan : To Boise
Sebastian Wilder : You should come
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah you can knock that off your bucket list
Mia Dolan : Oh that would be really exciting I wish I could
Mia Dolan : What are you doing after the tour
Sebastian Wilder : Why can't you
Mia Dolan : Come to Boise
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah
Mia Dolan : Cause I have to rehearse
Sebastian Wilder : But can't you rehearse anywhere
Mia Dolan : Anywhere you are
Sebastian Wilder : I mean I guess
Mia Dolan : Um
Mia Dolan : Well all my stuff is here and it's in two weeks so I don't really think that would be
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Mia Dolan : The best idea right now but
Mia Dolan : I wish I could
Sebastian Wilder : We're just gonna have to try and see each other We almost never see each other
Mia Dolan : I know but when are you done
Sebastian Wilder : What do you mean I mean
Mia Dolan : When are you finished with the whole tour
Sebastian Wilder : But after we finish we're gonna go and record and then we go back on tour
Sebastian Wilder : We tour so we can make the record so we can go back and tour the record
Mia Dolan : So it's like the long haul
Sebastian Wilder : What do you mean the long haul
Mia Dolan : I mean the long haul Like you're gonna stay in this band for a long time
Mia Dolan : On tour
Sebastian Wilder : I mean what did you think I was gonna do
Mia Dolan : I don't I hadn't really thought it through I didn't know that the band
Mia Dolan : was so important
Sebastian Wilder : You didn't think it would be successful
Mia Dolan : Um
Mia Dolan : No that's not really what I mean I just mean that you You're gonna be on tour for what months now Years
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah I don't believe This is it I mean it could feasibly be I could be on tour with this
Sebastian Wilder : For a couple of years at least Just this record
Mia Dolan : Do you like the music you're playing
Sebastian Wilder : I don't
Sebastian Wilder : I don't know what it matters
Mia Dolan : Well it matters because if you're gonna give up your dream I think it matters that you like what you're playing on the road for years
Sebastian Wilder : Do you like the music I'm playing
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Mia Dolan : I do
Sebastian Wilder : I just didn't think that you did
Mia Dolan : Yeah well You always said Keith is the worst
Mia Dolan : and now you're gonna be on tour with him for years so I just didn't know if you were happy What are you doing right now
Sebastian Wilder : Why are you doing this
Mia Dolan : I don't
Sebastian Wilder : What do you mean why am I doing this I thought you wanted me to do this
Sebastian Wilder : It just sounds like now you don't want me to do it
Mia Dolan : What do you mean I wanted you to do this
Sebastian Wilder : This is what you wanted for me
Mia Dolan : To be in this band
Sebastian Wilder : To be in a band To have a steady job you know
Sebastian Wilder : To to to be you know
Mia Dolan : Of course I wanted you to have a steady job so that you could take care of yourself and your life
Mia Dolan : and you could start your club
Sebastian Wilder : So I'm doing that So I don't understand Why aren't we celebrating
Mia Dolan : Why aren't you starting your club
Sebastian Wilder : You said yourself no one wants to go to that club
Sebastian Wilder : No one wants to go to a club called Chicken On A Stick
Mia Dolan : So change the name
Sebastian Wilder : Well no one likes jazz Not even you
Mia Dolan : I do like jazz now because of you
Sebastian Wilder : And this is what I thought you wanted me to do
Sebastian Wilder : What am I supposed to do Go back to playing Jingle Bells
Sebastian Wilder : Scraping pennies so I can start a club no one wants to go to and start the club
Mia Dolan : I'm not saying that I'm saying why don't you take what you've made
Mia Dolan : People will want to go to it because you're passionate about it
Mia Dolan : and people love what other people are passionate about
Mia Dolan : You remind people of what they forgot
Sebastian Wilder : Not in my experience
Sebastian Wilder : Well whatever all right It's just time to grow up you know I have a steady job this is what I'm doing
Sebastian Wilder : And now all of a sudden if you had these problems I wish you would have said them earlier before I signed on the goddamn dotted line
Mia Dolan : I'm pointing out that you had a dream
Mia Dolan : that you followed that you were sticking to
Sebastian Wilder : This is the dream
Mia Dolan : This is not your dream
Sebastian Wilder : Guys like me work their whole lives to be in something that's successful that people like
Sebastian Wilder : You know
Sebastian Wilder : I mean I'm finally in something that people enjoy
Mia Dolan : Since when do you care about being liked
Sebastian Wilder : Just cause I don't enjoy it doesn't matter
Mia Dolan : Why do you care so much about being liked
Sebastian Wilder : You're an actress What are you talking about
Sebastian Wilder : Maybe you just liked me when I was on my ass cause it made you feel better about yourself
Mia Dolan : Are you kidding
Sebastian Wilder : No
Sebastian Wilder : I don't know
Keith : Okay fellas I'll see you tomorrow
Keith : Sebastian
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah
Keith : You're good for tonight right
Sebastian Wilder : What are you talking about
Keith : 700 the photo shoot
Keith : Mojo Are you good
Sebastian Wilder : I thought that was next Thursday
Keith : No it's tonight
Keith : Is that okay
Photographer : Give me the other camera
Helper : What's wrong with that one
Photographer : What's wrong with it It doesn't bloody work that's what's wrong with it
Photographer : All right trumpet that's lovely
Photographer : Lovely Beautiful beautiful
Photographer : Okay keyboard Okay look up
Photographer : That's good That's good that's lovely Lovely
Photographer : Okay cut the music
Photographer : That is lovely That's lovely
Photographer : Okay now bite your lip like this sort of like
Photographer : Like you're concentrating on something I don't know like a piece of your music
Sebastian Wilder : Bite my what
Photographer : Your lip You know bite your lip
Sebastian Wilder : Okay
Photographer : Yeah that's good That's great Beautiful
Photographer : Beautiful Okay now just move your glasses down on onto the nose
Photographer : A little bit further just a little bit a touch further Keep your head down
Photographer : but look up at me Look sort of moody
Photographer : Yeah That's beautiful That is great
Photographer : Okay turn the keyboard on live
Sebastian Wilder : Do you wanna hear the keyboard then
Photographer : You don't have to bite your lip now
Photographer : Well actually play something
Photographer : Play something You know Anything
Photographer : You're a pianist aren't you Play something
Photographer : That's great that's beautiful
Photographer : That's lovely Oh that's good
Photographer : No don't stop Keep playing
Photographer : Go on just keep playing That was great
Man1 : shoot myself in the head
Man1 : She's not even good
Man1 : That whole window thing
Man2 : Yeah what was that shit with the window
Man1 : Oh my God Don't quit your day job
Man2 : Oh well
Man1 : Not good Onewoman shows are always terrible
Sebastian Wilder : Mia
Sebastian Wilder : Mia I'm so sorry
Sebastian Wilder : Just tell me how it went How was it
Mia Dolan : Don't help me
Sebastian Wilder : I'm sorry
Sebastian Wilder : I'm sorry I've been such a prick
Mia Dolan : You're sorry you're sorry
Mia Dolan : You're sorry
Sebastian Wilder : I'm gonna make it up to you
Sebastian Wilder : Let me make it up to you okay
Sebastian Wilder : I don't blame you for not wanting
Mia Dolan : It's over
Sebastian Wilder : What is
Sebastian Wilder : What
Mia Dolan : All of this
Mia Dolan : I'm done embarrassing myself I'm done I'm done
Mia Dolan : Nobody showed up
Sebastian Wilder : So what So what
Mia Dolan : I can't pay back the theater This is so
Mia Dolan : I'm gonna go home for a while
Sebastian Wilder : I'll come see you tomorrow
Mia Dolan : No I'm going home home
Sebastian Wilder : This is home
Mia Dolan : No it's not any more
Sebastian Wilder : Yep
Jane : Hi I'm trying to reach Mia Dolan
Sebastian Wilder : Wrong number
Jane : She's not answering her cell I was told I might find her here
Sebastian Wilder : Not any more
Jane : Okay well if you do talk to her
Sebastian Wilder : I won't
Jane : could you tell her Jane at Amy Brandt Casting is trying to reach her
Sebastian Wilder : Casting
Mia's Father : Who the hell is that
Mia's Neighbor : Shut that thing off
Mia Dolan : Why did you come here
Sebastian Wilder : Because I have good news
Mia Dolan : What
Sebastian Wilder : Amy Brandt the casting director
Sebastian Wilder : Yeah She was at your play
Sebastian Wilder : and she loved it
Sebastian Wilder : And she loved it so much
Sebastian Wilder : that she wants you to come in tomorrow and audition for this huge movie that she's got
Mia Dolan : I'm not going to that
Sebastian Wilder : What
Mia Dolan : That one's gonna be No That one's gonna be
Sebastian Wilder : I'm sorry
Mia Dolan : That will kill me
Sebastian Wilder : What
Mia Dolan : What
Mia Dolan : What Shh Stop
Sebastian Wilder : No
Mia Dolan : You have to be quiet We're in a neighbourhood
Sebastian Wilder : If you want me to be quiet you have to make some goddamn sense
Sebastian Wilder : You tell me why you're not going They'll call the police Because
Sebastian Wilder : Why
Mia Dolan : I've been to a million auditions and the same thing happens everytime where I get interrupted because someone wants to get a sandwich
Mia Dolan : Or I'm crying and they start laughing
Mia Dolan : Or there's people sitting in the waiting room
Mia Dolan : and they're like me but prettier and better at the
Mia Dolan : Because maybe I'm not good enough
Sebastian Wilder : Yes you are
Mia Dolan : No
Mia Dolan : No maybe I'm not
Sebastian Wilder : Yes you are
Mia Dolan : Maybe I'm not
Sebastian Wilder : You are
Mia Dolan : Maybe I'm one of those people that has always wanted to do it
Mia Dolan : but it's like a pipe dream for me You know And then you said it
Mia Dolan : you change your dreams and then you grow up
Mia Dolan : Maybe I'm one of those people and I'm not supposed to
Mia Dolan : And I can go back to school
Mia Dolan : and I can find something else that I'm supposed to do
Mia Dolan : Cause I left
Mia Dolan : to do that and it's been six years and I don't want to do it anymore
Sebastian Wilder : Why
Mia Dolan : Why what
Sebastian Wilder : Why don't you want to do it anymore
Mia Dolan : Cause I think it hurts a little bit too much
Sebastian Wilder : You're a baby
Mia Dolan : I'm not a baby I'm trying to grow up
Sebastian Wilder : You're crying like a baby
Mia Dolan : Oh my God
Sebastian Wilder : You have an audition tomorrow at five thirty
Sebastian Wilder : I'll be out front at eight a.m.
Sebastian Wilder : You'll be out front or not I don't know
Mia Dolan : How'd you find me here
Sebastian Wilder : The house in front of the library
Mia Dolan : I got coffee
Sebastian Wilder : Okay great
Helper : Mia
Amy : Hi Mia I'm Amy and this is Frank
Frank : Hi How are you
Mia Dolan : Nice to meet you
Amy : Glad we found you
Mia Dolan : Me too
Amy : The film shoots in Paris and we don't have a script
Frank : It's gonna be a process
Frank : We're gonna build the character around the actress It's a threemonth rehearsal and a fourmonth shoot
Mia Dolan : Okay
Amy : And we thought that you could just tell us a story
Mia Dolan : About
Amy : You can just tell us anything
Mia Dolan : Anything
Amy : Yeah just tell us a story You're a storyteller
Mia Dolan : Um
Amy : Whenever you're ready
Mia Dolan : My aunt used to live in Paris
Mia Dolan : I remember she used to come home and she would tell us these stories about being abroad
Mia Dolan : and I remember
Mia Dolan : she told us that she jumped into the river once
Mia Dolan : Barefoot
Mia Dolan : She smiled
Mia Dolan : Leapt without looking
Mia Dolan : And tumbled into
Mia Dolan : The Seine
Mia Dolan : The water was freezing
Mia Dolan : She spent a month sneezing
Mia Dolan : But said she would do it again
Mia Dolan : Here's to the ones who dream
Mia Dolan : Foolish as they may seem
Mia Dolan : Here's to the hearts that ache
Mia Dolan : Here's to the mess we make
Mia Dolan : She captured a feeling
Mia Dolan : Sky with no ceiling
Mia Dolan : The sunset inside a frame
Mia Dolan : She lived in her liquor
Mia Dolan : And died with a flicker
Mia Dolan : I'll always remember the flame
Mia Dolan : Here's to the ones who dream
Mia Dolan : Foolish as they may seem
Mia Dolan : Here's to the hearts that ache
Mia Dolan : Here's to the mess we make
Mia Dolan : She told me
Mia Dolan : A bit of madness is key
Mia Dolan : To give us new colours to see
Mia Dolan : Who knows where it will lead us
Mia Dolan : And that's why they need us
Mia Dolan : So bring on the rebels
Mia Dolan : The ripples from pebbles
Mia Dolan : The painters and poets and plays
Mia Dolan : And here's to the fools
Mia Dolan : Who dream
Mia Dolan : Crazy as they may seem
Mia Dolan : Here's to the hearts that break
Mia Dolan : Here's to the mess
Mia Dolan : We make
Mia Dolan : I Trace it all back to then
Mia Dolan : Her and the snow and The Seine
Mia Dolan : Smiling through it
Mia Dolan : She said she'd do it
Mia Dolan : Again
Sebastian Wilder : When do you find out
Mia Dolan : Oh they said the next couple days
Mia Dolan : But I'm not expecting to find anything out
Sebastian Wilder : You're gonna get it
Mia Dolan : I really might not
Sebastian Wilder : Yes you are
Mia Dolan : I hope you're not disappointed
Sebastian Wilder : I know
Sebastian Wilder : I know I know these things
Mia Dolan : Where are we
Sebastian Wilder : Griffith Park
Sebastian Wilder : I know
I don't know
Mia Dolan : What do we do
Sebastian Wilder : I don't think we can do anything
Sebastian Wilder : cause when you get this
Mia Dolan : If I get this
Sebastian Wilder : When you get this
Sebastian Wilder : you gotta give it everything you got
Sebastian Wilder : Everything
Sebastian Wilder : It's your dream
Mia Dolan : What are you gonna do
Sebastian Wilder : I gotta follow my own plan you know
Sebastian Wilder : Stay here and get my own thing going
Sebastian Wilder : You're gonna be in Paris
Sebastian Wilder : Good jazz there
Sebastian Wilder : And you love jazz now
Sebastian Wilder : Right
Mia Dolan : Yes
Sebastian Wilder : And I guess we're just gonna have to wait and see
Mia Dolan : I'm always gonna love you
Sebastian Wilder : I'm always gonna love you too
Sebastian Wilder : Look at this view
Mia Dolan : I've seen better
Sebastian Wilder : It's the worst
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Mia Dolan : I've never been here during the day
Mia Dolan : Hi Could I have two iced coffees please
Cafe Worker : Right Of course
Cafe Worker2 : On us
Mia Dolan : Oh no thank you I insist
Keith : Sounds good Harris did a good job
Sebastian Wilder : Took him long enough
Keith : It always does Signature time
Keith : Not doing too bad Seb
Sebastian Wilder : Not too bad is great
Keith : See you tonight
Mia Dolan : Hi
Mia Dolan : How was your day
Mia's Husband : Good
Mia Dolan : Hmm How is she
Mia's Husband : She's great
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Mia's Husband : Yeah come on
Mia Dolan : Hi buddy
Mia Dolan : I didn't think you were gonna be home yet
Mia Dolan : Are you drawing
Mia's Daughter : Yeah
Mia Dolan : Can I help You know I love to draw
Mia Dolan : Okay Chelsea we're gonna go
Mia Dolan : Are you good
Chelsea : We're good
Mia Dolan : You need anything
Mia Dolan : Bye baby
Chelsea : Say Bye Mommy
Mia Dolan : Sleep well
Mia's Daughter : Bye Mommy
Mia Dolan : Have fun with Chelsea
Mia's Daughter : Have fun
Chelsea : Bye Mia
Mia Dolan : Bye Thank you so much
Mia's Husband : Good night guys, Night sweetie
Chelsea : Good night
Mia's Husband : Oh boy
Mia's Husband : What if we miss this What do you wanna tell Natalie
Mia Dolan : Oh
Mia Dolan : We'll just see it back in New York
Mia's Husband : Okay
Mia Dolan : I do not miss this
Mia's Husband : This is bad
Mia Dolan : Do you want to just pull off here and get dinner
Mia's Husband : Sure yeah
Mia Dolan : Yeah
Mia's Husband : Yeah
Mia Dolan : Okay
Mia's Husband : Do you want to check it out
Mia's Husband : This place is pretty cool
Man : I love them
Sebastian Wilder : Cal Bennett on sax
Sebastian Wilder : Javier Gonzalez on trumpet
Sebastian Wilder : The lovely Nedra Wheeler on bass
Sebastian Wilder : The one and only Clifton Foufou Eddie on drums
Sebastian Wilder : And a little too good on piano so good he's gonna own this place if I'm not careful
Sebastian Wilder : Khirye Tyler everybody
Sebastian Wilder : Uh
Sebastian Wilder : Welcome to Seb's
Mia Dolan : I just heard you play and I wanted to
Mia's Husband : Do you want to stay for another
Mia Dolan : No we should go
Mia's Husband : All right
Sebastian Wilder : One two One two three four