Tala : In the beginning
Tala : there was only ocean
Tala : until the mother island emerged Te Fiti
Tala : Her heart held the greatest power ever known
Tala : It could create life itself
Tala : And Te Fiti shared it with the world
Tala : But in time some began to seek Te Fiti's heart
Tala : They believed if they could possess it the great power of creation would be theirs
Tala : And one day
Tala : the most daring of them all voyaged across the vast ocean to take it
Tala : He was a demigod of the wind and sea
Tala : He was a warrior
Tala : A trickster
Tala : A shapeshifter who could change form with the power of his magical fish hook
Tala : And his name was Maui
Tala : But without her heart Te Fiti began to crumble giving birth to a terrible darkness
Tala : Maui tried to escape but was confronted by another who sought the heart
Tala : Te Kā A demon of earth and fire
Tala : Maui was struck from the sky
Tala : never to be seen again
Tala : And his magical fish hook and the heart of Te Fiti were lost to the sea
Tala : Where even now 1000 years later
Tala : Te Kā and the demons of the deep still hunt for the heart
Tala : Hiding in a darkness that will continue to spread
Tala : chasing away our fish
Tala : draining the life from island after island
Tala : until every one of us is devoured
Tala : by the bloodthirsty jaws of inescapable death
Tala : But one day the heart will be found
by someone who will journey beyond our reef find Maui
Tala : deliver him across the great ocean to restore Te Fiti's heart
Tala : and save us all
Chief Tui : Whoa whoa whoa Thank you Mother That's enough
Toddler Moana : Papa
Chief Tui : No one goes outside the reef
Chief Tui : We are safe here There is no darkness
Chief Tui : There are no monsters
Children : Monsters
Chief Tui : There's no monsters no monsters
Boy1 : It's the darkness
Chief Tui : No there is nothing beyond our reef but storms and rough seas
Boy1 : I'm gonna throw up
Chief Tui : As long as we stay on our very safe island
Chief Tui : we'll be fine
Tala : The legends are true
Tala : Someone will have to go
Chief Tui : Mother Motunui is paradise
Chief Tui : Who would want to go anywhere else
Toddler Moana : Shoo shoo
Chief Tui : Moana
Chief Tui : There you are Moana What are you doing You scared me
Toddler Moana : What I wanna's go back
Chief Tui : I know I know But you don't go out there
Chief Tui : It's dangerous
Chief Tui : Moana come on
Chief Tui : Let's go back to the village
Chief Tui : You are the next great chief of our people
Sina : And you will do wondrous things my little minnow
Chief Tui : Oh yes But first you must learn where you're meant to be
Chief Tui : Moana
Chief Tui : Make way make way
Chief Tui : Moana it's time you knew
Chief Tui : The village of Motunui is all you need
Chief Tui : The dancers are practicing
Chief Tui : They dance to an ancient song
Motunui Villagers : Who needs a new song This old one's all we need
Chief Tui : This tradition is our mission
Chief Tui : And Moana there's so much to do
Chief Tui : Don't trip on the taro root
Chief Tui : That's all you need
Chief Tui : We share everything we make
Chief Tui : We joke and we weave our baskets
Chief Tui : The fishermen come back from the sea
Toddler Moana : I wanna see
Chief Tui : Don't walk away
Chief Tui : Moana stay on the ground now
Chief Tui : Our people will need a chief
Chief Tui : And there you are
Chief Tui;Sina : There comes a day
Chief Tui;Sina : When you're gonna look around And realize happiness is
Chief Tui : Where you are
Chief Tui : Consider the coconut
Motunui Villagers : The what
Chief Tui : Consider its tree
Chief Tui;Motunui Villagers : We use each part of the coconut It's all we need
Sina : We make our nets from the fibers
Sina : The water is sweet inside
Sina : We use the leaves to build fires We cook up the meat inside
Chief Tui : Consider the coconuts
Chief Tui : The trunks and the leaves
Chief Tui;Sina;Motunui Villagers : The island gives us what we need
Moana : And no one leaves
Chief Tui : That's right we stay
Chief Tui : We're safe and we're wellprovided
Chief Tui : And when we look to the future
Chief Tui : There you are
Chief Tui : You'll be okay
Chief Tui : In time you'll learn just as I did
Chief Tui;Sina : You must find happiness right where you are
Tala : I like to dance with the water The undertow and the waves
Tala : The water is mischievous Ha I like how it misbehaves
Tala : The village may think I'm crazy Or say that I drift too far
Tala : But once you know what you like Well there you are
Tala : You are your father's daughter Stubbornness and pride
Tala : Mind what he says but remember You may hear a voice inside
Tala : And if the voice starts to whisper To follow the farthest star
Tala : Moana that voice inside is who you are
Chief Tui : Uhhuh
Moana : Dad
Moana : I was only looking at the boats I wasn't gonna get on em
Chief Tui : Come on There's something I need to show you
Chief Tui : I've wanted to bring you here from the moment you opened your eyes
Chief Tui : This is a sacred place
Chief Tui : A place of chiefs
Chief Tui : There will come a time when you will stand on this peak and place a stone on this mountain
Chief Tui : Like I did Like my father did
Chief Tui : And his father and every chief that has ever been
Chief Tui : And on that day when you add your stone
Chief Tui : you will raise this whole island higher
Chief Tui : You are the future of our people Moana
Chief Tui : And they are not out there
Chief Tui : They are right here
Chief Tui : It's time to be who they need you to be
Motunui Villagers : We make our nets from the fibers
Motunui Villagers;Sina : We weave our nets from the fibers
Motunui Villagers : The water is sweet inside
Sina : A real tasty treat inside
Motunui Villagers : We use the leaves to build fires
Sina : We sing these songs in our choirs
Motunui Villagers : To cook up the meat inside
Sina : We have mouths to feed inside
Chief Tui : The village believes in us
Motunui Villagers : That's right
Chief Tui;Sina : The village believes
Motunui Villagers : The island gives us what we need
Chief Tui : And no one leaves
Moana : So here I'll stay
Moana : My home my people beside me And when I think of tomorrow
Motunui Villagers;Moana : There we are
Moana : I'll lead the way
Moana : I'll have my people to guide me
Moana : We'll build our future together
Motunui Villagers : Where we are
Moana : Cause every path leads ya back to
Motunui Villagers : Where you are
Moana : You can find happiness right
Villager1 : And every storm this roof leaks no matter how many fronds I add
Moana : Fixed Not the fronds
Moana : Wind shifted the post
Villager1 : Ah
Moana : Mmm That's good pork
Moana : Oh I didn't mean I wasn't
Moana : What They're calling me so I gotta Bye
Villager2 : Ow Ow Ow
Moana : You're doing great
Villager2 : Is it done yet
Moana : So close
Villager3 : I'm curious about that chicken eating the rock
Villager3 : He seems to lack the basic intelligence required for pretty much everything
Villager3 : Should we maybe just cook him
Moana : Sometimes our strengths lie beneath the surface
Moana : Far beneath in some cases
Moana : But I'm sure there's more to Heihei than meets the eye
Villager4 : It's the harvest
Villager4 : This morning I was husking the coconuts and
Moana : Well we should clear the diseased trees
Moana : and we will start a new grove There
Villager4 : Thanks Moana
Villager4 : She's doing great
Chief Tui : This suits you
Villager5 : Chief
Villager5 : There's something you need to see
Villager5 : Our traps in the east lagoon they're pulling up less and less fish
Moana : Then we'll rotate the fishing grounds
Villager5 : Uh we have There's no fish
Moana : Oh Then we'll fish the far side of the island
Villager5 : We tried
Moana : The windward side
Villager5 : And the leeward side the shallows the channel
Villager5 : We've tried the whole lagoon
Villager5 : They're just gone
Chief Tui : Have you tried using a different bait
Villager5 : I don't think it's the bait
Villager6 : There's no fish
Villager5 : It seems like it's getting worse and worse
Chief Tui : Of course I understand you have reason for concern
Chief Tui : I will talk to the council I'm sure we
Moana : we fish beyond the reef
Chief Tui : No one goes beyond the reef
Moana : I know But if there are no fish in the lagoon
Chief Tui : Moana
Moana : And there's a whole ocean
Chief Tui : We have one rule
Moana : An old rule when there were fish
Chief Tui : A rule that keeps us safe
Moana : But Dad I
Chief Tui : instead of endangering our people so you can run right back to the water
Chief Tui : Every time I think you're past this
Chief Tui : No one goes beyond the reef
Sina : Well it's not like you said it in front of your dad
Sina : Standing on a boat
Moana : I didn't say go beyond the reef because I want to be on the ocean
Sina : But you still do
Sina : He's hard on you because
Moana : Because he doesn't get me
Sina : Because he was you
Sina : Drawn to the ocean
Sina : Down by the shore
Sina : He took a canoe Moana
Sina : He crossed the reef
Sina : and found an unforgiving sea
Sina : Waves like mountains
Sina : His best friend begged to be on that boat
Sina : Your dad couldn't save him
Sina : He's hoping he can save you
Sina : Sometimes who we wish we were what we wish we could do
Sina : it's just not meant to be
Moana : I've been staring at the edge of the water
Moana : Long as I can remember
Moana : Never really knowing why
Moana : I wish I could be the perfect daughter
Moana : But I come back to the water
Moana : No matter how hard I try
Moana : Every turn I take Every trail I track
Moana : Every path I make Every road leads back
Moana : To the place I know Where I cannot go Where I long to be
Moana : See the line where the sky meets the sea It calls me
Moana : And no one knows How far it goes
Moana : If the wind in my sail on the sea Stays behind me
Moana : One day I'll know
Moana : If I go there's just no telling how far I'll go
Moana : I know everybody on this island Seems so happy on this island
Moana : Everything is by design
Moana : I know everybody on this island Has a role on this island
Moana : So maybe I can roll with mine
Moana : I can lead with pride I can make us strong
Moana : I'll be satisfied If I play along
Moana : But the voice inside Sings a different song
Moana : What is wrong with me
Moana : See the light as it shines on the sea
Moana : It's blinding
Moana : But no one knows
Moana : How deep it goes
Moana : And it seems like it's calling out to me So come find me
Moana : And let me know
Moana : What's beyond that line Will I cross that line
Moana : The line where the sky meets the sea
Moana : It calls me
Moana : And no one knows
Moana : How far it goes
Moana : If the wind in my sail on the sea stays behind me
Moana : One day I'll know
Moana : How far I'll go
Moana : Whoa
Moana : We're okay Pua
Moana : I can do this
Moana : There's more fish beyond the reef
Moana : There's more beyond the reef
Moana : Not so bad
Moana : Pua
Tala : Whatever just happened
Tala : blame it on the pig
Moana : Gramma
Moana : Are you gonna tell Dad
Tala : I'm his mom I don't have to tell him anything
Moana : He was right About going out there
Moana : It's time to put my stone on the mountain
Tala : Okay Well then head on back
Tala : Put that stone up there
Moana : Why aren't you trying to talk me out of it
Tala : You said that's what you wanted
Moana : It is
Tala : When I die
Tala : I'm going to come back as one of these
Tala : Or I chose the wrong tattoo
Moana : Why are you acting weird
Tala : I'm the village crazy lady That's my job
Moana : If there's something you want to tell me just tell me
Moana : Is there something you wanna tell me
Tala : Is there something you want to hear
Tala : You've been told all our people's stories
Tala : but one
Moana : What is this place
Tala : Do you really think our ancestors stayed within the reef
Tala : Ooh
Moana : What's in there
Tala : The answer to the question you keep asking yourself
Tala : Who are you meant to be
Tala : Go inside bang the drum and find out
Moana : Whoa
Moana : Oh
Moana : Bang the drum
Motunui Ancestors : We read the wind and the sky When the sun is high
Motunui Ancestors : We sail the length of the seas On the ocean breeze
Motunui Ancestors : At night we name every star We know where we are
Motunui Ancestors : We know who we are Who we are
Motunui Ancestors : We set a course to find
Motunui Ancestors : A brand new island everywhere we roam
Motunui Ancestors : We keep our island in our mind
Motunui Ancestors : And when it's time to find home We know the way
Motunui Ancestors : We are explorers reading every sign
Motunui Ancestors : We tell the stories of our elders In a neverending chain
Motunui Ancestors : We know the way
Moana : We were voyagers
Moana : We were voyagers We were voyagers
Moana : Why'd we stop
Tala : Maui
Tala : When he stole from the mother island darkness fell
Tala : Te Kā awoke
Tala : Monsters lurked and boats stopped coming back
Tala : To protect our people the ancient chiefs forbid voyaging and now we have forgotten who we are
And the darkness has continued to spread
Tala : chasing away our fish draining the life from island after island
Moana : Our island
Tala : But one day
Tala : someone will journey beyond our reef find Maui
Tala : deliver him across the great ocean
Tala : to restore the heart of Te Fiti
Tala : I was there that day
Tala : The ocean chose you
Moana : I thought it was a dream
Tala : Nope
Tala : Our ancestors believed Maui lies there at the bottom of his hook
Tala : Follow it and you will find him
Moana : But why would it choose me
Moana : I don't even know how to make it past the reef
Moana : But I know who does
Villager1 : VILLAGER 1 The crops are turning black
Villager2 : VILLAGER 2 What about the fish
Villager3 : VILLAGER 3 This is happening all over the island
Chief Tui : Please please settle down
Chief Tui : We will dig new fields
Chief Tui : We will find a way to
Moana : We can stop the darkness Save our island
Moana : There's a cavern of boats
Moana : Huge canoes
Moana : We can take them find Maui make him restore the heart
Moana : We were voyagers We can voyage again
Moana : You told me to help our people
Moana : This is how we help our people
Moana : Dad
Moana : What are you doing
Chief Tui : I should've burned those boats a long time ago
Moana : No Don't
Moana : We have to find Maui
Moana : We have to restore the heart
Chief Tui : There is no heart
Chief Tui : This this is just a rock
Moana : No
Villager1 : Chief It's your mother
Chief Tui : Mother
Chief Tui : What can be done
Tala : Go
Moana : Gramma
Moana : Not now I can't
Tala : You must
Tala : The ocean chose you
Tala : Follow the fish hook
Moana : Gramma
Tala : And when you find Maui you grab him by the ear
Tala : You say I am Moana of Motunui
Tala : You will board my boat sail across the sea
Tala : and restore the heart of Te Fiti
Moana : I can't leave you
Tala : There is nowhere you could go that I won't be with you
Tala : Go
Moana : There's a line where the sky meets the sea And it calls me
Moana : But no one knows How far it goes
Moana : All that time wondering where I need to be is behind me
Moana : I'm on my own To worlds unknown
Moana : Every turn I take Every trail I track Is a choice I make
Moana : Now I can't turn back from the great unknown
Moana : Where I go alone Where I long to be
Moana : See her light up the night in the sea
Moana : She calls me
Moana : And yes I know
Moana : That I can go
Moana : There's a moon in the sky And the wind is behind me
Moana : Soon I'll know
Moana : How far I'll go
Moana : I am Moana of Motunui
Moana : You will board my boat sail across the sea and restore the heart of Te Fiti
Moana : I am Moana
Moana : of Motu nui
Moana : Heihei
Moana : It's okay You're all right See
Moana : There we go Nice water
Moana : The ocean is a friend of mine
Moana : Heihei
Moana : Stay
Moana : Okay Next stop Maui
Moana : I am Moana of Motunui
Moana : You will board my boat
Moana : sail across the sea and restore the heart of Te Fiti
Moana : I am Moana of Motu
Moana : Board my boat
Moana : Oh no
Moana : No no no no no
Moana : Ocean can I get a little help
Moana : No no
Moana : Please
Moana : Come on
Moana : Help me Please
Moana : Whew
Moana : Um
Moana : What
Moana : I said help me And wrecking my boat
Moana : Not helping
Moana : Fish pee in you all day So
Moana : Maui
Moana : Maui demigod of the wind and sea
Moana : I am Moana of Motunui You will board my boat
Moana : No You will board my boat
Moana : Yeah I am Moana of Motunui
Moana : You will board my
Maui : Boat A boat
Maui : The gods have given me a
Moana : Maui shapeshifter demigod of the wind and sea
Moana : I am Moana
Maui : Hero of men
Moana : What
Maui : It's actually Maui shapeshifter demigod of the wind and sea hero of men
Maui : I interrupted From the top Hero of men Go
Moana : I am
Maui : Sorry sorry sorry sorry
Maui : And women Men and women
Maui : Both All
Maui : Not a guy girl thing
Maui : You know Maui is a hero to all
Maui : You're doing great
Moana : What No I'm here to
Maui : Of course
Maui : Yes yes yes yes
Maui : Maui always has time for his fans
Maui : When you use a bird to write with
Maui : it's called tweeting
Maui : I know not every day you get a chance to meet your hero
Moana : You are not my hero
Moana : And I'm not here so you can sign my oar
Moana : I'm here cause you stole the heart of Te Fiti
Moana : And you will board my boat
Moana : and sail across the sea and put it back
Maui : Um
Maui : Yeah it almost sounded like you don't like me
Maui : which is impossible because I got stuck here for 1000 years trying to get the heart as a gift for you mortals
Maui : So you could have the power to create life itself
Maui : Yeah So what I believe you were trying to say is thank you
Moana : Thank you
Maui : You're welcome
Moana : What No no no
Moana : I didn't I wasn't
Moana : Why would I ever say
Maui : Okay okay
Maui : I see what's happening Yeah
Maui : You're face to face with greatness and it's strange
Maui : You don't even know how you feel
Maui : It's adorable
Maui : Well it's nice to see that humans never change
Maui : Open your eyes Let's begin
Maui : Yes it's really me It's Maui Breathe it in
Maui : I know it's a lot
Maui : The hair The bod
Maui : When you're staring at a demigod
Maui : What can I say except You're welcome
Maui : For the tides the sun the sky
Maui : Hey it's okay it's okay You're welcome
Maui : I'm just an ordinary demiguy Hey
Maui : What has two thumbs and pulled up the sky
Maui : When you were waddling yay high This guy
Maui : When the nights got cold Who stole you fire from down below
Maui : You're looking at him yo
Maui : Oh also I lassoed the sun
Maui : You're welcome To stretch your days and bring you fun
Maui : Also I harnessed the breeze
Maui : You're welcome To fill your sails and shake your trees
Maui : So what can I say except You're welcome
Maui : For the islands I pulled from the sea
Maui : There's no need to pray It's okay You're welcome
Maui : Ha I guess it's just my way of being me
Maui : You're welcome
Maui : Well come to think of it
Maui : Kid honestly I could go on and on I could explain every natural phenomenon
Maui : The tide the grass the ground Oh that was Maui just messing around
Maui : I killed an eel I buried its guts Sprouted a tree Now you got coconuts
Maui : What's the lesson What is the take away Don't mess with Maui when he's on a breakaway
Maui : And the tapestry here on my skin Is a map of the victories I win
Maui : Look where I've been I make everything happen
Maui : Look at that Mean MiniMaui just tickety tappin
Maui : Ha ha Ha ha ha ha
Maui : Hey
Maui : Well anyway let me say You're welcome
Ensemble : You're welcome
Maui : For the wonderful world you know
Maui : Hey it's okay it's okay You're welcome
Ensemble : You're welcome
Maui : Well come to think of it I gotta go
Maui : Hey it's your day to say You're welcome
Ensemble : You're welcome
Maui : Cause I'm gonna need that boat
Maui : I'm sailing away away You're welcome
Ensemble : You're welcome
Maui : Cause Maui can do everything but float
Maui : You're welcome
Ensemble : You're welcome
Moana : Huh
Maui : And thank you
Moana : Hey
Moana : Let me out You lying slimy son of a
Maui : You're welcome
Maui : You're so welcome
Maui : No I'm not going to Te Fiti with some kid
Maui : I'm going to get my hook
Maui : You have yours and I'm not Maui without mine
Maui : Okay talk to the back
Maui : Boat snack
Maui : Good riddance you filthy pile of pebbles
Maui : Oh no no no Don't look at me like that It's a beautiful cave She's gonna love it
Maui : And I'm going to love you in ma belly
Maui : Now let's fatten you up drumstick
Maui : I could watch that all day
Maui : Okay Enjoy the island
Maui : Maui out
Moana : No Stop
Moana : Hey You have to put back the heart
Maui : Did not see that coming
Moana : I am Moana of Motunui
Moana : This is my canoe and you will journey to
Maui : All right get over it We gotta move
Maui : And she's back
Moana : I am Moana of Motunui
Maui : It was Moana right
Moana : Yes
Moana : And you will restore the heart
Maui : All right I'm out
Maui : Oh come on
Moana : What is your problem
Moana : Are you afraid of it
Maui : No No
Maui : I'm not afraid
Maui : Stay out of it or you're sleeping in my armpit
Maui : You stop it That is not a heart It is a curse
Maui : The second I took it I got blasted outta the sky and I lost my hook
Maui : Get it away from me
Moana : Get this away
Maui : Hey hey hey I'm a demigod okay Stop that I will smite you
Maui : You wanna get smote Smotten
Maui : Listen that thing doesn't give you power to create life it's a homing beacon of death
Maui : If you don't put it away bad things are gonna come for it
Moana : Come for this The heart
Moana : You mean this heart right here
Moana : Come and get it
Maui : You are gonna get us killed
Moana : No I'm gonna get us to Te Fiti so you can put it back
Moana : Thank you
Moana : You're welcome
Maui : Kakamora
Moana : Kakawhat
Maui : Murdering little pirates
Maui : Wonder what they're here for
Moana : They're kinda cute
Moana : Ocean Do something Help us
Maui : The ocean doesn't help you you help yourself
Maui : Tighten the halyard Bind the stays
Maui : You can't sail
Moana : I uh
Moana : I am selftaught
Maui : Can't you shapeshift or something
Maui : Do you see my hook No magic hook no magic powers
Moana : Their boat is turning into more boats
Moana : Yep I just did that
Moana : No no no no no No
Moana : Heihei
Moana : Maui
Moana : They took the heart
Maui : That's a chicken
Moana : The heart is in the
Moana : We have to get him back
Moana : Maui
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Moana : There Right there
Moana : You're turning
Moana : What are you doing
Maui : Escaping
Moana : The heart
Maui : Forget it You'll never get it back
Maui : Besides you got a better one
Maui : Hey
Maui : What am I gonna steer with
Maui : They're just gonna kill ya
Moana : Coconuts
Moana : Got it
Moana : Hey
Moana : Yeah
Moana : We did it
Maui : Congratulations on not being dead girlie
Maui : You surprise me
Maui : But I'm still not taking that thing back
Maui : You wanna get to Te Fiti you gotta go through a whole ocean of bad
Maui : Not to mention Te Kā
Maui : Lava monster
Maui : Ever defeat a lava monster
Moana : No Have you
Maui : I'm not going on a suicide mission with some mortal
Maui : You can't restore the heart without me and me says no
Maui : I'm getting my hook
Maui : End of discussion
Moana : You'd be a hero
Moana : That's what you're all about right
Maui : Little girl I am a hero
Moana : Maybe you were
Moana : But now
Moana : now you're just the guy who stole the heart of Te Fiti
Moana : The guy who cursed the world
Moana : You're no one's hero
Maui : No one
Moana : But put this back save the world
Moana : you'd be everyone's hero
Moana : Maui Maui Maui
Moana : You're so amazing
Maui : We'd never make it without my hook Not past Te Kā
Moana : Then we get your hook
Moana : We get your hook take out Te Kā restore the heart
Moana : Unless you don't wanna be
Moana : Maui demigod of the wind and sea Hero to all
Maui : First we get my hook
Moana : Then save the world
Moana : Deal
Maui : Deal
Maui : Worth a shot
Maui : Okay we go east
Maui : To the lair of Tamatoa
Maui : If anyone has my hook it's that beadyeyed bottomfeeder
Moana : Teach me to sail
Moana : My job is to deliver Maui across the great ocean
Moana : I should
Moana : I should be sailing
Maui : It's called wayfinding princess
Maui : And it's not just sails and knots it's seeing where you're going in your mind
Maui : Knowing where you are by knowing where you've been
Moana : Okay first I'm not a princess
Moana : I am the daughter of the chief
Maui : Same difference
Moana : No
Maui : If you wear a dress and you have an animal sidekick you're a princess
Maui : You are not a wayfinder
Maui : You will never be a wayfinder you will never be a way...
Maui : Really Blow dart in my butt cheek
Maui : You are a bad person
Moana : If you can talk you can teach
Moana : Wayfinding
Moana : Lesson one Hit it
Maui : Pull the sheet
Maui : Not the sheet
Maui : No No
Maui : Nope Nope
Maui : Tried that one already
Maui : You're measuring the stars not giving the sky a highfive
Maui : If the current's warm you're going the right way
Moana : It's cold
Moana : Wait it's getting warmer
Moana : Aah That is disgusting What is wrong with you
Moana : We're here
Moana : See told you I could do it
Moana : Motunui
Moana : I'm home
Chief Tui : Moana
Moana : Dad
Sina : Moana
Moana : Mom
Chief Tui : Help
Moana : No
Chief Tui : Moana
Maui : Enjoy your beauty rest
Maui : You know a real wayfinder never sleeps
Maui : so they actually get where they need to go
Maui : Muscle up buttercup
Maui : We're here
Moana : You're sure this guy's gonna have your hook
Maui : Tamatoa Oh he'll have it
Maui : He's a scavenger Collects stuff Thinks it makes him look cool
Maui : Ah
Maui : And for Tamatoa trust me
Maui : my hook is the coolest collectible
Moana : And he lives up there
Maui : No no no
Maui : That's just the entrance to Lalotai
Moana : Lalotai Realm of monsters
Moana : We're going to the realm of monsters
Maui : We No Me
Maui : You are gonna stay here with the other chicken
Maui : That's what I'm talking about Gimme some
Maui : Come on That was a good one How do you not get it
Maui : I called her a chicken there's a chicken on the boat
Maui : I know she's human but that's not the You know what Forget it Forget it
Maui : I'm not explaining it to you Cause then it's not funny
Maui : So daughter of the chief I thought you stayed in the village You know kissing babies and things
Maui : Hey I'm just trying to understand why your people decided to send
Maui : How do I phrase this You
Moana : My people didn't send me
Moana : The ocean did
Maui : The ocean
Maui : Makes sense You're what eight Can't sail
Maui : Obvious choice
Moana : It chose me for a reason
Maui : If the ocean's so smart
Maui : why didn't it just take the heart back to Te Fiti itself
Maui : Or bring me my hook
Maui : The ocean's straight up kookydooks
Maui : But I'm sure it's not wrong about you
Maui : You're the Chosen One
Moana : The ocean chose you for a reason
Maui : If you start singing I'm gonna throw up
Moana : So not seeing an entrance
Maui : Yes because it only appears after a human sacrifice
Maui : Kidding So serious
Maui : Don't worry it's a lot farther down than it looks
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Maui : I am still falling
Moana : You can do this
Moana : Go
Maui : And he sticks the landing
Maui : Huh
Maui : What Dumdum she's not even here
Maui : No mortal's gonna jump into the realm of
Maui : Huh
Maui : Well she's dead
Maui : Okay let's get my hook
Moana : Ew Ew ew ew ew
Moana : Maui's fishhook
Maui : Yeah
Moana : Sorry
Moana : I thought you were a monster
Moana : But I found your hook And you're right this Tamatoa guy really likes his treasure
Maui : Stay
Moana : What No I'm the one who found
Maui : Listen For a thousand years I've only been thinking of keeping this hair silky getting my hook and being awesome again
Maui : And it's not getting screwed up by a mortal who has no business inside of a monster cave except
Maui : Except
Maui : maybe as bait
Moana : Huh
Moana : Wow
Moana : The shiny glittery cave
Moana : And just like me
Moana : it is covered in sparkly treasure
Moana : Sparkle sparkle sparkle
Maui : You're not selling it
Moana : This is stupid I'm just gonna walk up and get it
Maui : You go up there he will kill you Just stick to the plan
Maui : Oh when he shows up keep him distracted
Maui : Make him talk about himself
Maui : He loves bragging about how great he is
Moana : You two must get along swell
Maui : No not since I ripped off his leg
Moana : You ripped off his
Moana : Maui
Tamatoa : What have we here
Tamatoa : It's a sparkly shiny Wait a minute
Tamatoa : Ugh It's a human
Tamatoa : What are you doing down here in the realm of the mons...
Tamatoa : Just pick an eye babe
Tamatoa : I can't concentrate on what I'm saying if you keep
Tamatoa : Yeah pick one pick one
Tamatoa : You're a funnylooking little thing aren't you
Moana : Don't That's my gramma's
Tamatoa : That's my gramma's
Tamatoa : I ate my gramma
Tamatoa : And it took a week cause she was absolutely humongous
Tamatoa : Why are you here
Moana : Cause you're amazing
Moana : And we mortals have heard of the tale of the crab who became a legend
Moana : And I just had to know how you became so crabulous
Tamatoa : Are you just trying to get me to talk about myself
Tamatoa : Because if you are
Tamatoa : I will gladly do so
Moana : Huh
Tamatoa : In song form
Tamatoa : Well Tamatoa hasn't always been this glam
Tamatoa : I was a drab little crab once
Tamatoa : Now I know I can be happy as a clam
Tamatoa : Because I'm beautiful baby
Tamatoa : And did your granny say Listen to your heart
Tamatoa : Be who you are on the inside
Tamatoa : I need three words To tear her argument apart
Tamatoa : Your granny lied I'd rather be shiny
Tamatoa : Like a treasure From a sunken pirate wreck
Tamatoa : Scrub the deck And make it look shiny
Tamatoa : I will sparkle like a Wealthy woman's neck
Tamatoa : Just a sec Don't ya know
Tamatoa : Fish are dumb dumb dumb They chase anything that glitters
Tamatoa : Beginners
Tamatoa : Oh and here they come come come To the brightest thing that glitters
Tamatoa : Mm fish dinners
Tamatoa : I just love free food
Tamatoa : And you look like seafood
Maui : Hey crab cake
Maui : I'm back
Maui : It's Maui Time
Maui : What do you say little buddy
Maui : Giant hawk Coming up
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Tamatoa : Well well well
Tamatoa : Little Maui's having trouble with his look
Tamatoa : Ya little semidemiminigod
Tamatoa : Ouch What a terrible performance
Tamatoa : Get the hook Get it
Tamatoa : You don't swing it Like you used to man
Tamatoa : Yet I have to give you Credit for my start
Tamatoa : And your tattoos on the outside
Tamatoa : For just like you I made myself a work of art
Tamatoa : I'll never hide I can't
Tamatoa : I'm too shiny
Tamatoa : Watch me dazzle Like a diamond in the rough
Tamatoa : Strut my stuff My stuff is so shiny
Tamatoa : Send your armies But they'll never be enough
Tamatoa : My shell's too tough Maui man
Tamatoa : You can try try try But you can't expect a demigod
Tamatoa : To beat a decapod Look it up
Tamatoa : You will die die die
Tamatoa : Now it's time for me to take apart
Tamatoa : Your achin heart
Tamatoa : Far from the ones who abandoned you
Tamatoa : Chasing the love of these humans
Tamatoa : Who made you feel wanted
Tamatoa : You tried to be tough
Tamatoa : But your armor's just not hard enough
Tamatoa : Maui Now it's time to kick your heinie
Tamatoa : Ever seen someone so shiny
Tamatoa : Soak it in Cause it's the last you'll ever see
Tamatoa : C'est la vie Mon ami
Tamatoa : I'm so shiny
Tamatoa : Now I eat you so prepare your final plea
Tamatoa : Just for me
Tamatoa : You'll never be quite as shiny
Tamatoa : You wish you were nice and shiny
Moana : Hey
Tamatoa : Huh
Moana : I got something shiny for ya
Tamatoa : The heart of Te Fiti
Tamatoa : You can't run from me
Tamatoa : Oh you can You keep surprising me
Tamatoa : There's only so far you can get on those two little legs
Tamatoa : The power of creation
Tamatoa : for a crustacean
Tamatoa : Where is it Where is it
Moana : We gotta go
Maui : What about the heart
Moana : He can have it I've got a better one
Tamatoa : Yes I have the
Tamatoa : Wait a minute
Tamatoa : I see she's taken a barnacle and she's covered it in bioluminescent algae as a diversion
Tamatoa : Come back here
Moana : Cheeeehoooo
Tamatoa : Hey hey
Tamatoa : Did you like the song
Moana : We're alive
Maui : Listen
Maui : I appreciate what you did down there
Moana : Mmhmm
Maui : Took guts
Moana : Mmhmm Mmhmm
Maui : But
Maui : I'm sorry
Maui : I'm trying to be sincere for once and it feels like you're distracted
Moana : No no No way
Maui : Really Because you're looking at me like I have a
Maui : shark head
Moana : What Do you have a shark head
Maui : Look the point is for a little girl child thing whatever who had no business being down there
Maui : you did me a solid
Maui : But you also almost died
Maui : And I couldn't even beat that dumb crab
Maui : So chances of beating Te Kā
Maui : Bupkis
Maui : We're never making it to Te Fiti This mission is cursed
Moana : It's not cursed
Maui : Shark head
Moana : It is not cursed
Maui : Cursed
Maui : What can I say except
Maui : We're dead soon
Moana : Can you at least try
Maui : Giant hawk
Maui : Hey it's okay it's okay We're dead soon
Moana : All right break time's over
Moana : Get up
Maui : Why Are you gonna give me a speech
Maui : Tell me I can beat Te Kā cause I'm Maui
Maui : Take a hike Tiny
Maui : How do you get your tattoos
Maui : They show up When I earn them
Moana : How'd you earn that one What's that for
Maui : That's man's discovery of Nunya
Moana : What's Nunya
Maui : Nunya business
Moana : I'll just keep asking
Moana : What's it for
Maui : You need to stop doing that
Maui : Back off
Moana : Just tell me what it is
Maui : I said back off
Moana : Is it why your hook's not working
Moana : You don't wanna talk don't talk
Moana : You wanna throw me off the boat throw me off
Moana : You wanna tell me I don't know what I'm doing
Moana : I know I don't
Moana : I have no idea why the ocean chose me
Moana : You're right
Moana : But my island is dying
Moana : so I am here
Moana : It's just me and you And I want to help
Moana : but I can't if you don't let me
Maui : I wasn't born a demigod I had human parents
Maui : They took one look and decided
Maui : they did not want me
Maui : They threw me into the sea like I was nothing
Maui : Somehow I was found by the gods
Maui : They gave me the hook
Maui : They made me Maui
Maui : And back to the humans I went
Maui : I gave them islands fire coconuts
Maui : Anything they could ever want
Moana : You took the heart for them
Moana : You did everything for them
Moana : So they'd love you
Maui : It was never enough
Moana : Maybe the gods found you for a reason
Moana : Maybe the ocean brought you to them
Moana : because it saw someone who was worthy of being saved
Moana : But the gods aren't the ones who make you Maui
Moana : You are
Maui : Okay okay
Maui : I love you too buddy
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Moana : Yeah
Moana : Next stop Te Fiti
Moana : What
Maui : I figured it out
Maui : You know the ocean used to love when I pulled up islands
Maui : cause your ancestors would sail her seas and find em
Maui : All those new lands new villages
Maui : It was the water that connected em all
Maui : And if I were the ocean
Maui : I think I'd be looking for a curlyhaired nonprincess
Maui : to start that again
Moana : That is literally the nicest thing you've ever said to me
Moana : Probably should have saved it for Te Fiti
Maui : I did
Maui : Moana of Motunui
Maui : I believe you have officially delivered Maui across the great sea
Maui : Moana Moana Moana You're so amazing
Maui : It's time
Moana : Go save the world
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Moana : Maui
Maui : What are you doing
Moana : Finding you a better way in
Maui : We won't make it
Moana : Yes we will
Maui : Turn around
Moana : No
Maui : Moana stop
Moana : Are you okay
Moana : Maui
Maui : I told you to turn back
Moana : I thought we could make it
Maui : We
Moana : I thought I could make it
Moana : We can fix it
Maui : It was made by the gods
Maui : You can't fix it
Moana : Next time we'll be more careful
Moana : Te Kā was stuck on the barrier islands
Moana : It's lava it can't go in the water
Moana : We can find a way around
Maui : I'm not going back
Moana : We still have to restore the heart
Maui : My hook is cracked
Maui : One more hit and it's over
Moana : Maui you have to restore the heart
Maui : Without my hook I am nothing
Moana : That's not true
Moana : We are only here because you stole the heart in the first place
Maui : No we're here because the ocean told you you're special and you believed it
Moana : I am Moana of Motunui
Moana : You will board my boat
Maui : Goodbye Moana
Moana : sail across the sea
Maui : I'm not killing myself so you can prove you're something you're not
Moana : and restore the heart of Te Fiti
Moana : The ocean chose me
Maui : It chose wrong
Moana : Maui
Moana : Why did you bring me here
Moana : I'm not the right person
Moana : You have to choose someone else
Moana : Choose someone else
Moana : Please
Moana : No
Tala : You're a long ways past the reef
Moana : Gramma
Tala : Guess I chose the right tattoo
Moana : I tried Gramma
Moana : I couldn't do it
Tala : It's not your fault
Tala : I never should have put so much on your shoulders
Tala : If you are ready to go home
Tala : I will be with you
Tala : Why do you hesitate
Moana : I don't know
Tala : I know a girl from an island
Tala : She stands apart from the crowd
Tala : She loves the sea and her people
Tala : She makes her whole family proud
Tala : Sometimes the world seems against you
Tala : The journey may leave a scar
Tala : But scars can heal and reveal just Where you are
Tala : The people you love will change you
Tala : The things you have learned will guide you
Tala : And nothing on earth can silence
Tala : The quiet voice still inside you
Tala : And when that voice starts to whisper
Moana you've come so far
Tala : Moana listen
Tala : Do you know who you are
Moana : Who am I
Moana : I am a girl who loves my island
Moana : And the girl who loves the sea
Moana : It calls me
Moana : I am the daughter of the village chief
Moana : We are descended from voyagers
Moana : Who found their way across the world
Moana : They call me
Moana : I've delivered us to where we are
Moana : I have journeyed farther
Moana : I am everything I've learned and more Still it calls me
Moana : And the call isn't out there at all It's inside me
Moana : It's like the tide Always falling and rising
Moana : I will carry you here in my heart You remind me
Moana : That come what may I know the way
Moana : I am Moana
Moana : I am Moana of Motunui
Moana : Aboard my boat
Moana : I will sail across the sea
Moana : and restore the heart of Te Fiti
Moana : Te Kā can't follow us into the water
Moana : We make it past the barrier islands
Moana : we make it to Te Fiti
Moana : None of which you understand
Moana : because you are a chicken
Moana : No
Moana : Heihei No no no
Moana : Nice work
Moana : Te Fiti
Moana : Maui
Moana : You came back
Moana : But your hook
Moana : One more hit and
Maui : Te Kā's gotta catch me first
Maui : I got your back Chosen One
Maui : Go save the world
Moana : Maui
Moana : Thank you
Maui : You're welcome
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Maui : Hothothot hothothot
Maui : Hey Te Kā
Maui : Shark head
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Maui : Moana
Maui : Get the heart to the spiral
Moana : Te Fiti
Moana : it's gone
Maui : Te Kā
Moana : Let her come to me
Moana : I have crossed the horizon to find you
Moana : I know your name
Moana : They have stolen the heart from inside you
Moana : But this does not define you
Moana : This is not who you are
Moana : You know who you are
Moana : Who you truly are
Moana : Te Fiti
Maui : The chicken lives
Moana : I'm sorry about your hook
Maui : Well hook no hook
Maui : I'm Maui
Maui : Te Fiti
Maui : Hey I mean how you been
Maui : Look what I did was wrong
Maui : I have no excuse
Maui : I'm sorry
Moana : You know it'd be rude to refuse a gift from a goddess
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Maui : Thank you
Maui : Your kind gesture is deeply appreciated
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Maui : Gonna miss you drumstick
Moana : You could come with us you know
Moana : My people are going to need a master wayfinder
Maui : They already have one
Moana : See you out there Maui
Maui : See you out there Moana
Maui : Cheeeehoooo
Moana : Mom Dad
Sina : Moana
Moana : I may have gone a little ways past the reef
Chief Tui : It suits you
Villager1 : She's back
Villager2 : Moana
Moana : Pua
Villager3 : Moana
Villager4 : Welcome home
Motunui Ancestors : We set a course to find
Motunui Ancestors : A brand new island everywhere we roam
Motunui Ancestors : We keep our island in our mind
Motunui Ancestors : And when it's time to find home We know the way
Motunui Ancestors : We are explorers reading every sign
Motunui Ancestors : We tell the stories of our elders In a neverending chain
Motunui Ancestors : We know the way
I've been staring at the edge of the water
Long as I can remember
Never really knowing why
I wish I could be the perfect daughter
But I come back to the water
No matter how hard I try
Every turn I take Every trail I track
Every path I make Every road leads back
To the place I know Where I cannot go
Where I long to be
See the line where the sky meets the sea
It calls me
And no one knows
How far it goes
If the wind in my sail on the sea Stays behind me
One day I'll know
If I go there's just no telling how far I'll go
I know everybody on this island
Seems so happy on this island
Everything is by design
I know everybody on this island
Has a role on this island
So maybe I can roll with mine
I can lead with pride I can make us strong
I'll be satisfied If I play along
But the voice inside Sings a different song
What is wrong with me
See the light as it shines on the sea
It's blinding
But no one knows
How deep it goes
And it seems like it's calling out to me
So come find me
And let me know
What's beyond that line Will I cross that line
See the line where the sky meets the sea
It calls me
And no one knows
How far it goes
If the wind in my sail on the sea stays behind me
One day I'll know
How far I'll go
I see what's happening Yeah
You're face to face with greatness and it's strange
You don't even know how you feel
It's adorable
It's nice to see that humans never change
Open your eyes Let's begin
Yes it's really me Breathe it in
I know it's a lot
The hair The bod
When you're staring at a demigod
So what can I say except
You're welcome
For the tides the sun the sky
Hey it's okay it's okay
You're welcome
I'm just an ordinary demiguy
What can I say except You're welcome
For the tides the sun the sky
Hey it's okay it's okay
You're welcome
I'm just an ordinary demiguy
Honestly I could go on and on
I could explain every natural phenomenon
The tide the grass the ground Oh that was me I was messing around
I killed a snake I buried its guts
Sprouted a tree Now you got coconuts
What's the lesson What is the take away
Don't mess with Maui when he's on a breakaway
And the tapestry here on my skin Is a map of the victories I win
Look where I've been I make everything happen
Look at that Mean MiniMaui just tickety tappin
Singing and scratchin
Flipping and snappin People are clappin hearing me rap
Bring the chorus back in
Well anyway let me say You're welcome
For the wonderful world you know
Hey it's okay it's okay You're welcome
Well come to think of it I gotta go
Hey it's your day to say You're welcome
Cause I'm gonna need that boat
I'm sailing away away You're welcome
Cause Maui's the ultimate God
You're welcome
Shiny
I'm so shiny
Didn't help me though did it
Still upside down here
Just need a little push
Can we be real
If my name was Sebastian and I had a cool Jamaican accent
you'd totally help me
You would You know you would