(BIRD SCREECHING) (GROANS)
(SCREECHING)
(OBJECT THRUSTING)
(SHUDDERS)
Soldier : We're under attack! Light the signal!
(GASPS) (GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING IN DISTANCE)
Soldier : Light the fire now! Light the signal!
Soldier : Now all of China knows you're here.
(FALCON SCREECHES)
Shan Yu : Perfect.
General : Your Majesty, the Huns have crossed our northern border.
Chi-Fu : Impossible. No one can get through the Great Wall.
General : Shan-Yu is leading them.
General : We'll set up defenses around your palace immediately.
The Emperor of China : No. Send your troops to protect my people. Chi Fu.
Chi-Fu : Yes, Your Highness?
The Emperor of China : Deliver conscription notices throughout all the provinces.
The Emperor of China : Call up reserves and as many new recruits as possible.
General : Forgive me, Your Majesty, but I believe my troops can stop him.
The Emperor of China : I won't take any chances, General.
The Emperor of China : A single grain of rice can tip the scale.
The Emperor of China : One man may be the difference between victory and defeat.
Fa Mulan : "Quiet and demure.
Fa Mulan : "Graceful. Polite.
Fa Mulan : "Delicate.
Fa Mulan : "Refined. Poised.
Fa Mulan : "Punctual."
(CROWING)
Fa Mulan : Ai-yah!
Fa Mulan : Little brother!
Fa Mulan : (BLOWING) Little brother.
Fa Mulan : Ah!
(SNORING)
Fa Mulan : There you are.
Fa Mulan : Who's the smartest doggy in the world? Come on, smart boy.
Fa Mulan : Can you help me with my chores today?
(GROWLS)
(BARKING)
(WHIMPERS)
(CACKLING)
(NICKERS)
(CONTINUES BARKING)
Fa Zhou : Honorable ancestors,
Fa Zhou : please help Mulan impress the Matchmaker today.
(BARKING)
(CACKLING)
Fa Zhou : Please.
Fa Zhou : Please help her.
(WHIMPERING)
(BARKING)
(GROWLS)
Fa Mulan : Father, I brought your... Whoa!
Fa Zhou : Mulan.
Fa Mulan : I brought a spare.
Fa Mulan : Remember, the doctor said three cups of tea in the morning...
Fa Zhou : Mulan.
Fa Mulan : And three at night.
Fa Zhou : Mulan, you should already be in town. We are counting on you... To
Fa Mulan : uphold the family honor.
Fa Mulan : Don't worry, Father. I won't let you down.
Fa Mulan : Wish me luck.
Fa Zhou : Hurry!
Fa Mulan : I'm going to pray some more.
Groomer1 : Fa Li, is your daughter here yet?
Groomer1 : The Matchmaker is not a patient woman.
Fa Li : Of all days to be late... I should have prayed to the ancestors for luck.
Grandmother Fa : How lucky can they be? They're dead.
Grandmother Fa : Besides, I've got all the luck we'll need.
(TWITTERS)
Grandmother Fa : This is your chance to prove yourself.
Fa Li : Grandma, no!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING) (ANIMAL GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Grandmother Fa : Yep, this cricket's a lucky one!
(CHIRPING SOFTLY)
(SIGHS) (HORSE NEIGHS)
Fa Mulan : I'm here.
Fa Mulan : What? But, Mama, I had to...
Fa Li : None of your excuses. Now, let's get you cleaned up.
Groomer1 : (SINGING) This is what you give me to work with
Groomer1 : Well, honey, I've seen worse
Groomer1 : We're gonna turn this sow's ear
(MULAN SCREAMS)
Groomer1 : Into a silk purse
Fa Mulan : It's freezing.
Fa Li : It would have been warm if you were here on time.
Groomer1 : We'll have you washed and dried Primped and polished till you glow with pride
Groomer1 : Trust my recipe for instant bride
Groomer1 : You'll bring honor to us all
Fa Li : Mulan, what's this?
Fa Mulan : Notes,
Fa Mulan : in case I forget something.
Grandmother Fa : Hold this. We'll need more luck than I thought.
Groomer1 : Wait and see when we're through
Groomer2 : Boys will gladly go to war for you
Groomer1 : With good fortune
Groomer2 : And a great hairdo
Groomer1;Groomer2 : You'll bring honor to us all
Villagers : A girl can bring her family Great honor in one way
Villagers : By striking a good match
Man : Huh?
Villagers : And this could be the day
Groomer2 : Men want girls with good taste
Groomer1 : -Calm
Fa Li : -Obedient
Groomer1 : Who work fast-paced With good breeding
Groomer1 : And a tiny waist
(GASPS)
Groomer1;Groomer2;Fa Li : You'll bring honor to us all
Villagers : We all must serve our Emperor Who guards us from the Huns
Villagers : The men by bearing arms
Villagers : A girl by bearing sons
Groomer2 : When we're through you can't fail
Fa Li : Like a lotus blossom soft and pale
Groomer2 : How could any fellow say, "No sale"
Groomer2 : You'll bring honor to us all You'll bring honor to us all You'll bring honor to us all
Fa Li : There. You're ready.
Grandmother Fa : Not yet. An apple for serenity.
Grandmother Fa : A pendant for balance.
Grandmother Fa : Beads of jade For beauty
Grandmother Fa : You must proudly Show it
Grandmother Fa : Now add a cricket Just for luck
Grandmother Fa : And even you can't blow it
Fa Mulan : Ancestors, hear my plea
Fa Mulan : Help me not to make a fool of me
Fa Mulan : And to not uproot my family tree
Fa Mulan : Keep my father standing tall
Fa Mulan : Scarier than the undertaker
Fa Mulan;Girls : We are meeting our matchmaker
Villagers : Destiny, guard our girls And our future as it fast unfurls
Villagers : Please look kindly on these cultured pearls
Villagers : Each a perfect porcelain doll
Girl1 : Please bring honor to us
Girl2 : Please bring honor to us
Girl3 : Please bring honor to us
Girl4 : Please bring honor to us
Villagers : Please bring honor to us all
The Matchmaker : "Fa Mulan."
Fa Mulan : Present.
The Matchmaker : Speaking without permission.
Fa Mulan : Oops.
Grandmother Fa : Who spit in her bean curd?
The Matchmaker : Huh. Hmm.
The Matchmaker : Mmm.
The Matchmaker : Too skinny.
The Matchmaker : Hmph.
The Matchmaker : Not good for bearing sons.
The Matchmaker : Recite the final admonition.
Fa Mulan : (MUFFLED CHIRPING) Mmm-hmm.
The Matchmaker : Well? (CLEARS THROAT)
Fa Mulan : Fulfill your duties calmly and respectfully.
Fa Mulan : Reflect before you snack...
Fa Mulan : Act! This shall bring you honor and glory.
Fa Mulan : (SIGHS)
The Matchmaker : Hmm. This way.
The Matchmaker : Now, pour the tea.
The Matchmaker : To please your future in-laws,
The Matchmaker : you must demonstrate a sense of dignity
The Matchmaker : and refinement.
The Matchmaker : You must also be poised.
(CHIRPS SOFTLY)
Fa Mulan : Pardon me.
The Matchmaker : And silent!
The Matchmaker : (SNIFFS) Ah!
Fa Mulan : Could I just take that back?
(GRUNTING)
Fa Mulan : One moment.
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
The Matchmaker : Why, you clumsy...
(CHIRPING)
The Matchmaker : Whoo! Whoo! (SCREAMING) Whoo! Aaah!
(FIRE SIZZLING) (SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING INTENSIFIES)
(LOUD CLATTERING)
Grandmother Fa : I think it's going well, don't you?
The Matchmaker : Put it out! Put it out! Put it out!
The Matchmaker : (PANTING) You are a disgrace!
The Matchmaker : You may look like a bride,
The Matchmaker : but you will never bring your family honor!
(TOWNSPEOPLE MURMURING)
(SIGHS)
Fa Mulan : (SINGING) Look at me
Fa Mulan : I will never pass
Fa Mulan : For a perfect bride
Fa Mulan : Or a perfect daughter
Fa Mulan : Can it be
Fa Mulan : I'm not meant to play this part?
Fa Mulan : Now I see
Fa Mulan : That if I were truly to be myself
Fa Mulan : I would break my family's heart
Fa Mulan : Who is that girl I see
Fa Mulan : Staring straight
Fa Mulan : Back at me?
Fa Mulan : Why is my reflection
Fa Mulan : Someone I don't know?
Fa Mulan : Somehow I cannot hide
Fa Mulan : Who I am
Fa Mulan : Though I've tried
Fa Mulan : When will my reflection show
Fa Mulan : Who I am inside?
Fa Mulan : Who I am
Fa Mulan : Inside?
(FA ZHOU CLEARS THROAT)
Fa Zhou : My, my.
Fa Zhou : What beautiful blossoms we have this year.
Fa Zhou : But, look, this one's late.
Fa Zhou : But I'll bet that when it blooms,
Fa Zhou : it will be the most beautiful of all.
(DRUMS POUNDING IN DISTANCE)
Fa Mulan : What is it?
Fa Li : Mulan. Stay inside.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Chi-Fu : Citizens, I bring a proclamation from the Imperial City.
Chi-Fu : The Huns have invaded China.
(TOWNSPEOPLE GASP)
Chi-Fu : By order of the Emperor,
Chi-Fu : one man from every family must serve in the Imperial Army.
Chi-Fu : The Hsiao family.
Chi-Fu : The Yi family.
Yi Family's Son : I will serve the Emperor in my father's place.
Chi-Fu : The Fa family.
Fa Mulan : No!
Fa Zhou : I am ready to serve the Emperor.
Fa Mulan : Father, you can't go.
Fa Zhou : Mulan!
Fa Mulan : Please, sir, my father has already fought bravely...
Chi-Fu : Silence!
Chi-Fu : You would do well to teach your daughter to hold her tongue in a man's presence.
Fa Zhou : Mulan, you dishonor me.
Chi-Fu : Report tomorrow to the Wu Zhong camp.
Fa Zhou : Yes, sir.
Chi-Fu : The Chu family!
Chi-Fu : The Wen family!
Chi-Fu : The Chang family!
Fa Zhou : (GRUNTS)
Fa Zhou : (GROANS)
(BODY THUMPS FLOOR)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(THUNDERCLAP)
Fa Mulan : You shouldn't have to go!
Fa Li : Mulan...
Fa Mulan : There are plenty of young men to fight for China.
Fa Zhou : It is an honor to protect my country and my family.
Fa Mulan : So, you'll die for honor.
Fa Zhou : I will die doing what's right.
Fa Mulan : But if you...
Fa Zhou : I know my place!
Fa Zhou : It is time you learned yours.
(SHUDDERS)
(CRYING)
(THUNDERCLAP)
(WHINNYING)
(GASPS)
Grandmother Fa : Mulan is gone!
Fa Zhou : What?
Fa Zhou : It can't be.
Fa Zhou : Mulan!
(GROANS)
Fa Zhou : No.
Fa Li : You must go after her. She could be killed.
Fa Zhou : If I reveal her,
Fa Zhou : she will be.
Grandmother Fa : Ancestors, hear our prayer.
Grandmother Fa : Watch over Mulan.
(WIND GUSTING)
First Ancestor : Mushu, awaken.
(CLANKING)
Mushu : I live!
Mushu : So tell me what mortal needs my protection, great ancestor.
Mushu : You just say the word and I'm there.
First Ancestor : Mushu...
Mushu : And let me say somethin'. Anybody who's foolish enough to threaten our family, vengeance will be mine!
(GROWLING)
First Ancestor : Mushu!
First Ancestor : These are the family guardians.
First Ancestor : They...
Mushu : Protect the family.
First Ancestor : And you, O demoted one?
Mushu : I ring the gong.
First Ancestor : That's right. Now, wake up the ancestors.
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
Mushu : One family reunion comin' right up.
Mushu : Okay, people, people, look alive. Let's go. Come on. Get up. Let's move it. Rise and shine.
Mushu : Y'all way past the beauty sleep thing, trust me.
(ANCESTORS MUTTERING)
Ancestor2 : I knew it. I knew it. That Mulan was a troublemaker from the start!
Ancestor3 : Don't look at me. She gets it from your side of the family.
Ancestor4 : She's just trying to help her father.
Ancestor5 : But if she's discovered, Fa Zhou will be forever shamed.
Ancestor5 : Dishonor will come to the family. Traditional values will disintegrate.
Ancestor6 : Not to mention, they'll lose the farm.
Ancestor2 : My children never caused such trouble. They all became acupuncturists.
Ancestor3 : We can't all be acupuncturists.
Ancestor4 : No!
Ancestor4 : Your great-granddaughter had to be a cross-dresser!
(ANCESTORS ARGUING)
Ancestor7 : Let a guardian bring her back.
Ancestor5 : Yes, awaken the most cunning.
Ancestor6 : No. The swiftest.
Ancestor4 : No. Send the wisest.
First Ancestor : Silence!
First Ancestor : We must send the most powerful of all.
(MUSHU LAUGHING)
Mushu : Okay, okay, I get the drift. I'll go.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Mushu : Y'all don't think I can do it. Watch this here.
(INHALES)
Mushu : Jump back. I'm pretty hot, huh?
Mushu : Don't make me have to singe nobody to prove no point.
First Ancestor : You had your chance to protect the Fa family.
Ancestor4 : Your misguidance led Fa Deng to disaster.
Ancestor5 : Yeah, thanks a lot.
Mushu : And your point is?
First Ancestor : The point is we will be sending a real dragon to retrieve Mulan.
Mushu : What... What... I'm a real dragon!
First Ancestor : You are not worthy of this spot. Now, awaken the Great Stone Dragon.
Mushu : So you'll get back to me on the job thing?
(DISGUSTED SIGH)
Mushu : Just one chance, is that too much to ask?
Mushu : I mean, it's not like it'd kill ya.
Mushu : Yo, Rocky, wake up! Ya gotta go fetch Mulan!
Mushu : Come on, boy! Go get her! Go on!
Mushu : (WHISTLES) Come on.
(GONG BANGING)
Mushu : (GROWLING)
Mushu : Hello?
Mushu : Hello!
Mushu : Uh-oh.
Mushu : Uh, Stony?
Mushu : Stony? Oh, man, they're gonna kill me.
First Ancestor : Great Stone Dragon,
First Ancestor : have you awakened?
Mushu : Uh, uh... Yes, I just woke up.
Mushu : I'm... I'm the Great Stone Dragon. Good morning.
Mushu : I will go forth and fetch Mulan.
Mushu : Did I mention that I was the Great Stone Dragon?
First Ancestor : Go! The fate of the Fa family rests in your claws.
Mushu : Don't even worry about it. I will not lose face.
(SCREAMING AND GRUNTING)
(MOANING)
Mushu : My elbow!
Mushu : (GROANING) I know I twisted somethin'.
Mushu : (GRUNTING)
Mushu : That's just great. Now what?
Mushu : I'm doomed,
Mushu : and all 'cause Miss Man decides to take her little drag show on the road.
(CHIRPS)
(SQUEAKING)
Mushu : Go get her? What's the matter with you?
Mushu : After this Great Stone, Humpty Dumpty mess, I'd have to bring her home with a medal to get back in the temple.
Mushu : (GASPS) Wait a minute. That's it!
Mushu : I make Mulan a war hero, and they'll be begging me to come back to work.
Mushu : That's the master plan. Oh, you done it now, man.
(CHIRPS)
(CRICKET CHIRPING)
Mushu : What makes you think you're comin'?
Mushu : (CHIRPING)
Mushu : You're lucky? (CHUCKLING)
Mushu : Do I look like a sucker to you?
Mushu : (CHIRPS)
Mushu : What you mean, a loser?
Mushu : How 'bout I pop one of your antennas off, throw it across the yard? Then who's the loser, me or you?
Mushu : (SCREECHING)
Mushu : (WHINNYING)
Mushu : (BOTH GROAN)
Hun Soldier : Imperial scouts.
Soldier : Shan-Yu.
(SCREECHES)
Shan Yu : Nice work, gentlemen. You found the Hun army.
(HUNS LAUGHING)
Soldier : The Emperor will stop you.
Shan Yu : Stop me? He invited me.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Shan Yu : By building his wall, he challenged my strength.
Shan Yu : Well, I'm here to play his game.
Shan Yu : Go! Tell your Emperor to send his strongest armies.
Shan Yu : I'm ready.
Shan Yu : How many men does it take to deliver a message?
Hun Soldier : One.
Fa Mulan : Okay, okay, how about this?
(COUGHS)
Fa Mulan : (IN DEEP VOICE) Excuse me.
Fa Mulan : Where do I sign in?
Fa Mulan : I see you have a sword. I have one, too.
Fa Mulan : They're very manly and tough.
Fa Mulan : (NEIGHING)
Fa Mulan : I'm working on it!
Fa Mulan : (SIGHS)
Fa Mulan : Who am I fooling?
Fa Mulan : It's going to take a miracle to get me into the army.
Mushu : Did I hear someone ask for a miracle?
Mushu : Let me hear you say "Aaah"!
Mulan : Aaah!
Mushu : That's close enough.
Fa Mulan : A ghost.
Mushu : Get ready, Mulan. Your serpentine salvation is at hand!
Mushu : For I have been sent by your ancestors to guide you through your masquerade.
Mushu : Come on. If you're gonna stay, you're gonna work.
Mushu : So heed my word! 'Cause if the army finds out you're a girl,
Mushu : the penalty is death!
Fa Mulan : Who are you?
Mushu : Who am I? Who am I?
Mushu : I am the guardian of lost souls.
Mushu : I am the powerful, the pleasurable,
Mushu : the indestructible Mushu.
Mushu : (CHUCKLES) Pretty hot, huh?
Mushu : (GROANS)
Fa Mulan : Uh, my ancestors sent a little lizard to help me?
Mushu : Hey, dragon, dragon, not lizard.
Mushu : I don't do that tongue thing.
Fa Mulan : You're...
Mushu : Intimidating? Awe-inspiring?
Fa Mulan : Tiny.
Mushu : Of course.
Mushu : I'm travel size for your convenience.
Mushu : If I was my real size, your cow here would die of fright.
Mushu : Down, Bessie. My powers are beyond your mortal imagination.
Mushu : For instance, my eyes can see straight through your armor.
Mushu : Oh!
Mushu : All right, that's it! Dishonor! Dishonor on your whole family.
Mushu : Make a note of this. Dishonor on you, dishonor on your cow...
Fa Mulan : Stop. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Fa Mulan : I'm just nervous. I've never done this before.
Mushu : Then you're gonna have to trust me. And don't you slap me no more.
Mushu : We clear on that? All right.
Mushu : Okey-dokey. Let's get this show on the road!
Mushu : Cri-Kee, get the bags.
Mushu : Let's move it, Heifer.
(SNORTS)
(MEN CHATTERING)
Mushu : Okay, this is it. Time to show 'em your man walk.
Mushu : Shoulders back, chest high, feet apart, head up and strut.
Mushu : Two, three... Break it down. Hup, two, three. And work it!
Soldier : Beautiful, isn't he?
Fa Mulan : They're disgusting.
Mushu : No, they're men.
Mushu : Now, you gonna have to act just like them, so pay attention.
Soldier : Look. This tattoo will protect me from harm.
Soldiers : Hmm.
(GROANS)
(LAUGHING)
Ling : I hope you can get your money back.
Fa Mulan : I don't think I can do this.
Mushu : It's all attitude. Be tough, like this guy here.
(SNORTING)
Yao : What are you lookin' at?
Mushu : Punch him. It's how men say hello.
Chien-Po : Yao, you've made a friend.
Mushu : Good. Now slap him on the behind. They like that.
Yao : Whoa-ho-ho!
Yao : I'm gonna hit you so hard, it'll make your ancestors dizzy.
Chien-Po : Yao, relax and chant with me.
(GROWLING)
(CHANTING)
(YAO CHANTING)
(MUTTERING GIBBERISH)
Chien-Po : Feel better?
Yao : Yeah. Ah, you ain't worth my time.
Yao : Chicken boy.
Mushu : (SCREAMING) Chicken boy?
Mushu : Say that to my face, ya limp noodle!
(GROWLS)
Yao : Oh! Sorry, Ling.
Yao : Hey!
Ling : You're dead!
Ling : Oh, there he goes!
(CLATTERING) (CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(GRUNTING)
(MEN GROANING)
Fa Mulan : Guys.
General : The Huns have struck here, here and here.
General : I will take the main troops up to the Tung Shao Pass, and stop Shan-Yu before he destroys this village.
Chi-Fu : Excellent strategy, sir.
Chi-Fu : I do love surprises. (CHUCKLING)
General : You will stay and train the new recruits.
General : When Chi Fu believes you're ready,
General : you will join us, Captain.
Li Shang : Captain?
Chi-Fu : (GASPS) This is an enormous responsibility, General.
Chi-Fu : Perhaps a soldier with more experience.
General : Number one in his class, extensive knowledge of training techniques, and impressive military lineage.
General : I believe Li Shang will do an excellent job.
Li Shang : Oh, I will. I won't let you down. This is... I mean... (CLEARS THROAT)
Li Shang : Yes, sir.
General : Very good, then.
General : We'll toast China's victory at the Imperial City.
General : I'll expect a full report in three weeks.
Chi-Fu : And I won't leave anything out.
Li Shang : Captain Li Shang.
Li Shang : Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
Li Shang : Leader of China's finest troops.
Li Shang : No. The greatest troops of all time.
(MEN YELLING)
(MOANING)
Chi-Fu : Most impressive.
General : (WHINNIES) Good luck, Captain!
(URGES HORSE)
Li Shang : Good luck, Father.
(MEN YELLING)
(FIGHTING CONTINUES)
Chi-Fu : Day one.
Li Shang : Soldiers!
Soldiers : He started it!
Li Shang : I don't need anyone causing trouble in my camp.
Fa Mulan : (SOFTLY) Sorry.
Fa Mulan : Uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
Fa Mulan : (IN DEEP VOICE) I mean, sorry you had to see that.
Fa Mulan : But you know how it is when you get those manly urges
Fa Mulan : and you just gotta kill somethin',
Fa Mulan : (GROANS) fix things, cook outdoors...
Li Shang : What's your name?
Fa Mulan : (STAMMERING) Uh... I I umm....
Chi-Fu : Your commanding officer just asked you a question.
Fa Mulan : I've got a name. And it's a boy's name, too.
Mushu : Ling. How 'bout Ling?
Fa Mulan : His name is Ling.
Li Shang : I didn't ask for his name. I asked for yours!
Mushu : Try, uh, uh, ah, Chu.
Fa Mulan : Ah Chu.
Li Shang : Ah Chu?
Mushu : Gesundheit. I kill myself.
Fa Mulan : Mushu.
Li Shang : Mushu?
Fa Mulan : No.
Li Shang : Then what is it?
Mushu : Ping was my best friend growin' up.
Fa Mulan : It's Ping.
Li Shang : Ping?
Mushu : Of course, Ping did steal my...
Fa Mulan : Yes, my name is Ping.
Li Shang : Let me see your conscription notice.
Li Shang : Fa Zhou? The Fa Zhou?
Chi-Fu : I didn't know Fa Zhou had a son.
Fa Mulan : Um, he doesn't talk about me much.
(SNORTING)
Chi-Fu : I can see why. That boy's an absolute lunatic.
(CHUCKLING)
Li Shang : Okay, gentlemen, thanks to your new friend, Ping,
Li Shang : you'll spend tonight picking up every single grain of rice.
(MEN GROAN)
Li Shang : And tomorrow, the real work begins.
(GROWLS)
Mushu : You know, we have to work on your people skills.
(BIRDS TWITTERING)
(CHIRPING)
(LEGS SQUEAKING)
(RINGING)
Mushu : All right! Rise and shine, Sleeping Beauty.
Mushu : Come on. Hup, hup, hup.
Mushu : (MOANS)
Mushu : (SHIVERS) Get your clothes on.
Mushu : Get ready. Got breakfast for ya.
Mushu : Look, you get porridge, and it's happy to see you.
Mushu : Get outta there! You gonna make people sick.
Fa Mulan : Am I late?
Mushu : No time to talk. Now remember, it's your first day of training,
Mushu : so listen to your teacher and no fightin', play nice with the other kids, unless one of the other kids wanna fight, then you have to kick the other kid's butt.
Fa Mulan : But I don't wanna kick the other kid's butt.
Mushu : Don't talk with your mouth full. Now let's see your war face.
Mushu : I think my bunny slippers just ran for cover.
Mushu : Come on! Scare me, girl.
Fa Mulan : (GROWLS)
Mushu : Yeah, that's my tough-lookin' warrior. That's what I'm talkin' about. Now, get out there and make me proud.
Mushu : (HORSE NEIGHS)
Mushu : (SNORTING)
Mushu : What do you mean the troops just left?
Fa Mulan : They what?
(MUFFLED SHOUTS)
Mushu : Wait! You forgot your sword.
Mushu : My little baby, off to destroy people.
Mushu : (WHIMPERS)
Mushu : (MAN SCREAMS)
Chi-Fu : Order. People, order.
Soldier : I'd like a pan-fried noodle.
Soldier : Sweet and pungent shrimp.
Soldier : Moo goo gai pan.
Chi-Fu : That's not funny.
(BRAYING)
Ling : Looks like our new friend slept in this morning.
Ling : Hello, Ping. Are ya hungry?
Yao : Yeah, 'cause I owe you a knuckle sandwich.
(MEN AGREEING)
Li Shang : Soldiers!
Li Shang : You will assemble swiftly and silently every morning.
Li Shang : Anyone who acts otherwise
Li Shang : will answer to me.
Yao : Ooh, tough guy.
Li Shang : Yao.
Li Shang : Thank you for volunteering. Retrieve the arrow.
Yao : I'll get that arrow, pretty boy,
Yao : and I'll do it with my shirt on.
Li Shang : One moment. You seem to be missing something.
Li Shang : This represents discipline,
Li Shang : and this represents strength.
Li Shang : You need both to reach the arrow.
(BIRD TWITTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Li Shang : We've got a long way to go.
Li Shang : (SINGING) Let's get down to business
Li Shang : (ALL GASP)
Li Shang : To defeat the Huns
Li Shang : (ALL GRUNT)
Li Shang : Did they send me daughters
Li Shang : When I asked for sons?
Li Shang : You're the saddest bunch I ever met
Li Shang : But you can bet before we're through
Li Shang : Mister, I'll make a man
Li Shang : Out of you
Li Shang : Tranquil as a forest
Li Shang : But on fire within
Li Shang : Once you find your center
Li Shang : You are sure to win
Li Shang : You're a spineless, pale, pathetic lot
Li Shang : And you haven't got a clue
Li Shang : Somehow I'll make a man
Li Shang : Out of you
Chien-Po : I'm never gonna catch my breath
Yao : Say goodbye to those who knew me
Ling : Boy, was I a fool in school for cutting gym
Mushu : This guy's got 'em scared to death
Fa Mulan : Hope he doesn't see right through me
Chien-Po : Now I really wish that I knew how to swim
Soldiers : Be a man
Li Shang : We must be swift as a coursing river
Li Shang : With all the force of a great typhoon
Soldiers : -Be a man
Li Shang : -With all the strength of a raging fire
Li Shang : Mysterious as the dark side of the moon
Li Shang : Time is racing toward us
Li Shang : Till the Huns arrive
Li Shang : Heed my every order
Li Shang : And you might survive
Li Shang : You're unsuited for the rage of war
Li Shang : So pack up, go home, you're through
Li Shang : How could I make a man
Li Shang : Out of you?
Soldiers : -Be a man
Li Shang : -We must be swift as a coursing river
Li Shang : -With all the force of a great typhoon
Soldiers : -Be a man
Li Shang : -With all the strength of a raging fire
Li Shang : Mysterious as the dark side
Li Shang : Of the moon
Soldiers : -Be a man
Li Shang : -We must be swift as a coursing river
Li Shang : -With all the force of a great typhoon
Soldiers : -Be a man
Li Shang : -With all the strength of a raging fire
Li Shang : Mysterious as the dark side
Li Shang : Of the moon
(FALCON SCREECHING)
(SNIFFING)
Shan Yu : What do you see?
Hun Soldier : Black pine, from the high mountains.
Hun Soldier : White horse hair. Imperial stallions.
Hun Soldier : (SNIFFING) Sulfur, from cannons.
Shan Yu : This doll came from a village in the Tung Shao Pass,
Shan Yu : where the Imperial Army is waiting for us.
Hun Soldier : We can avoid them easily.
Shan Yu : No.
Shan Yu : The quickest way to the Emperor is through that pass.
Shan Yu : And besides, the little girl will be missing her doll.
Shan Yu : We should return it to her.
Mushu : (STAMMERING) No, this is not a good idea. What if somebody sees you?
Fa Mulan : Just because I look like a man doesn't mean I have to smell like one.
Mushu : So a couple of guys don't rinse out their socks. Picky, picky, picky.
Mushu : Myself, I kind of like that corn chip smell.
Fa Mulan : Ah!
Mushu : Okay, all right. That's enough. Get out before you get all pruny and stuff.
Fa Mulan : Mushu, if you're so worried, go stand watch.
Mushu : Yeah, yeah. (IMITATING MULAN) "Stand watch, Mushu, "while I blow our secret with my stupid girlie habits."
Mushu : Pfft! Hygiene!
(MEN LAUGHING)
Yao : Me first! Me first!
(GASPS)
Mushu : We're doomed!
Mushu : There are a couple of things I know they're bound to notice!
(CHIRPING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
Chien-Po : Woo!
(SCREAMING)
(YAO LAUGHING)
Yao : Ping!
Fa Mulan : Hi, guys. I didn't know you were here.
Fa Mulan : I was just washing. So now I'm clean, and I'm gonna go. Bye-bye.
Ling : Come back here. I know we were jerks to you before,
Ling : so let's start over.
Ling : Hi. I'm Ling.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Chien-Po : And I'm Chien-Po.
Fa Mulan : Hello, Chien-Po.
Yao : And I am Yao!
Yao : King of the rock!
Yao : And there's nothin' you girls can do about it.
Ling : Yeah? I think Ping and I can take you.
Fa Mulan : I really don't wanna take him anywhere.
Ling : Ping, we have to fight!
Fa Mulan : No, we don't. We could just close our eyes and swim around.
Ling : Come on. Don't be such a...
(CRUNCHING)
Ling : Ouch! Something bit me!
Mushu : Ugh! (COUGHS) What a nasty flavor.
Ling : Snake! (SCREAMING)
(WHISTLES)
(WHINNIES)
Yao : Oh, snake! Snake!
Ling : Snake! Snake!
(MEN CONTINUE SCREAMING)
Ling : Some king of the rock. Aah!
Fa Mulan : Boy, that was close.
Mushu : No. That was vile.
Mushu : You owe me big.
Mushu : I never want to see a naked man again.
(MEN SHOUTING JOYFULLY)
(SNORTS)
(WATER SPLASHING)
Mushu : Hey, don't look at me. I ain't bitin' no more butts.
Chi-Fu : You think your troops are ready to fight?
Chi-Fu : They would not last a minute against the Huns!
Li Shang : They completed their training.
Chi-Fu : Those boys are no more fit to be soldiers than you are to be Captain.
Chi-Fu : Once the General reads my report, your troops will never see battle.
Mushu : No, you don't! I've worked too hard to get Mulan into this war.
Mushu : This guy's messin' with my plan.
Li Shang : We're not finished!
Chi-Fu : Be careful, Captain. The general may be your father, but I am the Emperor's counsel.
Chi-Fu : And by the way, I got that job on my own.
Chi-Fu : You're dismissed.
Fa Mulan : I'll hold him and you punch.
(CHUCKLES)
Fa Mulan : Or not.
Fa Mulan : For what it's worth, I think you're a great captain.
Mushu : I saw that.
Fa Mulan : What?
Mushu : You like him, don't you?
Fa Mulan : No!
Mushu : Yeah, all right. Yeah, sure. Go to your tent!
Mushu : I think it's time we took this war into our own hands.
Mushu : (SINISTER CHUCKLING)
Mushu : (HUMMING)
Chi-Fu : (INHALES DEEPLY)
Chi-Fu : (CONTINUES HUMMING)
Chi-Fu : (GASPS)
Chi-Fu : (CLACKING SOUND)
Mushu : Let me see what you got.
Mushu : "From General Li. Dear son, we're waiting for Huns at the pass.
Mushu : "It would mean a lot if you'd come and back us up."
Mushu : That's great, except you forgot, "And since we're out of potpourri, "perhaps you wouldn't mind bringing up some."
Mushu : Hello! This is the army!
Mushu : Make it sound more urgent! Know what I'm talkin' about?
Mushu : (CHIRPING)
Mushu : (CLACKING SOUND)
Mushu : That's better. Much better. Let's go.
Mushu : Khanny, baby. We need a ride.
Mushu : (CHIRPING NERVOUSLY)
Chi-Fu : (MEN LAUGHING)
Chi-Fu : Insubordinate ruffians!
Chi-Fu : You men owe me a new pair of slippers! (LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
Chi-Fu : And I do not squeal like a girl.
Chi-Fu : (HIGH-PITCHED SQUEAL)
Mushu : Urgent news from the General.
Mushu : What's the matter? You've never seen a black and white before?
Chi-Fu : Who are you?
Mushu : Excuse me? I think the question is, who are you?
Mushu : We're in a war, man! There's no time for stupid questions!
Mushu : I should have your hat for that. Snatch it right off your head.
Mushu : But I'm feeling gracious today, so carry on before I report you.
Chi-Fu : Captain, urgent news from the General! We're needed at the front.
Mushu : Pack your bags, Cri-Kee. We're movin' out.
(CHIRPS)
Soldiers : (SINGING) For a long time we've been marching off to battle
Yao : In our thundering herd we feel a lot like cattle
Yao : (MOOING)
Soldiers : Like a pounding beat our aching feet
Soldiers : Aren't easy to ignore
Ling : Hey! Think of instead
Ling : A girl worth fighting for
Fa Mulan : Huh?
Ling : That's what I said.
Ling : A girl worth fighting for
Ling : I want her paler than the moon
Ling : With eyes that shine like stars
Yao : My girl will marvel at my strength
Yao : Adore my battle scars
Chien-Po : I couldn't care less what she'll wear or what she looks like
Chien-Po : It all depends on what she cooks like
Chien-Po : Beef, pork, chicken
Soldiers : Mmm!
Yao : Bet the local girls thought you were quite the charmer
Ling : And I'll bet the ladies love a man in armor
Soldiers : You can guess what we have missed the most
Soldiers : Since we went off to war
Ling : What do we want?
Soldiers : A girl worth fighting for
Yao : My girl will think I have no faults
Chien-Po : That I'm a major find
Fa Mulan : How 'bout a girl who's got a brain
Fa Mulan : Who always speaks her mind?
Yao;Ling;Chien-Po : Nah!
Ling : My manly ways and turn of phrase
Ling : Are sure to thrill her
Yao : He thinks he's such a lady killer
Chi-Fu : I've a girl back home who's unlike any other
Yao : Yeah, the only girl who'd love him is his mother
Soldiers : But when we come home in victory
Soldiers : They'll line up at the door
Ling : What do we want?
Soldiers : A girl worth fighting for
Ling : -Wish that I had
Soldiers : -A girl worth fighting for
(WHISTLING)
Soldiers : A girl worth fighting...
(CLANKING)
Li Shang : Search for survivors.
Li Shang : (CREAKING) (WHINNIES)
(HORSE NICKERS)
Li Shang : I don't understand. My father should've been here.
Chi-Fu : Captain!
Chien-Po : The General.
Fa Mulan : I'm sorry.
(NICKERS)
Li Shang : The Huns are moving quickly.
Li Shang : We'll make better time to the Imperial City through the Tung Shao Pass.
Li Shang : We're the only hope for the Emperor now.
Li Shang : Move out!
(BELL CLANKING)
(ALL GASPING)
(CHIRPING)
Li Shang : What happened?
Mulan : Uh...
Li Shang : You just gave away our position! Now we're...
(GRUNTING)
(BATTLE CRIES)
Li Shang : Get out of range!
(SCREAMING)
Mushu : Aah!
(WHINNIES)
Li Shang : Save the cannons!
Soldiers : (ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY) Come on! Empty it! Empty it!
Mushu : Hey!
Mushu : Oh, sure. Save the horse.
Li Shang : Fire!
(SCREAMING)
(WHIMPERING)
Li Shang : Fire!
Li Shang : Hold the last cannon.
(WHINNIES)
(BATTLE CRIES)
Li Shang : Prepare to fight. If we die, we die with honor.
Li Shang : (YELLING)
Li Shang : (CRIES CONTINUE)
Li Shang : Yao, aim the cannon at Shan-Yu.
Yao : Hey!
Li Shang : Ping! Come back!
Li Shang : Ping!
(WHINNIES)
Li Shang : Stop!
Mushu : All right. You might want to light that right about now.
Mushu : Quickly. Quickly!
(FALCON SCREECHING)
Yao : Come on! We gotta help!
Mushu : You missed! How could you miss?
Mushu : It was three feet in front of you!
(MEN SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
(GROANING)
(CHEERING)
(ALL THREE EXCLAIMING)
(WHINNYING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(YELLING)
Mushu : Mulan!
Mushu : Mulan? (GROWLING)
Mushu : No.
Mushu : Mulan!
Mushu : Man, you are one lucky bug.
Fa Mulan : Shang!
Ling : Do you see them?
Yao : Yes.
Yao : Perfect. Now we'll pull them to safe...ty.
Mushu : Mulan! I found the lucky cricket!
Fa Mulan : We need help.
Mushu : Nice. Very nice. You can sit by me.
Mushu : We're gonna die!
Mushu : We're gonna die! We are definitely gonna die.
Mushu : No way we survive this. Death is coming!
Yao : (BLUBBERING) I let them slip through my fingers.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Yao : Pull!
Soldiers : Whoa!
Soldiers : Huh!
Mushu : I knew we could do it. You the man!
Mushu : Well, sort of.
Ling : Step back, guys. Give him some air.
(GASPING)
Li Shang : Ping?
Li Shang : You are the craziest man I've ever met.
Li Shang : And for that, I owe you my life.
Li Shang : From now on, you have my trust.
Ling : Let's hear it for Ping! The bravest of us all!
Yao : You're king of the mountain!
Chien-Po : Yes, yes, yes!
(ALL WHOOPING)
(GROANS)
Li Shang : Ping! What's wrong?
(GROANING)
Li Shang : He's wounded! Get help!
Li Shang : Ping, hold on.
Li Shang : Hold on.
(WHISPERING)
Fa Mulan : (SIGHS) I can explain.
Chi-Fu : (GASPS) So it's true!
Fa Mulan : Shang!
Chi-Fu : I knew there was something wrong with you.
Chi-Fu : A woman!
(GRUNTING)
Chi-Fu : Treacherous snake!
Fa Mulan : My name is Mulan.
Fa Mulan : I did it to save my father.
Chi-Fu : High treason!
Fa Mulan : I didn't mean for it to go this far.
Chi-Fu : Ultimate dishonor!
Fa Mulan : It was the only way. Please believe me.
Chi-Fu : (SCOFFS) Captain?
(NEIGHING WILDLY) (GASPS)
Chi-Fu : Restrain him!
Yao;Ling;Chien-Po : No!
Chi-Fu : You know the law.
Li Shang : A life for a life.
Li Shang : My debt is repaid.
Li Shang : Move out!
Chi-Fu : (STUTTERING) But you can't just...
Li Shang : I said, "Move out."
(SNORTS)
(NICKERS)
(CHIRPING)
(SHIVERS)
Mushu : I was this close.
Mushu : This close to impressin' the ancestors,
Mushu : gettin' the top shelf, an entourage.
Mushu : Man. All my fine work. Pfft.
Mushu : Hi.
Fa Mulan : I should never have left home.
Mushu : Hey, come on. You went to save your father's life.
Mushu : Who knew you'd end up shamin' him and disgracing your ancestors
Mushu : and losin' all your friends?
Mushu : You know, you just gotta... You gotta learn to let these things go. (CRYING)
Fa Mulan : Maybe I didn't go for my father.
Fa Mulan : Maybe what I really wanted was to prove I could do things right,
Fa Mulan : so when I looked in the mirror, I'd see someone worthwhile.
Fa Mulan : But I was wrong. I see nothing.
Mushu : Now, that's just 'cause this needs a little spit, that's all.
Mushu : (SPITS) Let me shine this up for ya.
Mushu : I can see you. Look at you. You look so pretty.
Mushu : The truth is, we're both frauds.
Mushu : Your ancestors never sent me. They don't even like me.
Mushu : I mean, you risked your life to help people you love.
Mushu : I risked your life to help myself.
Mushu : At least you had good intentions.
Mushu : (SOFT CHIRPING)
Mushu : What? What do you mean, "You're not lucky"?
Mushu : You lied to me?
Mushu : (CHIRPING)
Mushu : And what are you, a sheep?
Mushu : (SNORTS)
Mushu : (GRUMBLES)
Fa Mulan : I'll have to face my father sooner or later.
Fa Mulan : Let's go home.
Mushu : Yeah. This ain't gonna be pretty.
Mushu : But don't you worry, okay? Things will work out.
Mushu : We started this thing together, and that's how we'll finish it.
Mushu : I promise.
Mushu : (SCREECHING)
Mushu : (GRUNTING)
Mushu : (YELLING)
Mushu : (YELLING ECHOES)
Mushu : (GRUNTING)
Mushu : (BOTH GRUNTING)
Mushu : (GROWLING)
Mushu : (GASPS)
Mushu : Uh, home is that way.
Fa Mulan : I have to do something.
Mushu : Did you see those Huns?
Mushu : They popped out of the snow... Like daisies!
Fa Mulan : Are we in this together or not?
Fa Mulan : (CHIRPING)
Mushu : Well, let's go kick some Hunny buns!
Mushu : Yee-haw!
Mushu : (WHOOPING)
Mushu : (TRADITIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Mushu : (CROWD CHEERING)
Officer : Make way for the heroes of China.
(WOMAN CRIES OUT)
Fa Mulan : Shang!
Li Shang : Mulan?
Fa Mulan : The Huns are alive! They're in the city!
Li Shang : You don't belong here, Mulan. Go home.
Fa Mulan : Shang, I saw them in the mountains. You have to believe me.
Li Shang : Why should I?
Fa Mulan : Why else would I come back?
Fa Mulan : You said you'd trust Ping. Why is Mulan any different?
Fa Mulan : Keep your eyes open. I know they're here.
Fa Mulan : (CROWD CHEERING)
Mushu : Now, where are you going?
Fa Mulan : To find someone who will believe me.
The Emperor of China : My children, heaven smiles down
The Emperor of China : upon the Middle Kingdom.
The Emperor of China : China will sleep safely tonight.
The Emperor of China : Thanks to our brave warriors.
The Emperor of China : (CROWD CHEERING)
Fa Mulan : Sir, the Emperor's in danger.
Man1 : (HARRUMPHS)
Fa Mulan : But the Huns are here.
Fa Mulan : Please, you have to help.
(HARRUMPHS)
Fa Mulan : No one will listen.
Mushu : Huh? Oh, I'm sorry. Did you say something?
Fa Mulan : Mushu.
Mushu : Hey you're a girl again, remember?
Li Shang : Your Majesty, I present to you the sword of Shan-Yu.
The Emperor of China : I know what this means to you, Captain Li.
The Emperor of China : Your father would have been very proud.
(SCREECHING)
(ALL GASPING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING) (GASPING)
(SCREECHING)
(GROWLING)
Li Shang : No!
Yao : Come on!
(CACKLING)
(GRUNTING)
Fa Mulan : They'll never reach the Emperor in time.
(BATTERING CONTINUES)
Fa Mulan : (WHISTLING) Hey, guys!
Fa Mulan : I've got an idea.
Soldiers : (SINGING) Be a man
Soldiers : -We must be swift as a coursing river
Soldiers : -Be a man
Soldiers : -With all the force of a great typhoon
Soldiers : With all the strength of a raging fire
Soldiers : Mysterious as the dark side of the moon
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
Shan Yu : Boo.
Shan Yu : Guard the door.
Shan Yu : Your walls and armies have fallen, and now it's your turn.
Shan Yu : Bow to me.
Fa Mulan : (WHISPERING) Okay. Any questions?
Yao : Does this dress make me look fat?
(SLAPS)
Yao : Ow!
Hun Soldier : (GIRLISH GIGGLE) Who's there?
(GIGGLING)
Hun Soldier : Concubines.
Hun Soldier : Ugly concubines.
Yao;Ling;Chien-Po : He's so cute!
Li Shang : Oh.
(SCREECHING)
(SQUAWKING)
Mushu : Now, that's what I call Mongolian barbecue.
(CRICKET CHUCKLING)
(GRUNTING)
Fa Mulan : Shang, go!
Shan Yu : I tire of your arrogance, old man. Bow to me!
The Emperor of China : No matter how the wind howls, the mountain cannot bow to it.
Shan Yu : Then you will kneel in pieces!
(CROWD GASPING)
Fa Mulan : Chien-Po, get the Emperor!
Chien-Po : Sorry, Your Majesty.
(GRUNTING)
Shan Yu : No!
Yao : Come on!
(HISSING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHEERING)
Shan Yu : No.
(GROWLING)
Shan Yu : You!
Shan Yu : You took away my victory!
Fa Mulan : No!
Fa Mulan : I did.
Shan Yu : The soldier from the mountains.
(YELLING)
(SQUAWKING)
Mushu : So what's the plan?
Fa Mulan : Um...
Mushu : You don't have a plan?
Fa Mulan : Hey, I'm making this up as I... go.
Fa Mulan : Mushu!
Mushu : Way ahead of you, sister.
Mushu : Come on, Cri-Kee.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
Mushu : Citizens, I need firepower.
Men : (GASPING) Who are you?
Mushu : (IN MENACING VOICE) Your worst nightmare.
Citizen : On the roof! Look!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
Shan Yu : It looks like you're out of ideas.
Fa Mulan : Not quite.
Fa Mulan : Ready, Mushu?
Mushu : I am ready, baby! Light me.
Shan Yu : (GROWLING)
Shan Yu : (GASPS)
Shan Yu : (SCREAMS)
Fa Mulan : Get off the roof, get off the roof, get off the roof.
(SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
Mushu : You are a lucky bug.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Chi-Fu : That was a deliberate attempt on my life!
Chi-Fu : Where is she? Now she's done it.
Chi-Fu : What a mess! Stand aside!
Chi-Fu : That creature's not worth protecting.
Li Shang : She's a hero.
Chi-Fu : She's a woman.
Chi-Fu : She'll never be worth anything.
Li Shang : Listen, you pompous...
The Emperor of China : That is enough.
Li Shang : Your Majesty, I can explain.
The Emperor of China : I've heard a great deal about you, Fa Mulan.
The Emperor of China : You stole your father's armor, ran away from home,
The Emperor of China : impersonated a soldier, deceived your commanding officer,
The Emperor of China : dishonored the Chinese army, destroyed my palace and
The Emperor of China : you have saved us all.
Chi-Fu : Ah! Oh!
(MUSHU SNIFFLES)
Mushu : My little baby is all grown up and savin' China.
Mushu : You have a tissue?
The Emperor of China : Chi Fu?
Chi-Fu : Your Excellency?
The Emperor of China : See to it that this woman is made a member of my council.
Chi-Fu : (STUTTERING) Member? What?
Chi-Fu : But... There are no council positions open, Your Majesty.
The Emperor of China : Very well. You can have his job.
Chi-Fu : What? I... (GASPS)
Fa Mulan : With all due respect, Your Excellency,
Fa Mulan : I think I've been away from home long enough.
The Emperor of China : Then take this,
The Emperor of China : so your family will know what you have done for me.
The Emperor of China : And this,
The Emperor of China : so the world will know what you have done for China.
(CHUCKLES)
Yao : Is she allowed to do that?
(ALL SIGHING)
Li Shang : Um... You...
Li Shang : You fight good.
Fa Mulan : Oh. Thank you.
(GROANS)
Fa Mulan : Khan, let's go home.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
The Emperor of China : The flower that blooms in adversity
The Emperor of China : is the most rare and beautiful of all.
Li Shang : Sir?
The Emperor of China : You don't meet a girl like that every dynasty.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Fa Zhou : (GASPING) Mulan!
Fa Mulan : Father, I brought you the sword of Shan-Yu.
Fa Mulan : And the crest of the Emperor.
Fa Mulan : They're gifts to honor the Fa family.
Fa Zhou : The greatest gift and honor is having you for a daughter.
Fa Zhou : I've missed you so.
Fa Mulan : I've missed you too, Baba.
(SIGHS)
Grandmother Fa : Great. She brings home a sword.
Grandmother Fa : If you ask me, she should've brought home a man.
Li Shang : Excuse me. Does Fa Mulan live here?
Li Shang : Thank you.
Grandmother Fa : Whoo! Sign me up for the next war.
Li Shang : Honorable Fa Zhou, I...
Li Shang : Mulan!
Li Shang : Uh... You forgot your helmet.
Li Shang : Well, actually, it's your helmet, isn't it?
Li Shang : I mean...
Fa Mulan : Would you like to stay for dinner?
Grandmother Fa : Would you like to stay forever?
Li Shang : Dinner would be great.
Mushu : Come on. Who did a good job? Come on. Tell me. Who did a good job?
First Ancestor : All right! You can be a guardian again.
(LAUGHING TRIUMPHANTLY)
Mushu : Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Mushu : Take it, Cri-Kee!
(PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
(WHOOPING)
Ancestor2 : You know, she gets it from my side of the family.
(ALL TALKING EXCITEDLY)
Mushu : Call out for egg rolls!
(YELPING)
First Ancestor : Guardians.
Mushu : Oh!
Mulan : Thanks, Mushu.
(BARKING)
(CLUCKING)
First Ancestor : Mushu!
MAN : (SINGING) Whenever you feel Your world is crashin' down on you
Whenever you don't know where to turn or what to do
Don't look too far
You've got the guide To find your way
Let your heart decide
Be true to your heart You must be true to your heart
That's when the heavens will part
And show the world what you believe in
Open your eyes Your heart can tell you no lies
And when you're true to your heart
Then you've got all you need to make it through
Be true to your heart
Ah, someone you know is on your side Can set you free
I can do that for you if you believe in me
Why second guess
What feels so right
Just trust your heart
And you'll see the light
Be true to your heart You must be true to your heart
That's when the heavens will part
And show the world what you believe in
Open your eyes Your heart can tell you no lies
And when you're true to your heart
Then you've got all you need to make it through
CHORUS : You know it's true
It'll see you through Yeah, yeah, yeah
You've got to be true, baby
Be true to your heart
(ALL SCATTING)
Be true to your heart You must be true to your heart
That's when the heavens will part
And show the world what you believe in Open your eyes Your heart will tell you no lies
And when you're true to your heart
Then you've got all you need to make it through Be true
To your heart
Sing the chorus, boys
CHORUS : When things are gettin' crazy
And you don't know where to start
Keep on believin', baby
Just be true to your heart
-When all the world around you -Yeah
It seems to fall apart
Keep on believin', baby
Just be true to your heart True to your heart
Just be true
(SCATTING)
To your heart
Got to be true
Be true, true, true, true, true
To your heart
(SLOW SONG PLAYING)
WOMAN : (SINGING) Look at me
You may think you see who I really am
But you'll never know me
Every day
It's as if I play a part
Now I see
If I wear a mask, I can fool the world
But I cannot fool my heart
Who is that girl I see
Staring straight back at me?
When will my reflection show
Who I am inside?
I am now
In a world where I have to hide my heart
And what I believe in
But somehow
I will show the world
What's inside my heart
And be loved for who I am
Who is that girl I see
Staring straight back at me?
Why is my reflection
Someone I don't know?
Must I pretend that I'm
Someone else for all time?
When will my reflection show
Who I am? Inside, there's a heart
That must be free
To fly
And I burn
With a need to know
The reason why
Why must we all conceal
What we think, how we feel?
Must there be a secret me
I'm forced to hide?
I won't pretend that I'm
Someone else for all time
When will my reflection show
Who I am inside?
Oh, yeah