All : The second star to the right
All : Shines in the night for you
All : To tell you that the dreams you plan Really can come true
All : The second star to the right Shines with a light so rare
All : And if it's Never Land you need
All : Its light will lead you there
Woman : Twinkle twinkle little star
Woman : So we'll know where you are
Woman : Gleaming in the skies above
Woman : Lead us to the land We dream of
All : And when our journey is through
All : Each time we say
All : Good night
All : We'll thank the little star that shines
All : The second from
All : The right
Narrator : All this has happened before
Narrator : And it will all happen again
Narrator : But this time it happened in London
Narrator : It happened on a quiet street in Bloomsbury
Narrator : That corner house over there is the home of the Darling family
Narrator : And Peter Pan chose this particular house because there were people here who believed in him
Narrator : There was Mrs Darling
Mrs. Darling : George dear do hurry We mustn't be late for the party you know
Narrator : Mrs Darling believed that Peter Pan was the spirit of youth
Narrator : But Mr Darling
Mr. Darling : Mary unless I find my cuff links we don't go to the party
Mr. Darling : And if we don't go to the party I can never show my face in the office again
Mr. Darling : And if I can never Ow
Narrator : Well Mr Darling was a practical man
Narrator : The boys however John and Michael believed Peter Pan was a real person
Narrator : and made him the hero of all their nursery games
John Darling : Blast you Peter Pan
Michael Darling : Take that Give up Captain Hook Give up
John Darling : Never I'll teach you to cut off me hand
Wendy Darling : Oh no John It was the left hand
John Darling : Oh yes Thank you Wendy
Narrator : Wendy the eldest not only believed
Narrator : she was the supreme authority on Peter Pan and all his marvellous adventures
Wendy Darling : Oh Nana must we always take that nasty tonic
Narrator : Nana the nursemaid being a dog kept her opinions to herself
Narrator : and viewed the whole affair with a certain tolerance
Michael Darling : Take that
John Darling : Insolent boy I'll slash you to ribbons
Michael Darling : And I'll cut you to pieces
Michael Darling : Aha
John Darling : Uh
Michael Darling : Ouch
John Darling : Careful Michael my glasses
Michael Darling : I'm sorry John
John Darling : You'll never leave this ship alive
Michael Darling : Oh yes I will
Michael Darling : Take that
John Darling : Scuttle me bones boy I'll slit your gizzard
Michael Darling : Oh no you won't
Michael Darling : Back back back villain
John Darling : Insolent pup
Michael Darling : Wicked pirate
John Darling : Aha I got you
Michael Darling : You didn't either You never touched me
Michael Darling : Take that and that And that
Mr. Darling : Boys boys less noise please
John Darling : Oh hello Father
Michael Darling : You old bilge rat
Mr. Darling : Wh what Now see here Michael
Michael Darling : Oh not you Father You see he's Peter Pan
Michael Darling : And John's Captain Hook
Mr. Darling : Yes yes of course Have you seen my cuff
Mr. Darling : Oh Nana for goodness sake
Mr. Darling : Where are those cuff links
John Darling : Cuff links Father
Mr. Darling : Yes the gold ones
John Darling : Michael the buried treasure Where is it
Michael Darling : I don't know
John Darling : The map then Where's the treasure map
Michael Darling : It got lost
Mr. Darling : Good heavens my shirt front
Michael Darling : Hurray You found it You found it
Mr. Darling : So I have
Mr. Darling : And hereafter Don't paw me Michael This is my last clean
Mr. Darling : No
Mrs. Darling : George dear we must hurry or we'll be
Mr. Darling : Mary look
Mrs. Darling : George
Michael Darling : It's only chalk Father
Mrs. Darling : Why Michael
John Darling : It's not his fault It's in the story
Mr. Darling : Wendy Story
Mr. Darling : I might have known Wendy
Mr. Darling : Wendy
Wendy Darling : Yes Father
Mr. Darling : Would you kindly
Wendy Darling : Oh Mother You look simply lovely
Mrs. Darling : Thank you dear
Mr. Darling : Wendy
Mrs. Darling : Just my old gown made over But it did turn out rather
Mr. Darling : Mary if you don't mind
Wendy Darling : Why Father what have you done to your shirt
Mr. Darling : What have I Oh
Mrs. Darling : Now George really It comes right off
Mr. Darling : That's no excuse Wendy haven't I warned you
Mr. Darling : Stuffing the boys heads with a lot of silly stories
Wendy Darling : I say they are
Mr. Darling : I said they are
Mr. Darling : Captain Crook Peter Pirate
Wendy Darling : Peter Pan Father
Mr. Darling : Pan Pirate Poppycock
Wendy Darling : Oh No Father You
Michael Darling : don't understand
Mr. Darling : Absolute poppycock
Mr. Darling : And let me tell you this ridiculous
Mrs. Darling : Now George
Mr. Darling : Now George
Mr. Darling : Well Now George will have his say
Mrs. Darling : Please dear
Mr. Darling : Mary the child's growing up
Mr. Darling : It's high time she had a room of her own
Wendy Darling : Father
Mrs. Darling : George
John Darling : What
Michael Darling : No
Mr. Darling : I mean it
Mr. Darling : Young lady this is your last night in the nursery
Mr. Darling : And that's my last word on the matter
Mr. Darling : Oh Ah
Mr. Darling : No
Mrs. Darling;Wendy Darling;John Darling;Michael Darling : Oh
Mrs. Darling;Wendy Darling;John Darling;Michael Darling : Poor Nana
Mr. Darling : Poor Nana
Mr. Darling : This is the last straw
Mr. Darling : Outch Out I say
Michael Darling : No Father no
Mr. Darling : Yes! There'll be no more dogs for nursemaids in this house
Michael Darling : Goodbye Nana
Mr. Darling : Poor Nana Oh yes Poor Nana
Mr. Darling : But Poor Father Oh no
Mr. Darling : Blast it Where is that rope
Mr. Darling : Oh thank you
Mr. Darling : Dash it all Nana don't look at me like that
Mr. Darling : It's nothing personal It's just that
Mr. Darling : Well you're not really a nurse at all You're well a dog
Mr. Darling : And the children aren't puppies They're people
Mr. Darling : And sooner or later Nana people have to grow up
Wendy Darling : But Mother I don't want to grow up
Mrs. Darling : Now dear don't worry about it any more tonight
John Darling : He called Peter Pan absolute poppycock
Mrs. Darling : I'm sure he didn't mean it John Father was just upset
Michael Darling : Poor Nana out there all alone
Mrs. Darling : No more tears Michael It's a warm night
Mrs. Darling : She'll be all right
Michael Darling : Mother
Mrs. Darling : What is it dear
Michael Darling : Buried treasure
Mrs. Darling : Now children
Mrs. Darling : Don't judge your father too harshly
Mrs. Darling : After all he really loves you very much
Wendy Darling : Oh don't lock it Mother He might come back
Mrs. Darling : He?
Wendy Darling : Yes, Peter Pan.
Wendy Darling : You see, I found something that belongs to him
Mrs. Darling : Oh And what's that
Wendy Darling : His shadow
Mrs. Darling : Shadow Mm Nana had it
Wendy Darling : But I I took it away
Mrs. Darling : Oh Yes of course
Mrs. Darling : Good night dear
Mrs. Darling : But George do you think the children will be safe without Nana
Mr. Darling : Safe? Of course they'll be safe Why not
Mrs. Darling : Well Wendy said something about a shadow and I
Mr. Darling : Shadow Whose shadow
Mrs. Darling : Peter Pan
Mr. Darling : Oh Peter Pan Peter Pan
Mr. Darling : You don't say Goodness gracious whatever shall we do
Mrs. Darling : But George Sound the alarm
Mrs. Darling : Really?
Mr. Darling : Call Scotland Yard
Mrs. Darling : There must have been someone
Mr. Darling : Oh Mary of all the impossible childish fiddlefaddle
Mr. Darling : Peter Pan indeed How can we expect the children to grow up and be practical
Mrs. Darling : George when you're as bad as they are
Mr. Darling : No wonder Wendy gets these idiotic ideas
Peter Pan : Over there Tink in its den
Peter Pan : Is it there
Peter Pan : Must be here somewhere
Peter Pan : Tink
Peter Pan : Shh
Peter Pan : Stop playing and help me find my shadow
Peter Pan : Shadow Oh shadow
Peter Pan : Huh
Peter Pan : Aha
Wendy Darling : Peter Pan
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter
Wendy Darling : I knew you'd come back I saved your shadow for you
Wendy Darling : Oh I do hope it isn't rumpled
Wendy Darling : You know you look exactly the way I thought you would
Wendy Darling : Oh a little taller perhaps But then
Wendy Darling : Oh you can't stick it on with soap Peter
Wendy Darling : It needs sewing That's the proper way to do it
Wendy Darling : Come to think of it I've never thought about it sewing shadows
Wendy Darling : Of course I knew it was your shadow the minute I saw it
Wendy Darling : I said to myself I'll put it away for him until he comes back
Wendy Darling : Oh he's sure to come back And you did didn't you Peter
Wendy Darling : After all one can't leave his shadow lying about
Wendy Darling : and not miss it sooner or later Don't you agree
Wendy Darling : What I still don't understand is how Nana got it in the first place
Wendy Darling : She really isn't Oh sit down It won't take long
Wendy Darling : She really isn't vicious She's a wonderful nurse
Wendy Darling : Although Father says
Peter Pan : Girls talk too much
Wendy Darling : Yes girls talk too H mm Oh
Peter Pan : Well get on with it girl
Wendy Darling : My name is Wendy
Wendy Darling : Wendy Moira Angela Darl
Peter Pan : Wendy is enough
Wendy Darling : Oh
Wendy Darling : But how did Nana get your shadow Peter
Peter Pan : Jumped at me The other night at the window
Wendy Darling : What were you doing there
Peter Pan : I came to listen to the stories
Wendy Darling : My stories But they're all about you
Peter Pan : Of course That's why I like em I tell em to the Lost Boys
Wendy Darling : The Lost Boys Oh I remember
Wendy Darling : They're your men Uhhuh
Wendy Darling : I'm so glad you came back tonight
Wendy Darling : I might never have seen you
Peter Pan : Why
Wendy Darling : Because I have to grow up tomorrow
Peter Pan : Grow up
Wendy Darling : Tonight's my last night in the nursery
Peter Pan : But that means no more stories
Wendy Darling : Mmhmm
Peter Pan : No I won't have it Come on
Wendy Darling : But but where are we going
Peter Pan : To Never Land
Wendy Darling : Never Land
Peter Pan : You'll never grow up there
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter it will be so wonderful
Wendy Darling : But wait
Wendy Darling : But wait What would Mother say
Peter Pan : Mother What's Mother
Wendy Darling : Why Peter a mother is someone who
Wendy Darling : Who loves and cares for you and tells you stories
Peter Pan : Good You can be our mother Come on
Wendy Darling : Now just a minute I Let me see now I have to pack
Wendy Darling : Oh and I must leave a note when I'll be back I couldn't stay too long
Wendy Darling : And then I'll have to Oh but Never Land
Wendy Darling : Oh I I'm so happy I
Wendy Darling : I think I'll give you a a kiss
Peter Pan : What's a a kiss
Wendy Darling : Oh well uh I'll show you
Wendy Darling : Oh
Peter Pan : Stop Stop it Tink
Michael Darling : John John wake up He's here
John Darling : Huh
John Darling : Jiminy
Wendy Darling : Ooh what in the world was that
Peter Pan : Tinker Bell Don't know what got into her
Michael Darling : Hello Peter Pan I'm Michael
John Darling : And my name is John How do you do
Peter Pan : Hello
Michael Darling : Oh look a firefly
Wendy Darling : A pixie
John Darling : Amazing
Michael Darling : What's the pixie doing
Peter Pan : Talking
Wendy Darling : What did she say
Peter Pan : She says you're a big ugly girl
Wendy Darling : Oh Well I think she's lovely
Peter Pan : Well come on Wendy let's go
Michael Darling : Where are we going
Wendy Darling : To Never Land
Michael Darling : Never Land?
Wendy Darling : Peter's taking
Wendy Darling : Well of course I couldn't go without Michael and John
John Darling : I should like very much to cross swords with real buccaneers
Michael Darling : Yes and fight pirates too
Peter Pan : Well all right but ya gotta take orders
John Darling : Aye aye sir
Michael Darling : Me too
Wendy Darling : But Peter how do we get to Never Land
Peter Pan : Fly of course
Wendy Darling : Fly?
Peter Pan : It's easy All you have to do is to is to
Peter Pan : Is to
Peter Pan : Ha That's funny
Wendy Darling : What's the matter
Wendy Darling : Don't you know
Peter Pan : Well sure
Peter Pan : It's it's just that I never thought about it before
Peter Pan : Say that's it You think of a wonderful thought
Wendy Darling;John Darling : Any happy little thought
Peter Pan : Uhuh
Wendy Darling : Like toys at Christmas Sleigh bells snow
Peter Pan : Yep Watch me now Here I go
Peter Pan : It's easier than pie
Wendy Darling : He can fly
John Darling : He can fly
Michael Darling : He flewed
Peter Pan : Now you try
Wendy Darling : I'll think of a mermaid lagoon
Wendy Darling : underneath a magic moon
John Darling : I'll think I'm in a pirate's cave
Michael Darling : I think I'll be an Indian brave
Peter Pan : Now everybody try
Peter Pan;Wendy Darling;John Darling;Michael Darling : One two three
John Darling : We can fly
Wendy Darling;John Darling;Michael Darling : We can fly
Peter Pan : This won't do What's the matter with you
Peter Pan : All it takes is faith and trust
Peter Pan : Oh And something I forgot
Peter Pan : Dust
Wendy Darling;John Darling : Dust?
Michael Darling : Dust?
Peter Pan : Yep
Peter Pan : Just a little bit of pixie dust
Peter Pan : Now think of the happiest things
Peter Pan : It's the same as having wings
Wendy Darling : Let's all try it just once more
John Darling : Look We're rising off the floor
Michael Darling : Jiminy
Wendy Darling : Oh my We can fly
Peter Pan : You can fly
Wendy Darling;John Darling;Michael Darling : We can fly
Peter Pan : Come on everybody Here we go
Peter Pan : Off to Never Land
All : Think of a wonderful thought
All : Any merry little thought
All : Think of Christmas Think of snow
All : Think of sleigh bells Off you go like reindeer in the sky
All : You can fly you can fly You can fly
All;Women Ensemble : Think of the happiest things
Women Ensemble : It's the same as having wings
Men Ensemble : Take the path that moonbeams make
All : If the moon is still awake you'll see him wink his eye
All : You can fly you can fly You can fly
Men Ensemble : Up you go with a heigh and ho
Men Ensemble : To the stars beyond the blue
All : There's a Never Land waiting for you
All : Where all your happy dreams come true
All : Every dream that you dream will come true
Michael Darling : Come on Nana
Men Ensemble : When there's a smile in your heart
Men Ensemble : There's no better time to start
Men Ensemble : Think of all the joy you'll find
Women Ensemble : When you leave the world behind and bid your cares goodbye
All : You can fly you can fly You can fly you can fly
Peter Pan : There it is Wendy Second star to the right and straight on till morning
All : When there's a smile in your heart
All : There's no better time to start
Women Ensemble : Think of all the joy you'll find when you leave the world behind
All : And bid your cares goodbye
All : You can fly you can fly You can fly you can fly you can fly
Pirates : Oh a pirate's life is a wonderful life
Pirates : Arovin over the sea Give me a career as a buccaneer
Pirates : It's the life of a pirate for me oh The life of a pirate for me
Pirates : Oh a pirate's life is a wonderful life
Pirates : They never bury your bones
Pirates : For when it's all over a jolly sea rover drops in on his friend Davy Jones
Pirates : Oh my good friend Davy Jones
Mr. Smee : Good morning shipmates
Pirate1 : And what's good about it Mr Smee
Pirate1 : Here we are collecting barnacles on this miserable island
Pirate2 : While his nibs plays ringaroundtherosy with Peter Pan
Mr. Smee : Look out It might go off
Pirate3 : We ought to be tending to the business of looting ships
Pirate4 : Why I've almost forgotten how to slit a throat
Pirate1 : Better hop it And tell the captain we wants to put to sea
Captain Hook : Peter Pan
Captain Hook : Blast that Peter Pan
Captain Hook : If I could only find his hideout I'd trap him in his lair
Captain Hook : But where is it
Captain Hook : Mermaid Lagoon
Captain Hook : No we've searched that
Captain Hook : We've combed Cannibal Cove
Captain Hook : Here No No no no That's Indian terri
Captain Hook : But wait
Captain Hook : Those redskins know this island better than I do me own ship
Captain Hook : Ah
Captain Hook : I wonder
Mr. Smee : Good morning captain
Captain Hook : I've got you
Captain Hook : Tiger Lily Smee
Mr. Smee : T Tiger Lily captain
Captain Hook : The chief's daughter She'll know where Pan is hiding
Mr. Smee : B but but will she talk captain
Captain Hook : Oh a little persuasion might be in order
Captain Hook : Now let me see
Captain Hook : Boiling in oil
Mr. Smee : Keelhauling Marooning
Pirate5 : A pirate's life is a wonderful life
Pirate5 : You'll find adventure and sport
Pirate5 : But live every minute for all that is in it
Pirate5 : The life of a pirate is short
Pirate5 : Oh the life
Captain Hook : Now let me see where was I
Mr. Smee : Oh dear dear dear Captain Hook
Mr. Smee : Shooting a man in the middle of his cadenza
Mr. Smee : It ain't good form you know
Captain Hook : Good form Mr Smee Blast good form
Captain Hook : Did Pan show good form when he did this to me
Mr. Smee : Why captain cutting your hand off was only a childish prank you might say
Captain Hook : Aye But throwing it to the crocodile
Captain Hook : That cursed beast liked the taste of me so well
Captain Hook : he's followed me ever since
Captain Hook : licking his chops for the rest of me
Mr. Smee : And he'd have had you by now captain
Mr. Smee : if he hadn't swallowed that alarm clock
Mr. Smee : But now when he's about he warns ya as ya might say
Mr. Smee : with his ticktock ticktock ticktock
Captain Hook : Smee Smee
Captain Hook : Save me Smee Please don't let him get me Smee
Captain Hook : Please don't let him get me Smee Smee
Mr. Smee : Here now shame on ya Upsettin the poor captain
Mr. Smee : There'll be no handouts today Shoo now shoo
Mr. Smee : Go on go on off it Off with ya I say go away go away out of here
Captain Hook : Is he gone Smee
Mr. Smee : I can't be no clear
Mr. Smee : Nothin to worry about
Captain Hook : Oh Smee Smee I can't stand it any longer I tell you I can't
Mr. Smee : Now now now now captain Just relax
Mr. Smee : What you need is a shave
Mr. Smee : A nice soothing shave There now
Mr. Smee : Oh a pirate's life is a wonderful life
Mr. Smee : Asailing over the sea Give me a career as a Captain you know I can't help noticin
Mr. Smee : you just ain't been your usual jolly self of late
Mr. Smee : Give me a career as a buccaneer And the crew's gettin a might uneasy captain
Mr. Smee : That is what's left of it
Mr. Smee : Now why don't we put to sea see Leave Never Land
Mr. Smee : Forget Peter Pan There now
Mr. Smee : Give me a career as a buccaneer
Mr. Smee : We'd all be a lot happier not to mention a lot healthier
Mr. Smee : Oh
Mr. Smee : Captain Oh dear I never shaved him this close before
Mr. Smee : Ooh Ooh Ooh
Mr. Smee : Now don't worry captain It must be somewhere about
Captain Hook : Get up you idiot
Mr. Smee : Aye aye sir
Mr. Smee : Ooh I found it captain
Mr. Smee : Good as new
Captain Hook : Why you blithering blockhead
Pirate5 : Peter Pan ahoy
Captain Hook : What Where away
Pirate5 : Three points off the starboard bow
Captain Hook : Swoggle me eyes It is Pan
Captain Hook : Headed this way with some more of those scurvy brats
Captain Hook : Mr Smee pipe up the crew
Mr. Smee : Aye aye sir The Pipe up the crew The Pipe up the crew
Mr. Smee : All hands on deck
Captain Hook : Look alive you swabs
Captain Hook : We've got him this time Mr Smee
Mr. Smee : That we have captain
Captain Hook : Man the Long Tom you bilge rats
Captain Hook : I've waited years for this
Mr. Smee : That's not countin holidays either
Captain Hook : Double the powder shorten the fuse
Captain Hook : A pretty sight Mr Smee We'll pot em like sitting ducks
Captain Hook : All right men Range 42
Mr. Smee : Range 42
Captain Hook : Elevation 65
Mr. Smee : Elevation 65
Captain Hook : Three degrees west
Mr. Smee : Three degrees west
Captain Hook : Steady now
Captain Hook : Steady
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter it's just as I've always dreamed it would be
Wendy Darling : Oh look John there's Mermaid Lagoon
Wendy Darling : By Jove And the Indian encampment
Michael Darling : Oh look there's Captain Hook and the pirates
Peter Pan : Look out
Peter Pan : Tink take Wendy and the boys to the island
Peter Pan : I'll stay here and draw Hook's fire
Peter Pan : Hook Hook You codfish Here
Wendy Darling : Tinker Bell Not so fast Please Tinker Bell
Wendy Darling : We can't keep up with you
Wendy Darling : Tinker Bell Wait
Michael Darling : Ouch
Michael Darling : So
The Twins : Who ya shovin
Curly : That's who
Slightly : Huh Orders from Pan
Slightly : Hold it men
Nibs : What's the orders Tink
Curly : A terrible what
Slightly : Wendy Bird
Curly : Wendy Bird
Slightly : Flying this way
Curly : Pan's orders are What
Curly : Smash it
Slightly : Kick it
The Twins : Stomp it
Slightly : Oh Shoot it down
Nibs : Shoot it down
Slightly : Yeah shoot it down Come on follow Tink
Curly : Yeah come on Let's go then We're gonna get er
Slightly : I see it
The Twins : Me too
The Lost Boys : Ready aim
The Lost Boys : Fire
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter you saved my life
Michael Darling : Are you hurted Wendy
Wendy Darling : No Michael
John Darling : Good heavens Wendy you might have been killed
The Lost Boys : Hey Hey Pan We followed your orders Pan
Slightly : hey Pan I got it with my skull buster
The Twins : Ya did not We did
Tootles : I did it Pan I
Curly : did it No I did
Peter Pan : Attention
Peter Pan : Well I'm certainly proud of you
Peter Pan : You blockheads
Peter Pan : I bring ya a mother to tell stories
Slightly : Mother?
Peter Pan : And you shoot her down
Curly : Well Tink said it was a bird
Peter Pan : Tink said what
Nibs : Well she said you said to shoot it down
Peter Pan : Tinker Bell Tink
Peter Pan : Come here
Peter Pan : You're charged with high treason Tink
Peter Pan : Are you guilty or not guilty
Peter Pan : Guilty But don't ya know ya might have killed her
Peter Pan : Tinker Bell
Peter Pan : I hereby banish you forever
Wendy Darling : Please, not forever.
Peter Pan : Well for a week then
Peter Pan : Come on Wendy I'll show you the island
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter the mermaids
Curly : Aw let's go huntin
Nibs : Tigers?
The Twins : Naw bears Naw bears
John Darling : Personally I prefer to see the aborigines
Michael Darling : And the Indians too
Peter Pan : All right men
Peter Pan : Go out and capture a few Indians
Peter Pan : John you be the leader
John Darling : I shall try to be worthy of my post
John Darling : Forward March
Michael Darling : Come on bear
Wendy Darling : Oh Michael do be careful
Peter Pan : Come on Wendy I'll show you the mermaids
The Lost Boys : Following the leader The leader the leader
The Lost Boys : We're following the leader wherever he may go
The Lost Boys : Tee dum tee dee A teedle ee do tee day
The Lost Boys : Tee dum tee dee It's part of the game we play
The Lost Boys : Tee dum tee dee The words are easy to say
The Lost Boys : Just a teedle ee dum a teedle ee do tee day
The Lost Boys : Tee dum tee dee A teedle ee do tee dum
The Lost Boys : We're one for all and all of us out for fun
The Lost Boys : We march in line and follow the other one
The Lost Boys : With a teedle ee do A teedle ee di tee dum
The Lost Boys : We're following the leader the leader the leader
The Lost Boys : We're following the leader wherever he may go
The Lost Boys : We're out to fight the Injuns the Injuns the Injuns
The Lost Boys : We're out to fight the Injuns because he told us so
The Lost Boys;John Darling : Tee dum tee dee A teedle ee do tee dum
The Lost Boys;John Darling : We march along and these are the words we say
The Lost Boys;John Darling : Tee dum tee dee A teedle ee do tee day
The Lost Boys;John Darling : Oh a teedle dee dum A teedle ee do tee day
The Lost Boys : Oh a teedle ee dum A teedle ee do tee day
John Darling : Indians
John Darling : Oh Blackfoot tribe
John Darling : Belongs to the Algonquin group
John Darling : Quite savage you know
Curly : Let's go get'em
Slightly : Come on We'll get em Gentlemen gentlemen
John Darling : First we must plan our strategy
Curly : Uh what's stragety
John Darling : A plan of attack
John Darling : The initial phase is an encircling manoeuvre thus
Michael Darling : John Indians Indians
Michael Darling : Let me in
John Darling : Now Remember the Indian is cunning
John Darling : but not intelligent
John Darling : Therefore we simply surround them and take them by surprise
John Darling : I'm frightfully sorry old chaps It's all my fault
Curly : Aw that's all right Wildcat
Slightly : Oh we don't mind
Nibs : That's OK
Indian Chief : How
Curly : How chief
The Lost Boys : How
Indian Chief : For many moons red man fight paleface Lost Boys
Indian Chief : Sometime you win
Indian Chief : Sometime we win
Curly : OK chief You win this time Now turn us loose
John Darling : Turn us loose You mean this is only a game
Slightly : Sure When we win we turn them loose
Nibs : When they win they turn us loose
Indian Chief : This time no turn em loose
Slightly;Curly : Huh
Slightly : It's a great spoofer
Indian Chief : Me no spoof em
Indian Chief : Where you hide Princess Tiger Lily
Curly : Uh Tiger Lily
Slightly : We ain't got your old princess
John Darling : I've certainly never seen her
Curly : Me neither
The Twins : Honest we don't
Indian Chief : Heap big lie
Indian Chief : If Tiger Lily not back by sunset
Indian Chief : burn em at stake
Wendy Darling : Just imagine real live mermaids
Peter Pan : Would you like to meet em
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter I'd love to
Peter Pan : All right come on
Wendy Darling;Mermaids : It's Peter Oh
Mermaids : Hello Peter
Redhead Mermaid : Hello Peter
Peter Pan : Hello girls
Blonde Mermaid : I'm so glad to see you
Redhead Mermaid : Why did you stay away so long Did you miss me
Blackhead Mermaid : Tell us one of your adventures Something exciting
Peter Pan : Want to hear about the time I cut off Hook's hand and threw it to the crocodile
Redhead Mermaid : Oh I've always liked that one
Blackhead Mermaid : Me too
Peter Pan : There I was on Marooner's Rock surrounded
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter
Blackhead Mermaid : Who's she
Peter Pan : Huh Her
Peter Pan : Oh that's Wendy
Blonde Mermaid : A girl?
Blackhead Mermaid : What's she doing here?
Redhead Mermaid : And in her nightdress too
Redhead Mermaid : Come on dearie Join us for a swim
Wendy Darling : Oh please I'm not dressed for it
Blonde Mermaid : But you must
Wendy Darling : No no please
Redhead Mermaid : Too good for us eh
Wendy Darling : Peter
Wendy Darling : If you dare to come near me again...
Peter Pan : Wendy Wendy
Peter Pan : They were just having a little fun weren't you girls
Blonde Mermaid : That's all
Redhead Mermaid : We were only trying to drown her
Peter Pan : Ya see
Wendy Darling : Well if you think for one minute that I'm going to put up with a
Peter Pan : Shh Hold it Wendy
Peter Pan : Yep it's Hook
Blonde Mermaid : Hook
Redhead Mermaid : Hook
Mermaids : Hook Oh
Peter Pan : Quick Wendy
Peter Pan : They've captured Tiger Lily
Peter Pan : Looks like they're headin for Skull Rock Come on Wendy
Peter Pan : Let's see what they're up to
Captain Hook : Now me dear princess this is me proposition
Captain Hook : You tell me the hiding place of Peter Pan and I shall set you free
Peter Pan : You dog Poor Tiger Lily
Captain Hook : Am I not a man of me word Mr Smee
Mr. Smee : Oh yes Always captain
Captain Hook : You'd better talk me dear for soon the tide will be in and then it will be too late
Peter Pan : I'll show the old codfish
Peter Pan : Stay here and watch the fun
Wendy Darling : Fun
Captain Hook : Remember there is no path through water to the happy hunting ground
Captain Hook : This is your last chance Tiger Lily
Peter Pan : Manatoa great spirit of mighty seawater speak
Peter Pan : Beware Captain Hook
Peter Pan : Beware Beware
Captain Hook : Did you hear that Smee
Mr. Smee : It's an evil spirit captain
Captain Hook : Stand by Smee while I take a look around
Captain Hook : Spirit of the great seawater is it
Peter Pan : Psst Wendy Watch this
Peter Pan : Mr Smee
Mr. Smee : Uh yes captain
Peter Pan : Release the princess and take her back to her people
Mr. Smee : Aye aye sir Release the princess
Mr. Smee : But but captain
Peter Pan : Those are me orders Mr Smee
Mr. Smee : Aye aye sir
Mr. Smee : Captain Hook's comin to his senses
Captain Hook : Odd's fish
Mr. Smee : I told him you Indians wouldn't betray Peter Pan But
Captain Hook : And just what do you think you are doing Mr Smee
Mr. Smee : Just what you told me captain Carryin out your orders
Captain Hook : My orders
Mr. Smee : Why yes captain Didn't you just say to go
Captain Hook : Put her back You blithering idiot
Peter Pan : Mr Smee
Peter Pan : Just exactly what do you think you are doing
Mr. Smee : Putting her back like you said captain
Peter Pan : I said nothing of the sort
Mr. Smee : But captain didn't you I thought that
Peter Pan : For the last time Mr Smee
Peter Pan : take the princess back to her people
Peter Pan : Understand
Mr. Smee : Aye aye sir
Peter Pan : Oh And one more thing
Peter Pan : When you return to the ship tell the whole crew
Peter Pan : to help themselves to me best rum
Wendy Darling : Huh Peter
Captain Hook : Here's your spirit Smee
Mr. Smee : Why it's Peter Pan
Wendy Darling : Whew
Captain Hook : Scurvy brat
Peter Pan : Thank you captain
Captain Hook : Come down boy if you've a taste for cold steel
Peter Pan : Watch this Wendy
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter do be careful
Peter Pan : Try your luck Mr Smee
Captain Hook : Let him have it
Captain Hook : Well come on you idiot Blast him
Peter Pan : Right here Mr Smee
Captain Hook : Hold it you fool No No
Mr. Smee : Captain
Wendy Darling : Oh how dreadful
Peter Pan : What a pity Mr Smee I'm afraid we've lost the dear captain
Mr. Smee : Captain
Peter Pan : In the back captain
Mr. Smee : Give it to him captain Cleave him to the brisket
Captain Hook : I've got you this time Pan
Peter Pan : Well well a codfish on a hook
Captain Hook : I'll get you for this Pan if it's the last thing I do
Peter Pan : I say captain do you hear something
Captain Hook : No
Peter Pan : Oh Mr Crocodile do you like codfish
Peter Pan : You do
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter no
Captain Hook : No
Captain Hook : Smee
Mr. Smee : D don't go away captain
Mr. Smee : Stay right there now sir I'll save ya sir
Captain Hook : Smee
Captain Hook : Ow
Mr. Smee : Captain Captain
Captain Hook : Smee Smee
Captain Hook : Give him back Smee
Captain Hook : Row for the ship Row for the shi
Captain Hook : Smee
Wendy Darling : Peter what about Tiger Lily
Peter Pan : Tiger Lily Oh Tiger Lily
Tiger Lily : Help
Wendy Darling : Peter Wait for me
Captain Hook : That cursed Peter Pan
Captain Hook : Making a fool out of me
Captain Hook : I sh I sh Whew
Captain Hook : Ahchoo
Captain Hook : Oh my head
Pirate1 : Oh a pirate's life is a wonderful life
Pirate1 : Your hot water Mr Smee
Mr. Smee : Shh
Mr. Smee : The poor captain has a splitting headache
Mr. Smee : We mustn't annoy him
Mr. Smee : Well captain it's nice to see you smilin again
Mr. Smee : Brings back the good old days when we was leadin a healthy normal life
Mr. Smee : Scuttlin ships cuttin throats
Mr. Smee : Oh captain why don't we put to sea again
Mr. Smee : You know there's trouble brewin on the island
Mr. Smee : Women trouble
Mr. Smee : I wouldn't want this to go any farther
Mr. Smee : but the cook told me that the first mate told him
Mr. Smee : that he heard that Pan has banished Tinker Bell
Captain Hook : Whoa
Captain Hook : Why you doddering imbecile I
Captain Hook : Did you say Pan has banished Tinker Bell
Mr. Smee : Aye aye captain That he has
Captain Hook : But why
Mr. Smee : Well on account of Wendy captain
Mr. Smee : Tink tried to do her in she did Tink's terrible jealous
Captain Hook : Well well That's why we ought to leave captain
Mr. Smee : This ain't no place for a respectable pirate
Captain Hook : That's it Smee That's it
Mr. Smee : I'm glad you agrees captain
Captain Hook : Quick me coat Me best dress coat
Mr. Smee : Aye aye sir The sooner we gets going the better
Captain Hook : Ah yes a jealous female can be tricked into anything
Captain Hook : My case of hooks
Mr. Smee : Aye aye sir
Mr. Smee : Here you are sir Your Sunday set
Captain Hook : If we impress the pixie convince her we're eager to help her
Captain Hook : the wench may chart our course
Captain Hook : to a certain hiding place
Mr. Smee : Our best hiding place is the Spanish main sir I'll set our course
Captain Hook : And where do you think you are going
Mr. Smee : To tell the boys we sails with the tide sir
Captain Hook : You will go ashore pick up Tinker Bell and bring her to me
Captain Hook : Understand?
Mr. Smee : Aye aye sir
Indian Chief : How
Peter Pan : How
Wendy Darling : What's the chief doing John
John Darling : He's delivering an oration in sign language
Michael Darling : What's he saying
John Darling : He says Peter Pan mighty warrior
John Darling : Save Tiger Lily
John Darling : Make big chief heap glad
Wendy Darling : Well he certainly doesn't look heap glad
Indian Chief : Make Peter Pan heap big chief
Indian Chief : You now Little Flying Eagle
The Lost Boys : Hurray Flying Eagle
The Lost Boys;Wendy Darling;John Darling;Michael Darling : Bravo Bravo
Wendy Darling : Oh how wonderful
Michael Darling : Hurray!
Indian Chief : Teach em paleface brother all about red man
John Darling : Good this should be most enlightening
Curly : Hey what makes the red man red
The Twins : When did he first say Ugh
Michael Darling : Why does he ask you How
Indian Chief : Why does he ask you How
Indians : Why does he ask you How
Indians : Once the Injun didn't know all the things that he know now
Indians : But the Injun he sure learn a lot
Indians : And it's all from asking how
Indians : We translate for you
Indians : Hana means what mana means and ganda means that too
Indian Woman : Squaw no dance
Indian Woman : Squaw get em firewood
Indians : When did he first say Ugh
Indians : In the Injun book it say when first brave married squaw
Indians : He gave out with heap big ugh when he saw his motherinlaw
Indians : What made the red man red
Indians : Let's go back a million years to the very first Injun prince
Indians : He kissed a maid and start to blush and we've all been blushin since
Indians : Now you've got it right from the head man
Indians : The real true story of the red man
Indians : No matter what's been written or said
Indians : Now you know why the red man's red
John Darling : Wahoo
Michael Darling : Squaw take em papoose
Michael Darling : Wahoo
Wendy Darling : Michael
Indian Woman : Squaw get em firewood
Wendy Darling : Squaw no get em firewood
Wendy Darling : Squaw go home
Mr. Smee : Beggin your pardon Miss Bell but Captain Hook'd like a word with ya
Captain Hook : Yes Miss Bell Captain Hook admits defeat
Captain Hook : Tomorrow I leave the island never to return
Mr. Smee : Glad to hear that captain I'll tell the crew and
Captain Hook : And that's why I asked you over me dear to tell Peter I bear him no ill will
Captain Hook : Oh Pan has his faults to be sure
Captain Hook : Bringing that Wendy to the island for instance
Captain Hook : Dangerous business that
Captain Hook : Why rumour has it that already she has come between you and Peter
Captain Hook : But what's this
Captain Hook : Tears
Captain Hook : Then it is true
Captain Hook : Oh Smee The way of a man with a maid
Captain Hook : Taking the best years of her life and then
Captain Hook : casting her aside
Captain Hook : like an old glove
Mr. Smee : Ain't it a bloomin shame
Captain Hook : But we mustn't judge Peter too harshly me dear
Captain Hook : It's that Wendy who's to blame
Captain Hook : Mr Smee we must save the lad from himself
Captain Hook : But how
Captain Hook : We've so little time We sail in the morning
Captain Hook : Sail
Captain Hook : That's it Smee
Captain Hook : We'll shanghai Wendy
Captain Hook : Shanghai Wendy captain
Captain Hook : Take her to sea with us
Captain Hook : With her gone Peter will soon forget this mad infatuation
Captain Hook : Come Smee we must leave immediately Surround Peter's home
Mr. Smee : But captain We don't know where Peter Pan lives
Captain Hook : Great Scott you're right Smee
Captain Hook : What's that my dear
Captain Hook : You could show us the way Why I never thought of that
Captain Hook : Take this down Smee
Mr. Smee : Take this down Smee
Mr. Smee : Aye aye captain
Captain Hook : Start at Pegleg Point
Mr. Smee : Start at Pegleg Point
Captain Hook : Forty paces west of Blindman's Bluff
Mr. Smee : Blindman's Bluff
Captain Hook : Yes yes
Captain Hook : Hop skip and a jump across Crocodile Creek
Captain Hook : nor by nor'east one two three
Captain Hook : Well get on with Continue my dear
Captain Hook : I mustn't harm Peter
Captain Hook : Madam Captain Hook gives his word not to lay a finger
Captain Hook : or a hook on Peter Pan
Captain Hook : Ah Hangman's Tree
Captain Hook : So that's the entrance to his hiding place
Captain Hook : Thank you me dear You've been most helpful
Michael Darling : What makes red men red
Peter Pan : Big Chief Flying Eagle greets his braves
Peter Pan : How
The Lost Boys : How chief how
John Darling : How
Michael Darling : How
Peter Pan : Big chief greets little mother
Peter Pan : How
Wendy Darling : Ugh
Peter Pan : Aw Wendy is that all you have to say
Peter Pan : Everyone else thinks I'm wonderful
Wendy Darling : Especially Tiger Lily
Peter Pan : Tiger Lily
Wendy Darling : John
Wendy Darling : Michael Take off that war paint and get ready for bed
John Darling : Bed
Michael Darling : Brave no sleep
Michael Darling : Go for days without sleep
Wendy Darling : But boys we're going home in the morning
John Darling;Michael Darling : Home
Michael Darling : And Oh Wendy we don't want to go home
Peter Pan : No go home Stay many moons Have heap big time
Wendy Darling : Now Peter let's stop pretending and be practical
Peter Pan : Chief Flying Eagle has spoken
Wendy Darling : Oh for goodness sake Please boys
Wendy Darling : Do you want to stay here and grow up like like savages
Michael Darling : Of course
Wendy Darling : But you can't You need a mother
Wendy Darling : We all do
Michael Darling : Aren't you our mother Wendy
Wendy Darling : Michael of course not Surely you haven't forgotten our real mother
Michael Darling : Did she have silky ears
Michael Darling : and wear a fur coat
Wendy Darling : Oh no Michael That was Nana
Curly : I think I had a mother once
The Twins : What was she like
Curly : I forgot
Slightly : I had a white rat
Curly : That's no mother
Slightly : Hey who ya shovin
Wendy Darling : No no boys Please I'll tell you what a mother is
The Twins : Yeah tell us Please Wendy
Wendy Darling : Well a mother a real mother
Wendy Darling : is the most wonderful person in the world
Wendy Darling : She's the angel voice
Wendy Darling : that bids you good night
Wendy Darling : kisses your cheek
Wendy Darling : whispers Sleep tight
Wendy Darling : Your mother And mine
Wendy Darling : The helping hand that guides you along
Wendy Darling : Whether you're right
Wendy Darling : Whether you're wrong
Wendy Darling : Your mother And mine
Wendy Darling : What makes mothers all that they are
Wendy Darling : Might as well ask
Wendy Darling : What makes a star
Wendy Darling : Ask your heart to tell you her worth
Wendy Darling : Your heart will say
Wendy Darling : Heaven on earth
Wendy Darling : Another word
Wendy Darling : For divine
Wendy Darling : Your mother And mine
Michael Darling : I wanna see my mother
Wendy Darling : Yes Michael
John Darling : I propose we leave for home at once
Curly : Could I go too Wendy
The Twins : Me too Wendy
Wendy Darling : All right boys All right I'm sure Mother would be glad to have you
Wendy Darling : Uh that is if Peter doesn't mind
Peter Pan : Go on Go back and grow up
Peter Pan : But I'm warning ya once you're grown up
Peter Pan : you can never come back
Peter Pan : Never
Wendy Darling : Oh dear
John Darling : Well then shall we be off
Curly : Yeah come on Let's go
The Lost Boys : Yeah See ya Peter
Peter Pan : They'll be back
Wendy Darling : Peter
Wendy Darling : Goodbye Peter
Captain Hook : All right men Take them away
Captain Hook : And now Smee to take care of Master Peter Pan
Mr. Smee : But captain wouldn't it be more humanelike to  slit his throat
Captain Hook : Aye that it would Mr Smee
Captain Hook : But I have given me word not to lay a finger
Captain Hook : or a hook on Peter Pan
Captain Hook : And Captain Hook never breaks a promise
Pirates : Yo ho yo ho Yo ho yo ho yo ho
Pirates : So try the life of a thief
Pirates : Just sample the life of a crook
Pirates : There isn't a boy who won't enjoy Aworkin for Captain Hook
Pirates : The world's most famous crook
Mr. Smee : Crook crook Crickety crockety crickety crick The croc is after Captain
Captain Hook : A special offer for today I'll tell you what I'll do
Captain Hook : All those who sign without delay Will get a free tattoo
Captain Hook : Why it's like money in the bank
Captain Hook : Come on join up and I'll be frank
Captain Hook : Unless you do you'll walk the plank
Captain Hook : The choice is up to you
Pirates : The choice is up to you
Pirates : Yo ho yo ho Yo ho yo ho yo ho
Pirates : You'll love the life of a thief
Pirates : You'll relish the life of a crook
Pirates : There's barrels of fun for everyone And you'll get treasures by the ton
Pirates : So come and sign the book
Pirates : Join up with Captain Hook
The Lost Boys : I wanna be a pirate
The Lost Boys : Oh boy A pirate
Wendy Darling : Boys
Wendy Darling : Aren't you ashamed of yourselves
John Darling : But Captain Hook is most insistent Wendy
Curly : Yeah He says we'll walk the plank if we don't
Wendy Darling : Oh no we won't Peter Pan will save us
Captain Hook : Peter Pan will save them Smee
Mr. Smee : Peter Pan will save them
Mr. Smee : Oh captain you did it
Captain Hook : But a thousand pardons my dear
Captain Hook : I don't believe you are in on our little joke
Captain Hook : You see we left a present for Peter
Mr. Smee : Sort of a surprise package you might say
Captain Hook : Why I can see our little friend at this very moment
Captain Hook : reading the tender inscription
Peter Pan : To Peter with love from Wendy
Peter Pan : Do not open till 6. 00
Peter Pan : Ha
Peter Pan : I wonder what's in it
Captain Hook : Could he but see within the package he would find an ingenious little device
Mr. Smee : Set so that when the clock is like this
Captain Hook : Peter Pan will be blasted out of Never Land forever
Captain Hook : But time grows short
Captain Hook : We have but 18 seconds
Captain Hook : Fifteen seconds
Captain Hook : Thirteen seconds
Peter Pan : Twelve seconds
Peter Pan : Well I guess I can open it now
Peter Pan : Hey Tink Look what Wendy left
Peter Pan : Hey stop that Stop it What's the matter with you
Peter Pan : Hook A bomb
Peter Pan : Don't be ridiculous
Captain Hook : And so passeth a worthy opponent
Mr. Smee : Amen
Peter Pan : Hook It was a bomb
Peter Pan : Why if it hadn't been for Tink... Tinker Bell
Peter Pan : Tink Tinker Bell
Peter Pan : Where are you Tink
Peter Pan : Tink Are you all right
Peter Pan : Wendy The boys
Peter Pan : But I've gotta save you first Hold on Tink Hold on
Peter Pan : Don't go out Don't you understand Tink
Peter Pan : You mean more to me than anything in this whole world
Captain Hook : And now which will it be The pen or the plank
Wendy Darling : Captain Hook we will never join your crew
Captain Hook : As you wish Ladies first me dear
Wendy Darling : Goodbye boys
The Lost Boys : Goodbye Wendy
Wendy Darling : Be brave John
John Darling : I shall strive to Wendy
Wendy Darling : Goodbye Michael
Michael Darling : Goodbye
Pirate1 : Come on Get along over there
Pirate2 : Get going Don't give us no trouble
Pirate2 : Go on Go on Get it over with
Pirate2 : Move along The captain's waitin
Michael Darling : Wendy Wendy
Mr. Smee : Captain no splash
Captain Hook : Not a sound
Pirate3 : Not a bloomin ripple
Pirate4 : It's a jinx that's what it is
Pirate5 : No splash No sign of the wench
Pirate5 : Did you hear a splash
Pirate4 : I'm telling you mates it's a black day
Pirate4 : Mark me words We'll all pay for this
Pirate3 : No splash captain
Captain Hook : So you want a splash Mr Starkey
Captain Hook : I'll give you a splash
Captain Hook : Who's next
Peter Pan : You're next Hook
Peter Pan : This time you've gone too far
The Lost Boys : It's Pan Peter Pan
Michael Darling : And Wendy
Captain Hook : It can't be
Mr. Smee : It's his blinkin ghost what's talkin
Peter Pan : Say your prayers Hook
Captain Hook : I'll show you this ghost has blood in his veins
Captain Hook : I'll run him through
Captain Hook : Take that
Captain Hook : Curse this hook
Peter Pan : Come on everybody
John Darling : Hurry Michael Hurry
Captain Hook : Don't stand there you bilge rats
Captain Hook : Get those scurvy brats
Pirate1 : After the brats men
Captain Hook : This is no mere boy
Captain Hook : Tis some fiend fighting me A flying devil
John Darling : Hold your fire
John Darling : Steady men Steady
Pirate2 : Club em with the marline
Pirate3 : I'll crack their bloomin skulls
Pirate4 : Let me at em
John Darling : Down you blackguard
Michael Darling : Right through Michael
Curly : Yea Bear Killer
Captain Hook : Fly Fly Fly You coward
Peter Pan : Coward Me
Captain Hook : You wouldn't dare fight old Hook mantoman
Captain Hook : You'd fly away like a cowardly sparrow
Peter Pan : Nobody calls Pan a coward and lives
Peter Pan : I'll fight you mantoman one hand behind my back
Captain Hook : You mean you won't fly
Wendy Darling : No don't Peter It's a trick
Peter Pan : I give my word Hook
Captain Hook : Good then let's have at it
Captain Hook : Insolent youth prepare to die
Wendy Darling : Fly Fly Peter Fly
Peter Pan : No I gave my word
Peter Pan : You're mine Hook
Michael Darling : Cleave him to the brisket
Captain Hook : You wouldn't do old Hook in now would you lad
Captain Hook : I'll go away forever I'll do anything you say
Peter Pan : Well all right If ya say you're a codfish
Captain Hook : I'm a codfish
Peter Pan : Louder
All : Hurray
All : Hook is a codfish a codfish a codfish
All : Hook is a codfish
Peter Pan : All right Hook
Peter Pan : you're free to go and never return
Wendy Darling : Peter
Captain Hook : Smee Smee
Captain Hook : Smee
Mr. Smee : Captain
Mr. Smee : Captain Captain
All : Hurray
All : Hurray for Captain Pan
Peter Pan : All right ya swabs aloft with ya
Peter Pan : We're castin off Heave those halyards
Wendy Darling : But but Peter Oh that is Captain Pan
Peter Pan : At your service madam
Wendy Darling : Could you tell me sir where we're sailing
Peter Pan : To London madam
Wendy Darling : Oh Peter
Wendy Darling : Michael John We're going home
Peter Pan : Man the capstan
Peter Pan : Hoist anchor
Peter Pan : Pixie dust
Mrs. Darling : George I'm so glad you changed your mind about Wendy
Mrs. Darling : After all she's still a child
Mr. Darling : Mary you know I never mean those things
Mr. Darling : Do I Nana
Mrs. Darling : Oh
Mrs. Darling : Wendy
Mrs. Darling : Wendy what on earth are you doing there
Wendy Darling : Hmm
Wendy Darling : Oh Mother we're back
Mr. Darling : Back
Wendy Darling : All except the Lost Boys They weren't quite ready
Mr. Darling : Lost bo Ready
Wendy Darling : To grow up
Wendy Darling : That's why they went back to Never Land
Mr. Darling : Never Land
Wendy Darling : Yes but I am
Mr. Darling : Am
Wendy Darling : Ready to grow up
Mr. Darling : Oh Oh
Mr. Darling : Well my dear all in good time
Mr. Darling : After all perhaps we were too
Wendy Darling : Oh but Mother
Wendy Darling : it was such a wonderful adventure
Wendy Darling : Tinker Bell and the mermaids and Peter Pan
Wendy Darling : Oh he was the most wonderful of all
Wendy Darling : Why even when we were kidnapped
Mr. Darling : Kidnapped
Wendy Darling : Mmhmm I knew Peter Pan would save us and he did
Wendy Darling : And we all called him a codfish
Wendy Darling : Captain Hook I mean
Wendy Darling : And then we sailed away on a ship in the sky
Mr. Darling : Mary I'm going to bed
Wendy Darling : Oh Mother He really is wonderful isn't he
Wendy Darling : See how well he sails the ship
Mrs. Darling : George George
Mr. Darling : Now what Mary
Mr. Darling : Nana did you see
Mr. Darling : You know I have the strangest feeling that I've seen that ship before
Mr. Darling : A long time ago
Mr. Darling : when I was very young
Mrs. Darling : George dear Father
All : When there's a smile in your heart
All : There's no better time to start
Women Ensemble : Think of all the joy you'll find
Women Ensemble : When you leave the world behind
All : And bid your cares goodbye
All : You can fly