Flynn : This is the story of how I died
Flynn : But don't worry this is a fun story and the truth is it isn't even mine
Flynn : This is the story of a girl named Rapunzel
Flynn : And it starts with the sun
Flynn : Once upon a time a single drop of sunlight fell from the heavens
Flynn : And from this small drop of sun grew a magic golden flower
Flynn : It had the ability to heal the sick and injured
Flynn : Oh you see that old woman over there
Flynn : You might want to remember her
Flynn : She's kind of important
Flynn : Centuries passed and a hop skip and a boat ride away there grew a kingdom
Flynn : The kingdom was ruled by a beloved king and queen
Flynn : And the queen was about to have a baby
Flynn : But she got sick
Flynn : Really sick
Flynn : She was running out of time and that's when people start to look for a miracle
Flynn : Or in this case a magic golden flower
Flynn : Ah I told you she'd be important
Flynn : Instead of sharing the sun's gift
Flynn : this woman Mother Gothel hoarded its healing power and used it to keep herself young for hundreds of years
Flynn : And all she had to do was sing a special song
Gothel : Flower gleam and glow
Gothel : Let your power shine
Gothel : Make the clock reverse
Gothel : Bring back what once was mine
Gothel : What once was mine
Flynn : Alright You get the gist She sings to it she turns young Creepy right
Soldiers : We found it
Flynn : The magic of the golden flower healed the queen
Flynn : A healthy baby girl a princess was born with beautiful golden hair
Flynn : I'll give you a hint that's Rapunzel
Flynn : To celebrate her birth the king and queen launched a flying lantern into the sky
Flynn : And for that one moment everything was perfect
Flynn : And then that moment ended
Gothel : Flower gleam and glow
Gothel : Let your power shine
Gothel : Make the clock re...
Flynn : Gothel broke into the castle stole the child and just like that gone
Flynn : The kingdom searched and searched but they could not find the princess
Flynn : For deep within the forest in a hidden tower
Flynn : Gothel raised the child as her own
Baby Rapunzel : Save what has been lost
Baby Rapunzel : Bring back what once was mine
Baby Rapunzel : What once was mine
Flynn : Gothel had found her new magic flower
Flynn : but this time she was determined to keep it hidden
Baby Rapunzel : Why can't I go outside
Gothel : The outside world is a dangerous place filled with horrible selfish people
Gothel : You must stay here where you're safe
Gothel : Do you understand flower
Baby Rapunzel : Yes Mommy
Flynn : But the walls of that tower could not hide everything
Flynn : Each year on her birthday the king and queen released thousands of lanterns into the sky
Flynn : in hope that one day their lost princess would return
Rapunzel : Ha
Rapunzel : Hmm Well I guess Pascal's not hiding out here
Rapunzel : Gotcha
Rapunzel : That's 22 for me How about 23 out of 45
Rapunzel : Okay Well what do you want to do
Rapunzel : Yeah I don't think so I like it in here and so do you
Rapunzel : Oh come on Pascal It's not so bad in there
Rapunzel : Seven a.m. the usual morning lineup
Rapunzel : Start on the chores and sweep till the floor's all clean
Rapunzel : Polish and wax do laundry and mop and shine up
Rapunzel : Sweep again and by then it's like seven fifteen
Rapunzel : And so I'll read a book or maybe two or three
Rapunzel : I'll add a few new paintings to my gallery
Rapunzel : I'll play guitar and knit and cook and basically
Rapunzel : Just wonder when will my life begin
Rapunzel : Then after lunch it's puzzles and darts and baking
Rapunzel : Papiermâché a bit of ballet and chess
Rapunzel : Pottery and ventriloquy candlemaking
Rapunzel : Then I'll stretch maybe sketch take a climb sew a dress
Rapunzel : And I'll reread the books if I have time to spare
Rapunzel : I'll paint the walls some more I'm sure there's room somewhere
Rapunzel : And then I'll brush and brush and brush and brush my hair
Rapunzel : Stuck in the same place I've always been
Rapunzel : And I'll keep wondering and wondering and wondering and wondering
Rapunzel : When will my life begin
Rapunzel : Tomorrow night
Rapunzel : The lights will appear
Rapunzel : Just like they do
Rapunzel : On my birthday each year
Rapunzel : What is it like
Rapunzel : Out there where they glow
Rapunzel : Now that I'm older
Rapunzel : Mother might just let me go
Flynn : Wow I could get used to a view like this
Stabbington Brothers : Rider, come on!
Flynn : Hold on Yep I'm used to it Guys I want a castle
Stabbington Brothers : We do this job you can buy your own castle
Flynn : Hay fever?
Soldier : Yeah
Soldier : Huh
Soldier : Wait wait Hey wait
Flynn : Can't you picture me in a castle of my own Because I certainly can
Flynn : All the things we've seen and it's only eight in the morning
Flynn : Gentlemen this is a very big day
Rapunzel : This is it This is a very big day Pascal
Rapunzel : I'm finally going to do it I'm going to ask her
Gothel : Rapunzel
Gothel : Let down your hair
Rapunzel : It's time
Rapunzel : I know I know Come on Don't let her see you
Gothel : I'm not getting any younger down here
Rapunzel : Coming Mother
Rapunzel : Hi Welcome home Mother
Gothel : Uh Rapunzel how you manage to do that
Gothel : every single day without fail
Gothel : It looks absolutely exhausting darling
Rapunzel : Oh it's nothing
Gothel : Then I don't know why it takes so long
Gothel : Oh darling I'm just teasing
Rapunzel : All right
Rapunzel : So Mother as you know tomorrow is a very big day
Gothel : Rapunzel look in that mirror
Gothel : You know what I see
Gothel : I see a strong confident beautiful young lady
Gothel : Oh look you're here too
Gothel : I'm just teasing Stop taking everything so seriously
Rapunzel : Okay So Mother as I was saying tomorrow is
Gothel : Rapunzel Mother's feeling a little rundown
Gothel : Would you sing for me dear Then we'll talk
Rapunzel : Oh Of course Mother
Rapunzel : Flower gleam and glow Let your power shine Make
Rapunzel : the clock reverse Bring back what once was mine
Rapunzel : Heal what has been hurt Change the Fates design Save what has been lost Bring back what once was mine
Gothel : Rapunzel
Rapunzel : So Mother earlier I was saying tomorrow is a big day and you didn't respond
Rapunzel : So I'm just going to tell you it's my birthday
Rapunzel : Tada
Gothel : No no no Can't be
Gothel : I distinctly remember Your birthday was last year
Rapunzel : That's the funny thing about birthdays They're kind of an annual thing
Rapunzel : Mother I'm turning 18 and I wanted to ask
Rapunzel : What I really want for this birthday
Rapunzel : Actually what I wanted for quite a few birthdays now
Gothel : Rapunzel please stop with the mumbling
Gothel : You know how I feel about the mumbling Blahblahblahblah
Gothel : It's very annoying I'm just teasing You're adorable I love you so much darling
Rapunzel : I want to see the floating lights
Gothel : What
Rapunzel : Oh.. well I was hoping you would take me to see the floating lights
Gothel : Oh You mean the stars
Rapunzel : That's the thing
Rapunzel : I've charted stars and they're always constant
Rapunzel : But these they appear every year on my birthday Mother
Rapunzel : Only on my birthday
Rapunzel : And I can't help but feel like they're meant for me
Rapunzel : I need to see them Mother And not just from my window in person
Rapunzel : I have to know what they are
Gothel : You want to go outside Why Rapunzel
Gothel : Look at you as fragile as a flower
Gothel : Still a little sapling just a sprout
Gothel : You know why we stay up in this tower
Rapunzel : I know but
Gothel : That's right
Gothel : To keep you safe and sound dear
Gothel : Guess I always knew this day was coming
Gothel : Knew that soon you'd want to leave the nest
Gothel : Soon but not yet
Rapunzel : But...
Gothel : Shh Trust me pet
Gothel : Mother knows best
Gothel : Mother knows best Listen to your mother
Gothel : It's a scary world out there
Gothel : Mother knows best One way or another something will go wrong I swear
Gothel : Ruffians thugs poison ivy quicksand
Gothel : Cannibals and snakes the plague
Rapunzel : No!
Gothel : Yes.
Rapunzel : But...
Gothel : Also large bugs
Gothel : Men with pointy teeth And stop No more you'll just upset me
Gothel : Mother's right here Mother will protect you
Gothel : Darling here's what I suggest
Gothel : Skip the drama Stay with Mama
Gothel : Mother knows best
Gothel : Mother knows best Take it from your mumsy
Gothel : On your own you won't survive
Gothel : Sloppy underdressed Immature clumsy Please they'll eat you up alive
Gothel : Gullible naive Positively grubby
Gothel : Ditsy and a bit well hmm vague
Gothel : Plus I believe getting kind of chubby
Gothel : I'm just saying cause I wuv you
Gothel : Mother understands Mother's here to help you
Gothel : All I have is one request
Gothel : Rapunzel
Rapunzel : Yes
Gothel : Don't ever ask to leave this tower again
Rapunzel : Yes Mother
Gothel : Oh
Gothel : I love you very much dear
Rapunzel : I love you more
Gothel : I love you most
Gothel : Don't forget it
Gothel : You'll regret it
Gothel : Mother knows best
Gothel : Tata I'll see you in a bit my flower
Rapunzel : I'll be here
Flynn : Oh no
Flynn : No no no no no This is bad This is very very bad This is really bad
Flynn : They just can't get my nose right
The Stabbington Brothers : Who cares
Flynn : It's easy for you to say You guys look amazing
Flynn : All right Okay Give me a boost and I'll pull you up
The Stabbington Brothers : Give us the satchel first
Flynn : What
Flynn : I just
Flynn : I can't believe that after all we've been through together you don't trust me
Ouch
The Stabbington Brothers : Now help us up pretty boy
Flynn : Sorry my hands are full
The Stabbington Brothers : What
Flynn : Rider
General : Retrieve that satchel at any cost
Soldiers : Yes sir
General : We got him now Maximus
Flynn : Come on fleabag Forward
Flynn : No No
Flynn : Stop it Stop it Give it to me Give me that
Flynn : Ha
Flynn : Alone at last
Rapunzel : Huh
Rapunzel : Hmm
Rapunzel : Okay okay okay I've got a person in my closet
Rapunzel : I've got a person in my closet
Rapunzel : Too weak to handle myself out there huh Mother
Rapunzel : Well tell that to my frying pan
Rapunzel : Huh
Rapunzel : Hmm
Gothel : Rapunzel
Rapunzel : Oh
Gothel : Let down your hair
Rapunzel : One moment Mother
Gothel : I have a big surprise
Rapunzel : Uh I do too
Gothel : Ooh I bet my surprise is bigger
Rapunzel : I seriously doubt it
Gothel : I brought back parsnips. I'm going to make hazelnut soup for dinner.
Gothel : Your favorite. Surprise!
Rapunzel : Well Mother there's something I want to tell you
Gothel : Oh Rapunzel you know I hate leaving you after a fight Especially when I've done absolutely nothing wrong
Rapunzel : Ok I've been thinking a lot about what you said earlier
Gothel : I hope you're not still talking about the stars
Rapunzel : Floating lights and yes I'm leading up to that
Gothel : Because I really thought we dropped the issue sweetheart
Rapunzel : No Mother I'm just saying you think I'm not strong enough to handle myself out there
Gothel : Oh darling I know you're not strong enough to handle yourself out there
Rapunzel : But if you just
Gothel : Rapunzel We're done talking about this
Rapunzel : Trust me
Gothel : Rapunzel
Rapunzel : I know what I'm
Rapunzel : Oh come on
Gothel : Enough with the lights Rapunzel
Gothel : You are not leaving this tower! Ever!
Gothel : Oh Great. Now I'm the bad guy
Rapunzel : All I was going to say, Mother, is that…
Rapunzel : I know what I want for my birthday now
Gothel : And what is that
Rapunzel : New paint
Rapunzel : The paint made from the white shells you once brought me
Gothel : That is a very long trip, Rapunzel. Almost three days' time.
Rapunzel : I just thought it was a better idea than the stars
Gothel : You'll be all right on your own
Rapunzel : I know I'm safe as long as I'm here
Gothel : I'll be back in three days' time
Gothel : I love you very much dear
Rapunzel : I love you more
Gothel : I love you most
Rapunzel : Okay
Rapunzel : Huh
Flynn : Huh uh what
Flynn : Is this hair
Rapunzel : Struggling Struggling is pointless
Flynn : Huh
Rapunzel : I know why you're here and I'm not afraid of you
Flynn : What
Rapunzel : Who are you And how did you find me
Flynn : Uhuh
Rapunzel : Who are you and how did you find me
Flynn : I know not who you are nor how I came to find you
Flynn : But may I just say…
Flynn : Hi
Flynn : How you doing The name's Flynn Rider
Flynn : How's your day going Huh
Rapunzel : Who else knows my location Flynn Rider
Flynn : All right blondie
Rapunzel : Rapunzel
Flynn : Gesundheit Here's the deal
Flynn : I was in a situation gallivanting through the forest
Flynn : I came across your tower and
Flynn : Oh Oh no Where is my satchel
Rapunzel : I've hidden it Somewhere you'll never find it
Flynn : It's in that pot isn't it
Flynn : Huh
Flynn : Would you stop that
Rapunzel : Now it's hidden where you'll never find it
Rapunzel : So what do you want with my hair To cut it
Flynn : What
Rapunzel : Sell it
Flynn : No Listen the only thing I want to do with your hair is to get out of it literally
Rapunzel : You Wait You don't want my hair
Flynn : Why on earth would I want your hair
Flynn : Look I was being chased I saw a tower I climbed it End of story
Rapunzel : You're telling the truth
Flynn : Yes
Rapunzel : Hmm
Rapunzel : I know I need someone to take me
Rapunzel : I think he's telling the truth too
Rapunzel : He doesn't have fangs But what choice do I have
Rapunzel : Okay Flynn Rider I'm prepared to offer you a deal
Flynn : Deal
Rapunzel : Look this way
Rapunzel : Do you know what these are
Flynn : You mean the lantern thing they do for the princess
Rapunzel : Lanterns I knew they weren't stars
Rapunzel : Well tomorrow evening they will light the night sky with these lanterns
Rapunzel : You will act as my guide take me to these lanterns
Rapunzel : and return me home safely Then and only then will I return your satchel to you
Rapunzel : That is my deal
Flynn : Yeah
Flynn : No can do
Flynn : Unfortunately the kingdom and I aren't exactly simpatico at the moment
Flynn : so I won't be taking you anywhere
Rapunzel : Something brought you here Flynn Rider
Rapunzel : Call it what you will fate destiny
Flynn : A horse
Rapunzel : So I have made the decision to trust you
Flynn : A horrible decision really
Rapunzel : But trust me when I tell you this
Rapunzel : You can tear this tower apart brick by brick
Rapunzel : but without my help you will never find your precious satchel
Flynn : Let me get this straight
Flynn : I take you to see the lanterns bring you back home and you'll give me back my satchel
Rapunzel : I promise
Rapunzel : And when I promise something I never ever break that promise
Rapunzel : Ever
Flynn : All right listen I didn't want to have to do this but you leave me no choice
Flynn : Here comes the smolder
Flynn : This is kind of an off day for me This doesn't normally happen
Flynn : Fine I'll take you to see the lanterns
Rapunzel : Really
Rapunzel : Oops
Flynn : You broke my smolder
Flynn : Are you coming blondie
Rapunzel : Look at the world so close And I'm halfway to it
Rapunzel : Look at it all so big Do I even dare
Rapunzel : Look at me there at last I just have to do it
Rapunzel : Should I No Here I go
Rapunzel : Just smell the grass the dirt Just like I dreamed they'd be
Rapunzel : Just feel that summer breeze The way it's calling me
Rapunzel : For like the first time ever I'm completely free
Rapunzel : I could go running and racing And dancing and chasing
Rapunzel : And leaping and bounding Hair flying heart pounding
Rapunzel : And splashing and reeling and finally feeling
Rapunzel : That's when my life
Rapunzel : begins
Rapunzel : I can't believe I did this
Rapunzel : Mother would be so furious
Rapunzel : But that's okay What she doesn't know won't kill her right
Rapunzel : Oh my gosh This would kill her
Rapunzel : This is so fun
Rapunzel : I am a horrible daughter I'm going back
Rapunzel : I am never going back
Rapunzel : I am a despicable human being
Rapunzel : Best day ever
Flynn : You know I can't help but notice you seem a little at war with yourself here
Rapunzel : What
Flynn : Nah I'm only picking up bits and pieces of course Overprotective mother forbidden road trip
Flynn : I mean This is serious stuff
Flynn : But let me ease your conscience This is part of growing up
Flynn : A little rebellion a little adventure that's good Healthy even
Rapunzel : You think
Flynn : I know You're way overthinking this trust me
Flynn : Does your mother deserve it No
Flynn : Would this break her heart and crush her soul Of course
Flynn : But you've got to do it
Rapunzel : Break her heart?
Flynn : In half
Rapunzel : Crush her soul
Flynn : Like a grape
Rapunzel : She would be heartbroken You're right
Flynn : I am, aren't I? Oh, bother.
Flynn : All right I can't believe I'm saying this but I'm letting you out of the deal
Rapunzel : What
Flynn : That's right but don't thank me
Flynn : Let's turn around and get you home Here's your pan here's your frog
Flynn : I get back my satchel you get back a motherdaughter relationship based on mutual trust and voilà we part ways as unlikely friends
Rapunzel : No I am seeing those lanterns
Flynn : Oh come on What is it going to take for me to get my satchel back
Rapunzel : I will use this
Rapunzel : Is it ruffians Thugs Have they come for me
Flynn : Stay calm It can probably smell fear
Rapunzel : Oh Sorry Guess I'm just a little bit jumpy
Flynn : Probably be best if we avoid ruffians and thugs though
Rapunzel : Yeah that would probably be best
Flynn : Are you hungry I know a great place for lunch
Rapunzel : Where
Flynn : Oh don't you worry You'll know it when you smell it
Gothel : A palace horse
Gothel : Where's your rider
Gothel : Rapunzel.
Gothel : Rapunzel!
Gothel : Rapunzel! Let down your hair!
Gothel : Rapunzel?
Gothel : Rapunzel!
Flynn : I know it's around here somewhere
Flynn : Ah there it is The Snuggly Duckling
Flynn : Don't worry Very quaint place Perfect for you
Flynn : Don't want you scaring and giving up on this whole endeavor now do we
Rapunzel : Well I do like ducklings
Flynn : Yay
Flynn : Garçon your finest table please
Flynn : You smell that Take a deep breath through the nose
Flynn : Really let that seep in What are you getting
Flynn : Because to me it's part mansmell and the other part is really bad mansmell
Flynn : I don't know why but overall it smells like the color brown Your thoughts
Pub Thug1 : That's a lot of hair
Flynn : She's growing it out. Is that blood in your mustache?
Flynn : Goldie look at all the blood in his mustache
Flynn : Good sir, that's a lot of blood!
Flynn : You don't look so good blondie Maybe we should get you home call it a day
Flynn : Probably better off This is a five-star joint after all and if you can't handle this place maybe you should be back in your tower
Pub Thug3 : Is this you
Flynn : Now they're just being mean
Pub Thug4 : It's him all right
Pub Thug4 : Greno go find some guards
Pub Thug4 : That reward is going to buy me a new hook
Pub Thug5 : I could use the money
Pub Thug6 : What about me I'm broke
Pub Thug7 : Get back!
Pub Thug7 : Mine Ruffians
Rapunzel : Stop!
Flynn : We can work this out
Rapunzel : Hey Leave him alone
Flynn : Gentlemen please
Rapunzel : Give me back my guide Ruffians
Flynn : Not the nose Not the nose Not the nose
Rapunzel : Put him down
Rapunzel : I don't know where I am and I need him to take me to see the lanterns because I've been dreaming about them my entire life
Rapunzel : Find your humanity Haven't any of you ever had a dream
Pub Thug2 : I had a dream once
Pub Thug2 : I'm malicious mean and scary
Pub Thug2 : My sneer could curdle dairy
Pub Thug2 : And violencewise my hands are not the cleanest
Pub Thug2 : But despite my evil look and my temper and my hook
Pub Thug2 : I've always yearned to be a concert pianist
Pub Thug2 : Can't you see me on the stage performing Mozart
Pub Thug2 : Tickling the ivories till they gleam
Pub Thug2 : Yep I'd rather be called deadly for my killer show tune medley
Pub Thug2 : Thank you
Pub Thug2 : Cause way down deep inside I've got a dream
Pub Thugs : He's got a dream He's got a dream
Pub Thug2 : See I ain't as cruel and vicious as I seem
Pub Thug2 : Though I do like breaking femurs You can count me with the dreamers
Pub Thug2 : Like everybody else I've got a dream
Pub Thug3 : I've got scars and lumps and bruises plus something here that oozes
Pub Thug3 : And let's not even mention my complexion
Pub Thug3 : But despite my extra toes and my goiter and my nose
Pub Thug3 : I really want to make a love connection
Pub Thug3 : Can't you see me with a special little lady
Pub Thug3 : Rowing in a rowboat down the stream
Pub Thug3 : Though I'm one disgusting blighter I'm a lover not a fighter
Pub Thug3 : Cause way down deep inside I've got a dream
Pub Thug3 : I've got a dream
Pub Thugs : He's got a dream
Pub Thug3 : And I know one day romance will reign supreme
Pub Thug3 : Though my face leaves people screaming There's a child behind it dreaming
Pub Thug3 : Like everybody else I've got a dream
Pub Thug4 : Thor would like to quit and be a florist
Pub Thug5 : Gunther does interior design
Pub Thug6 : Ulf is into mime
Pub Thug7 : Attila's cupcakes are sublime
Pub Thugs : Bruiser knits Killer sews Fang does little puppet shows
Pub Thug2 : And Vladimir collects ceramic unicorns
Pub Thug2 : What about you?
Flynn : I'm sorry, me?
Pub Thug3 : What's your dream?
Flynn : No, no, no. Sorry, boys. I don't sing.
Flynn : I have dreams like you No really
Flynn : Just much less touchy-feely
Flynn : They mainly happen somewhere warm and sunny
Flynn : On an island that I own Tanned and rested and alone
Flynn : Surrounded by enormous piles of money
Rapunzel : I've got a dream
Pub Thugs : She's got a dream
Rapunzel : I just want to see the floating lanterns gleam
Rapunzel : And with every passing hour I'm so glad I left my tower
Rapunzel : Like all you lovely folks I've got a dream
Pub Thugs : She's got a dream He's got a dream They've got a dream We've got a dream
Pub Thugs : So our differences ain't really that extreme
Pub Thugs : We're one big team
Pub Thugs : Call us brutal
Pub Thugs : Sick
Pub Thugs : Sadistic And
Pub Thugs : grotesquely optimistic
Pub Thugs : Cause way down deep inside we've got a dream
Pub Thugs : I've got a dream
Pub Thugs : Yes way down deep inside
Pub Thug7 : I found the guards
General : Where's Rider Where is he
General : I know he's in here somewhere Find him
General : Turn the place upside down if you have to
Pub Thug2 : Go. Live your dream.
Flynn : I will
Pub Thug2 : Your dream stinks
Pub Thug2 : I was talking to her
Rapunzel : Thanks for everything
Pub Thug3 : I believe this is the man you're looking for
Pub Thug8 : You got me
Soldier : Sir there's no sign of Rider
General : Maximus!
Soldier : What's he doing
General : A passage Come on men Let's go
General : Conli! Make sure those boys don't get away.
The Stabbington Brothers : Play it safe
The Stabbington Brothers : or go get the crown?
Pub Thug8 : I got a dream I got some dreams
Pub Thug8 : Oh! Somebody get me a glass!
Pub Thug8 : Because I just found me a tall drink of water.
Gothel : Oh stop it you big lug
Gothel : Where does that tunnel let out
Pub Thug8 : Knife
Flynn : Well I've gotta say I didn't know you had that in you back there That was pretty impressive
Rapunzel : I know!
Rapunzel : I know.
Rapunzel : So Flynn Where are you from
Flynn : Whoa Sorry blondie I don't do backstory
Flynn : However I am becoming very interested in yours
Flynn : I know I'm not supposed to mention the hair
Rapunzel : Nope
Flynn : Or the mother
Rapunzel : Uhuh
Flynn : Frankly I'm too scared to ask about the frog
Rapunzel : Chameleon
Flynn : Nuance
Flynn : Here's my question though if you want to see the lanterns so badly
Flynn : why haven't you gone before
Rapunzel : Uh
Rapunzel : Well
Rapunzel : Uh Flynn
Rapunzel : Flynn
General : Rider
Flynn : Run Run
Rapunzel : Who's that?
Flynn : They don't like me
Flynn : They don't like me either
Rapunzel : Who's that
Flynn : Let's assume that everyone in here doesn't like me
Rapunzel : Here
General : I waited a long time for this
Flynn : Oh mama I have got to get me one of these
Flynn : Ha!
Flynn : You should know that this is the strangest thing I've ever done
Flynn : How about two out of three
Rapunzel : Flynn!
Rapunzel : Flynn look out
Flynn : Ha You should see your faces because you look
Flynn : ...ridiculous.
Flynn : Come on, blondie! Jump!
Flynn : It's no use I can't see anything
Flynn : Hey there's no point It's pitchblack down there
Rapunzel : This is all my fault
Rapunzel : She was right I never should have done this
Rapunzel : I'm so
Rapunzel : I'm so sorry Flynn
Flynn : Eugene
Rapunzel : What
Flynn : My real name is Eugene Fitzherbert
Flynn : Someone might as well know
Rapunzel : I have magic hair that glows when I sing
Flynn : What
Rapunzel : Flower gleam and glow Let your power shine
Rapunzel : We made it
Flynn : Her hair glows
Rapunzel : We're alive I'm alive
Flynn : I didn't see that coming
Rapunzel : Eugene
Flynn : The hair actually glows
Flynn : Why does her hair glow
Rapunzel : Eugene
Flynn : What
Rapunzel : It doesn't just glow
Flynn : Why is he smiling at me
The Stabbington Brother : I'll kill him I'll kill that Rider
The Stabbington Brother : We'll cut him off at the kingdom and get back the crown Come on
Gothel : Or
Gothel : Perhaps you want to stop acting like wild dogs
Gothel : chasing their tails and think for a moment
Gothel : Oh please there's no need for that
Gothel : Well if that's all you desire then be on your way
Gothel : I was going to offer you something worth 1000 crowns
Gothel : Would have made you rich beyond belief and that wasn't even the best part
Gothel : Oh well C'est la vie Enjoy your crown
The Stabbington Brother : What's the best part
Gothel : It comes with revenge on Flynn Rider
Flynn : You're being strangely cryptic as you wrap your magic hair around my injured hand
Rapunzel : Sorry
Rapunzel : Just don't Don't freak out
Rapunzel : Flower gleam and glow
Rapunzel : Let your power shine
Rapunzel : Make the clock reverse
Rapunzel : Bring back what once was mine
Rapunzel : Heal what has been hurt
Rapunzel : Change the Fates design
Rapunzel : Save what has been lost
Rapunzel : Bring back what once was mine
Rapunzel : What once was mine
Rapunzel : Please don't freak out
Flynn : I'm not freaking out Are you freaking out
Flynn : I'm just interested in your hair and the magical qualities it possesses How long has it been doing that exactly
Rapunzel : Forever I guess
Rapunzel : Mother says when I was a baby people tried to cut it
Rapunzel : They wanted to take it for themselves
Rapunzel : But once it's cut it turns brown and loses its power
Rapunzel : A gift like that it has to be protected
Rapunzel : That's why Mother never let me
Rapunzel : That's why I never left and
Rapunzel : You never left that tower
Flynn : And you're still going to go back
Rapunzel : No!
Rapunzel : Yes.
Rapunzel : It's complicated
Rapunzel : So, Eugene Fitzherbert, huh?
Flynn : Ah yeah Well
Flynn : I'll spare you the sob story of poor orphan Eugene Fitzherbert It's a little bit of a It's a little bit of a downer
Flynn : There was this book I used to read every night to all the younger kids The Tales of Flynnagan Rider
Flynn : Swashbuckling rogue richest man alive not bad with the ladies either
Flynn : Not that he'd ever brag about it of course
Rapunzel : Was he a thief too
Flynn : Uh
Flynn : Well no
Flynn : He had enough money to do anything that he wanted to do He could go anywhere that he wanted to go
Flynn : And for a kid with nothing, I don't know, I…
Flynn : Just seemed like the better option
Flynn : You can't tell anyone about this okay
Flynn : It could ruin my whole reputation
Rapunzel : Ah We wouldn't want that
Flynn : A fake reputation is all a man has
Flynn : Well I should um
Flynn : I should get some more firewood
Rapunzel : Hey
Rapunzel : For the record, I like Eugene Fitzherbert much better than Flynn Rider.
Flynn : Well Then you'd be the first. But thank you.
Gothel : Well I thought he'd never leave
Rapunzel : Mother?
Gothel : Hello dear
Rapunzel : But I... I I don't
Rapunzel : How did you find me
Gothel : Oh it was easy really
Gothel : I just listened for the sound of complete and utter betrayal and followed that
Rapunzel : Mother
Gothel : We're going home Rapunzel Now
Rapunzel : You don't understand
Rapunzel : I've been on this incredible journey and I've seen and learned so much
Rapunzel : I even met someone
Gothel : Yes the wanted thief I'm so proud Come on Rapunzel
Rapunzel : Mother, wait. I think…
Rapunzel : I think he likes me
Gothel : Likes you? Please, Rapunzel, that's demented!
Rapunzel : But Mother... I
Gothel : This is why you never should have left
Gothel : Dear this whole romance that you've invented
Gothel : Just proves you're too naive to be here
Gothel : Why would he like you Come on now really
Gothel : Look at you You think that he's impressed
Gothel : Don't be a dummy come with Mummy
Gothel : Mother…
Rapunzel : No!
Gothel : No?
Gothel : Oh I see how it is
Gothel : Rapunzel knows best Rapunzel's so mature now
Gothel : Such a clever grownup miss
Gothel : Rapunzel knows best Fine if you're so sure now
Gothel : Go ahead then give him this
Rapunzel : How did you
Gothel : This is why he's here Don't let him deceive you
Gothel : Give it to him watch you'll see
Rapunzel : I will
Gothel : Trust me my dear That's how fast he'll leave you
Gothel : I won't say I told you so
Gothel : No Rapunzel knows best So if he's such a dreamboat
Gothel : Go and put him to the test
Rapunzel : Mother wait
Gothel : If he's lying don't come crying
Gothel : Mother knows best
Flynn : Rapunzel uh can I ask you something
Flynn : Is there any chance that I'm going to get super strength in my hand
Flynn : Because I'm not going to lie That would be stupendous
Flynn : Hey you all right
Rapunzel : Oh Sorry yes Just lost in thought I guess
Flynn : I mean because Here's the thing
Flynn : superhuman good looks I've always had them Born with it
Flynn : But superhuman strength Can you imagine the possibilities of this
Gothel : Patience boys
Gothel : All good things to those who wait
Flynn : Huh
Flynn : Well I hope you're here to apologize
Flynn : No put me down Stop it No
Flynn : Let me go
Rapunzel : Give me him
Rapunzel : Stop stop stop
Rapunzel : Whoa whoa whoa
Rapunzel : Easy boy Easy Settle down
Rapunzel : Easy boy Easy
Rapunzel : Easy
Rapunzel : That's it
Rapunzel : Now sit
Rapunzel : Sit
Flynn : What
Rapunzel : Now drop the boot
Rapunzel : Drop it
Rapunzel : Aw You're such a good boy
Rapunzel : Yes you are
Rapunzel : You all tired from chasing this bad man all over the place
Flynn : Excuse me
Rapunzel : Nobody appreciates you do they
Rapunzel : Do they
Flynn : Oh come on He's a bad horse
Rapunzel : Oh he's nothing but a big sweetheart
Rapunzel : Isn't that right
Rapunzel : Maximus
Flynn : You've got to be kidding me
Rapunzel : Look Today is kind of the biggest day of my life
Rapunzel : and the thing is I need you not to get him arrested
Rapunzel : Just for 24 hours and then you can chase each other to your heart's content
Rapunzel : Okay?
Rapunzel : And it's also my birthday.
Rapunzel : Just so you know.
Rapunzel : Excuse
Rapunzel : me Sorry
Rapunzel : Thank you
Girl : It's for the lost princess
Man : To the boats
Flynn : Hey Max
Flynn : What I bought them
Flynn : Most of them
Rapunzel : Where are we going
Flynn : Well Best day of your life I figured you should have a decent seat
Flynn : You okay?
Rapunzel : I'm terrified
Flynn : Why?
Rapunzel : I've been looking out a window for 18 years
Rapunzel : dreaming about what it might feel like when those lights rise in the sky
Rapunzel : What if it's not everything that I dreamed it would be
Flynn : It will be
Rapunzel : And what if it is What do I do then
Flynn : That's the good part I guess You get to go find a new dream
Rapunzel : All those days watching from the windows
Rapunzel : All those years outside looking in
Rapunzel : All that time never even knowing
Rapunzel : Just how blind I've been
Rapunzel : Now I'm here blinking in the starlight
Rapunzel : Now I'm here suddenly I see
Rapunzel : Standing here it's oh so clear
Rapunzel : I'm where I'm meant to be
Rapunzel : And at last I see the light
Rapunzel : And it's like the fog has lifted
Rapunzel : And it's like the sky is new
Rapunzel : And it's warm and real and bright
Rapunzel : And the world has somehow shifted
Rapunzel : All at once everything looks different
Rapunzel : Now that I see you
Rapunzel : I have something for you too
Rapunzel : I should have given it to you before but I was just scared
Rapunzel : And the thing is I'm not scared anymore You know what I mean
Flynn : I'm starting to
Flynn : All those days chasing down a daydream
Flynn : All those years living in a blur
Flynn : All that time never truly seeing
Flynn : Things the way they were
Flynn : Now she's here shining in the starlight
Flynn : Now she's here suddenly I know
Flynn : If she's here it's crystal clear
Flynn : I'm where I'm meant to go
Rapunzel; Flynn : And at last I see the light
Rapunzel; Flynn : And it's like the fog has lifted
Rapunzel; Flynn : And it's like the sky is new
Rapunzel; Flynn : And it's warm and real and bright
Rapunzel; Flynn : And the world has somehow shifted
Rapunzel; Flynn : All at once everything is different
Rapunzel; Flynn : Now that I see you
Rapunzel; Flynn : Now that I
Rapunzel; Flynn : See you
Rapunzel : Is everything okay
Flynn : Huh
Flynn : Oh yes uh Yes of course I just
Flynn : I'm sorry Everything is fine
Flynn : There's just something I have to take care of
Rapunzel : Okay
Flynn : I'll be right back
Rapunzel : It's all right Pascal
Flynn : Ah There you are
Flynn : I've been searching everywhere for you guys since we got separated
Flynn : Hey The sideburns are coming in nice huh Got to be excited about that
Flynn : Anyhow I just wanted to say I shouldn't have split
Flynn : The crown is all yours I'll miss you but I think it's for the best
The Stabbington Brothers : Holding out on us again, eh, Rider?
Flynn : What
The Stabbington Brothers : We heard you found something
The Stabbington Brothers : Something much more valuable than a crown
The Stabbington Brothers : We want her instead
Rapunzel : I was starting to think you ran off with the crown and left me
The Stabbington Brothers : He did
Rapunzel : What No He wouldn't
The Stabbington Brothers : See for yourself
Rapunzel : Eugene?
Rapunzel : Eugene!
The Stabbington Brothers : A fair trade A crown for the girl with the magic hair
The Stabbington Brothers : How much do you think someone would pay to stay young and healthy forever
Rapunzel : No Please No
Rapunzel : No No
Gothel : Rapunzel!
Rapunzel : Mother?
Gothel : Oh, my precious girl!
Rapunzel : Mother.
Gothel : Are you all right? Are you hurt?
Rapunzel : Mother How did you…
Gothel : I was so worried about you dear
Gothel : So I followed you And I saw them attack you and
Gothel : Oh my Let's go before they come to
Rapunzel : You were right Mother You were right about everything
Gothel : I know darling I know
Soldier : Look!
Soldier : The crown!
Flynn : Rapunzel.
Flynn : Rapunzel!
Flynn : No no no no Wait Wait wait guys guys
General : Let's get this over with Rider
Flynn : Where are we going?
Flynn : Oh.
Gothel : There. It never happened.
Gothel : Now, wash up for dinner. I'm making hazelnut soup.
Gothel : I really did try, Rapunzel. I tried to warn you what was out there.
Gothel : The world is dark and selfish and cruel
Gothel : If it finds even the slightest ray of sunshine
Gothel : it destroys it
Flynn : How did you know about her? Tell me, now!
The Stabbington Brothers : It wasn't us! It was the old lady!
Flynn : Old lady?
Flynn : Wait. No! Wait!
Flynn : You don't understand! She's in trouble! Wait!
Gothel : Rapunzel?
Gothel : What's going on up there?
Gothel : Are you all right?
Rapunzel : I'm the lost princess.
Gothel : Please speak up, Rapunzel. You know how I hate the mumbling.
Rapunzel : I am the lost princess
Rapunzel : Aren't I?
Rapunzel : Did I mumble Mother
Rapunzel : Or should I even call you that
Gothel : Oh, Rapunzel, do you even hear yourself?
Gothel : Why would you ask such a ridiculous question?
Rapunzel : It was you! It was all you!
Gothel : Everything I did was to protect you.
Gothel : Rapunzel
Rapunzel : I've spent my entire life hiding from people who would use me for my power
Rapunzel : when I should have been hiding from you
Gothel : Where will you go? He won't be there for you.
Rapunzel : What did you do to him
Gothel : That criminal is to be hanged for his crimes
Rapunzel : No
Gothel : Now now it's all right
Gothel : Listen to me All of this is as it should be
Rapunzel : No You were wrong about the world
Rapunzel : And you were wrong about me
Rapunzel : And I will never let you use my hair again
Gothel : You want me to be the bad guy
Gothel : Fine now I'm the bad guy
General : What's this
General : Open up
Pub Thug8 : What's the password
General : What
Pub Thug8 : Nope
General : Open this door
Pub Thug8 : Not even close
General : You have three seconds One
General : Two
General : Three
General : Huh
Flynn : Frying pans Who knew right
Pub Thug2 : Head down
Flynn : Head down
Pub Thug2 : Arms in
Flynn : Arms in
Pub Thug2 : Knees apart
Flynn : Knees apar... Knees apart?
Flynn : Why do I need to keep my knees apart
Flynn : Max You brought them here
Flynn : Thank you
Flynn : No really Thank you
Flynn : I feel maybe this whole time we've just been misunderstanding one another and we're really just
Flynn : You're right we should go
Flynn : Max?
Flynn : Max!
Flynn : Okay Max Let's see how fast you can run
Flynn : Rapunzel?
Flynn : Rapunzel, let down your hair!
Flynn : Rapunzel, I thought I'd never see you again.
Flynn : Huh?
Gothel : Now look what you've done, Rapunzel.
Gothel : Oh, don't worry, dear. Our secret will die with him.
Gothel : And as for us
Gothel : We are going where no one will ever find you again
Gothel : Rapunzel, really!
Gothel : Enough already! Stop fighting me!
Rapunzel : No! I won't stop! For every minute of the rest of my life, I will fight!
Rapunzel : I will never stop trying to get away from you!
Rapunzel : But if you let me save him, I will go with you.
Flynn : No! No, Rapunzel.
Rapunzel : I'll never run I'll never try to escape
Rapunzel : Just let me heal him and you and I will be together
Rapunzel : forever just like you want
Rapunzel : Everything will be the way it was
Rapunzel : I promise
Rapunzel : Just like you want
Rapunzel : Just let me heal him
Gothel : In case you get any ideas about following us
Rapunzel : Eu Eugene!
Rapunzel : I'm so sorry. Everything is going to be okay, though.
Flynn : No, Rapunzel.
Rapunzel : I promise. You have to trust me. Come on. Just breathe.
Flynn : I can't let you do this.
Rapunzel : And I can't let you die.
Flynn : But if you do then you will die.
Rapunzel : Hey. It's going to be all right.
Flynn : Rapunzel
Flynn : Wait.
Rapunzel : Eugene...
Gothel : No!
Gothel : What have you done? What have you done?
Gothel : No No No no no no
Rapunzel : No no no no Eugene
Rapunzel : No! Look at me. I'm right here. Don't go. Stay with me.
Rapunzel : Flower, gleam and glow Let your power shine
Rapunzel : Make the clock reverse Bring back what once was mine
Flynn : Rapunzel.
Rapunzel : What?
Flynn : You were my new dream
Rapunzel : And you were mine
Rapunzel : Heal what has been hurt
Rapunzel : Change the Fates design
Rapunzel : Save what has been lost
Rapunzel : Bring back what once was mine
Rapunzel : What once was mine
Flynn : Rapunzel?
Rapunzel : Eugene?
Flynn : Did I ever tell you I've got a thing for brunettes?
Rapunzel : Eugene!
Flynn : Well you can imagine what happened next
Flynn : The kingdom rejoiced for their lost princess had returned
Flynn : The party lasted an entire week and honestly I don't remember most of it
Flynn : Dreams came true all over the place
Flynn : That guy went on to become the most famous concert pianist in the world if you can believe it
Flynn : And this guy He eventually found true love
Flynn : As for this guy I assume he's happy He's never told me otherwise
Flynn : Thanks to Maximus
Flynn : crime in the kingdom disappeared almost overnight
Flynn : As did most of the apples
Flynn : Pascal never changed
Flynn : At last Rapunzel was home And she finally had a real family
Flynn : She was a princess worth waiting for
Flynn : Beloved by all she led her kingdom with all the grace and wisdom that her parents did before her
Flynn : And as for me I started going by Eugene again
Flynn : stopped thieving and turned it all around But I know what the big question is
Flynn : Did Rapunzel and I ever get married
Flynn : I'm pleased to tell you that after years and years of asking and asking and asking
Flynn : I finally said yes
Rapunzel : Eugene
Flynn : All right I asked her
Rapunzel : Rapunzel And we're living happily ever after
Flynn : Yes we are