(CRIES)
(CRIES) (CHATTERING)
All : (SINGING) I'll tell you a tale of the bottomless blue And it's hey to the starboard, heave-ho
All : Look out, lad A mermaid be waiting for you In mysterious fathoms below
Prince Eric : Isn't this great? The salty sea air, the wind blowing in your face.
(BARKS)
Prince Eric : A perfect day to be at sea.
Grimsby : Oh, yes. Delightful. (RETCHES)
Sailor1 : A fine strong wind and a following sea.
Sailor1 : King Triton must be in a friendly type mood.
Prince Eric : King Triton?
Sailor2 : Why, ruler of the merpeople, lad. Thought every good sailor knew about him.
Grimsby : Merpeople.
Grimsby : Eric, pay no attention to this nautical nonsense.
Sailor2 : But it ain't nonsense. It's the truth.
Sailor2 : I'm tellin' ya! Down in the depths of the ocean they live! Oh!
Grimsby : Aah!
All : In mysterious fathoms below
(SIGHS)
(FANFARE OF TRUMPETS)
Servant : (COUGHS) His Royal Highness, King Triton!
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
Servant : And presenting the distinguished court composer,
Servant : Horatio Felonious Ignacious Crustaceous Sebastian!
(FANFARE OF KAZOOS)
(APPLAUSE)
(BOTH WHINNY)
Sebastian : Whoa!
King Triton : I'm really looking forward to this performance, Sebastian.
Sebastian : (CHUCKLES) Your Majesty!
Sebastian : This will be the finest concert I have ever conducted.
Sebastian : Your daughters, they will be spectacular!
Sebastian : Yes.
King Triton : And especially my little Ariel.
Sebastian : Yes, yes.
Sebastian : She has the most beautiful voice. Hmm?
Sebastian : If only she'd show up for rehearsals once in a while.
(ORCHESTRA TUNING) (APPLAUSE)
Daughters of Triton : Ah, we are the daughters of Triton Great father who loves us and named us well
Daughters of Triton : Aquata Andrina
Daughters of Triton : Arista, Attina Adella, Alana
Daughters of Triton : And then there is the youngest in her musical debut
Daughters of Triton : Our seventh little sister We're presenting her to you
Daughters of Triton : To sing a song Sebastian wrote Her voice is like a bell
Daughters of Triton : She's our sister Ari...
Daughters of Triton : (ALL GASP)
Daughters of Triton : (GASPS)
King Triton : Ariel!
Flounder : Ariel, wait for me.
Ariel : Flounder, hurry up.
Flounder : (PANTS) You know I can't swim that fast.
Ariel : There it is.
Ariel : Isn't it fantastic?
Flounder : Yeah, sure. It's great. Now let's get out of here.
Ariel : Oh! You're not getting cold fins now, are you?
Flounder : Who, me? No way.
Flounder : It's just... It... It looks damp in there. Yeah.
Flounder : And I think I may be coming down with something.
Flounder : Yeah, I got this cough. (COUGHS)
Ariel : (WHISPERS) All right. I'm going inside.
Ariel : You can just stay here and watch for sharks.
Flounder : Okay.
Flounder : (WHISPERING) Yeah, you go. I'll stay and...
Flounder : What? Sharks? Ariel!
Flounder : (GRUNTS) Ariel, I can't... I mean...
Flounder : Ariel, help!
Ariel : (LAUGHS) Oh, Flounder.
Flounder : (WHISPERS) Ariel. Do you really think there might be sharks around here?
Ariel : Flounder, don't be such a guppy.
Flounder : I'm not a guppy. (GRUNTS)
Flounder : This is great. I mean, I really love this.
Flounder : Excitement, adventure, danger lurking around every corner...
Flounder : (SCREAMS)
Flounder : Ariel!
Flounder : (GRUNTS) Oh,
Ariel : are you okay?
Flounder : Yeah, sure. No problem. I'm okay.
Ariel : Shh!
Ariel : Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh!
Ariel : Have you ever seen anything so wonderful in your entire life?
Flounder : Wow! Cool! But, uh, what is it?
Ariel : I don't know, but I bet Scuttle will.
Flounder : What was that? Did you hear something?
Ariel : I wonder what this one is.
Flounder : Ariel?
Ariel : Flounder, will you relax? Nothing is going to happen.
Flounder : (GROWLS) -Shark! Shark! We're gonna die!
(FLOUNDER SCREAMS)
Flounder : Oh, no!
(GRUNTS)
(FLOUNDER SCREAMS)
(GROWLS) (FLOUNDER WHIMPERS)
Flounder : You big bully!
Flounder : (BLOWS RASPBERRY)
Flounder : (GASPS)
Flounder : (ARIEL CHUCKLES)
Ariel : Flounder, you really are a guppy.
Flounder : I am not.
Scuttle : Fourteen hundred and ninety-two Dah-de-dum Dee-do-do
Scuttle : Rum-dim-dim Dee-do-dee-do
Ariel : Scuttle!
Scuttle : Whoa! Mermaid off the port bow!
Scuttle : (SHOUTS) Ariel, how you doin', kid?
Scuttle : Whoa, what a swim.
Ariel : Scuttle, look what we found.
Flounder : Yeah. We were in this sunken ship, and it was really creepy...
Scuttle : Human stuff, huh? Hey, let me see.
Scuttle : Oh! Oh! Look at this.
Scuttle : Wow. This is special. This is very, very unusual.
Ariel : What? What is it?
Scuttle : It's a dinglehopper.
Scuttle : Humans use these little babies
Scuttle : to straighten their hair out.
Scuttle : See? Just a little twirl here and a yank there and violee...
Scuttle : Ya got an aesthetically-pleasing configuration of hair
Scuttle : that humans go nuts over.
Ariel : A dinglehopper.
Flounder : What about that one?
Scuttle : Ah! This I haven't seen in years. This is wonderful!
Scuttle : A banded, bulbous snarfblatt.
Ariel;Flounder : Oh!
Scuttle : Now, the snarfblatt dates back to prehistorical times when humans used to sit around
Scuttle : and stare at each other all day.
Scuttle : Got very boring.
Scuttle : So, they invented this snarfblatt to make fine music.
Scuttle : Allow me.
Scuttle : (SCUTTLE COUGHS)
Ariel : Music!
Scuttle : It's stuck!
Ariel : Oh, the concert! Oh, my gosh! My father's gonna kill me!
Flounder : Concert was today?
Scuttle : Maybe you could make a little planter out of it or some,
Ariel : Oh, I'm sorry! I gotta go! Thank you, Scuttle!
Scuttle : Any time, sweetie! Any time.
Ursula : Yes, hurry home, Princess.
Ursula : We wouldn't want to miss old Daddy's celebration, now, would we?
Ursula : Ha! Celebration, indeed. Oh, bah!
Ursula : In my day, we had fantastical feasts,
Ursula : When I lived in the palace.
Ursula : (GULPS)
Ursula : And now look at me. Wasted away to practically nothing.
Ursula : Banished and exiled and practically starving,
Ursula : while he and his flimsy fish folk celebrate.
Ursula : Well, I'll give 'em something to celebrate soon enough.
Ursula : Flotsam! Jetsam!
Ursula : I want you to keep an extra close watch on this pretty little daughter of his.
Ursula : She may be the key to Triton's undoing.
King Triton : I just don't know what we're going to do with you, young lady.
Ariel : Daddy, I'm sorry. I just forgot.
King Triton : As a result of your careless behavior...
Sebastian : Careless and reckless behavior!
King Triton : ...the entire celebration was, uh...
Sebastian : Well, it was ruined! That's all! Completely destroyed!
Sebastian : This concert was to be the pinnacle of my distinguished career.
Sebastian : Now, thanks to you, I am the laughingstock of the entire kingdom!
Flounder : But it wasn't her fault. Uh, oh, first, uh, the shark chased us.
Flounder : Yeah, yeah. And we tried to... But we couldn't, and he... Grrrr... And... And we... Whoa!
Flounder : (SIGHS) And then we were safe.
Flounder : But then this seagull came, and it was, "This is this, and that is that, and..."
King Triton : Seagull?
(GASPS)
King Triton : What? Oh! You went up to the surface again, didn't you? Didn't you?
Ariel : Nothing happened.
King Triton : Ariel, how many times must we go through this?
King Triton : You could have been seen by one of those barbarians, by one of those humans!
Ariel : Daddy, they're not barbarians.
King Triton : They are dangerous.
King Triton : Do you think I want to see my youngest daughter snared by some fish-eater's hook?
Ariel : I'm 16 years old. I'm not a child anymore.
King Triton : Don't you take that tone of voice with me, young lady!
King Triton : As long as you live under my ocean, you'll obey my rules!
Ariel : But if you would just listen...
King Triton : Not another word! And I am never, never to hear of you going to the surface again! Is that clear?
Sebastian : Hmph! Teenagers. They think they know everything.
Sebastian : You give them an inch, they swim all over you.
King Triton : Do you think I was too hard on her?
Sebastian : Definitely not.
Sebastian : Why, if Ariel was my daughter, I'd show her who was boss.
Sebastian : None of this flitting to the surface and other such nonsense.
Sebastian : No, sir. I'd keep her under tight control.
King Triton : You're absolutely right, Sebastian.
Sebastian : Of course.
King Triton : Ariel needs constant supervision.
Sebastian : Constant.
King Triton : Someone to watch over her, to keep her out of trouble.
Sebastian : All the time.
King Triton : And you are just the crab to do it.
Sebastian : How do I get myself into these situations?
Sebastian : I should be writing symphonies, not tagging along after some headstrong teenager.
Sebastian : Hmm? What is that girl up to?
Sebastian : (SEBASTIAN PANTS)
Sebastian : (GASPS)
Sebastian : Huh?
Flounder : Ariel, are you okay?
Ariel : If only I can make him understand
Ariel : I just don't see things the way he does.
Ariel : I don't see how a world that makes such wonderful things
Ariel : could be bad.
Ariel : Look at this stuff Isn't it neat?
Ariel : Wouldn't ya think my collection's complete?
Ariel : Wouldn't ya think I'm the girl
Ariel : The girl who has everything?
Ariel : Look at this trove Treasures untold
Ariel : How many wonders can one cavern hold?
Ariel : Lookin' around here you'd think
Ariel : Sure, she's got everything
Ariel : I've got gadgets and gizmos aplenty
Ariel : I've got whozits and whatzits galore
Ariel : You want thingamabobs I got 20
Ariel : But who cares No big deal
Ariel : I want more
Ariel : I wanna be where the people are
Ariel : I wanna see Wanna see 'em dancin'
Ariel : Walkin' around on those...
Ariel : What do ya call 'em?
Ariel : Oh, feet.
Ariel : (GIGGLES) (HARRUMPHS)
Ariel : Flippin' your fins you don't get too far
Ariel : Legs are required for jumpin', dancin' Strollin' along down a...
Ariel : What's that word again?
Ariel : Street
Ariel : Up where they walk Up where they run
Ariel : Up where they stay all day in the sun Wanderin' free
Ariel : Wish I could be Part of that world
Ariel : What would I give if I could live Out of these waters
Ariel : What would I pay to spend a day Warm on the sand?
Ariel : Betcha on land they understand
Ariel : Bet they don't reprimand their daughters
Ariel : Bright young women sick of swimmin'
Ariel : Ready to stand
Ariel : And ready to know what the people know
Ariel : Ask 'em my questions and get some answers
Ariel : What's a fire and why does it...
Ariel : What's the word?
Ariel : Burn?
Ariel : When's it my turn? Wouldn't I love
Ariel : Love to explore that shore up above?
Ariel : Out of the sea
Ariel : Wish I could be
Ariel : Part of that
Ariel : World
Ariel : Sebastian!
Sebastian : Ariel, what are you... How could you... What is all this?
Ariel : It's, uh... It's just my collection.
Sebastian : Oh, I see. Your collection, hmm.
Sebastian : If your father knew about this place...
Flounder : You're not gonna tell him, are you?
Ariel : please, Sebastian, he would never understand.
Sebastian : Ariel, you're under a lot of pressure down here.
Sebastian :  Come with me, I'll take you home and get you something warm to drink.  What do you suppose... -Ariel?
Sebastian : Ariel? Ariel!
Sebastian : (RUMBLING CONTINUES)
Sebastian : (ARIEL GASPS)
Sebastian : Ariel, what are you...
Sebastian : Jumpin' jellyfish!
Sebastian : Ariel? Ariel! Please! Come back!
Sebastian : (MEN LAUGH AND CHATTER)
Sebastian : (ACCORDION PLAYING)
Sebastian : (LAUGHTER)
Sebastian : (BARKS)
Sebastian : (SNIFFS)
Sebastian : (GASPS)
Prince Eric : Max! Here, boy!
(MAX BARKS)
Prince Eric : Hey, come on, mutt. What ya doin', huh, Max?
Prince Eric : Come on, Max. (LAUGHS)
Scuttle : Hey there, sweetie! Quite a show, eh?
Ariel : Scuttle, be quiet. They'll hear you.
Scuttle : Ooh, I got ya. I got ya.
Scuttle : We're bein' intrepidaceous. We're out to discover!
Ariel : I've never seen a human this close before.
Ariel : Oh. He's very handsome, isn't he?
Scuttle : I don't know. He looks kind of hairy and slobbery to me.
Ariel : Not that one.
Ariel : The one playing the snarfblatt.
Grimsby : Silence, silence.
Grimsby : It is now my honor and privilege to present our esteemed Prince Eric
Grimsby : with a very special, very expensive, very large birthday present.
Prince Eric : Ah, Grimsby, ya old beanpole, you shouldn't have.
Grimsby : I know.
Grimsby : Happy birthday, Eric.
(GASPING)
(GROWLS)
Prince Eric : Uh, gee, Grim... Ha! (CLEARS THROAT)
Prince Eric : It's, uh... It's really somethin'.
Grimsby : Yes, I commissioned it myself.
Grimsby : Of course, I had hoped it would be a wedding present.
Prince Eric : Come on, Grim. Don't start.
Prince Eric : Look, you're not still sore because I didn't fall for the Princess of Glowerhaven, are you?
Grimsby : Oh, my! Eric, it isn't me alone.
Grimsby : The entire kingdom wants to see you happily settled down with the right girl.
Prince Eric : Oh, she's out there somewhere. I just...
Prince Eric : I just haven't found her yet.
Grimsby : Perhaps you haven't been looking hard enough.
Prince Eric : Believe me, Grim, when I find her, I'll know.
Prince Eric : Without a doubt, it'll just, bam, hit me, like lightning.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Sailor1 : Hurricane a-comin'! Stand fast! Secure the riggin'!
(SHOUTING)
(BARKS)
Scuttle : Whoa! The wind's all of a sudden on the move here! Yo!
Scuttle : Ariel!
(BELL CLANGS)
Prince Eric : Look out!
(CLANGING) (SCREAMING)
Prince Eric : Grim! Hang on!
(COUGHS)
(MAX BARKS)
Prince Eric : Max!
(BARKS)
Prince Eric : Jump, Max! Come on, boy! Jump! You can do it, Max!
(MAX YELPS)
Grimsby : Eric!
(MAX BARKS)
Ariel : Is he dead?
Scuttle : It's hard to say.
Scuttle : Oh, I... I can't make out a heartbeat.
Ariel : No, look! He's breathing.
Ariel : He's so beautiful.
Ariel : What would I give to live where you are?
Ariel : What would I pay to stay here beside you?
Ariel : What would I do to see you smiling at me?
Ariel : Where would we walk Where would we run
Ariel : If we could stay all day in the sun?
Ariel : Just you and me and I could be
Ariel : Part of your world
(MAX BARKS)
Grimsby : Eric?
Grimsby : Eric!
Grimsby : You really delight in these sadistic strains on my blood pressure, don't you?
Prince Eric : A girl rescued me.
Prince Eric : She... She was singing.
Prince Eric : She had the most beautiful voice.
Grimsby : Ah, Eric, I think you've swallowed a bit too much seawater.
Grimsby : Off we go. Come along, Max.
Sebastian : We just gonna forget this whole thing ever happened.
Sebastian : The sea king will never know.
Sebastian : You won't tell him. I won't tell him. I will stay in one piece.
Ariel : I don't know when I don't know how
Ariel : But I know something's starting right now
Ariel : Watch and you'll see
Ariel : Someday I'll be
Ariel : Part of your World
(MAX BARKS)
Ursula : Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. I can't stand it. It's too easy.
Ursula : The child is in love with a human.
Ursula : And not just any human. A prince!
Ursula : (CHUCKLES) Her daddy will love that.
Ursula : King Triton's headstrong, lovesick girl
Ursula : would make a charming addition to my little garden.
Ursula : (CACKLES)
Andrina : Ariel, dear, time to come out.
Andrina : You've been in there all morning.
(HUMS)
Alana : What is with her lately?
(ARIEL HUMS)
Ariel : Oh. Morning, Daddy.
King Triton : Well! (CHUCKLES)
(HUMS)
Attina : Oh, she's got it bad.
King Triton : What? What has she got?
Andrina : Isn't it obvious, Daddy? Ariel's in love.
Ariel? In love?
Sebastian : Okay. So far, so good. I don't think the king knows.
Sebastian : But it will not be easy keeping something like this a secret for long.
Ariel : (SIGHS) He loves me.
Ariel : Mmm. He loves me not.
Ariel : He loves me!
Ariel : (LAUGHS) I knew it!
Sebastian : Ariel, stop talking crazy!
Ariel : I gotta see him again, tonight.
Ariel : Scuttle knows where he lives.
Sebastian : Ariel, please!
Sebastian : Will you get your head out of the clouds and back in the water where it belongs?
Ariel :  I'll swim up to his castle, then Flounder will splash around to get his attention. And then we'll go...
Sebastian : Down here is your home!
Sebastian : Ariel, listen to me.
Sebastian : The human world, it's a mess. Life under the sea is better than anything they got up there.
Sebastian : The seaweed is always greener In somebody else's lake
Sebastian : You dream about going up there But that is a big mistake
Sebastian : Just look at the world around you Right here on the ocean floor
Sebastian : Such wonderful things surround you What more is you lookin' for?
Sebastian : Under the sea Under the sea
Sebastian : Darling, it's better down where it's wetter Take it from me
Sebastian : Up on the shore they work all day Out in the sun they slave away
Sebastian : While we devoting full time to floating under the sea
Sebastian : (STEEL DRUMS PLAYING)
Sebastian;Fish : Down here all the fish is happy As off through the waves they roll, yeah
Sebastian;Fish : The fish on the land ain't happy They sad 'cause they in their bowl
Sebastian : But fish in the bowl is lucky They in for a worser fate
Sebastian;Fish2 : One day when the boss get hungry Guess who's gonna be on the plate
Sebastian : Oh, no! Under the sea Under the sea
Sebastian : Nobody beat us Fry us and eat us In fricassee
Sebastian : We what the land folks loves to cook Under the sea we off the hook
Sebastian : We got no troubles Life is the bubbles
Sebastian : - Under the sea
All : -Under the sea
Sebastian : -Under the sea
Sebastian : -Since life is sweet here We got the beat here Naturally
All : -Naturally
Sebastian;All : - Even the sturgeon and the ray
Sebastian : They get the urge and start to play
Sebastian : We got the spirit You got to hear it Under the sea
Sebastian : The newt play the flute The carp play the harp The plaice play the bass and they soundin' sharp
Sebastian : The bass play the brass The chub play the tub The fluke is the duke of soul
Fish2 : Yeah.
Sebastian : The ray, he can play The ling's on the strings The trout's rocking out The blackfish, she sings
Sebastian : The smelt and the sprat They know where it's at And, oh, that blowfish blow
Sebastian : (SEBASTIAN LAUGHS)
Sebastian : -Yeah, under the sea
All : -Under the sea
Sebastian : -Under the sea
Sebastian : When the sardine begin the beguine It's music to me
All : Music it is to me
Sebastian : What do they got? A lot of sand We got a hot crustacean band
Sebastian : Each little clam here know how to jam here under the sea
Sebastian : Each little slug here cutting a rug here under the sea
Sebastian : Each little snail here know how to wail here That's why it's hotter under the water
Sebastian : Yeah, we in luck here down in the muck here Under the sea
Sebastian : Ariel?
Sebastian : Oh, somebody's got to nail that girl's fins to the floor.
Servant : Sebastian!
Servant : (PANTS) Sebastian, I've been looking all over for you.
Servant : I've got an urgent message from the sea king.
Sebastian : The sea king?
Servant : He wants to see you right away. Something about Ariel.
Sebastian : (GASPS) He knows.
King Triton : (LAUGHS) Hey, let's see now. Oh, who could the lucky merman be?
King Triton : (CLEARS THROAT) Come in, Sebastian.
Sebastian : (INHALES SHARPLY) I mustn't overreact. I must remain calm.
Sebastian : (SQUEAKY VOICE) Yes? (CLEARS THROAT)
Sebastian : Yes, Your Majesty?
King Triton : Sebastian.
King Triton : I'm concerned about Ariel.
King Triton : Have you noticed she's been acting peculiar lately?
Sebastian : Oh! Uh, peculiar?
King Triton : You know, mooning about. Daydreaming, singing to herself.
King Triton : You haven't noticed, hmm?
Sebastian : Oh, well, I...
King Triton : Sebastian?
Sebastian : Hmm?
King Triton : I know you've been keeping something from me.
Sebastian : (GULPS) Keeping something?
King Triton : About Ariel?
Sebastian : Ariel?
King Triton : In love, hmm?
Sebastian : (WHIMPERS) I tried to stop her, sir! She wouldn't listen!
Sebastian : I told her to stay away from humans! They are bad! They are trouble!
King Triton : Humans? What about humans?
Sebastian : Humans? (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Sebastian : Who said anything about humans? (YELPS)
Ariel : Flounder, why
can't you just tell me what this is all about?
Flounder : You'll
see. It's a surprise.
Ariel : Oh, Flounder.
Ariel : Flounder, you're the best!
Ariel : It looks just like him. It even has his eyes.
Ariel : (GIGGLES) Why, Eric, run away with you?
Ariel : Oh, this is all so, so sudden.
Ariel : (LAUGHS)
Ariel : (GASPS)
Ariel : Daddy?
King Triton : I consider myself a reasonable merman.
King Triton : I set certain rules, and I expect those rules to be obeyed.
Ariel : But, Dad, I..
King Triton : Is it true you rescued a human from drowning?
Ariel : Daddy, I had to...
King Triton : Contact between the human world and the mer-world is strictly forbidden.
King Triton : Ariel, you know that! Everyone knows that.
Ariel : He would have died.
King Triton : One less human to worry about.
Ariel : You don't even know him.
King Triton : Know him? I don't have to know him! They're all the same.
King Triton : Spineless, savage, harpooning fish-eaters incapable of any feeling...
Ariel : Daddy, I love him!
King Triton : No!
King Triton : Have you lost your senses completely?
King Triton : He's a human. You're a mermaid.
Ariel : I don't care.
King Triton : So help me, Ariel, I am going to get through to you.
King Triton : And if this is the only way, so be it!
Ariel : Daddy! No!
Ariel : No! Please!
Ariel : Daddy, stop! Daddy, stop it!
Ariel : Daddy, no!
(ARIEL SOBS)
Sebastian : Ariel, I...
Ariel : (SOBS) Just go away.
Ursula;Flotsam and Jetsam : Poor child. Poor, sweet child.
Flotsam and Jetsam : She has a very serious problem.
Flotsam and Jetsam : If only there were something we could do.
Flotsam and Jetsam : But there is something.
Ariel : Who... Who are you?
Flotsam and Jetsam : Don't be scared.
Flotsam and Jetsam : We represent someone who can help you.
Flotsam and Jetsam : Someone who can make all your dreams come true.
Flotsam and Jetsam : Just imagine...
Flotsam and Jetsam : You and your prince...
Flotsam and Jetsam : Together forever.
Ariel : I don't understand.
Flotsam and Jetsam : Ursula has great powers.
Ariel : (GASPS) The sea witch? Why, that's... I couldn't possibly.
Ariel : No! Get out of here. Leave me alone!
Flotsam and Jetsam : Suit yourself.
Flotsam and Jetsam : That was only a suggestion.
Ariel : Wait.
Flotsam and Jetsam : Yes?
Flounder : (SNIFFLES) Poor Ariel.
Sebastian : I didn't mean to tell. It was an accident.
(MUTTERS)
Sebastian : Ariel? Where are you going? Ariel, what are you doing here with this riffraff?
Ariel : I'm going to see Ursula.
Sebastian : (GASPS) Ariel, no! No! She's a demon. She's a monster.
Ariel : Why don't you go tell my father? You're good at that.
But... But I...
Sebastian : Come on!
Flotsam and Jetsam : This way.
(CREATURES MOAN)
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
(PANTS)
Ursula : Come in. Come in, my child.
Ursula : We mustn't lurk in doorways. It's rude.
Ursula : One might question your upbringing. (CHUCKLES)
Ursula : Now, then, you're here because you have a thing for this human, this prince fellow.
Ursula : Not that I blame you. He is quite a catch, isn't he?
Ursula : Well, angelfish, the solution to your problem is simple.
Ursula : The only way to get what you want is to become a human yourself.
Ariel : (GASPS) Can you do that?
Ursula : My dear, sweet child. That's what I do.
Ursula : It's what I live for. To help unfortunate merfolk, like yourself,
Ursula : poor souls with no one else to turn to.
Ursula : I admit that in the past I've been a nasty They weren't kidding when they called me, well, a witch
Ursula : But you'll find that nowadays I've mended all my ways
Ursula : Repented, seen the light and made a switch
Ursula : True? Yes.
Ursula : And I fortunately know a little magic
Ursula : It's a talent that I always have possessed
Ursula : And here lately, please don't laugh, I use it on behalf Of the miserable, lonely and depressed
Ursula : Pathetic.
Ursula : Poor unfortunate souls In pain, in need
Ursula : This one longing to be thinner That one wants to get the girl And do I help them? Yes, indeed
Ursula : Those poor, unfortunate souls So sad, so true
Ursula : They come flocking to my cauldron Crying spells, Ursula, please And I help them Yes, I do
Ursula : Now it's happened once or twice Someone couldn't pay the price
Ursula : And I'm afraid I had to rake 'em across the coals
Ursula : Yes, I've had the odd complaint But on the whole I've been a saint
Ursula : To those poor unfortunate souls
Ursula : Now, here's the deal.
Ursula : I will make you a potion that will turn you into a human for three days.
Ursula : Got that? Three days.
Ursula : Now, listen, this is important.
Ursula : Before the sun sets on the third day,
Ursula : you've got to get dear old princie to fall in love with you.
Ursula : That is, he's got to kiss you.
Ursula : Not just any kiss, the kiss of true love.
Ursula : If he does kiss you before the sun sets on the third day, you'll remain human permanently.
Ursula : But if he doesn't, you'll turn back into a mermaid, and you belong to me!
Sebastian : No, Ariel! (MUFFLED)
Ursula : Have we got a deal?
Ariel : If I become human, I'll never be with my father or sisters again.
Ursula : That's right! But you'll have your man.
Ursula : (CHUCKLES) Life's full of tough choices, isn't it?
Ursula : (CACKLES)
Ursula : Oh! And there is one more thing.
Ursula : We haven't discussed the subject of payment.
Ursula : You can't get something for nothing, you know.
Ariel : But I don't have any...
Ursula : I'm not asking much. Just a token really, a trifle. You'll never even miss it.
Ursula : What I want from you is your voice.
Ariel : My voice?
Ursula : You've got it, sweetcakes.
Ursula : No more talking, singing. Zip!
Ariel : But without my voice, how can I...
Ursula : You'll have your looks, your pretty face.
Ursula : And don't underestimate the importance of body language! Ha!
Ursula : The men up there don't like a lot of blabber
Ursula : They think a girl who gossips is a bore
Ursula : Yes, on land it's much preferred for ladies not to say a word And, after all, dear What is idle prattle for?
Ursula : Come on, they're not all that impressed with conversation
Ursula : True gentlemen avoid it when they can
Ursula : But they dote and swoon and fawn On a lady who's withdrawn
Ursula : It's she who holds her tongue who gets her man
Ursula : Come on, you poor unfortunate soul
Ursula : Go ahead, make your choice
Ursula : I'm a very busy woman and I haven't got all day It won't cost much, just your voice
Ursula : Ya poor, unfortunate soul
Ursula : It's sad, but true
Ursula : If you want to cross a bridge, my sweet you've got to pay the toll Take a gulp and take a breath and go ahead and sign the scroll
Ursula : Flotsam, Jetsam Now I've got her, boys The boss is on a roll
Ursula : This poor, unfortunate soul
Ursula : Beluga, sevruga Come, winds of the Caspian Sea
Ursula : Larynxis, glossitis Et max laryngitis La voce to me
Ursula : Now, sing!
Ariel : (VOCALIZES)
Ursula : Keep singing!
Ariel : (VOCALIZING CONTINUES)
(CACKLES)
(PIPE PLAYS)
(BARKS)
Prince Eric : That voice. I can't get it out of my head.
Prince Eric : I've looked everywhere, Max. Where could she be?
Scuttle : Well, look at what the catfish dragged in.
Scuttle : (LAUGHS) Look at ya. Look at ya.
Scuttle : There's somethin' different. Don't tell me.
Scuttle : I got it. It's your hairdo, right?
Scuttle : You've been usin' the dinglehopper, right?
Scuttle : No? No, huh? Well, let me see.
Scuttle : New seashells?
Scuttle : No new seashells.
Scuttle : I gotta admit I can't put my foot on it right now. But if I just stand here long enough...
Sebastian : She's got legs, you idiot!
Sebastian : She traded her voice to the sea witch and got legs. Geez, man!
Scuttle : I knew that.
Flounder : Ariel's been turned into a human.
Flounder : She's gotta make the prince fall in love with her, and he's gotta kiss her.
Sebastian : And she's only got three days!
Sebastian : Just look at her! On legs! On human legs!
Sebastian : (GASPS)
Sebastian : My nerves are shot! This is a catastrophe! What would her father say? I'll tell you what her father'd say.
Sebastian : He'd say he's gonna kill himself a crab! That's what her father'd say!
Sebastian : I'm gonna march meself straight home right now and tell him just like I should have done the minute...
Sebastian : And don't you shake your head at me, young lady.
Sebastian : Maybe there's still time.
Sebastian : If we could get that witch to give you back your voice, you could go home with all the normal fish and just be...
Sebastian : Just be...
Sebastian : Just be miserable for the rest of your life.
Sebastian : All right, all right. I'll try to help ya find that prince.
Sebastian : Boy, what a soft shell I'm turning out to be.
Scuttle : Now, Ariel, I'm telling ya. If you wanna be a human, the first thing ya gotta do is dress like one. Now, let me see.
(SNIFFS)
Prince Eric : Max? What?
Prince Eric : Huh? What? Max!
Scuttle : Ya look great, kid. Ya look sensational.
(GASPS)
(PANTS) (SEBASTIAN MUTTERS)
Prince Eric : Max!
Prince Eric : Quiet, Max.
Prince Eric : What's gotten into you, fella? Oh. Oh, I see.
Prince Eric : Are you okay, miss? I'm sorry if this knucklehead scared you. He's harmless, really, uh...
Prince Eric : You seem very familiar to me. Have we met?
(BARKS)
Prince Eric : We have met. I knew it. You're the one, the one I've been looking for. What's your name?
Prince Eric : What's wrong? What is it?
Prince Eric : You can't speak? Oh!
Prince Eric : Oh, then you couldn't be who I thought.
(SIGHS) (SIGHS)
Prince Eric : What is it? You're hurt?
Prince Eric : No, no. You need help?
Prince Eric : Whoa, whoa, careful! Careful, easy.
Prince Eric : Gee, you must have really been through something.
Prince Eric : Don't worry. Don't worry. I'll help you. Come on. Come on. You'll be okay.
Prince Eric : (BARKS)
Carlotta : Washed up from a shipwreck. Oh, the poor thing.
Carlotta : We'll have you feeling better in no time.
(CARLOTTA HUMS) (GASPS)
Carlotta : I'll just... I'll just get this washed for you.
(GASPS, SPLUTTERS)
Servant1 : Well, you must have at least heard about this girl.
Servant2 : No!
Servant1 : Gertrude says When has
Servant1 : Gertrude ever gotten anything right?
(BURPS)
Servant1 : I mean, really.
Sebastian : Madam, please...
Servant1 : She shows up in rags and doesn't speak.
Servant1 : Not my idea of a princess.
Servant1 : If Eric's looking for a girl, I know a couple of highly available ones right here.
(GASPS)
Grimsby : Oh, Eric, be reasonable.
Grimsby : Nice young ladies just don't swim around rescuing people in the middle of the ocean
Grimsby : and then flitter off into oblivion like some...
Prince Eric : I'm tellin' ya, Grim. She was real. I'm gonna find that girl, and I'm gonna marry her.
Carlotta : (LAUGHS) Come on, honey. Don't be shy.
Grimsby : Oh, Eric, isn't she a vision?
Prince Eric : Uh, you look wonderful.
Grimsby : Come, come, come. You must be famished. Let me help you, my dear.
Grimsby : There we go. That's better.
Grimsby : Now, quite comfy? Good.
Grimsby : It's not often that we have such a lovely dinner guest, eh, Eric?
(MATCH STRIKES)
Grimsby : Uh, do you like it? It is rather a fine one.
Carlotta : Oh, my.
Prince Eric : (CLEARS THROAT) Sorry, Grim.
Carlotta : Why, Eric, that's the first time I've seen you smile in weeks.
Grimsby : Ah, very amusing. (SNIFFS)
Grimsby : Carlotta, my dear, what's for dinner?
Carlotta : Oh, you're gonna love it! Chef's been fixing his specialty, stuffed crab.
(GASPS)
Chef Louis : (SINGING) Nouvelle cuisine Les Champs-lyses
Chef Louis : Maurice Chevalier
Chef Louis : (CHUCKLES)
Chef Louis : Les poissons, les poissons How I love les poissons
Chef Louis : Love to chop and to serve little fish
Chef Louis : First I cut off their heads Then I pull out their bones Ah, mais oui a c'est toujours delish
Chef Louis : Les poissons, les poissons
Chef Louis : (LAUGHS IN RHYTHM)
Chef Louis : With the cleaver I hack them in two
Chef Louis : I pull out what's inside and I serve it up fried
Chef Louis : 'Cause I love little fishes Don't you?
Chef Louis : Here's something for tempting the palate
Chef Louis : Prepared in the classic technique
Chef Louis : First you pound the fish flat with the mallet
Chef Louis : Then you slash through the skin Give the belly a slice
Chef Louis : Then you rub some salt in 'Cause that makes it taste nice
Chef Louis : Zut alors! I have missed one.
Chef Louis : Sacrebleu, what is this?
Chef Louis : How on Earth could I miss Such a sweet, little succulent crab?
Chef Louis : Quel dommage, what a loss Here we go, in the sauce
Chef Louis : Now some flour, I think, just a dab
Chef Louis : Now I'll stuff you with bread It don't hurt 'cause you're dead
Chef Louis : And you're certainly lucky, you are
Chef Louis : 'Cause it's gonna be hot in my big silver pot Toodle-oo Mon poisson, au revoir
Chef Louis : Eh?
Chef Louis : What is this? Ow!
Chef Louis : Yeow! Oh, ow, ow, oh!
Chef Louis : (SCREAMING)
Chef Louis : (CRASHING)
Carlotta : I think I'd better go see what Louis is up to.
Chef Louis : Come out, you little pipsqueak, and fight like a man!
Carlotta : Louis!
Chef Louis : Ow.
Carlotta : What are you doing?
Chef Louis : Well, I was just, uh... I'm sorry, madame.
Grimsby : You know, Eric, perhaps our young guest might enjoy seeing some of the sights of the kingdom.
Grimsby : Something in the way of a tour.
Prince Eric : (CHUCKLES) I'm sorry, Grim. What was that?
Grimsby : You can't spend all your time moping about. You need to get out.
Grimsby : Do something. Have a life.
Sebastian : Shh!
Grimsby : Get your mind off...
Prince Eric : Easy, Grim, easy.
Prince Eric : It's not a bad idea, if she's interested.
Prince Eric : Well, what do ya say?
Prince Eric : Would you like to join me on a tour of my kingdom tomorrow?
Grimsby : Wonderful! Now, let's eat before this crab wanders off my plate.
Prince Eric : Come here, boy.
Prince Eric : (BARKS) (ERIC GROWLS)
Sebastian : This has got to be, without a doubt, the single most humiliating day of my life.
Sebastian : I hope that you appreciate what I go through for you, young lady.
Sebastian : Now, we got to make a plan to get that boy to kiss you.
Sebastian : Tomorrow when he takes you for that ride, you gotta look your best.
Sebastian : You gotta bat your eyes, like this.
Sebastian : You gotta pucker up your lips, like this.
Sebastian : Hmm.
Sebastian : You are hopeless, child. You know that?
Sebastian : Completely hopeless. (YAWNS)
King Triton : Any sign of them?
Servant : No, Your Majesty. We've searched everywhere. We've found no trace of your daughter or Sebastian.
King Triton : Well, keep looking. Leave no shell unturned, no coral unexplored.
King Triton : Let no one in this kingdom sleep until she's safe at home.
Servant : Yes, sire.
King Triton : Oh, what have I done? What have I done?
Flounder : Has he kissed her yet?
Sebastian : Not yet.
Flounder : Oh!
(CHATTER)
(CLUCKING)
Woman1 : Oh, Judy!
Scuttle : Yo, Flounder! Any kissing?
Flounder : No, not yet.
Scuttle : Well, they'd better get crackin'!
Flounder : Move over. Move your big feathers. I can't see a thing.
Scuttle : Nothing is happening.
Scuttle : Only one day left, and that boy ain't puckered up once.
Scuttle : Okay. All right, this calls for a little vocal romantic stimulation.
Scuttle : Stand back!
Scuttle : (CLEARS THROAT) Wa, wa, wa, wa-wa!
Prince Eric : Wow. Somebody should find that poor animal and put it out of its misery.
Scuttle : Wa, wa, wa-wa!
Scuttle : Wa, wa, wa, wa-wa!
Sebastian : Geez, man. I'm surrounded by amateurs.
Scuttle : Wa, wa, wa, wa!
Sebastian : You want something done, you've got to do it yourself.
Sebastian : First we got to create the mood.
Sebastian : Percussion. Strings. Winds.
Sebastian : Words.
Sebastian : (SINGING) There you see her Sitting there across the way
Sebastian : She don't got a lot to say But there's something about her
Sebastian : And you don't know why but you're dyin' to try You wanna kiss the girl
Prince Eric : Did you hear something?
Sebastian : Yes
Sebastian : You want her Look at her You know you do
Sebastian : Possible she want you, too There is one way to ask her
Sebastian : It don't take a word Not a single word Go on and kiss the girl
Sebastian : Sing with me now.
Sebastian : Sha-la-la-la-la-la My, oh, my Look like the boy too shy He ain't gonna kiss the girl
Sebastian : Sha-la-la-la-la-la Ain't that sad? Ain't it a shame? Too bad he gonna miss the girl
Prince Eric : You know, I feel really bad not knowing your name. Maybe I could guess.
Prince Eric : Is it Mildred?
Prince Eric : (LAUGHS) Okay, no.
Prince Eric : How about Diana? Rachel?
Sebastian : Ariel. Her name is Ariel.
Prince Eric : Ariel?
Prince Eric : That's kind of pretty. Okay. Ariel.
Sebastian : Now's your moment
Sebastian : Floating in a blue lagoon
Sebastian : Boy, you better do it soon No time will be better
Sebastian : She don't say a word And she won't say a word Until ya kiss the girl
Sebastian : (FISH CHATTER)
Sebastian : Sha-la-la-la-la-la Don't be scared You got the mood prepared Go on and kiss the girl
Sebastian : Sha-la-la-la-la-la Don't stop now Don't try to hide it how You wanna kiss the girl
Sebastian :  Whoa, whoa  Sha-la-la-la-la-la Float along
Sebastian : -And listen to the song Song say kiss the girl Whoa, whoa
Sebastian : Sha-la-la-la-la-la The music play Do what the music say You gotta kiss the girl
Sebastian : (MAKING KISSING SOUNDS)
Sebastian : Kiss the girl
Bird : Why don't you
Sebastian : Kiss the girl?
Sebastian : Go on and kiss the girl
Sebastian : Go on and...
Sebastian : Kiss the girl
Prince Eric : Whoa! Hang on, I've got ya.
(BOTH CACKLE)
Ursula : Nice work, boys. That was a close one. Too close.
Ursula : The little tramp! Ah, she's better than I thought.
Ursula : Well, at this rate, he'll be kissing her by sunset for sure.
Ursula : Well, it's time Ursula took matters into her own tentacles.
Ursula : Triton's daughter will be mine! And then I'll make him writhe.
Ursula : I'll see him wriggle like a worm on a hook!
Ursula : (CACKLES)
(PIPE PLAYS)
Grimsby : Eric? If I may say,
Grimsby : far better than any dream girl is one of flesh and blood,
Grimsby : one warm and caring and right before your eyes.
(SIGHS)
(ARIEL'S VOICE VOCALIZING)
Scuttle : Ariel!
Scuttle : Ariel, wake up! Wake up. I just heard the news. Congratulations. Kiddo, we did it!
(YAWNS)
Sebastian : What is this idiot babbling about?
Scuttle : Right, as if you two didn't know, huh?
Scuttle : The whole town's buzzin' about the prince gettin' himself hitched this afternoon!
Scuttle : You know, he's getting married.
Scuttle : You silly side-walker. I just wanted to wish ya luck.
Scuttle : I'll catch ya later. I wouldn't miss it!
Grimsby : Well, now, Eric.
Grimsby : It appears that I was mistaken.
Grimsby : This mystery maiden of yours does, in fact, exist.
Grimsby : And she is lovely.
Grimsby : Congratulations, my dear.
Prince Eric : We wish to be married as soon as possible.
Grimsby : Oh, yes, of course, Eric, but, uh, these things do take time, you know.
Prince Eric : This afternoon, Grimsby. The wedding ship departs at sunset.
Grimsby : Oh. Oh. Very well, Eric, uh, as you wish.
(SNICKERS)
(ORGAN PLAYS)
(CRIES)
(HUMMING THE WEDDING MARCH)
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : What a lovely little bride I'll make My dear, I'll look divine
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : (LAUGHS)
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : Things are working out According to my ultimate design
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : Soon I'll have that little mermaid And the ocean will be mine
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula);Ursula : (CACKLES)
Scuttle : The sea witch! Oh, no! She's gonna... I gotta...
Scuttle : Ariel! Ariel!
Scuttle : Ariel, I was flying... Of course, I was flying.
Scuttle : And... I saw the... The watch... The witch was watching the mirror,
Scuttle : and she was singin' with a stolen set of pipes.
Scuttle : Do you hear what I'm tellin' you?
Scuttle : The prince is marrying the sea witch in disguise!
Sebastian : Are you sure about this?
Scuttle : Have I ever been wrong? I mean, when it's important?
Flounder : What are we gonna do?
Ursula : Before the sun sets on the third day.
(URSULA'S VOICE ECHOES)
Sebastian : Ariel, grab onto that.
Sebastian : Flounder, get her to that boat as fast as your fins can carry you.
Flounder : I'll try!
Sebastian : I gotta get to the sea king. He must know about this.
Scuttle : What about me? What about me?
Sebastian : You!
Sebastian : Find a way to stall that wedding!
Scuttle : Stall the wedding. What am I? What? That's it!
(SQUAWKING)
Scuttle : Move it! Let's go! We got an emergency here.
Scuttle : (SQUAWKING, CHIRPING)
Scuttle : (ORGAN PLAYS)
Scuttle : (GROWLS)
Scuttle : (MAX YELPS)
Bishop : Dearly beloved...
Flounder : (PANTING) Don't worry, Ariel. We're gonna make it.
Flounder : We're almost there.
Bishop : Yes, do you, Eric, take Vanessa to be your lawfully-wedded wife
Bishop : for as long as you both shall live?
Prince Eric : I do.
(SCUTTLE SQUAWKS)
Bishop : And do you...
(SQUAWKING, CHIRPING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS) (BARKS)
All : Oh!
(SEALS BARK)
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : Oh! Oh! Oh!
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : (SCREAMS)
Bishop : Then by the power...
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : Get away from me, you slimy... Oh!
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : Oh!
Vanessa(Disguised Ursula) : Oh, why, you little...
(BARKS)
(GROWLS) (SCREAMS)
(ARIEL'S VOICE VOCALIZING)
Prince Eric : (MOANS) Huh?
(VOCALIZING CONTINUES)
(VOCALIZES)
Prince Eric : Ariel?
Ariel : Eric.
Prince Eric : You... You can talk?
Prince Eric : You're the one.
Ursula : Eric, get away from her.
Prince Eric : It was you all the time.
Ariel : Oh, Eric, I wanted to tell you.
Ursula : Eric, no!
(MOANS)
Ursula : You're too late! (CACKLES)
Ursula : You're too late!
(ALL GASP) (CACKLES)
Ursula : (GASPS) So long, lover boy.
Prince Eric : Ariel!
Ursula : Poor little princess. It's not you I'm after. I've a much bigger fish to...
King Triton : Ursula, stop!
Sebastian : Hmph!
Ursula : Why, King Triton!
Ursula : (CHUCKLES)
Ursula : How are you?
King Triton : Let her go!
Ursula : Not a chance, Triton! She's mine now!
Ursula : We made a deal.
Ariel : Daddy, I'm sorry! I... I didn't mean to! I didn't know!
(URSULA LAUGHS)
You see? The contract's legal, binding and completely unbreakable,
Ursula : even for you.
Ursula : Of course, I always was a girl with an eye for a bargain.
Ursula : The daughter of the great sea king is a very precious commodity.
Ursula : But I might be willing to make an exchange
Ursula : for someone even better.
Grimsby : Eric, what are you doing?
Prince Eric : Grim, I lost her once. I'm not gonna lose her again!
Ursula : Now, do we have a deal?
Ursula : Ha! It's done, then!
Ariel : No! Oh, no!
Sebastian : Your Majesty.
Ariel : Daddy.
Ursula : At last.
Ariel : No.
Ursula : It's mine.
Ariel : You!
Ariel : You monster!
Ursula : Don't fool with me, ya little brat! Contract or no, I'll blast... Ow!
Ursula : Why, you little fool.
Ariel : Eric, look out!
Ursula : After him!
(PANTS)
Sebastian : Come on!
Flotsam and Jetsam : Ow!
Ursula : Say goodbye to your sweetheart.
(SHRIEKS)
(BOTH SCREAM)
Ursula : Babies! My poor little poopsies.
(GROWLS)
Ariel : Eric, you've gotta get away from here.
Prince Eric : No, I won't leave you.
(CACKLES)
(GUTTURAL LAUGHTER)
Ursula : You pitiful, insignificant fools!
Prince Eric : Look out!
Ursula : Now I am the ruler of all the ocean! The waves obey my every whim!
Ariel : Eric!
(ERIC SCREAMS)
Ursula : The sea and all its spoils bow to my power!
Ariel : Eric!
(PANTS)
Ariel : Oh! Oh!
(URSULA CACKLES)
Ursula : So much for true love!
(SCREAMS)
(ALL MOAN)
(MURMURING)
King Triton : She really does love him, doesn't she, Sebastian?
Sebastian : Mmm. Well, it's like I always say, Your Majesty,
Sebastian : children got to be free to lead their own lives.
King Triton : You always say that?
(CHUCKLES)
King Triton : (SIGHS) Then I guess there's just one problem left.
Sebastian : And what's that, Your Majesty?
King Triton : How much I'm going to miss her.
(CHEERING)
(GASPS)
Sebastian : Ah-ha!
(CHEF LOUIS SHOUTS)
Sebastian : (LAUGHS) Yes!
Sebastian : Thank you. Thank you.
Ariel : (WHISPERS) I love you, Daddy.
All : (SINGING) Now we can walk Now we can run
All : Now we can stay all day in the sun
All : Just you and me
All : And I can be
All : Part of your world
All : (CHORUS VOCALIZES)
Sebastian : The seaweed is always greener In somebody else's lake
Sebastian : You dream about going up there But that is a big mistake
Sebastian : Just look at the world around you Right here on the ocean floor
Sebastian : Such wonderful things surround you What more is you lookin' for?
Sebastian : Under the sea Under the sea
Sebastian : Darling, it's better down where it's wetter Take it from me
Sebastian : Up on the shore they work all day Out in the sun they slave away
Sebastian : While we devoting full time to floating under the sea
Sebastian : Down here all the fish is happy As off through the waves they roll, yeah
Sebastian : The fish on the land ain't happy They sad 'cause they in their bowl
Sebastian : But fish in the bowl is lucky They in for a worser fate
Sebastian : One day when the boss get hungry Guess who's gonna be on the plate
Sebastian : Oh, no! Under the sea Under the sea
Sebastian : Nobody beat us Fry us and eat us In fricassee
Sebastian : We what the land folks loves to cook Under the sea we off the hook
Sebastian : We got no troubles Life is the bubbles Under the sea Under the sea Under the sea Under the sea
Sebastian : Since life is sweet here We got the beat here Naturally Naturally
Sebastian : Even the sturgeon and the ray They get the urge and start to play
Sebastian : We got the spirit You got to hear it Under the sea
Sebastian : The newt play the flute The carp play the harp The plaice play the bass and they soundin' sharp
Sebastian : The bass play the brass The chub play the tub The fluke is the duke of soul
Sebastian : The ray, he can play The ling's on the strings The trout's rocking out The blackfish, she sings
Sebastian : The smelt and the sprat They know where it's at And, oh, that blowfish blow
Sebastian : -Yeah, under the sea -Under the sea
Sebastian : -Under the sea -Under the sea
Sebastian : -When the sardine begin the beguine It's music to me Music it is to me
Sebastian : What do they got? A lot of sand
Sebastian : We got a hot crustacean band
Sebastian : Each little clam here know how to jam here under the sea
Sebastian : Each little slug here cutting a rug here under the sea
Sebastian : Each little snail here know how to wail here That's why it's hotter under the water
Sebastian : Yeah, we in luck here down in the muck here Under the sea