Narrator : TWAS A LONG TIME AGO
Narrator : LONGER NOW THAN IT SEEMS
Narrator : IN A PLACE THAT PERHAPS YOU'VE SEEN IN YOUR DREAMS
Narrator : FOR THE STORY THAT YOU ARE ABOUT TO BE TOLD
Narrator : TOOK PLACE IN THE HOLIDAY WORLDS OF OLD
Narrator : NOW YOU'VE PROBABLY WONDERED WHERE HOLIDAYS COME FROM
Narrator : IF YOU HAVEN'T
Narrator : I'D SAY IT'S TIME YOU BEGUN
Halloween Citizens : BOYS AND GIRLS OF EVERY AGE
Halloween Citizens : WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO SEE SOMETHING STRANGE
Halloween Citizens : COME WITH US AND YOU WILL SEE
Halloween Citizens : THIS OUR TOWN OF HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : THIS IS HALLOWEEN THIS IS HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : PUMPKINS SCREAM IN THE DEAD OF NIGHT
Halloween Citizens : THIS IS HALLOWEEN EVERYBODY MAKE A SCENE
Halloween Citizens : TRICK OR TREAT
Halloween Citizens : TILL THE NEIGHBORS GONNA DIE OF FRIGHT
Halloween Citizens : IT'S OUR TOWN EVERYBODY SCREAM
Halloween Citizens : IN THIS TOWN OF HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : I AM THE ONE HIDING UNDER YOUR BED
Halloween Citizens : TEETH GROUND SHARP AND EYES GLOWING RED
Halloween Citizens : I AM THE ONE HIDING UNDER YOUR STAIRS
Halloween Citizens : FINGERS LIKE SNAKES AND SPIDERS IN MY HAIR
Halloween Citizens : THIS IS HALLOWEEN THIS IS HALLOWEEN
Vampires : HALLOWEEN HALLOWEEN
Vampires : IN THIS TOWN WE CALL HOME
Halloween Citizens;Vampires : EVERYONE HAIL TO THE PUMPKIN SONG
Halloween Citizens;Mayor of Halloween Town : IN THIS TOWN DON'T WE LOVE IT NOW
Mayor of Halloween Town : EVERYBODY'S WAITING FOR THE NEXT SURPRISE
Halloween Citizens : ROUND THAT CORNER
Halloween Citizens : MAN HIDING IN THE TRASH CAN
Halloween Citizens : SOMETHING'S WAITING NOW TO POUNCE AND HOW YOU'LL
Halloween Citizens : SCREAM THIS IS HALLOWEEN
Werewolf : RED N BLACK
Melting Man : AND SLIMY GREEN
Werewolf : AREN'T YOU SCARED
Witches : WELL THAT'S JUST FINE
Witches : SAY IT ONCE SAY IT TWICE TAKE A CHANCE AND ROLL THE DICE
Witches : RIDE WITH THE MOON IN THE DEAD OF NIGHT
Haunted Tree : EVERYBODY SCREAM EVERYBODY SCREAM
Skeletons : IN OUR TOWN OF HALLOWEEN
The Clown with the Tear-Away Face : I AM THE CLOWN WITH THE TEARAWAY FACE
The Clown with the Tear-Away Face : HERE IN A FLASH AND GONE WITHOUT A TRACE
Halloween Citizens : I AM THE WHO WHEN YOU CALL WHO'S THERE
Halloween Citizens : I AM THE WIND BLOWING THROUGH YOUR HAIR
Oogie Boogie : I AM THE SHADOW ON THE MOON AT NIGHT
Oogie Boogie : FILLING YOUR DREAMS TO THE BRIM WITH FRIGHT
Halloween Citizens : THIS IS HALLOWEEN THIS IS HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : HALLOWEEN HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : TENDER LUMPLINGS EVERYWHERE
Halloween Citizens : LIFE'S NO FUN WITHOUT A GOOD SCARE
Halloween Citizens : THAT'S OUR JOB
Halloween Citizens : BUT WE'RE NOT MEAN
Halloween Citizens : IN OUR TOWN OF HALLOWEEN
Mayor of Halloween Town : IN THIS TOWN
Mayor of Halloween Town : DON'T WE LOVE IT NOW EVERYONE'S WAITING FOR THE NEXT SURPRISE
Halloween Citizens : SKELETON JACK MIGHT CATCH YOU IN THE BACK
Halloween Citizens : AND SCREAM LIKE A BANSHEE
Halloween Citizens : MAKE YOU JUMP OUT OF YOUR SKIN
Halloween Citizens : THIS IS HALLOWEEN EVERYBODY SCREAM
Halloween Citizens : WON'T YA PLEASE MAKE WAY FOR A VERY SPECIAL GUY
Halloween Citizens : OUR MAN JACK IS KING OF THE PUMPKIN PATCH
Halloween Citizens : EVERYONE HAIL TO THE PUMPKIN KING NOW
Halloween Citizens : THIS IS HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : THIS IS HALLOWEEN HALLOWEEN HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : HALLOWEEN HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : IN THIS TOWN WE CALL HOME
Halloween Citizens : EVERYONE HAIL TO THE PUMPKIN SONG
Halloween Citizens : LA LALA LA HALLOWEEN HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : LA LALA LA
Halloween Citizens : WHEE
Halloween Citizens : IT'S OVER
Halloween Citizens : WE DID IT
Werewolf : WASN'T IT TERRIFYING
Halloween Citizens : WHAT A NIGHT
Mayor of Halloween Town : GREAT HALLOWEEN EVERYBODY
Jack Skellington : I BELIEVE IT WAS OUR MOST HORRIBLE YET
Jack Skellington : THANK YOU EVERYONE
Mayor of Halloween Town : NO THANKS TO YOU JACK
Mayor of Halloween Town : WITHOUT YOUR BRILLIANT LEADERSHIP
Jack Skellington : Jack NOT AT ALL MAYOR
Halloween Citizens : YOU'RE SUCH A SCREAM JACK
Halloween Citizens;Witch : YOU'RE A WITCH'S FONDEST DREAM
Witch : YOU MADE WALLS FALL JACK
Witch : Witch WALLS FALL
Witch : YOU MADE THE VERY MOUNTAINS CRACK JACK
Dr. Finkelstein : THE DEADLY NIGHTSHADE YOU SLIPPED ME WORE OFF SALLY
Sally : LET GO
Dr. Finkelstein : YOU'RE NOT READY FOR SO MUCH EXCITEMENT
Sally : YES I AM
Dr. Finkelstein : YOU'RE COMING WITH ME
Sally : NO I'M NOT
Dr. Finkelstein : COME BACK HERE YOU FOOLISH
Dr. Finkelstein : OAF OH OHH
Undersea Gal : OOH JACK YOU MADE WOUNDS OOZE AND FLESH CRAWL
Jack Skellington : THANK YOU THANK YOU
Jack Skellington : THANK YOU VERY MUCH
Mayor of Halloween Town : Mayor using megaphone HOLD IT
Mayor of Halloween Town : WE HAVEN'T GIVEN OUT THE PRIZES YET
Halloween Citizens : Crowd OOH
Mayor of Halloween Town : OUR FIRST AWARD GOES TO THE VAMPIRES FOR MOST BLOOD DRAINED IN A SINGLE EVENING
Mayor of Halloween Town : Mayor A FRIGHTENING AND HONORABLE MENTION
Mayor of Halloween Town : GOES TO THE FABULOUS DARK LAGOON LEECHES
The Zombie Band : NICE WORK BONE DADDY
Jack Skellington : YEAH I GUESS SO
Jack Skellington : JUST LIKE LAST YEAR AND THE YEAR BEFORE THAT AND THE YEAR BEFORE THAT
Sally : OHH
Jack Skellington : THERE ARE FEW WHO'D DENY AT WHAT I DO I AM THE BEST
Jack Skellington : FOR MY TALENTS ARE RENOWNED FAR AND WIDE
Jack Skellington : WHEN IT COMES TO SURPRISES IN THE MOONLIT NIGHT
Jack Skellington : I EXCEL WITHOUT EVER EVEN TRYING
Jack Skellington : WITH THE SLIGHTEST LITTLE EFFORT OF MY GHOSTLIKE CHARMS
Jack Skellington : I HAVE SEEN GROWN MEN GIVE OUT A SHRIEK
Jack Skellington : WITH THE WAVE OF MY HAND AND A WELLPLACED MOAN
Jack Skellington : I HAVE SWEPT THE VERY BRAVEST OFF THEIR FEET
Jack Skellington : YET YEAR AFTER YEAR IT'S THE SAME ROUTINE
Jack Skellington : AND I GROW SO WEARY OF THE SOUND OF SCREAMS
Jack Skellington : AND I JACK THE PUMPKIN KING
Jack Skellington : HAVE GROWN SO TIRED OF THE SAME OLD THING
Jack Skellington : OH SOMEWHERE DEEP INSIDE OF THESE BONES
Jack Skellington : AN EMPTINESS BEGAN TO GROW
Jack Skellington : THERE'S SOMETHING OUT THERE FAR FROM MY HOME
Jack Skellington : A LONGING THAT I'VE NEVER KNOWN
Jack Skellington : I'M THE MASTER OF FRIGHT AND A DEMON OF LIGHT
Jack Skellington : AND I'LL SCARE YOU RIGHT OUT OF YOUR PANTS
Jack Skellington;Ghosts : OHH
Jack Skellington : TO A GUY IN KENTUCKY I'M MR UNLUCKY
Jack Skellington : AND I'M KNOWN THROUGHOUT ENGLAND AND FRANCE
Jack Skellington : AND SINCE I AM DEAD I CAN TAKE OFF MY HEAD
Jack Skellington : TO RECITE SHAKESPEAREAN QUOTATIONS
Jack Skellington : NO ANIMAL NOR MAN CAN SCREAM LIKE I CAN
Jack Skellington : WITH THE FURY OF MY RECITATIONS
Jack Skellington : BUT WHO HERE WOULD EVER UNDERSTAND
Jack Skellington : THAT THE PUMPKIN KING WITH HIS SKELETON GRIN
Jack Skellington : WOULD TIRE OF HIS CROWN IF THEY ONLY UNDERSTOOD
Jack Skellington : HE'D GIVE IT ALL UP IF HE ONLY COULD
Jack Skellington : OH THERE'S AN EMPTY PLACE IN MY BONES
Jack Skellington : THAT CALLS OUT FOR SOMETHING UNKNOWN
Jack Skellington : THE FAME AND PRAISE COME YEAR AFTER YEAR
Jack Skellington : DOES NOTHING FOR
Jack Skellington : THESE EMPTY TEARS
Sally : JACK
Sally : I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
Dr. Finkelstein : SALLY
Dr. Finkelstein : YOU'VE COME BACK
Sally : I HAD TO
Dr. Finkelstein : FOR THIS
Sally : YES
Dr. Finkelstein : SHALL WE THEN
Dr. Finkelstein : THAT'S TWICE THIS MONTH YOU'VE SLIPPED DEADLY NIGHTSHADE INTO MY TEA AND RUN OFF
Sally : 3 TIMES
Dr. Finkelstein : YOUR MINE YOU KNOW
Dr. Finkelstein : I MADE YOU WITH MY OWN HANDS
Sally : YOU CAN MAKE OTHER CREATIONS
Sally : I'M RESTLESS I CAN'T HELP IT
Dr. Finkelstein : IT'S A PHASE MY DEAR IT'LL PASS
Dr. Finkelstein : WE NEED TO BE PATIENT THAT'S ALL
Sally : BUT I DON'T WANT TO BE PATIENT
Jack Skellington : NO ZERO NOT NOW
Jack Skellington : I'M NOT IN THE MOOD
Jack Skellington : ALL RIGHT
Jack Skellington : HERE YOU GO BOY
The Zombie Band : HUH HEY
Mayor of Halloween Town : MORNING GENTS
Mayor of Halloween Town : JACK YOU HOME
Mayor of Halloween Town : JACK I'VE GOT THE PLANS FOR NEXT HALLOWEEN
Mayor of Halloween Town : I NEED TO GO OVER THEM WITH YOU SO WE CAN GET STARTED
Mayor of Halloween Town : JACK PLEASE I'M ONLY AN ELECTED OFFICIAL HERE I CAN'T MAKE DECISIONS BY MYSELF
Mayor of Halloween Town : JACK
Mayor of Halloween Town : ANSWER ME AAH
The Zombie Band : HE'S NOT HOME
Mayor of Halloween Town : WHERE IS HE
The Zombie Band : HE HASN'T BEEN HOME ALL NIGHT
Mayor of Halloween Town : OHH
Jack Skellington : WHERE ARE WE
Jack Skellington : IT'S SOMEPLACE NEW
Jack Skellington : WHAT IS THIS
Jack Skellington : WHOA
Jack Skellington : WHOOOOA
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS WHAT'S THIS THERE'S COLOR EVERYWHERE
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS THERE'S WHITE THINGS IN THE AIR
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS
Jack Skellington : I CAN'T BELIEVE MY EYES I MUST BE DREAMING WAKE UP JACK THIS ISN'T FAIR
Jack Skellington;Christmas Kids : LA LA LA LA
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS WHAT'S THIS
Jack Skellington : THERE'S SOMETHING VERY WRONG
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS THERE'S PEOPLE SINGING SONGS
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS
Jack Skellington : THE STREETS ARE LINED WITH LITTLE CREATURES LAUGHING EVERYBODY SEEMS SO HAPPY HAVE I POSSIBLY GONE DAFFY WHAT IS THIS
Jack Skellington : THERE'S CHILDREN THROWING SNOWBALLS INSTEAD OF THROWING HEADS
Jack Skellington : THEY'RE BUSY BUILDING TOYS AND ABSOLUTELY NO ONE'S DEAD
Jack Skellington : THERE'S FROST IN EVERY WINDOW OH I CAN'T BELIEVE MY EYES
Jack Skellington : AND IN MY BONES I FEEL THE WARMTH THAT'S COMING FROM INSIDE
Jack Skellington : OH LOOK WHAT'S THIS THEY'RE HANGING MISTLETOE
Jack Skellington : THEY KISS? WHY THAT LOOKS SO UNIQUE
Jack Skellington : INSPIRED
Jack Skellington : THEY'RE GATHERING AROUND TO HEAR A STORY ROASTING CHESTNUTS ON A FIRE
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS IN HERE THEY'VE GOT A LITTLE TREE
Jack Skellington : HOW QUEER AND WHO WOULD EVER THINK
Jack Skellington : AND WHY THEY'RE COVERING IT WITH TINY LITTLE THINGS
Jack Skellington : THEY'VE GOT ELECTRIC LIGHTS ON STRINGS AND THERE'S A SMILE ON EVERYONE
Jack Skellington : SO NOW CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG THIS LOOKS LIKE FUN THIS LOOKS LIKE FUN OH COULD IT BE I GOT MY WISH
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS
Jack Skellington : OH MY WHAT NOW THE CHILDREN ARE ASLEEP
Jack Skellington : BUT LOOK THERE'S NOTHING UNDERNEATH
Jack Skellington : NO GHOULS NO WITCHES HERE TO SCREAM AND SCARE THEM OR ENSNARE THEM ONLY LITTLE COZY THINGS SECURE INSIDE THEIR DREAMLAND
Jack Skellington : AH
Jack Skellington : WHAT'S THIS
Jack Skellington : THE MONSTERS ARE ALL MISSING AND THE NIGHTMARES CAN'T BE FOUND
Jack Skellington : AND IN THEIR PLACE THERE SEEMS TO BE GOOD FEELING ALL AROUND
Jack Skellington : INSTEAD OF SCREAMS I SWEAR I CAN HEAR MUSIC IN THE AIR
Jack Skellington : THE SMELL OF CAKES AND PIES ARE ABSOLUTELY EVERYWHERE
Jack Skellington : THE SIGHTS THE SOUNDS
Jack Skellington : THEY'RE EVERYWHERE AND ALL AROUND
Jack Skellington : I'VE NEVER FELT SO GOOD BEFORE
Jack Skellington : THIS EMPTY PLACE INSIDE OF ME IS FILLING UP I SIMPLY CANNOT GET ENOUGH
Jack Skellington : I WANT IT OH I WANT IT OH I WANT IT FOR MY OWN I'VE GOT TO KNOW I'VE GOT TO KNOW WHAT IS THIS PLACE THAT I HAVE FOUND
Jack Skellington : WHAT IS THIS
Jack Skellington : CHRISTMAS TOWN
Jack Skellington : HMM
Santa Claus : HO HO HO HO HO HO HOHO
Halloween Citizens : THIS HAS NEVER HAPPENED BEFORE
Witch : IT'S SUSPICIOUS
Witch : IT'S PECULIAR
Vampires : IT IS SCARY
Mayor of Halloween Town : STAND ASIDE
Mayor of Halloween Town : COMING THROUGH GRR
Mayor of Halloween Town : UHH
Mayor of Halloween Town : WE'VE GOT TO FIND JACK
Mayor of Halloween Town : THERE'S ONLY 365 DAYS LEFT TILL NEXT HALLOWEEN
Mayor of Halloween Town : IS THERE ANYWHERE WE'VE FORGOTTEN TO CHECK
The Clown with the Tear-Away Face : I LOOKED IN EVERY MAUSOLEUM
Witches : WE OPENED THE SARCOPHAGI
Halloween Citizens : I TROMPED THROUGH THE PUMPKIN PATCH
Vampires : I PEEKED BEHIND THE CYCLOPS EYE
Vampires : I DID BUT HE WASN'T THERE
Mayor of Halloween Town : IT'S TIME TO SOUND THE ALARMS
Sally : FROG'S BREATH WILL OVERPOWER ANY ODOR
Sally : OH
Sally : BITTER
Sally : WORM'S WORT WHERE'S THAT WORM'S WORT
Dr. Finkelstein : SALLY?
Dr. Finkelstein : THAT SOUP READY YET
Sally : AH
Sally : COMING
Sally : LUNCH
Dr. Finkelstein : AH WHAT'S THAT
Dr. Finkelstein : WORM'S WORT
Dr. Finkelstein : MMM
Dr. Finkelstein : AND FROG'S BREATH
Sally : WELL WHAT'S WRONG
Sally : II THOUGHT YOU LIKED FROG'S BREATH
Dr. Finkelstein : NOTHING'S MORE SUSPICIOUS THAN FROG'S BREATH
Dr. Finkelstein : UNTIL YOU TASTE IT
Dr. Finkelstein : I WON'T SWALLOW A SPOONFUL
Sally : I'M NOT HUNGRY
Sally : OOPS
Dr. Finkelstein : YOU WANT ME TO STARVE
Dr. Finkelstein : AN OLD MAN LIKE ME WHO HARDLY HAS STRENGTH AS IT IS
Dr. Finkelstein : ME TO WHOM YOU OWE YOUR VERY LIFE
Sally : OH DON'T BE SILLY
Sally : MMM SEE SCRUMPTIOUS
Mayor of Halloween Town : DID ANYONE THINK TO DREDGE THE LAKE
Vampires : THIS MORNING
Witch : HEAR THAT
Witch : WHAT
Witch : SHH
Vampires : ZERO
Halloween Citizens : JACK'S BACK
Halloween Citizens : YAY YAY
Mayor of Halloween Town : WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
Jack Skellington : CALL A TOWN MEETING AND I'LL TELL EVERYONE ALL ABOUT IT
Mayor of Halloween Town : WHEN
Jack Skellington : IMMEDIATELY
Mayor of Halloween Town : TOWN MEETING
Mayor of Halloween Town : TOWN MEETING TONIGHT
Sally : OH
The Clown with the Tear-Away Face : HA HA HA
Jack Skellington : LISTEN EVERYONE
Jack Skellington : I WANT TO TELL YOU ABOUT CHRISTMAS TOWN
Jack Skellington : THERE WERE OBJECTS SO PECULIAR THEY WERE NOT TO BE BELIEVED
Jack Skellington : ALL AROUND THINGS TO TANTALIZE MY BRAIN
Jack Skellington : IT'S A WORLD UNLIKE ANYTHING I'VE EVER SEEN
Jack Skellington : AND AS HARD AS I TRY
Jack Skellington : I CAN'T SEEM TO DESCRIBE LIKE A MOST IMPROBABLE DREAM
Jack Skellington : BUT YOU MUST BELIEVE WHEN I TELL YOU THIS
Jack Skellington : IT'S AS REAL AS MY SKULL AND IT DOES EXIST
Jack Skellington : HERE LET ME SHOW YOU
Halloween Citizens : OOH
Sally : OOH
Jack Skellington : THIS IS A THING CALLED A PRESENT
Jack Skellington : THE WHOLE THING STARTS WITH A BOX
Halloween Citizens : A BOX
Halloween Citizens : IS IT STEEL
Halloween Citizens : ARE THERE LOCKS
Halloween Citizens : IS IT FILLED WITH A POX
Halloween Citizens : A POX HOW DELIGHTFUL A POX
Jack Skellington : IF YOU PLEASE
Jack Skellington : JUST A BOX WITH BRIGHTCOLORED PAPER
Jack Skellington : AND THE WHOLE THING'S TOPPED WITH A BOW
Witch : A BOW
Witch : BUT WHY
Witch : HOW UGLY WHAT'S IN IT
Witches : WHAT'S IN IT
Jack Skellington : THAT'S THE POINT OF THE THING NOT TO KNOW
The Clown with the Tear-Away Face : IT'S A BAT
Halloween Citizens : WILL IT BEND
The Clown with the Tear-Away Face : IT'S A RAT
Halloween Citizens : WILL IT BREAK
Halloween Citizens : PERHAPS IT'S THE HEAD THAT I FOUND IN THE LAKE
Jack Skellington : LISTEN NOW
Jack Skellington : YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
Jack Skellington : THAT'S NOT THE POINT OF CHRISTMAS LAND
Jack Skellington : NOW PAY ATTENTION
Jack Skellington : WE PICK UP AN OVERSIZED SOCK
Jack Skellington : AND HANG IT LIKE THIS ON THE WALL
Halloween Citizens : OH YES DOES IT STILL HAVE A FOOT
Halloween Citizens : LET ME SEE LET ME LOOK
Halloween Citizens : IS IT ROTTED AND COVERED WITH GOOK
Jack Skellington : UM LET ME EXPLAIN
Jack Skellington : THERE'S NO FOOT INSIDE BUT THERE'S CANDY
Jack Skellington : OR SOMETIMES IT'S FILLED WITH SMALL TOYS
Halloween Citizens : SMALL TOYS DO THEY BITE
Halloween Citizens : DO THEY SNAP
Halloween Citizens : OR EXPLODE IN A SACK
Mummy Boy : OR PERHAPS THEY JUST SPRING OUT AND SCARE GIRLS AND BOYS
Mayor of Halloween Town : WHAT A SPLENDID IDEA
Mayor of Halloween Town : THIS CHRISTMAS SOUNDS FUN
Mayor of Halloween Town : I FULLY ENDORSE IT
Mayor of Halloween Town : LET'S TRY IT AT ONCE
Jack Skellington : EVERYONE PLEASE
Jack Skellington : NOW NOT SO FAST
Jack Skellington : THERE'S SOMETHING HERE THAT YOU DON'T QUITE GRASP
Jack Skellington : WELL
Jack Skellington : I MAY AS WELL GIVE THEM WHAT THEY WANT
Jack Skellington : AND THE BEST I MUST CONFESS I HAVE SAVED FOR THE LAST
Jack Skellington : FOR THE RULER OF THIS CHRISTMAS LAND
Jack Skellington : IS A FEARSOME KING WITH A DEEP MIGHTY VOICE
Jack Skellington : LEAST THAT'S WHAT I'VE COME TO UNDERSTAND
Jack Skellington : AND I'VE ALSO HEARD IT TOLD THAT HE'S SOMETHING TO BEHOLD
Jack Skellington : LIKE A LOBSTER HUGE AND RED
Jack Skellington : WHEN HE SETS OUT TO SLAY WITH HIS RAIN GEAR ON
Jack Skellington : CARTING BULGING SACKS WITH HIS BIG GREAT ARMS
Jack Skellington : THAT IS SO I'VE HEARD IT SAID
Jack Skellington : AND ON A DARK COLD NIGHT UNDER FULL MOONLIGHT
Jack Skellington : HE FLIES INTO A FOG LIKE A VULTURE IN THE SKY
Jack Skellington : AND THEY CALL HIM
Jack Skellington : SANDY CLAWS
Jack Skellington : HEH HEH HEH
Jack Skellington : WELL AT LEAST THEY'RE EXCITED
Jack Skellington : BUT THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND
Jack Skellington : THAT SPECIAL KIND OF FEELING IN CHRISTMAS LAND
Jack Skellington : OH WELL
Jack Skellington : HMM
Jack Skellington : THERE'S GOT TO BE A LOGICAL WAY TO EXPLAIN THIS CHRISTMAS THING
Dr. Finkelstein : YOU'VE POISONED ME FOR THE LAST TIME YOU WRETCHED GIRL
Dr. Finkelstein : OHH MY HEAD
Dr. Finkelstein : THE DOOR IS OPEN
Jack Skellington : HELLO
Dr. Finkelstein : JACK SKELLINGTON
Dr. Finkelstein : UP HERE MY BOY
Jack Skellington : DOCTOR
Jack Skellington : I NEED TO BORROW SOME EQUIPMENT
Dr. Finkelstein : IS THAT SO
Dr. Finkelstein : WHATEVER FOR
Jack Skellington : I'M CONDUCTING A SERIES OF EXPERIMENTS
Dr. Finkelstein : HOW PERFECTLY MARVELOUS
Dr. Finkelstein : CURIOSITY KILLED THE CAT YOU KNOW
Jack Skellington : I KNOW
Dr. Finkelstein : COME ON INTO THE LAB AND WE'LL GET YOU ALL FIXED UP
Sally : HMM
Sally : EXPERIMENTS?
Jack Skellington : ZERO I'M HOME
Jack Skellington : INTERESTING REACTION
Jack Skellington : BUT WHAT DOES IT MEAN
Dr. Finkelstein : YOU CAN COME OUT NOW IF YOU PROMISE TO BEHAVE
Dr. Finkelstein : SALLY
Dr. Finkelstein : OOH GONE AGAIN
Jack Skellington : HMM
Sally : OH
Vampires : SOMETHING'S UP WITH JACK SOMETHING'S UP WITH JACK
Vampires : DON'T KNOW IF WE'RE EVER GOING TO GET HIM BACK
Werewolf : HE'S ALL ALONE UP THERE LOCKED AWAY INSIDE
Halloween Citizens : NEVER SAYS A WORD
Halloween Citizens : HOPE HE HASN'T DIED
Halloween Citizens : SOMETHING'S UP WITH JACK SOMETHING'S UP WITH JACK
Jack Skellington : CHRISTMASTIME IS BUZZING IN MY SKULL
Jack Skellington : WILL IT LET ME BE I CANNOT TELL
Jack Skellington : THERE'S SO MANY THINGS I CANNOT GRASP
Jack Skellington : WHEN I THINK I'VE GOT IT AND THEN AT LAST
Jack Skellington : THROUGH MY BONY FINGERS IT DOES SLIP
Jack Skellington : LIKE A SNOWFLAKE IN A FIERY GRIP
Jack Skellington : SOMETHING HERE I'M NOT QUITE GETTING THOUGH I TRY I KEEP FORGETTING
Jack Skellington : LIKE A MEMORY LONG SINCE PASSED
Jack Skellington : HERE IN AN INSTANT GONE IN A FLASH
Jack Skellington : WHAT DOES IT MEAN WHAT DOES IT MEAN
Jack Skellington : IN THESE LITTLE BRICABRAC A SECRET'S WAITING TO BE CRACKED
Jack Skellington : THESE DOLLS AND TOYS CONFUSE ME SO CONFOUND IT ALL I LOVE IT THOUGH
Jack Skellington : SIMPLE OBJECTS NOTHING MORE BUT SOMETHING'S HIDDEN THROUGH A DOOR
Jack Skellington : THOUGH I DO NOT HAVE THE KEY
Jack Skellington : SOMETHING'S HERE I CANNOT SEE
Jack Skellington : WHAT DOES IT MEAN WHAT DOES IT MEAN
Jack Skellington : WHAT DOES IT MEAN
Jack Skellington : HMM
Jack Skellington : I'VE READ THESE CHRISTMAS BOOKS SO MANY TIMES
Jack Skellington : I KNOW THE STORIES AND I KNOW THE RHYMES
Jack Skellington : I KNOW THE CHRISTMAS CAROLS ALL BY HEART
Jack Skellington : MY SKULL'S SO FULL IT'S TEARING ME APART
Jack Skellington : AS OFTEN AS I'VE READ THEM SOMETHING'S WRONG
Jack Skellington : SO HARD TO PUT MY BONY FINGER ON
Jack Skellington : OR PERHAPS IT'S REALLY NOT AS DEEP AS I'VE BEEN LEAD TO THINK
Jack Skellington : AM I TRYING MUCH TOO HARD
Jack Skellington : OF COURSE I'VE BEEN TOO CLOSE TO SEE THE ANSWER'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME
Jack Skellington : RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME
Jack Skellington : IT'S SIMPLE REALLY VERY CLEAR LIKE MUSIC DRIFTING IN THE AIR
Jack Skellington : INVISIBLE BUT EVERYWHERE
Jack Skellington : JUST BECAUSE I CANNOT SEE IT DOESN'T MEAN I CAN'T BELIEVE IT
Jack Skellington : YOU KNOW I THINK THIS CHRISTMAS THING IS NOT AS TRICKY AS IT SEEMS
Jack Skellington : AND WHY SHOULD THEY HAVE ALL THE FUN
Jack Skellington : IT SHOULD BELONG TO ANYONE
Jack Skellington : NOT ANYONE IN FACT BUT ME
Jack Skellington : WHY I COULD MAKE A CHRISTMAS TREE
Jack Skellington : AND THERE'S NO REASON I CAN FIND
Jack Skellington : I COULDN'T HANDLE CHRISTMASTIME
Jack Skellington : I BET I COULD IMPROVE IT TOO
Jack Skellington : AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I'LL DO
Jack Skellington : HEE HEE HEE HEE HEE
Jack Skellington : EUREKA
Jack Skellington : THIS YEAR CHRISTMAS WILL BE
Jack Skellington : OURS
Mayor of Halloween Town : PATIENCE EVERYONE
Mayor of Halloween Town : JACK HAS A SPECIAL JOB FOR EACH OF YOU
Mayor of Halloween Town : DR FINKLESTEIN
Mayor of Halloween Town : YOUR CHRISTMAS ASSIGNMENT IS READY
Mayor of Halloween Town : DR FINKLESTEIN TO THE FRONT OF THE LINE
Toy : WAH
Vampires : WHAT KIND OF NOISE IS THAT FOR A BABY TO MAKE
Jack Skellington : PERHAPS IT CAN BE IMPROVED
Vampires : NO PROBLEM
Jack Skellington : I KNEW IT
Jack Skellington : DOCTOR THANK YOU FOR COMING
Jack Skellington : WE NEED SOME OF THESE
Dr. Finkelstein : HMM
Dr. Finkelstein : THEIR CONSTRUCTION SHOULD BE EXCEEDINGLY SIMPLE I THINK
Mayor of Halloween Town : HOW HORRIBLE OUR CHRISTMAS WILL BE
Jack Skellington : NO HOW JOLLY
Mayor of Halloween Town : OH HOW JOLLY OUR CHRISTMAS WILL BE
Mayor of Halloween Town : WHOA HEY
Mayor of Halloween Town : GRR
Mayor of Halloween Town : WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE
Lock : JACK SENT FOR US
Shock : SPECIFICALLY
Shock;Barrel : BY NAME
Lock : LOCK
Shock : SHOCK
Barrel : BARREL
Mayor of Halloween Town : JACK JACK
Mayor of Halloween Town : IT'S BOOGIE'S BOYS
Jack Skellington : AH HALLOWEEN'S FINEST TRICKORTREATERS
Jack Skellington : THE JOB I HAVE FOR YOU IS TOP SECRET
Jack Skellington : IT REQUIRES CRAFT CUNNING MISCHIEF
Shock : AND WE THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T LIKE US JACK
Jack Skellington : ABSOLUTELY NO ONE IS TO KNOW ABOUT IT NOT A SOUL NOW
Jack Skellington : Christmastime No
Mayor of Halloween Town : OW
Jack Skellington : AND ONE MORE THING
Jack Skellington : LEAVE THAT NOACCOUNT OOGIE BOOGIE OUT OF THIS
Barrel : WHATEVER YOU SAY JACK
Shock : OF COURSE JACK
Lock : WOULDN'T DREAM OF IT JACK
Boogie's Boys : KIDNAP MR SANDY CLAWS
Lock : I WANNA DO IT
Barrel : LET'S DRAW STRAWS
Shock : JACK SAID WE SHOULD WORK TOGETHER
Barrel : 3 OF A KIND
Lock : BIRDS OF A FEATHER
Boogie's Boys : NOW AND FOREVER
Shock : LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA
Shock : KIDNAP THE SANDY CLAWS LOCK HIM UP REAL TIGHT
Shock : THROW AWAY THE KEY AND THEN TURN OFF ALL THE LIGHTS
Shock : FIRST WE'RE GOING TO SET SOME BAIT INSIDE A NASTY TRAP AND WAIT
Shock : WHEN HE COMES ASNIFFING WE WILL SNAP THE TRAP AND CLOSE THE GATE
Shock : WAIT I'VE GOT A BETTER PLAN TO CATCH THIS BIG RED LOBSTER MAN
Lock : LET'S POP HIM IN A BOILING POT AND WHEN HE'S DONE WE'LL BUTTER HIM UP
Shock : KIDNAP THE SANDY CLAWS THROW HIM IN A BOX
Shock : BURY HIM FOR 90 YEARS THEN SEE IF HE TALKS
Shock : THEN MR OOGIE BOOGIE MAN
Boogie's Boys : CAN TAKE THE WHOLE THING OVER THEN
Boogie's Boys : HE'LL BE SO PLEASED I DO DECLARE
Boogie's Boys : THAT HE WILL COOK HIM RARE WHEE
Oogie Boogie : AAH EEE
Lock : I SAY THAT WE TAKE A CANNON AIM IT AT HIS DOOR AND THEN
Lock : KNOCK 3 TIMES AND WHEN HE ANSWERS SANDY CLAWS WILL BE NO MORE
Shock : YOU'RE SO STUPID THINK NOW IF WE BLOW HIM UP TO SMITHEREENS
Shock : WE MAY LOSE SOME PIECES AND THEN JACK WILL BEAT US BLACK AND GREEN
Shock : KIDNAP THE SANDY CLAWS TIE HIM IN A BAG
Shock : THROW HIM IN THE OCEAN THEN SEE IF HE IS SAD
Boogie's Boys : BECAUSE MR OOGIE BOOGIE IS THE MEANEST GUY AROUND
Boogie's Boys : IF I WERE ON HIS BOOGIE LIST
Boogie's Boys : I'D GET OUT OF TOWN
Barrel : HE'LL BE SO PLEASED BY OUR SUCCESS
Barrel : THAT HE'LL REWARD US TOO I'LL BET
Boogie's Boys : PERHAPS HE'LL MAKE HIS SPECIAL BREW
Boogie's Boys : OF SNAKE AND SPIDER STEW MMM
Boogie's Boys : WE'RE HIS LITTLE HENCHMEN AND WE TAKE OUR JOB WITH PRIDE
Boogie's Boys : WE DO OUR BEST TO PLEASE HIM AND STAY ON HIS GOOD SIDE
Shock : I WISH MY COHORTS WEREN'T SO DUMB
Barrel : I'M NOT THE DUMB ONE
Lock : YOU'RE NO FUN
Shock : SHUT UP
Lock : MAKE ME
Shock : I'VE GOT SOMETHING LISTEN NOW
Shock : THIS ONE IS REAL GOOD YOU'LL SEE
Shock : WE'LL SEND A PRESENT TO HIS DOOR
Shock : UPON THERE'LL BE A NOTE TO READ
Shock : NOW IN THE BOX WE'LL WAIT AND HIDE
Shock : UNTIL HIS CURIOSITY
Shock : ENTICES HIM TO LOOK INSIDE
Boogie's Boys : AND THEN WE'LL HAVE HIM 1 2 3
Shock : KIDNAP THE SANDY CLAWS BEAT HIM WITH A STICK
Shock : LOCK HIM UP FOR 90 YEARS SEE WHAT MAKES HIM TICK
Boogie's Boys : KIDNAP THE SANDY CLAWS CHOP HIM INTO BITS
Boogie's Boys : MR OOGIE BOOGIE IS SURE TO GET HIS KICKS
Boogie's Boys : KIDNAP THE SANDY CLAWS SEE WHAT WE WILL SEE
Boogie's Boys : LOCK HIM IN A CAGE AND THEN THROW AWAY THE KEY
Oogie Boogie : SANDY CLAWS HA
Jack Skellington : IT GOES SOMETHING LIKE THIS
Jack Skellington : HOW ABOUT IT THINK YOU CAN MANAGE
The Zombie Band : A 1 AND A 2 AND A 3 AND A
Mayor of Halloween Town : NEXT
Jack Skellington : FANTASTIC
Jack Skellington : NOW WHY DON'T YOU ALL PRACTICE ON THAT AND WE'LL BE IN GREAT SHAPE
Jack Skellington : SALLY I NEED YOUR HELP MORE THAN ANYONE
Sally : YOU CERTAINLY DO JACK I HAD THE MOST TERRIBLE VISION
Jack Skellington : THAT'S SPLENDID
Sally : NO IT WAS ABOUT YOUR CHRISTMAS
Sally : THERE WAS SMOKE AND FIRE
Jack Skellington : THAT'S NOT MY CHRISTMAS
Jack Skellington : MY CHRISTMAS IS FILLED WITH LAUGHTER AND JOY
Jack Skellington : AND THIS
Jack Skellington : MY SANDY CLAWS OUTFIT
Jack Skellington : I WANT YOU TO MAKE IT
Sally : JACK PLEASE LISTEN TO ME
Sally : IT'S GOING TO BE A DISASTER
Jack Skellington : HOW COULD IT BE
Jack Skellington : JUST FOLLOW THE PATTERN
Jack Skellington : THIS PART'S RED THE TRIM IS WHITE
Sally : IT'S A MISTAKE JACK
Jack Skellington : NOW DON'T BE MODEST
Jack Skellington : WHO ELSE IS CLEVER ENOUGH TO MAKE MY SANDY CLAWS OUTFIT
Mayor of Halloween Town : NEXT
Jack Skellington : I HAVE EVERY CONFIDENCE IN YOU
Sally : BUT IT SEEMS WRONG TO ME VERY WRONG
Jack Skellington : THIS DEVICE IS CALLED A NUTCRACKER
Boogie's Boys : JACK JACK WE GOT HIM WE GOT HIM
Jack Skellington : PERFECT
Jack Skellington : OPEN IT UP QUICKLY
Jack Skellington : THAT'S NOT SANDY CLAWS
Shock : IT ISN'T
Lock : WHO IS IT
Halloween Citizens : BUNNY
Jack Skellington : NOT SANDY CLAWS TAKE HIM BACK
Lock : WE FOLLOWED YOUR INSTRUCTIONS
Barrel : WE WENT THROUGH THE DOOR
Jack Skellington : WHICH DOOR THERE'S MORE THAN ONE
Jack Skellington : SANDY CLAWS IS BEHIND THE DOOR SHAPED LIKE THIS
Shock : I TOLD YOU
Boogie's Boys : KNOCK IT OFF OW OW
Boogie's Boys : AAH AAH AAH
Jack Skellington : I'M VERY SORRY FOR THE INCONVENIENCE SIR
Jack Skellington : TAKE HIM HOME FIRST
Jack Skellington : AND APOLOGIZE AGAIN
Jack Skellington : BE CAREFUL WITH SANDY CLAWS WHEN YOU FETCH HIM
Jack Skellington : TREAT HIM NICELY
Boogie's Boys : GOT IT
Shock : WE'LL GET IT RIGHT
Boogie's Boys : NEXT TIME
Dr. Finkelstein : YOU WILL BE A DECIDED IMPROVEMENT OVER THAT TREACHEROUS SALLY
Igor : MASTER
Igor : THE PLANS
Dr. Finkelstein : EXCELLENT IGOR
Halloween Citizens : THIS TIME
Halloween Citizens : MAKING CHRISTMAS
Mayor of Halloween Town : MAKING CHRISTMAS MAKING CHRISTMAS IS SO FINE
Halloween Citizens : IT'S OURS THIS TIME
Halloween Citizens : AND WON'T THE CHILDREN BE SURPRISED
Halloween Citizens : MAKING CHRISTMAS
Witches : TIME TO GIVE THEM SOMETHING FUN
Undersea Gal : THEY'LL TALK ABOUT FOR YEARS TO COME
Halloween Citizens : LET'S HAVE A CHEER FROM EVERYONE
Halloween Citizens : IT'S TIME TO PARTY
Halloween Citizens : MAKING CHRISTMAS
Vampires : SNAKES AND MICE GET WRAPPED UP SO NICE
Vampires : WITH SPIDER LEGS AND PRETTY BOWS
Halloween Citizens : IT'S OURS THIS TIME
Halloween Citizens : ALL TOGETHER THAT AND THIS
Halloween Citizens : WITH ALL OUR TRICKS WE'RE MAKING CHRISTMASTIME
Werewolf : HERE COMES JACK
Jack Skellington : I DON'T BELIEVE WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME
Jack Skellington : MY HOPES
Jack Skellington : MY DREAMS
Jack Skellington : MY FANTASY
Jack Skellington : HEE HEE HEE HEE
Halloween Citizens : WON'T THEY BE IMPRESSED I AM A GENIUS
Halloween Citizens : SEE HOW I TRANSFORMED THIS OLD RAT INTO A MOST DELIGHTFUL HAT
Halloween Citizens : HMMM
Jack Skellington : MY COMPLIMENTS FROM ME TO YOU ON THIS YOUR MOST INTRIGUING HAT
Jack Skellington : CONSIDER THOUGH THIS SUBSTITUTE A BAT IN PLACE OF THIS OLD RAT
Jack Skellington : NO NO NO NOW THAT'S ALL WRONG THIS THING WILL NEVER MAKE A PRESENT
Jack Skellington : IT'S BEEN DEAD FOR MUCH TOO LONG
Jack Skellington : TRY SOMETHING FRESHER SOMETHING PLEASANT
Jack Skellington : TRY AGAIN DON'T GIVE UP
Halloween Citizens : ALL TOGETHER THAT AND THIS
Halloween Citizens : WITH ALL OUR TRICKS WE'RE MAKING CHRISTMASTIME
Halloween Citizens : THIS TIME THIS TIME THIS TIME
Halloween Citizens : MAKING CHRISTMAS MAKING CHRISTMAS
Halloween Citizens : LA LA LA
Halloween Citizens : IT'S ALMOST HERE
Werewolf : AND WE CAN'T WAIT
Halloween Citizens : SO RING THE BELLS AND CELEBRATE
Halloween Citizens : CAUSE WHEN THE FULL MOON STARTS TO CLIMB
Halloween Citizens : WE'LL ALL SING OUT
Jack Skellington : IT'S CHRISTMASTIME
Jack Skellington : HEE HEE HEE
Santa Claus : KATHLEEN BOBBY SUSIE YES SUSIE'S BEEN NICE
Santa Claus : NICE NICE NAUGHTY NICE NICE NICE
Santa Claus : THERE ARE HARDLY ANY NAUGHTY CHILDREN THIS YEAR
Santa Claus : NOW WHO COULD THAT BE
Boogie's Boys : TRICK OR TREAT
Santa Claus : HUH
Boogie's Boys : YEEEAH
Sally : YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE YOURSELF JACK NOT AT ALL
Jack Skellington : ISN'T THAT WONDERFUL
Jack Skellington : IT COULDN'T BE MORE WONDERFUL
Sally : BUT YOU'RE THE PUMPKIN KING
Jack Skellington : NOT ANYMORE
Jack Skellington : AND I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER NOW
Sally : JACK I KNOW YOU THINK SOMETHING'S MISSING BUT
Jack Skellington : OW
Sally : SORRY
Jack Skellington : YOU'RE RIGHT
Jack Skellington : SOMETHING IS MISSING BUT WHAT
Jack Skellington : I'VE GOT THE BEARD THE COAT THE BOOTS
Boogie's Boys : JACK JACK
Boogie's Boys : THIS TIME WE BAGGED HIM
Lock : THIS TIME WE REALLY DID
Barrel : HE SURE IS BIG JACK
Shock : AND HEAVY
Santa Claus : LET ME OUT
Jack Skellington : SANDY CLAWS IN PERSON
Jack Skellington : WHAT A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU
Jack Skellington : WHY YOU HAVE HANDS
Jack Skellington : YOU DON'T HAVE CLAWS AT ALL
Santa Claus : WHERE AM I
Jack Skellington : SURPRISED AREN'T YOU
Jack Skellington : I KNEW YOU WOULD BE
Jack Skellington : YOU DON'T NEED TO HAVE ANOTHER WORRY ABOUT CHRISTMAS THIS YEAR
Santa Claus : WHAT... WHA... WHAT?
Jack Skellington : CONSIDER THIS A VACATION SANDY A REWARD
Jack Skellington : IT'S YOUR TURN TO TAKE IT EASY
Santa Claus : BUT THERE MUST BE SOME MISTAKE
Jack Skellington : SEE THAT HE'S COMFORTABLE
Jack Skellington : JUST A SECOND FELLAS
Jack Skellington : OF COURSE
Jack Skellington : THAT'S WHAT I'M MISSING
Santa Claus : BU BU... BUT
Jack Skellington : THANKS
Santa Claus : YOU JUST CAN'T
Santa Claus : HOLD ON WHERE ARE WE GOING NOW
Jack Skellington : HO HO HO NO
Sally : THIS IS WORSE THAN I THOUGHT
Sally : MUCH WORSE
Sally : I KNOW
Sally : ME ON VACATION ON CHRISTMAS EVE
Barrel : WHERE ARE WE TAKING HIM
Shock : WHERE
Lock : TO OOGIE BOOGIE OF COURSE
Lock : THERE ISN'T ANYWHERE IN THE WHOLE WORLD MORE COMFORTABLE THAN THAT
Lock : AND JACK SAID TO MAKE HIM COMFORTABLE
Lock : DIDN'T HE
Shock;Barrel : YES HE DID
Santa Claus : HAVEN'T YOU HEARD OF PEACE ON EARTH
Santa Claus : AND GOODWILL TOWARD MEN
Boogie's Boys : NO HA HA HA HA HA
Sally : UHH
Sally : THIS'LL STOP JACK
Dr. Finkelstein : WHAT A JOY TO THINK OF ALL WE'LL HAVE IN COMMON
Dr. Finkelstein : WE'LL HAVE CONVERSATIONS WORTH HAVING
Santa Claus : DON'T DO THIS
Santa Claus : NAUGHTY CHILDREN NEVER GET ANY PRESENTS
Shock : I THINK HE MIGHT BE TOO BIG
Santa Claus : UHH
Lock : NO HE'S NOT
Lock : IF HE CAN GO DOWN A CHIMNEY
Lock : HE CAN FIT DOWN HERE
Oogie Boogie : WELL WELL WELL WHAT HAVE WE HERE
Oogie Boogie : SANDY CLAWS
Oogie Boogie : HUH OH I'M REALLY SCARED
Oogie Boogie : SO YOU'RE THE ONE EVERYBODY'S TALKIN ABOUT
Oogie Boogie : HA HA HA
Oogie Boogie : YOU'RE JOKIN YOU'RE JOKIN
Oogie Boogie : I CAN'T BELIEVE MY EYES
Oogie Boogie : YOU'RE JOKIN ME YOU GOTTA BE
Oogie Boogie : THIS CAN'T BE THE RIGHT GUY
Oogie Boogie : HE'S ANCIENT HE'S UGLY
Oogie Boogie : I DON'T KNOW WHICH IS WORSE
Oogie Boogie : I MIGHT JUST SPLIT A SEAM NOW IF I DON'T DIE LAUGHING FIRST
Oogie Boogie : MR OOGIE BOOGIE SAYS THERE'S TROUBLE CLOSE AT HAND
Oogie Boogie : YOU'D BETTER PAY ATTENTION NOW
Oogie Boogie : CAUSE I'M THE BOOGIE MAN
Oogie Boogie : AND IF YOU AREN'T SHAKIN
Oogie Boogie : THERE'S SOMETHING VERY WRONG
Oogie Boogie : CAUSE THIS MAY BE THE LAST TIME
Oogie Boogie : YOU HEAR THE BOOGIE SONG
Oogie Boogie : WOHHH WOHHH WOHHH WOHHH
Oogie Boogie : WHOAOHHH WHOAOHHH
Oogie Boogie : I'M THE OOGIE BOOGIE MAN
Oogie Boogie : RELEASE ME NOW OR YOU MUST FACE THE DIRE CONSEQUENCES
Oogie Boogie : THE CHILDREN ARE EXPECTING ME SO PLEASE COME TO YOUR SENSES
Oogie Boogie : YOU'RE JOKIN YOU'RE JOKIN I CAN'T BELIEVE MY EARS
Oogie Boogie : WOULD SOMEONE SHUT THIS FELLA UP
Oogie Boogie : I'M DROWNIN IN MY TEARS
Oogie Boogie : IT'S FUNNY I'M LAUGHING
Oogie Boogie : YOU REALLY ARE TOO MUCH
Oogie Boogie : AND NOW WITH YOUR PERMISSION
Oogie Boogie : I'M GOING TO DO MY STUFF
Oogie Boogie : WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
Oogie Boogie : I'M GONNA DO THE BEST I CAN
Oogie Boogie : WHOAOHH
Oogie Boogie : THE SOUND OF THE DICE TO ME IS MUSIC IN THE AIR
Oogie Boogie : CAUSE I'M A GAMBLIN BOOGIE MAN
Oogie Boogie : ALTHOUGH I DON'T PLAY FAIR
Oogie Boogie : IT'S MUCH MORE FUN I MUST CONFESS
Oogie Boogie : WITH LIVES ON THE LINE
Oogie Boogie : NOT MINE OF COURSE BUT YOURS OLD BOY
Oogie Boogie : NOW THAT'D BE JUST FINE
Oogie Boogie : RELEASE ME FAST OR YOU WILL HAVE TO ANSWER FOR THIS HEINOUS ACT
Oogie Boogie : OH BROTHER YOU'RE SOMETHING YOU PUT ME IN A SPIN
Oogie Boogie : YOU AREN'T COMPREHENDING
Oogie Boogie : THE POSITION THAT YOU'RE IN
Oogie Boogie : IT'S HOPELESS YOU'RE FINISHED
Oogie Boogie : YOU HAVEN'T GOT A PRAYER
Oogie Boogie : CAUSE I'M MR OOGIE BOOGIE
Oogie Boogie : AND YOU AIN'T GOING NOWHERE
Oogie Boogie : HA HA HA HA HA
Mayor of Halloween Town : THINK OF US AS YOU SOAR TRIUMPHANTLY THROUGH THE SKY
Mayor of Halloween Town : OUTSHINING EVERY STAR
Mayor of Halloween Town : YOUR SILHOUETTE A DARK BLOT ON THE MOON
Mayor of Halloween Town : YOU WHO ARE OUR PRIDE
Mayor of Halloween Town : YOU WHO ARE OUR GLORY
Mayor of Halloween Town : YOU WHO HAVE FRIGHTENED BILLIONS INTO AN EARLY GRAVE
Mayor of Halloween Town : YOU WHO HAVE EH
Mayor of Halloween Town : DEVASTATED THE SOULS OF THE LIVING
Jack Skellington : OH NO
Jack Skellington : WE CAN'T TAKE OFF IN THIS
Jack Skellington : THE REINDEER CAN'T SEE AN INCH IN FRONT OF THEIR NOSES
Sally : WHEW
Vampires : THIS FOG'S AS THICK ASAS
Halloween Citizens : JELLIED BRAINS
Vampires : THICKER
Jack Skellington : THERE GO ALL OF MY HOPES
Jack Skellington : MY PRECIOUS PLANS MY GLORIOUS DREAMS
Halloween Citizens : THERE GOES CHRISTMAS
Halloween Citizens : AW
Jack Skellington : NO ZERO DOWN BOY
Jack Skellington : MY WHAT A BRILLIANT NOSE YOU HAVE
Jack Skellington : THE BETTER TO LIGHT MY WAY
Jack Skellington : TO THE HEAD OF THE TEAM ZERO
Jack Skellington : WE'RE OFF
Sally : WAIT JACK NO
Jack Skellington : HO HO HO HA HA HA HA HO
Sally : GOODBYE JACK MY DEAREST JACK
Sally : OH HOW I HOPE MY PREMONITION IS WRONG
Sally : I SENSE THERE'S SOMETHING IN THE WIND
Sally : THAT FEELS LIKE TRAGEDY'S AT HAND
Sally : AND THOUGH I'D LIKE TO STAND BY HIM
Sally : CAN'T SHAKE THIS FEELING THAT I HAVE
Sally : THE WORST IS JUST AROUND THE BEND
Sally : AND DOES HE NOTICE
Sally : MY FEELINGS FOR HIM
Sally : AND WILL HE SEE HOW MUCH HE MEANS TO ME
Sally : I THINK IT'S NOT TO BE
Sally : WHAT WILL BECOME OF MY DEAR FRIEND
Sally : WHERE WILL HIS ACTIONS LEAD US THEN
Sally : ALTHOUGH I'D LIKE TO JOIN THE CROWD
Sally : IN THEIR ENTHUSIASTIC CLOUD
Sally : TRY AS I MAY IT DOESN'T LAST
Sally : AND WILL WE EVER
Sally : END UP TOGETHER
Sally : NO I THINK NOT
Sally : IT'S NEVER TO BECOME
Sally : FOR I AM NOT THE ONE
Jack Skellington : HO HO HO HO HO HO HO
Jack Skellington : HEE HEE HEE HEE HEE
Kid1 : SANTA
Jack Skellington : MERRY CHRISTMAS
Jack Skellington : AND WHAT IS YOUR NAME
Kid1 : UH UH
Jack Skellington : THAT'S ALL RIGHT
Jack Skellington : I HAVE A SPECIAL PRESENT FOR YOU ANYWAY
Jack Skellington : THERE YOU GO SONNY
Jack Skellington : HO HO HO HO HEE HEE HEE HEE
Kid's Mom : AND WHAT DID SANTA BRING YOU HONEY
Kid's Mom;Kid's Dad : AAH AAH
Jack Skellington : MERRY CHRISTMAS
Police Officer : HELLO POLICE
Police Officer : ATTACKED BY CHRISTMAS TOYS
Police Officer : THAT'S STRANGE THAT'S THE SECOND TOY COMPLAINT WE'VE HAD
Jack Skellington : HO HO HO HO HA HA HA HA HA HA
Kid2 : HUH
Kid3 : OOH WHEE
Kid2;Kid3 : AAH AAH
Kid2;Kid3 : MOM DAD MOM
Kid2;Kid3 : AAH AAH AAH
Kid4 : AAH
Jack Skellington : Jack YOU'RE WELCOME ONE AND ALL
Police Officer : WHERE'D YOU SPOT HIM FAST AS WE CAN MA'AM
Police Officer : POLICE I KNOW I KNOW A SKELETON KEEP CALM
Police Officer : TURN OFF ALL THE LIGHTS
Police Officer : MAKE SURE THE DOORS ARE LOCKEDHELLO POLICE
Reporter : REPORTS ARE POURING IN FROM ALL OVER THE GLOBE
Reporter : THAT AN IMPOSTOR IS SHAMELESSLY IMPERSONATING SANTA CLAUS
Reporter : MOCKING AND MANGLING THIS JOYOUS HOLIDAY
Reporter : POLICE ASSURE US THAT AT THIS MOMENT
Reporter : MILITARY UNITS ARE MOBILIZING TO STOP THE PERPETRATOR OF THIS HEINOUS CRIME
Sally : JACK SOMEONE HAS TO HELP JACK
Sally : WHERE'D THEY TAKE THAT SANDY CLAWS
Sally : COME BACK AND SAVE CHRISTMAS
Jack Skellington : LOOK ZERO SEARCHLIGHTS
Jack Skellington : THEY'RE CELEBRATING
Jack Skellington : THEY'RE THANKING US FOR DOING SUCH A GOOD JOB
Jack Skellington : WHOA CAREFUL DOWN THERE
Jack Skellington : YOU ALMOST HIT US
Jack Skellington : IT'S OK ZERO
Jack Skellington : HEAD HIGHER
Oogie Boogie : Oogie Boogie ARE YOU A GAMBLIN MAN SANDY
Oogie Boogie : LET'S PLAY
Oogie Boogie : HMM
Oogie Boogie : MY MY
Oogie Boogie : WHAT HAVE WE HERE
Sally : I'll get you out of here
Oogie Boogie : AH LOVELY
Oogie Boogie : TICKLE TICKLE TICKLE
Oogie Boogie : AH HA HA HA
Oogie Boogie : WHAT
Oogie Boogie : YOU TRYING TO MAKE A DUPE OUT OF ME
Oogie Boogie : RRARR
Sally : OHH
Jack Skellington : WHO'S NEXT ON MY LIST
Jack Skellington : AH LITTLE HARRY AND JORDAN
Jack Skellington : WON'T THEY BE SURPRISED
Jack Skellington : THEY'RE TRYING TO HIT US
Jack Skellington : ZERO
Jack Skellington : Jack MERRY CHRISTMAS TO ALL
Jack Skellington : AND TO ALL A GOOD NIGHT
Mayor of Halloween Town : I KNEW THIS CHRISTMAS THING WAS A BAD IDEA
Mayor of Halloween Town : I FELT IT IN MY GUT
Mayor of Halloween Town : TERRIBLE NEWS FOLKS
Mayor of Halloween Town : THE WORST TRAGEDY OF OUR TIMES
Mayor of Halloween Town : JACK HAS BEEN BLOWN TO SMITHEREENS
Mayor of Halloween Town : TERRIBLE TERRIBLE NEWS
Police Officer : ATTENTION ATTENTION CITIZENS
Police Officer : TERRIBLE NEWS
Police Officer : THERE'S STILL NO SIGN OF SANTA CLAUS
Police Officer : ALTHOUGH THE IMPOSTOR HAS BEEN SHOT DOWN
Police Officer : IT LOOKS LIKE CHRISTMAS WILL HAVE TO BE CANCELED THIS YEAR
Police Officer : I REPEAT THE IMPOSTOR HAS BEEN SHOT DOWN
Police Officer : BUT THERE'S STILL NO SIGN
Jack Skellington : WHAT HAVE I DONE
Jack Skellington : HOW COULD I BE SO BLIND
Jack Skellington : ALL IS LOST
Jack Skellington : WHERE WAS I
Jack Skellington : SPOILED ALL
Jack Skellington : EVERYTHING'S GONE ALL WRONG
Jack Skellington : WHAT HAVE I DONE
Jack Skellington : FIND A DEEP CAVE TO HIDE IN
Jack Skellington : IN A MILLION YEARS THEY'LL FIND ME
Jack Skellington : ONLY DUST
Jack Skellington : AND A PLAQUE THAT READS
Jack Skellington : HERE LIES POOR OLD JACK
Jack Skellington : BUT I NEVER INTENDED ALL THIS MADNESS
Jack Skellington : NEVER
Jack Skellington : AND NOBODY REALLY UNDERSTOOD
Jack Skellington : WELL HOW COULD THEY
Jack Skellington : THAT ALL I EVER WANTED WAS TO BRING THEM SOMETHING GREAT
Jack Skellington : WHY DOES NOTHING EVER TURN OUT LIKE IT SHOULD
Jack Skellington : WELL WHAT THE HECK
Jack Skellington : I WENT AND DID MY BEST
Jack Skellington : AND BY GOD I REALLY TASTED SOMETHING SWELL
Jack Skellington : AND FOR A MOMENT WHY I EVEN TOUCHED THE SKY
Jack Skellington : AND AT LEAST I LEFT SOME STORIES THEY CAN TELL
Jack Skellington : I DID
Jack Skellington : AND FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE I DON'T REMEMBER WHEN
Jack Skellington : I FELT JUST LIKE MY OLD BONY SELF AGAIN
Jack Skellington : AND I JACK THE PUMPKIN KING
Jack Skellington : THAT'S RIGHT
Jack Skellington : I AM THE PUMPKIN KING HA HA HA HA
Jack Skellington : AND I JUST CAN'T WAIT UNTIL NEXT HALLOWEEN
Jack Skellington : CAUSE I'VE GOT SOME NEW IDEAS THAT WILL REALLY MAKE THEM SCREAM
Jack Skellington : AND BY GOD I'M REALLY GOING TO GIVE IT ALL MY MIGHT
Jack Skellington : UHOH I HOPE THERE'S STILL TIME TO SET THINGS RIGHT
Jack Skellington : SANDY CLAWS HMM
Sally : YOU WAIT TILL JACK HEARS ABOUT THIS BY THE TIME HE'S THROUGH WITH YOU
Sally : YOU'LL BE LUCKY IF YOU
Mayor of Halloween Town : THE KING OF HALLOWEEN HAS BEEN BLOWN TO SMITHEREENS
Mayor of Halloween Town : SKELETON JACK
Jack Skellington : COME ON ZERO
Jack Skellington : CHRISTMAS ISN'T OVER YET
Oogie Boogie : WHAT'S THAT YOU WERE SAYING ABOUT LUCK RAG DOLL
Sally : HELP HELP HELP
Sally : HELP HELP
Jack Skellington : SHH
Oogie Boogie : SANDY
Oogie Boogie : LOOKS LIKE IT'S OOGIE'S TURN TO BOOGIE NOW
Oogie Boogie : 1 2 3 4 567
Oogie Boogie : HA HA HA HELP
Santa Claus : Santa Claus THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING
Oogie Boogie : ASHES TO ASHES AND DUST TO DUST
Oogie Boogie : OH I'M FEELING WEAK WITH HUNGER
Oogie Boogie : ONE MORE ROLL OF THE DICE OUGHTA DO IT
Oogie Boogie : HA HA HA HA
Oogie Boogie : WHAT SNAKE EYES
Oogie Boogie : UHH
Oogie Boogie : HA HA HA LOOKS LIKE I WON THE JACKPOT
Oogie Boogie : BYEBYE DOLLFACE AND SANDMAN AAH
Oogie Boogie : HA HA HA HA
Oogie Boogie : WHAT THE
Jack Skellington : HELLO OOGIE
Oogie Boogie : JJJACK
Oogie Boogie : BUT THEY SAID YOU WERE DEAD
Oogie Boogie : YOU MUST BE DOUBLE DEAD
Jack Skellington : OH
Oogie Boogie : HEE HEE HEE
Oogie Boogie : WELL COME ON BONE MAN
Oogie Boogie : OOOH
Oogie Boogie : EH
Oogie Boogie : FIRE
Oogie Boogie : OOH
Oogie Boogie : WHEE
Oogie Boogie : UHH
Sally : JACK LOOK OUT
Oogie Boogie : SO LONG JACK
Oogie Boogie : HA HA HA HA
Jack Skellington : HOW DARE YOU TREAT MY FRIENDS SO SHAMEFULLY
Oogie Boogie : NOW LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE
Oogie Boogie : MY BUGS MY BUGS MY BUGS
Oogie Boogie : MY BUGS MY BUGS
Oogie Boogie : MY BUGS
Santa Claus : FORGIVE ME MR CLAWS
Jack Skellington : I'M AFRAID I'VE MADE A TERRIBLE MESS OF YOUR HOLIDAY
Santa Claus : BUMPY SLEIGH RIDE JACK
Santa Claus : THE NEXT TIME YOU GET THE URGE TO TAKE OVER SOMEONE ELSE'S HOLIDAY
Santa Claus : I'D LISTEN TO HER
Sally : SHE'S THE ONLY ONE WHO MAKES ANY SENSE AROUND THIS INSANE ASYLUM
Santa Claus : SKELETONS
Jack Skellington : I HOPE THERE'S STILL TIME
Santa Claus : TO FIX CHRISTMAS
Santa Claus : OF COURSE THERE IS I'M SANTA CLAUS
Sally : HE'LL FIX THINGS JACK HE KNOWS WHAT TO DO
Jack Skellington : HOW DID YOU GET DOWN HERE SALLY
Sally : OH I WAS TRYING TO
Sally : WELL I WANTED TOTO
Jack Skellington : TO HELP ME
Sally : I COULDN'T JUST LET YOU JUST
Jack Skellington : SALLY I CAN'T BELIEVE I NEVER REALIZED THAT YOU
Mayor of Halloween Town : JACK JACK
Boogie's Boys : HERE HE IS ALIVE
Shock : JUST LIKE WE SAID
Mayor of Halloween Town : GRAB AHOLD MY BOY
Jack Skellington : WHOA
Reporter : GOOD NEWS FOLKS
Reporter : SANTA CLAUS THE ONE AND ONLY HAS FINALLY BEEN SPOTTED
Reporter : OLD SAINT NICK APPEARS TO BE TRAVELING AT SUPERSONIC SPEED
Reporter : HE'S SETTING THINGS RIGHT BRINGING JOY AND CHEER WHEREVER HE GOES
Reporter : YES FOLKS KRIS KRINGLE HAS PULLED IT OUT OF THE BAG AND DELIVERED CHRISTMAS
Reporter : TO EXCITED CHILDREN ALL OVER THE WORLD
Halloween Citizens : LA LA LA LA LA LA LA
Halloween Citizens : JACK
Halloween Citizens : JACK'S BACK
Halloween Citizens : JACK'S OK
Halloween Citizens : HE'S ALL RIGHT JACK
Halloween Citizens : JACK'S OK AND HE'S BACK OK
Halloween Citizens : HE'S ALL RIGHT
Halloween Citizens : LET'S SHOUT
Halloween Citizens : MAKE A FUSS SCREAM IT OUT
Halloween Citizens : WHEE
Halloween Citizens : JACK IS BACK NOW EVERYONE SING
Halloween Citizens : IN OUR TOWN OF HALLOWEEN
Jack Skellington : IT'S GREAT TO BE HOME
Santa Claus : HAPPY HALLOWEEN
Jack Skellington : MERRY CHRISTMAS
Halloween Citizens : WHAT'S THIS
Halloween Citizens : I HAVEN'T GOT A CLUE
Halloween Citizens : WHY IT'S COMPLETELY NEW
Halloween Citizens : MUST BE A CHRISTMAS THING
Halloween Citizens : WHAT'S THIS
Mayor of Halloween Town : IT'S REALLY VERY STRANGE
Halloween Citizens : THIS IS HALLOWEEN HALLOWEEN
Halloween Citizens : HALLOWEEN HALLOWEEN WHAT'S THIS
Halloween Citizens : WHAT'S THIS
Boogie's Boys : HA HA HA
Dr. Finkelstein : CAREFUL MY PRECIOUS JEWEL
Jack Skellington : MY DEAREST FRIEND
Jack Skellington : IF YOU DON'T MIND
Jack Skellington : I'D LIKE TO JOIN YOU
Jack Skellington : BY YOUR SIDE
Jack Skellington : WHERE WE CAN GAZE INTO THE STARS
Jack Skellington : AND SIT TOGETHER
Sally;Jack Skellington : NOW AND FOREVER
Sally;Jack Skellington : FOR IT IS PLAIN
Sally;Jack Skellington : AS ANYONE CAN SEE
Sally;Jack Skellington : WE'RE SIMPLY MEANT TO BE