Auctioneer : Sold Your number sir
Auctioneer : Thank you
Auctioneer : Lot 663 then Ladies and gentlemen a poster
Auctioneer : for this house's production of Hannibal by Chalumeau
Man : Showing here
Auctioneer : Do I have 10 francs
Auctioneer : Five then Five I am bid
Auctioneer : Six Six Do I see seven Seven
Auctioneer : Against you sir seven Eight Eight
Auctioneer : Eight once
Auctioneer : Selling twice
Auctioneer : Sold to Raoul Vicomte de Chagny
Auctioneer : Thank you very much
Auctioneer : Lot 664 Ladies and gentlemen
Auctioneer : a wooden pistol and three human skulls
Auctioneer : from the 1831 production of Robert le Diable by Meyerbeer
Auctioneer : Ten francs for this
Auctioneer : Ten thank you
Auctioneer : Ten I am bid
Auctioneer : Ten francs still
Auctioneer : Fifteen thank you sir
Auctioneer : Fifteen I am bid
Auctioneer : Going for 15
Auctioneer : Your number sir Thank you
Auctioneer : Lot 665 Ladies and gentlemen
Auctioneer : a papiermch musical box in the shape of a barrel organ
Auctioneer : Attached the figure of a monkey in Persian robes playing the cymbals
Auctioneer : This item discovered in the vaults of the theatre
Auctioneer : still in working order ladies and gentlemen
Auctioneer : Showing here
Auctioneer : May I commence at 20 francs
Auctioneer : Oh come come ladies and gentlemen Fifteen then
Auctioneer : Fifteen I am bid Thank you very much
Auctioneer : Yes 20 from you sir Thank you very much
Woman : Twentyfive
Auctioneer : Twentyfive on my right
Auctioneer : Thank you madam
Auctioneer : Twentyfive I am bid
Auctioneer : Thirty 30
Auctioneer : Selling at 30 francs then
Auctioneer : Thirty once 30 twice
Auctioneer : Sold for 30 francs
Auctioneer : to the Vicomte de Chagny
Auctioneer : Thank you very much sir
Raoul : Boy
Raoul : A collector's piece indeed
Raoul : Every detail exactly as she said
Raoul : She often spoke of you my friend
Raoul : Your velvet lining and your figurine of lead
Raoul : Will you still play when all the rest of us are dead
Auctioneer : Lot 666 then
Auctioneer : A chandelier in pieces
Auctioneer : Some of you may recall the strange affair of The Phantom of the Opera
Auctioneer : a mystery never fully explained
Auctioneer : We are told ladies and gentlemen that this is the very chandelier
Auctioneer : that figures in that famous disaster
Auctioneer : Our workshops have restored it
Auctioneer : and fitted parts of it with wiring for the new electric light
Auctioneer : so that we may get a hint of how it may look when reassembled
Auctioneer : Perhaps we may even frighten away the ghost of so many years ago
Auctioneer : with a little illumination gentlemen
Carlotta Giudicelli : This
Carlotta Giudicelli : Trophy
Carlotta Giudicelli : From our saviours
Carlotta Giudicelli : From the enslaving force
Carlotta Giudicelli : Of Rome
Ensemble : With feasting and dancing and song
Ensemble : Tonight in celebration
Ensemble : We greet the victorious throng
Ensemble : Returned to bring salvation
Ensemble : The trumpets of Carthage resound
Ensemble : Hear Romans now and tremble
Ensemble : Hark to our step on the ground
Ensemble : Hear the drums Hannibal comes
Ubaldo Piangi : Sad to return to find the land we love
Ubaldo Piangi : Threatened once more by Roma's farreaching grasp
Reyer : No no no no
Reyer : Signor if you please
Reyer : Rome We say Rome not Roma
Ubaldo Piangi : Rome Rome is very hard for me
Reyer : Well once again if you please signor Sad to return It's very very hard
Reyer : I am from Italy Just get it right please
Reyer : Rome Signor
Ubaldo Piangi : Sad to return to find the land we love
Ubaldo Piangi : Threatened once more by Rome's farreaching grasp
Ubaldo Piangi : Tomorrow we shall break the chains of Rome
Ubaldo Piangi : Tonight rejoice
Ubaldo Piangi : Your army
Ubaldo Piangi : Has come home
Ensemble : Bid welcome to Hannibal's guests
Ensemble : The elephants of Carthage
Ensemble : As guides on our conquering quests
Ensemble : Dido sends
Ensemble : Hannibal's friends
Carlotta Giudicelli : Once more to my welcoming arms
Carlotta Giudicelli : My love returns in splendour
Ubaldo Piangi : Once more to the sweetest of charms
Ubaldo Piangi : My heart and soul surrender
Ensemble : The trumpeting elephants sound
Ensemble : Hear Romans now and tremble
Ensemble : Hark to their step on the ground
Ensemble : Hear the drums
Ensemble : Hannibal
Ensemble : comes
Reyer : Hey Hey We're doing that all again
Reyer : Thank you very much
Reyer : You were very good This song is marvellous Thank you
Lefèvre : This way gentlemen this way
Reyer : Girls
Lefèvre : Rehearsals as you see are underway for a new production of Chalumeau's Hannibal
Lefèvre : Ladies and gentlemen
Lefèvre : Ladies and gentlemen please
Lefèvre : Ladies and
Lefèvre : Madame Giry
Lefèvre : Thank you
Lefèvre : May I have your attention please
Lefèvre : As you know for some weeks there have been rumours about my imminent retirement
Lefèvre : I can now tell you these were all true
Lefèvre : and it is now my pleasure to introduce you to the two gentlemen who now own the Opera Populaire
Lefèvre : Monsieur Richard Firmin and Monsieur Giles Andr
Monsieur Gilles André : ANDR Oh no please
Lefèvre : Gentlemen Signora Carlotta Giudicelli
Lefèvre : our leading soprano for 19 seasons now
Monsieur Gilles André : Of course of course I have experienced all your greatest roles signora
Lefèvre : And Signor Ubaldo Piangi
Ubaldo Piangi : An honour signor
Monsieur Gilles André : If I remember rightly Elissa has a rather fine aria
Monsieur Gilles André : in Act Three of Hannibal
Monsieur Gilles André : I wonder signora if as a personal favour you would oblige us with a private rendition
Monsieur Gilles André : Unless of course Monsieur Reyer objects
Carlotta Giudicelli : No my manager commands
Reyer : My diva commands Would two bars be sufficient introduction
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Two bars will be quite sufficient
Monsieur Gilles André : Signora
Carlotta Giudicelli : Think of me
Carlotta Giudicelli : Think of me fondly When we've said goodbye
Carlotta Giudicelli : Remember me Every so often
Carlotta Giudicelli : Promise me you'll try
Carlotta Giudicelli : On that day that not so distant day
Carlotta Giudicelli : When you are far away and free
Carlotta Giudicelli : If you ever find a moment
Carlotta Giudicelli : Spare a thought for me
Carlotta Giudicelli : Think of me
Carlotta Giudicelli : Think of me warmly j
Meg Giry : He's here The Phantom of the Opera
Meg Giry : He's there The Phantom of the Opera
Ensemble : He is with us It's the ghost j
Monsieur Gilles André : Good heavens will you show a little courtesy
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Mademoiselle please
Lefèvre : Signora Are you all right Buquet Where is Buquet
Lefèvre : Get that man down here
Lefèvre : Buquet chief of the flys He's responsible for this
Lefèvre : Buquet For God's sake man what's going on up there
Joseph Buquet : Please monsieur don't look at me
Joseph Buquet : As God's my witness I was not at my post
Joseph Buquet : Please monsieur there's no one there
Joseph Buquet : And if there is well then it must be a ghost
Meg Giry : He's there The Phantom of the Opera
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Good heavens I have never known such insolence
Monsieur Gilles André : Signora please
Monsieur Gilles André : These things do happen
Carlotta Giudicelli : These things do happen
Carlotta Giudicelli : You have been here five minutes What do you know
Carlotta Giudicelli : Si these things do happen all the time
Carlotta Giudicelli : For the past three years these things do happen
Carlotta Giudicelli : And did you stop them happening No
Carlotta Giudicelli : And you You're as bad as him
Carlotta Giudicelli : These things do happen
Carlotta Giudicelli : Well until you stop these things happening
Carlotta Giudicelli : this thing does not happen
Carlotta Giudicelli : Ubaldo andiamo
Ubaldo Piangi : Amateurs
Ubaldo Piangi : I don't think there's much more I can do to assist you gentlemen Good luck
Lefèvre : If you need me I shall be in Frankfurt
Monsieur Gilles André : But monsieur
Lefèvre : Move please Out of the way
Lefèvre : Oh
Monsieur Gilles André : La Carlotta will be back
Madame Giry : You think so monsieur
Monsieur Gilles André : Yes
Madame Giry : I have a message sir from the Opera Ghost
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Oh God in heaven you're all obsessed
Madame Giry : He merely welcomes you to his opera house
Madame Giry : Commands that you continue to leave Box Five empty for his use
Madame Giry : and reminds you that his salary is due
Monsieur Richard Firmin : His salary
Madame Giry : Monsieur Lefevre paid him 20000 francs a month
Madame Giry : Perhaps you could afford more with the Vicomte de Chagny as your patron
Monsieur Gilles André : Madame I had hoped to have made that announcement myself
Madame Giry : Will the Vicomte be at the performance this evening monsieur
Monsieur Richard Firmin : In our box
Monsieur Gilles André : Madame who is the understudy for the role
Reyer : There is no understudy monsieur The production is new
Meg Giry : Christine Daa could sing it sir
Monsieur Richard Firmin : A ballet girl
Meg Giry : Well she's been taking lessons from a great teacher
Monsieur Gilles André : Oh from whom
Christine Daaé : I don't know sir
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Oh not you as well Can you believe it
Monsieur Richard Firmin : A full house and we have to cancel
Monsieur Gilles André : Daa That's a curious name
Monsieur Gilles André : Any relation to the violinist
Christine Daaé : My father sir
Madame Giry : Let her sing for you monsieur
Madame Giry : She has been well taught
Monsieur Gilles André : Very well
Reyer : Oh from the beginning of the aria then mam'selle
Reyer : Gentlemen please
Christine Daaé : Think of me
Christine Daaé : Think of me fondly
Christine Daaé : When we've said goodbye
Christine Daaé : Remember me
Christine Daaé : Every so often
Christine Daaé : Promise me you'll try
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Andr this is doing nothing for my nerves
Monsieur Gilles André : Don't fret Firmin
Christine Daaé : On that day that not so distant day
Christine Daaé : When you are far away and free
Christine Daaé : If you ever find a moment
Christine Daaé : Spare a thought for me
Reyer : Madame Monsieur
Christine Daaé : Thank you Thank you so much
Christine Daaé : And though it's clear
Christine Daaé : Though it was always clear That this was never meant to be
Christine Daaé : If you happen to remember
Christine Daaé : Stop and think of me
Christine Daaé : Think of August
Christine Daaé : When the world was green
Christine Daaé : Don't think about the way
Christine Daaé : Things might have been
Christine Daaé : Think of me
Christine Daaé : Think of me waking
Christine Daaé : Silent and resigned
Christine Daaé : Imagine me
Christine Daaé : Trying too hard
Christine Daaé : To put you from my mind
Christine Daaé : Think of me
Christine Daaé : Please say you'll think of me
Christine Daaé : Whatever else you choose to do
Christine Daaé : There will never be a day
Christine Daaé : When I won't think of you
Raoul : Can it be Can it be Christine
Raoul : Brava Brava
Raoul : Long ago It seems so long ago
Raoul : How young and innocent we were
Raoul : She may not remember me
Raoul : But I remember her
Christine Daaé : Flowers fade The fruits of summer fade
Christine Daaé : They have their seasons So do we
Christine Daaé : But please promise me That sometimes
Christine Daaé : You will think
Christine Daaé : Of me j
Reyer : Brava Brava
Meg Giry : Christine Daa that was unbelievable
Madame Giry : Yes you did well
Madame Giry : He will be pleased
Madame Giry : And you You were a disgrace
Madame Giry : Such ronds de jambes Such temps de cuisse
Madame Giry : Come We rehearse Now
Erik (The Phantom) : Brava
Erik (The Phantom) : Bravissima
Meg Giry : Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine
Meg Giry : Where in the world have you been hiding
Meg Giry : Really you were perfect
Meg Giry : I only wish I knew your secret
Meg Giry : Who is this new tutor
Christine Daaé : Father once spoke of an angel
Christine Daaé : I used to dream he'd appear
Christine Daaé : Now as I sing I can sense him
Christine Daaé : And I know he's here
Christine Daaé : Here in this room he calls me softly
Christine Daaé : Somewhere inside hiding
Christine Daaé : Somehow I know he's always with me
Christine Daaé : He the unseen genius
Meg Giry : I watched your face from the shadows
Meg Giry : Distant through all the applause
Meg Giry : I hear your voice in the darkness
Meg Giry : Yet the words aren't yours
Christine Daaé : Angel of Music guide and guardian
Christine Daaé : Grant to me your glory
Meg Giry : Who is this angel
Christine Daaé;Meg Giry : This Angel of Music hide no longer
Meg Giry;Christine Daaé : Secret and strange angel
Christine Daaé : He's with me even now
Meg Giry : Your hands are cold
Christine Daaé : All around
Meg Giry : Your face Christine it's white
Christine Daaé : It frightens me j
Meg Giry : Don't be frightened j
Madame Giry : Meg Giry Are you a dancer
Madame Giry : Then go and practice
Madame Giry : My dear I was asked to give you this
Christine Daaé : Thank you
Christine Daaé : A red scarf The attic Little Lotte
Monsieur Gilles André : ANDR A tour de force There's no other way to describe it
Monsieur Richard Firmin : What a relief Not a single refund
Woman : Greedy
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Richard I think we've made quite a discovery with Miss Daa
Monsieur Gilles André : Here we are Monsieur Vicomte
Raoul : Gentlemen if you wouldn't mind
Raoul : This is one visit I should prefer to make unaccompanied
Monsieur Gilles André : As you wish monsieur
Monsieur Richard Firmin : They appear to have met before
Raoul : Christine Daa where is your red scarf
Christine Daaé : Monsieur
Raoul : Well you can't have lost it
Raoul : After all the trouble I took
Raoul : I was just 14 and soaked to the skin
Christine Daaé : Because you had run into the sea to fetch my scarf
Christine Daaé : Oh Raoul So it is you
Raoul : Christine
Raoul : Little Lotte let her mind wander
Christine Daaé : You remember that too
Raoul : Little Lotte thought am I fonder of dolls
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Or of goblins of shoes
Christine Daaé : Or of riddles of frocks
Raoul : Those picnics in the attic Or of chocolates
Christine Daaé : Father playing the violin
Raoul : As we read to each other dark stories of the north
Christine Daaé : No what I love best Lotte said
Christine Daaé : Is when I'm asleep in my bed
Christine Daaé : And the Angel of Music sings songs in my head
Christine Daaé;Raoul : The Angel of Music sings songs in my head j
Christine Daaé : Father said When I'm in heaven child
Christine Daaé : I will send the Angel of Music to you
Christine Daaé : Well Father is dead Raoul
Christine Daaé : and I have been visited by the Angel of Music
Raoul : No doubt of it And now we go to supper
Christine Daaé : No Raoul the Angel of Music is very strict
Raoul : I shan't keep you up late
Christine Daaé : No
Raoul : You must change I must get my hat
Raoul : Two minutes Little Lotte
Christine Daaé : Raoul
Christine Daaé : Things have changed Raoul
Erik (The Phantom) : Insolent boy the slave of fashion
Erik (The Phantom) : Basking in your glory
Erik (The Phantom) : Ignorant fool this brave young suitor
Erik (The Phantom) : Sharing in my triumph
Christine Daaé : Angel I hear you Speak I listen
Christine Daaé : Stay by my side guide me
Christine Daaé : Angel my soul was weak forgive me
Christine Daaé : Enter at last master
Erik (The Phantom) : Flattering child you shall know me
Erik (The Phantom) : See why in shadow I hide
Erik (The Phantom) : Look at your face in the mirror
Erik (The Phantom) : I am there inside
Christine Daaé : Angel of Music guide and guardian
Christine Daaé : Grant to me your glory
Christine Daaé : Angel of Music hide no longer
Christine Daaé : Come to me strange angel
Erik (The Phantom) : I am your Angel of Music
Erik (The Phantom) : Come to me Angel of Music
Erik (The Phantom) : Come to me Angel of Music j
Raoul : Christine
Christine Daaé : In sleep he sang to me
Christine Daaé : In dreams he came
Christine Daaé : That voice which calls to me And speaks my name
Christine Daaé : And do I dream again
Christine Daaé : For now I find
Christine Daaé : The Phantom of the Opera is there
Christine Daaé : Inside my mind
Erik (The Phantom) : Sing once again with me
Erik (The Phantom) : Our strange duet
Erik (The Phantom) : My power over you
Erik (The Phantom) : Grows stronger yet
Erik (The Phantom) : And though you turn from me
Erik (The Phantom) : To glance behind
Erik (The Phantom) : The Phantom of the Opera is there
Erik (The Phantom) : Inside your mind
Christine Daaé : Those who have seen your face
Christine Daaé : Draw back in fear
Christine Daaé : I am the mask you wear
Erik (The Phantom) : It's me they hear
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : My(Your) spirit and my(your) voice
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : In one combined
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : The Phantom of the Opera is there
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : Inside my(your) mind
Ensemble : Beware The Phantom of the Opera
Erik (The Phantom) : In all your fantasies
Erik (The Phantom) : You always knew
Erik (The Phantom) : That man and mystery
Erik (The Phantom) : Were both in you
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : And in this labyrinth
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : Where night is blind
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : The Phantom of the Opera is there
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : Inside my mind Inside your mind
Erik (The Phantom) : Sing for me
Erik (The Phantom) : My Angel of Music
Christine Daaé : He's there The Phantom of the Opera
Erik (The Phantom) : Sing
Erik (The Phantom) : Sing for me
Erik (The Phantom) : I have brought you
Erik (The Phantom) : To the seat of sweet music's throne
Erik (The Phantom) : To this kingdom where all must pay homage to music
Erik (The Phantom) : Music
Erik (The Phantom) : You have come here
Erik (The Phantom) : For one purpose and one alone
Erik (The Phantom) : Since the moment I first heard you sing
Erik (The Phantom) : I have needed you with me to serve me
Erik (The Phantom) : To sing for my music
Erik (The Phantom) : My music
Erik (The Phantom) : Nighttime sharpens
Erik (The Phantom) : Heightens each sensation
Erik (The Phantom) : Darkness stirs
Erik (The Phantom) : And wakes imagination
Erik (The Phantom) : Silently the senses
Erik (The Phantom) : Abandon their defenses
Erik (The Phantom) : Slowly gently
Erik (The Phantom) : Night unfurls its splendour
Erik (The Phantom) : Grasp it sense it
Erik (The Phantom) : Tremulous and tender
Erik (The Phantom) : Turn your face away
Erik (The Phantom) : From the garish light of day
Erik (The Phantom) : Turn your thoughts away
Erik (The Phantom) : From cold unfeeling light
Erik (The Phantom) : And listen to the music
Erik (The Phantom) : Of the night
Erik (The Phantom) : Close your eyes and surrender
Erik (The Phantom) : To your darkest dreams
Erik (The Phantom) : Purge your thoughts of the life you knew before
Erik (The Phantom) : Close your eyes
Erik (The Phantom) : Let your spirit start to soar
Erik (The Phantom) : And you'll live
Erik (The Phantom) : As you've never lived before
Erik (The Phantom) : Softly deftly
Erik (The Phantom) : Music shall surround you
Erik (The Phantom) : Hear it feel it
Erik (The Phantom) : Closing in around you
Erik (The Phantom) : Open up your mind
Erik (The Phantom) : Let your fantasies unwind
Erik (The Phantom) : In this darkness
Erik (The Phantom) : Which you know you cannot fight
Erik (The Phantom) : The darkness of the music
Erik (The Phantom) : Of the night
Erik (The Phantom) : Let your mind start a journey through a strange new world
Erik (The Phantom) : Leave all thoughts of the world you knew before
Erik (The Phantom) : Let your soul
Erik (The Phantom) : Take you where you long to be
Erik (The Phantom) : Only then Can you belong
Erik (The Phantom) : To me
Erik (The Phantom) : Floating falling
Erik (The Phantom) : Sweet intoxication
Erik (The Phantom) : Touch me trust me
Erik (The Phantom) : Savour each sensation
Erik (The Phantom) : Let the dream begin
Erik (The Phantom) : Let your darker side give in
Erik (The Phantom) : To the power of the music
Erik (The Phantom) : That I write
Erik (The Phantom) : The power of the music
Erik (The Phantom) : Of the night
Erik (The Phantom) : You alone can make
Erik (The Phantom) : My song take flight
Erik (The Phantom) : Help me make the music
Erik (The Phantom) : Of the
Erik (The Phantom) : Night
Christine Daaé : I remember there was mist
Christine Daaé : Swirling mist upon a vast glassy lake
Christine Daaé : There were candles all around
Christine Daaé : And on the lake there was a boat
Christine Daaé : And in the boat there was a man
Christine Daaé : Who was that shape in the shadows
Christine Daaé : Whose is that face in the mask
Erik (The Phantom) : Damn you You little prying Pandora
Erik (The Phantom) : You little demon Is this what you wanted to see
Erik (The Phantom) : Curse you
Erik (The Phantom) : You little lying Delilah
Erik (The Phantom) : You little viper Now you cannot ever be free
Erik (The Phantom) : Damn you
Erik (The Phantom) : Curse you
Erik (The Phantom) : Stranger than you dreamt it
Erik (The Phantom) : Can you even dare to look
Erik (The Phantom) : Or bear to think of me
Erik (The Phantom) : This loathsome gargoyle who burns in hell
Erik (The Phantom) : But secretly yearns for heaven
Erik (The Phantom) : Secretly secretly
Erik (The Phantom) : But Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : Fear can turn to love
Erik (The Phantom) : You'll learn to see
Erik (The Phantom) : To find the man behind the monster
Erik (The Phantom) : This repulsive carcass
Erik (The Phantom) : Who seems a beast
Erik (The Phantom) : But secretly dreams of beauty
Erik (The Phantom) : Secretly secretly
Erik (The Phantom) : Oh Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : No
Erik (The Phantom) : Come we must return
Erik (The Phantom) : Those two fools who run my theatre will be missing you j
Meg Giry : Let's go this way
Meg Giry : Quick Come this way
Joseph Buquet : Like yellow parchment is his skin
Joseph Buquet : A great black hole serves as the nose which never grew
Joseph Buquet : You must be always on your guard
Joseph Buquet : Or he will catch you with his magical lasso
Madame Giry : Those who speak of what they know
Madame Giry : Find too late that prudent silence is wise
Madame Giry : Joseph Buquet hold your tongue
Madame Giry : He will burn you with the heat of his eyes
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Mystery after gala night
Monsieur Richard Firmin : It says Mystery of soprano's flight
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Mystified baffled Sret say
Monsieur Richard Firmin : We are mystified We suspect foul play
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Bad news on soprano scene
Monsieur Richard Firmin : First Carlotta now Christine
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Still at least the seats get sold
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Gossip's worth its weight in gold
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Diva tenders resignation
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Cover does a moonlight flit
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Half your cast disappears but the crowd still cheers
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Opera to hell with Gluck and Handel Have a scandal and you're sure to have a hit
Monsieur Gilles André : Damnable will they all walk out
Monsieur Gilles André : This is damnable
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Andr please don't shout It's publicity And the take is vast Free publicity
Monsieur Gilles André : But we have no cast
Monsieur Gilles André : But Andr have you seen the queue
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Oh it seems you've got one too
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Hmm
Monsieur Gilles André : Dear Andr what a charming gala
Monsieur Gilles André : Christine enjoyed a great success
Monsieur Gilles André : We were hardly bereft when Carlotta left
Monsieur Gilles André : Otherwise the chorus was entrancing But the dancing was a lamentable mess
Monsieur Gilles André : Dear Firmin just a brief reminder
Monsieur Richard Firmin : My salary has not been paid
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Send it care of the Ghost by return of post
Monsieur Richard Firmin : PTO no one likes a debtor So it's better if my orders are obeyed
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Who would have the gall to send this
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Someone with a puerile brain
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : These are both signed O. G Who the hell is he
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Opera Ghost
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : It's really not amusing
Monsieur Richard Firmin : He's abusing our position
Monsieur Gilles André : In addition he wants money
Monsieur Richard Firmin : He's a funny sort of spectre
Monsieur Gilles André : To expect a large retainer Nothing plainer He is clearly quite insane
Monsieur Gilles André;Monsieur Richard Firmin : Where is she
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : You mean Carlotta
Monsieur Gilles André : I mean Miss Daa Where is she
Raoul : Well how should we know
Raoul : I want an answer
Raoul : I take it that you sent me this note
Monsieur Richard Firmin : What's all this nonsense
Monsieur Gilles André : Of course not Don't look at us
Raoul : She's not with you then
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Of course not
Monsieur Gilles André : We're in the dark
Raoul : Monsieur don't argue
Raoul : Isn't this the letter you wrote
Monsieur Richard Firmin : And what is it that we're meant to have wrote
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Written
Monsieur Gilles André : Do not fear for Miss Daa
Monsieur Gilles André : The Angel of Music has her under his wing
Monsieur Gilles André : Make no attempt to see her again
Raoul : Well if you didn't write it who did
Carlotta Giudicelli : Where is he
Monsieur Gilles André : Ah welcome back
Carlotta Giudicelli : Your precious patron
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : Where is he
Raoul : What is it now
Carlotta Giudicelli : I have your letter A letter which I rather resent
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Did you send it
Raoul : Of course not
Ubaldo Piangi : As if he would
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : You didn't send it
Raoul : Of course not
Monsieur Richard Firmin : What's going on
Carlotta Giudicelli : You dare to tell me that this is not the letter you sent
Raoul : And what is it that I'm meant to have sent
Raoul : Your days at the Opera Populaire are numbered
Raoul : Christine Daa will be singing on your behalf tonight
Raoul : Be prepared for a great misfortune
Raoul : Should you attempt to take her place
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Far too many notes for my taste
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : And most of them about Christine
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : All we've heard since we came is Miss Daas name
Madame Giry : Miss Daa has returned
Monsieur Richard Firmin : In which case I think our meeting is adjourned
Monsieur Gilles André : Where precisely is she now
Madame Giry : I thought it best that she went home
Meg Giry : She needed rest
Raoul : May I see her
Madame Giry : No monsieur she will see no one
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : Will she sing
Carlotta Giudicelli : Will she sing
Madame Giry : Here I have a note
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : Let me see it
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Please
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Gentlemen I have now sent you several notes of the most amiable nature
Monsieur Richard Firmin : detailing how my theatre is to be run
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Hmm
Monsieur Richard Firmin : You have not followed my instructions
Erik (The Phantom);Monsieur Richard Firmin : I shall give you one last chance
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine Daa has returned to you
Erik (The Phantom) : And I am anxious her career should progress
Erik (The Phantom) : In the new production of El Muto
Erik (The Phantom) : You will therefore cast Carlotta as the pageboy
Erik (The Phantom) : And put Miss Daa in the role of Countess
Erik (The Phantom) : The role which Miss Daa plays calls for charm and appeal
Erik (The Phantom) : The role of the pageboy is silent
Erik (The Phantom) : Which makes my casting in a word ideal
Erik (The Phantom) : I shall watch the performance from my normal seat in Box Five
Erik (The Phantom) : which will be kept empty for me
Erik (The Phantom);Monsieur Richard Firmin : Should these commands be ignored
Erik (The Phantom);Monsieur Richard Firmin : a disaster beyond your imagination will occur
Monsieur Richard Firmin : I remain gentlemen your obedient servant O. G
Meg Giry : Christine Christine
Carlotta Giudicelli : Christine
Raoul : Whatever next
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : It's all a ploy to help Christine
Monsieur Gilles André : This is insane
Carlotta Giudicelli : I know who sent this
Carlotta Giudicelli : The Vicomte her lover
Raoul : Indeed Can you believe this
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Signora
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : How can you do this
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : O traditori O mentitori
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Signora
Monsieur Gilles André : You are our star
Monsieur Richard Firmin : And always will be
Monsieur Gilles André : Signora
Monsieur Richard Firmin : The man is mad
Monsieur Richard Firmin : We don't take orders Miss Daa will be playing the pageboy
Monsieur Richard Firmin : The silent role
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Carlotta will be playing the lead
Ubaldo Piangi : You don't deserve her
Carlotta Giudicelli : It's useless trying to appease me
Ubaldo Piangi : Appease her
Carlotta Giudicelli : You're only saying this to please me
Ubaldo Piangi : To please her
Carlotta Giudicelli : Signori vero
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : No no non voglio udire Lasciatemi morire
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : O Padre mio Dio
Madame Giry : Who scorn his word beware to those
Madame Giry : The Angel sees The Angel knows
Raoul : Why did Christine fly from my arms
Carlotta Giudicelli : You have rebuked me
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Signora pardon us
Carlotta Giudicelli : You have replaced me
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Please signora we beseech you
Madame Giry : This hour shall see your darkest fears
Raoul : I must see her
Madame Giry : The Angel knows The Angel hears
Carlotta Giudicelli : Abbandonata desiderata O sventura disgraziata
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Signora sing for us
Carlotta Giudicelli : Abbandonata Don't be unfeeling
All : What new surprises are in store Our star
Monsieur Gilles André : Your public needs you
Monsieur Richard Firmin : We need you too
Carlotta Giudicelli : Would you not rather have your precious little ingnue
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Signora no The world wants you
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Prima donna first lady of the stage
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Your devotees are on their knees to implore you
Monsieur Gilles André : Can you bow out when they're shouting your name
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Think of how they all adore you
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Prima donna enchant us once again
Monsieur Gilles André : Think of your muse
Monsieur Richard Firmin : And of the queues round the theatre
Monsieur Gilles André;Monsieur Richard Firmin : Can you deny us the triumph in store
Ubaldo Piangi;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Sing prima donna once more
Raoul : Christine spoke of an angel
Carlotta Giudicelli : Prima donna your song shall live again
Carlotta Giudicelli : You took a snub
Ubaldo Piangi;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Think of your public
Carlotta Giudicelli : But there's a public who needs you
Ubaldo Piangi;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Those who hear your voice liken you to an angel
Madame Giry : Think of their cry of undying support
Raoul : Is this the Angel of Music
Monsieur Gilles André : We get our opera
Monsieur Richard Firmin : She gets her limelight Follow where the limelight leads you Leading ladies are a trial
Carlotta Giudicelli : Prima donna your song will never die
Carlotta Giudicelli : You'll sing again and to an unending ovation
Carlotta Giudicelli : Think how you'll shine in that final encore
Carlotta Giudicelli : Sing prima donna once more
Raoul;Madame Giry;Monsieur Richard Firmin : demands are rejected
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Who'd believe a diva happy to relieve a chorus girl Who's gone and slept with the patron
Monsieur Gilles André;Monsieur Richard Firmin : Raoul and the soubrette entwined in love's duet
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Although he may demur He must have been with her
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : You'd never get away with all this in a play
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : But if it's loudly sung and in a foreign tongue
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : It's just the sort of story audiences adore
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : In fact a perfect opera
Madame Giry : For if his curse is on this opera
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Prima donna the world is at your feet
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : A nation waits and how it hates to be cheated
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André;Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : Light up the stage with that ageold rapport
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Sing prima donna
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Once more
Erik (The Phantom) : So it is to be war between us
Erik (The Phantom) : If these demands are not met
Erik (The Phantom) : a disaster beyond imagination will occur
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Once more
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Gentlemen if you would care to take your seats We shall be sitting in Box Five
Monsieur Gilles André : Do you really think that's wise monsieur
Monsieur Richard Firmin : My dear Andr there would appear to be no seats available other than Box Five
Woman : They say that this youth has set my lady's heart aflame
Man : His Lordship sure would die of shock
Man : His Lordship is a laughing stock
Woman : Should he suspect her God protect her
Man;Woman : Shame shame shame
Woman;Man : This faithless lady's bound for Hades
Woman;Man : Shame shame shame
Carlotta Giudicelli : Serafimo your disguise is perfect
Carlotta Giudicelli : Why who can this be
Ubaldo Piangi : Gentle wife admit your loving husband
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Every seat sold
Monsieur Gilles André : Hardly a disaster beyond imagination
Ubaldo Piangi : My love I am called to England on affairs of State
Ubaldo Piangi : And must leave you with your new maid
Ubaldo Piangi : Though I'd happily take the maid with me
Carlotta Giudicelli : The old fool's leaving
Ubaldo Piangi : I suspect my young bride is untrue to me
Ubaldo Piangi : I shall not leave but shall hide over there
Ubaldo Piangi : To observe her
Ubaldo Piangi : Addio
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : Addio
Carlotta Giudicelli : Serafimo away with this pretence
Carlotta Giudicelli : You cannot speak
Carlotta Giudicelli : But kiss me in my husband's absence
Carlotta Giudicelli : Poor fool he makes me laugh Ha ha ha ha ha
Carlotta Giudicelli : Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Carlotta Giudicelli : Time I tried to get a better better half
Ensemble : Poor fool he doesn't know Ho ho ho ho ho
Ensemble : Ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho Ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho
Ensemble : If he knew the truth he'd never ever go
Erik (The Phantom) : Did I not instruct that Box Five was to be kept empty
Meg Giry : He's here The Phantom of the Opera
Christine Daaé : It's him I know it It's him
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Calm down
Carlotta Giudicelli : Your part is silent little toad
Erik (The Phantom) : A toad madame
Erik (The Phantom) : Perhaps it is you who are the toad
Carlotta Giudicelli : Maestro da capo per piacere
Carlotta Giudicelli : Serafimo away with this pretence
Carlotta Giudicelli : You cannot speak but kiss me in my
Carlotta Giudicelli : Poor fool he makes me laugh Ha ha ha ha ha
Man : Maestro Maestro no
Erik (The Phantom) : Behold She is singing to bring down the chandelier
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Ladies and gentlemen we apologise
Monsieur Richard Firmin : The performance will continue in 10 minutes time
Monsieur Richard Firmin : when the role of the Countess will be sung by Miss Christine Daa
Monsieur Gilles André : Ladies and gentlemen
Monsieur Gilles André : Oh In the meantime ladies and gentlemen
Monsieur Gilles André : we shall be giving you the ballet
Monsieur Gilles André : Uh from Act
Monsieur Gilles André : Three of tonight's opera
Monsieur Gilles André : Maestro bring the ballet forward
Monsieur Gilles André : The ballet Now
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Ladies and gentlemen please remain in your seats
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Do not panic It was an accident
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Simply an accident
Raoul : Why have you brought us here
Christine Daaé : Don't take me back there
Raoul : We must return
Christine Daaé : He'll kill me
Christine Daaé : His eyes will find me there
Raoul : Christine don't say that
Christine Daaé : Those eyes that burn
Raoul : Don't even think it
Christine Daaé : And if he has to kill a thousand men
Raoul : Forget this
Raoul : waking nightmare
Christine Daaé : The Phantom of the Opera will kill again
Raoul : The Phantom is a fable Believe me there is no Phantom of the Opera
Christine Daaé : My God who is this man
Raoul : My God who is this man
Christine Daaé : Who hunts to kill
Raoul : This mask of death
Christine Daaé : I can't escape from him
Raoul : Whose is this voice you hear
Christine Daaé : I never will
Raoul : With every breath
Christine Daaé;Raoul : And in this labyrinth where night is blind
Christine Daaé;Raoul : The Phantom of the Opera is here The Phantom of the Opera is there
Christine Daaé : Inside my mind
Raoul : Inside your mind
Raoul : There is no Phantom of the Opera
Christine Daaé : Raoul I've been there
Christine Daaé : To his world of unending night
Christine Daaé : To a world where the daylight dissolves into darkness
Christine Daaé : Darkness
Christine Daaé : Raoul I've seen him
Christine Daaé : Can I ever forget that sight
Christine Daaé : Can I ever escape from that face
Christine Daaé : So distorted deformed
Christine Daaé : It was hardly a face in that darkness
Christine Daaé : Darkness
Christine Daaé : But his voice filled my spirit
Christine Daaé : With a strange sweet sound
Christine Daaé : In that night there was music
Christine Daaé : In my mind
Christine Daaé : And through music
Christine Daaé : My soul began to soar
Christine Daaé : And I heard
Christine Daaé : As I'd never heard before
Raoul : What you heard was a dream and nothing more
Christine Daaé : Yet in his eyes
Christine Daaé : All the sadness of the world
Christine Daaé : Those pleading eyes
Christine Daaé : That both threaten
Christine Daaé : And adore
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine
Christine Daaé : What was that
Raoul : Christine come here
Raoul : No more talk of darkness
Raoul : Forget these wideeyed fears
Raoul : I'm here nothing will harm you
Raoul : My words will warm and calm you
Raoul : Let me be your freedom
Raoul : Let daylight dry your tears
Raoul : I'm here with you beside you
Raoul : To guard you and to guide you
Christine Daaé : Say you'll love me every waking moment
Christine Daaé : Turn my head with talk of summertime
Christine Daaé : Say you need me with you now and always
Christine Daaé : Promise me that all you say is true
Christine Daaé : That's all I ask of you
Raoul : Let me be your shelter
Raoul : Let me be your light
Raoul : You're safe no one can find you
Raoul : Your fears are far behind you
Christine Daaé : All I want is freedom
Christine Daaé : A world with no more night
Christine Daaé : And you always beside me
Christine Daaé : To hold me and to hide me
Raoul : Then say you'll share with me one love
Raoul : One lifetime
Raoul : Let me lead you from your solitude
Raoul : Say you need me with you Here beside you
Raoul : Anywhere you go let me go too
Raoul : Christine that's all I ask of you
Christine Daaé : Say you'll share with me one love One lifetime
Christine Daaé : Say the word and I will follow you
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Share each day with me Each night each morning
Christine Daaé : Say you love me
Raoul : You know I do
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Love me
Christine Daaé;Raoul : That's all I ask of you
Christine Daaé : Anywhere you go let me go too
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Love me
Christine Daaé;Raoul : That's all I ask
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Of you
Christine Daaé : I must go
Christine Daaé : They'll wonder where I am Wait for me Raoul
Raoul : Christine I love you
Christine Daaé : Order your fine horses
Christine Daaé : Be with them at the door
Raoul : And soon you'll be beside me
Christine Daaé : You'll guard me and you'll guide me
Erik (The Phantom) : I gave you my music
Erik (The Phantom) : Made your song take wing
Erik (The Phantom) : And now
Erik (The Phantom) : How you've repaid me
Erik (The Phantom) : Denied me and betrayed me
Erik (The Phantom) : He was bound to love you
Erik (The Phantom) : When he heard you sing
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Say you'll share with me one love
Christine Daaé;Raoul : One lifetime
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Say the word and I will follow you
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Share each day with me
Christine Daaé;Raoul : Each night each morning
Erik (The Phantom) : You will curse the day you did not do
Erik (The Phantom) : All that the Phantom
Erik (The Phantom) : Asked of you
Monsieur Gilles André : Monsieur Firmin
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Monsieur Andr
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Dear Andr what a splendid party
Monsieur Gilles André : The prologue to a bright new year
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Quite a night I'm impressed Well one does one's best
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Here's to us
Monsieur Gilles André
: A toast to all the city
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Such a pity that The
Phantom can't be here
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Paper faces on parade
Ensemble : Hide your face so the world will never find you
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Every face a different shade
Ensemble : Look around There's another mask behind you
Ensemble : Flash of mauve Splash of puce Fool and king Ghoul and goose
Ensemble;Madame Giry;Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : Green and black Queen and priest Trace of rouge Face of beast
Ensemble : Faces
Ensemble : Take your turn Take a ride On the merrygoround In an inhuman race
Ensemble : Thigh of blue
Ensemble : True is false
Ensemble : Who is who
Monsieur Gilles André : Curl of lip Swirl of gown
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : Ace of hearts Face of clown
Ensemble : Faces
Ensemble : Drink it in Drink it up
Ensemble : Till you've drowned in the light In the sound
Raoul;Christine Daaé : But who can name the face
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Grinning yellows Spinning reds
Ensemble : Take your fill Let the spectacle astound you
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Burning glances Turning heads
Ensemble : Stop and stare at the sea of smiles around you
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Seething shadows Breathing lies
Ensemble : Masquerade You can fool any friend who ever knew you
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Leering satyrs Peering eyes
Ensemble : Masquerade Run and hide But the face will still pursue you
Madame Giry : What a night
Christine Daaé : What a crowd
Monsieur Gilles André : Makes you glad
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Makes you proud
Monsieur Richard Firmin : All the crme de la
Carlotta Giudicelli : crme Watching us
And watching them
Madame Giry : And all our fears are in the past
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Six months
Monsieur Gilles André : Of relief
Madame Giry : Of delight
Monsieur Gilles André : Of Elysian peace
Madame Giry;Meg Giry : And we can breathe at last
Carlotta Giudicelli : No more notes
Ubaldo Piangi : No more ghost
Carlotta Giudicelli : Here's a health
Ubaldo Piangi : Here's a toast
Monsieur Richard Firmin : To a prosperous year
Monsieur Gilles André : To the new chandelier
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : And may its splendour never fade
Ensemble : What a change
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : What a blessed release
Monsieur Richard Firmin : And what a masquerade
Christine Daaé : Think of it
Christine Daaé : A secret engagement Look
Christine Daaé : Your future bride Just think of it
Raoul : But why is it secret What have we to hide
Christine Daaé : You promised me
Raoul : You promised me
Christine Daaé : No Raoul please don't They'll see
Raoul : Well let them see
Raoul : It's an engagement not a crime
Raoul : Christine what are you afraid of
Christine Daaé : Let's not argue
Raoul : Let's not argue
Christine Daaé : Please pretend
Raoul : I can only hope
Christine Daaé : You will understand in time
Raoul : I'll understand in time
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Paper faces on parade
Ensemble : Hide your face So the world will never find you
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Every face a different shade
Ensemble : Look around There's another mask behind you
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Burning glances Turning heads
Ensemble : Stop and stare At the sea of smiles around you
Ensemble : Masquerade
Ensemble : Grinning yellows Spinning reds
Ensemble : Take your fill Let the spectacle astound you
Erik (The Phantom) : Why so silent good messieurs
Erik (The Phantom) : Did you think that I had left you for good
Erik (The Phantom) : Have you missed me good messieurs
Erik (The Phantom) : I have written you an opera
Erik (The Phantom) : Here I bring the finished score
Erik (The Phantom) : Don Juan Triumphant
Erik (The Phantom) : I advise you to comply
Erik (The Phantom) : My instructions should be clear
Erik (The Phantom) : Remember there are worse things than a shattered chandelier
Erik (The Phantom) : Your chains are still mine You will sing for me
Raoul : Madame Giry
Madame Giry : Monsieur don't ask me
Madame Giry : I know no more than anyone else
Raoul : That's not true You know something don't you
Madame Giry : I know nothing
Madame Giry : Please monsieur don't ask me
Raoul : Madame for all our sakes
Madame Giry : Very well
Madame Giry : It was years ago
Madame Giry : There was a travelling fair in the city
Madame Giry : Tumblers conjurers human oddities
Raoul : Go on
Madame Giry : And there was I shall never forget him
Madame Giry : A man locked in a cage
Raoul : In a cage
Madame Giry : Aprodigy monsieur
Madame Giry : Scholar architect musician
Raoul : A composer
Madame Giry : And an inventor too monsieur
Madame Giry : They boasted he had once built for the Shah of Persia
Madame Giry : a maze of mirrors
Raoul : Who was this man
Madame Giry : A freak of nature
Madame Giry : More monster than man
Raoul : Deformed
Madame Giry : From birth it seemed
Raoul : My God
Madame Giry : Then he went missing
Madame Giry : He escaped
Raoul : Go on
Madame Giry : They never found him
Madame Giry : It was said he had died
Raoul : But he didn't die did he
Madame Giry : The world forgot him But I never can
Madame Giry : For in this darkness
Raoul : And so our phantom's this man
Madame Giry : I have seen him again
Madame Giry : I have said too much monsieur too much
Raoul : No Wait
Madame Giry : And there have been too many accidents
Raoul : Accidents Madame Giry
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Ludicrous Have you seen the score
Monsieur Gilles André : Simply ludicrous
Monsieur Gilles André : It's the final straw
Monsieur Richard Firmin : This is lunacy
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Well you know my views
Monsieur Gilles André : Utter lunacy
Monsieur Richard Firmin : But we daren't refuse
Monsieur Gilles André : Not another chandelier
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Look my friend what we have here
Monsieur Gilles André : Dear Andr Re my orchestrations
Monsieur Gilles André : We need another first bassoon
Monsieur Gilles André : Every note's overblown And that third trombone has to go
Monsieur Gilles André : The man could not be deafer So please preferably one who plays in tune
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Dear Firmin Visvis my opera
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Some chorus members must be sacked
Monsieur Richard Firmin : If you could find out which has a sense of pitch
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Wisely though
Monsieur Richard Firmin : I've managed to assign a rather minor role to those who cannot act
Carlotta Giudicelli : Outrage
Monsieur Richard Firmin : What is it now
Carlotta Giudicelli : This whole affair is an outrage
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Signora please
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Now what's the matter
Carlotta Giudicelli : Have you seen the size of my part
Monsieur Gilles André : Signora listen
Ubaldo Piangi : It's an insult
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Not you as well
Ubaldo Piangi : Just look at this
Ubaldo Piangi : It's an insult
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Please understand
Monsieur Gilles André : Signor Signora
Carlotta Giudicelli : The things I have to do for my art
Ubaldo Piangi : If you can call this gibberish art
Carlotta Giudicelli : Ah here's our little flower
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Ah Miss Daa Quite the lady of the hour
Monsieur Gilles André : You have secured the largest role in this Don Juan
Carlotta Giudicelli : Christine Daa She doesn't have the voice
Monsieur Gilles André : Signora please
Raoul : Then I take it you're agreeing
Carlotta Giudicelli : She's behind this
Monsieur Gilles André : It appears we have no choice
Carlotta Giudicelli : She's the one behind this Christine Daa
Christine Daaé : How dare you
Carlotta Giudicelli : I'm not a fool
Christine Daaé : You evil woman How dare you
Carlotta Giudicelli : You think I'm blind
Christine Daaé : This isn't my fault
Christine Daaé : I don't want any part in this plot
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Miss Daa surely
Monsieur Gilles André : But why not
Monsieur Richard Firmin : What does she say It's
Monsieur Richard Firmin : your decision
Monsieur Richard Firmin : But why not
Carlotta Giudicelli : She's backing out
Monsieur Richard Firmin : You have a duty
Christine Daaé : I cannot sing it duty or not
Raoul : Christine Christine
Raoul : You don't have to They can't make you
Madame Giry : Please monsieur Another note
Madame Giry : Fondest greetings to you all
Madame Giry : A few instructions just before rehearsal starts
Madame Giry : Carlotta must be taught to act
Madame Giry;Erik (The Phantom) : Not her normal trick of Strutting round the stage
Erik (The Phantom) : Our Don Juan must lose some weight
Erik (The Phantom) : It's not healthy in a man of Piangi's age
Erik (The Phantom) : And my managers must learn
Erik (The Phantom) : That their place is in an office Not the arts
Erik (The Phantom) : As for Miss Christine Daa
Erik (The Phantom) : No doubt she'll do her best
Erik (The Phantom) : It's true her voice is good She knows
Erik (The Phantom) : Though should she wish to excel
Erik (The Phantom) : She has much still to learn
Erik (The Phantom) : If pride will let her return to me
Erik (The Phantom) : Her teacher her teacher
Erik (The Phantom) : Your obedient friend and Angel
Christine Daaé : I can't I won't do it
Raoul : We have all been blind
Raoul : And yet the answer is staring us in the face
Raoul : This could be the chance
Raoul : To ensnare our clever friend
Monsieur Richard Firmin : We're listening
Monsieur Gilles André : Go on
Raoul : We shall play his game
Raoul : Perform his work But remember we hold the ace
Raoul : For if Miss Daa sings
Raoul : He is certain to attend
Monsieur Gilles André : We make certain the doors are barred
Monsieur Richard Firmin : We make certain our men are there
Monsieur Gilles André : We make certain they're armed
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André;Raoul : The curtain falls
Raoul;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : His reign will end
Madame Giry : Madness
Monsieur Gilles André : I'm not so sure
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Not if it works
Madame Giry : This is madness
Monsieur Gilles André : The tide will turn
Madame Giry : Monsieur believe me
Madame Giry : There is no way of turning the tide
Monsieur Richard Firmin : You stick to ballet
Raoul : Then help us
Madame Giry : Monsieur I can't
Raoul : Instead of warning us
Raoul;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Help us
Madame Giry : I wish I could
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : Don't make excuses
Raoul : Or could it be that you're on his side
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ubaldo Piangi : She's his accomplice
Madame Giry : Monsieur believe me I intend no ill
Madame Giry : But messieurs be careful We have seen him kill
Raoul;Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : We'll say he'll fall And fall he will
Carlotta Giudicelli : She's the one behind this
Carlotta Giudicelli : Christine
Ubaldo Piangi : This is the truth
Carlotta Giudicelli : This is all her doing
Ubaldo Piangi;Carlotta Giudicelli : Christine Daa
Monsieur Richard Firmin : This is his undoing
Monsieur Richard Firmin : If you succeed you free us all
Raoul : Angel of Music fear my fury
Monsieur Richard Firmin;Monsieur Gilles André : This socalled Angel has to fall
Madame Giry : Hear my warning
Madame Giry : Hear his fury
Christine Daaé : Please don't
Christine Daaé : If you don't stop this I'll go mad
Christine Daaé : Raoul I'm frightened Don't make me do this
Christine Daaé : Raoul it scares me Don't put me through this ordeal
Christine Daaé : By fire He'll take me I know
Christine Daaé : We'll be parted forever He won't let me go
Christine Daaé : What I once used to dream I now dread
Christine Daaé : If he finds me it won't ever end
Christine Daaé : And he'll always be there Singing songs in my head
Christine Daaé : He'll always be there
Christine Daaé : Singing songs in my head
Carlotta Giudicelli : She's mad
Raoul : You said yourself
Raoul : He was nothing but a man
Raoul : Yet while he lives
Raoul : He will haunt us till we're dead
Christine Daaé : Twisted every way What answer can I give
Christine Daaé : Am I to risk my life to win the chance to live
Christine Daaé : Can I betray the man who once inspired my voice
Christine Daaé : Do I become his prey
Christine Daaé : Do I have any choice
Christine Daaé : He kills without a thought
Christine Daaé : He murders all that's good I know I can't refuse
Christine Daaé : And yet I wish I could Oh God if I agree
Christine Daaé : What horrors wait for me
Christine Daaé : In this The Phantom's opera
Raoul : Christine Christine
Raoul : Don't think that I don't care
Raoul : But every hope and every prayer
Raoul : Rests on you now
Christine Daaé : I can't
Raoul : Christine
Raoul : So it is to be war between us
Raoul : But this time my clever friend the disaster will be yours
Ensemble : Hide your sword now wounded knight
Ensemble : Your vainglorious gasconade
Ensemble : Brought you to your final fight
Ensemble : For your pride high price you've paid
Christine Daaé : Silken couch and hayfilled barn
Christine Daaé : Both have been his battlefield
Ubaldo Piangi : Those who tangle with Don Juan
Reyer : No no no
Reyer : Chorus rest please
Reyer : Don Juan Signor Piangi
Ubaldo Piangi : Si This is the phrase
Reyer : Those who tangle with Don Juan
Reyer : If you please
Ubaldo Piangi : Those who tangle with Don Juan
Reyer : Nearly but no
Reyer : Those who tang Tang Tang
Ubaldo Piangi : Those who tang Tang Tang
Carlotta Giudicelli : His way is better At least he makes it sound like music
Madame Giry : Signora would you speak that way in the presence of the composer
Carlotta Giudicelli : The composer is not here
Carlotta Giudicelli : And if he were here I would
Madame Giry : Can you be certain of that
Madame Giry : signora
Reyer : Once again if you please Signor Piangi After seven
Reyer : Five six seven
Ubaldo Piangi : Those who have been tangling with Don Juan
Carlotta Giudicelli : What does it matter what notes we sing
Carlotta Giudicelli : No one will know if it is right or wrong
Carlotta Giudicelli : No one will care
Ensemble : Poor young maiden For the thrill on your tongue of stolen sweets
Ensemble : You will have to pay the bill
Ensemble : Tangled in the winding sheets
Christine Daaé : In sleep he sang to me
Christine Daaé : In dreams he came
Christine Daaé : That voice which calls to me
Christine Daaé : And speaks my name
Christine Daaé : Little Lotte thought of everything and nothing
Christine Daaé : Her father promised her that he would send her the Angel of Music
Christine Daaé : Her father promised her
Christine Daaé : You were once
Christine Daaé : My one companion
Christine Daaé : You were all that mattered
Christine Daaé : You were once a friend and father
Christine Daaé : Then my world was shattered
Christine Daaé : Wishing you were somehow here again
Christine Daaé : Wishing you were somehow near
Christine Daaé : Sometimes it seemed If I just dreamed
Christine Daaé : Somehow you would be here
Christine Daaé : Wishing I could hear your voice again
Christine Daaé : Knowing that I never would
Christine Daaé : Dreaming of you won't help me to do
Christine Daaé : All that you dreamed I could
Christine Daaé : Passing bells and sculpted angels
Christine Daaé : Cold and monumental
Christine Daaé : Seemed for you the wrong companions
Christine Daaé : You were warm and gentle
Christine Daaé : Too many years fighting back tears
Christine Daaé : Why can't the past just die
Christine Daaé : Wishing you were somehow here again
Christine Daaé : Knowing we must say goodbye
Christine Daaé : Try to forgive teach me to live
Christine Daaé : Give me the strength to try
Christine Daaé : No more memories
Christine Daaé : No more silent tears
Christine Daaé : No more gazing across
Christine Daaé : The wasted years
Christine Daaé : Help me say
Christine Daaé : Goodbye
Erik (The Phantom) : Wandering child So lost so helpless
Erik (The Phantom) : Yearning for my guidance
Christine Daaé : Angel or father Friend or phantom
Christine Daaé : Who is it there
Christine Daaé : Staring
Erik (The Phantom) : Have you forgotten your angel
Erik (The Phantom) : Angel oh speak
Christine Daaé : What endless longings
Christine Daaé : Echo in this whisper
Erik (The Phantom) : Too long you've wandered in Winter
Raoul : Once again she is His
Erik (The Phantom) : Far from my fathering gaze
Raoul : Once again she returns
Christine Daaé : Wildly my mind
Christine Daaé : Beats against you
Erik (The Phantom) : You resist
Christine Daaé;Erik (The Phantom) : Yet my(your) soul obeys
Raoul : Into the arms of her
Christine Daaé : Angel of Music
Christine Daaé : I denied you
Erik (The Phantom) : Angel of Music you denied me
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : Angel or demon
Raoul : still he calls her
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : Turning from true beauty
Raoul : Luring her back from the grave
Raoul : Turning from true beauty
Raoul;Erik (The Phantom) : Angel of Music do not shun me Angel or dark seducer
Christine Daaé : Angel of Music my protector
Christine Daaé : Come to me strange angel
Erik (The Phantom) : I am your Angel of Music
Erik (The Phantom) : Come to me Angel of Music
Raoul : Angel of darkness cease this torment
Erik (The Phantom) : I am your Angel of Music
Raoul : Christine
Raoul : Christine Listen to me
Raoul : whatever you may believe this man This This thing is not your father
Erik (The Phantom) : I am your Angel of Music
Raoul : Let her go For God's sake let her go Christine
Christine Daaé : Raoul
Erik (The Phantom) : Bravo monsieur such spirited words
Raoul : More tricks monsieur
Erik (The Phantom) : Let's see monsieur how far you dare go
Raoul : More deception more violence
Erik (The Phantom) : That's right that's right
Erik (The Phantom) : keep walking this way
Raoul : You can't win her love by making her your prisoner
Erik (The Phantom) : I'm here I'm here monsieur The angel of death
Erik (The Phantom) : Come on Come on Don't stop Don't stop
Erik (The Phantom) : So be it
Erik (The Phantom) : Now let it be war upon you both
Joseph Buquet : You understand your instructions
Joseph Buquet : When you hear the whistle take up your positions
Joseph Buquet : I shall then instruct you to secure the doors
Joseph Buquet : It is essential that all doors are properly secured
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Andr are we doing the right thing
Monsieur Gilles André : Well have you got a better idea
Joseph Buquet : Monsieur Vicomte am I to give the order
Raoul : Give the order
Raoul : You in the pit do you have a clear view of that box
Guard : Yes sir
Raoul : Remember when the time comes shoot
Raoul : Only if you have to but shoot to kill
Guard : How will I know sir
Raoul : You'll know
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Monsieur le Vicomte are you confident this will work
Monsieur Richard Firmin : Will Miss Daa sing
Raoul : Don't worry Firmin Andr
Monsieur Gilles André : We're in your hands monsieur
Joseph Buquet : My men are now in position sir
Raoul : Go ahead then
Joseph Buquet : Are the doors secure
Guard : Secure
Erik (The Phantom) : I'm here The Phantom of the Opera
Erik (The Phantom) : I'm here I'm here I'm here
Raoul : Idiot I said only when the time comes
Guard : But Monsieur le Vicomte
Erik (The Phantom) : No buts
Erik (The Phantom) : For once Monsieur Vicomte is right
Erik (The Phantom) : Seal my fate tonight
Erik (The Phantom) : I hate to have to cut the fun short
Erik (The Phantom) : But the joke's wearing thin
Erik (The Phantom) : Let my opera begin
Ensemble : Here the sire may serve the dam
Ensemble : Here the master takes his meat
Ensemble : Here the sacrificial lamb
Ensemble : Utters one despairing bleat
Carlotta Giudicelli : Poor young maiden
Carlotta Giudicelli : For the thrill on your tongue of stolen sweets
Carlotta Giudicelli : You will have to pay the bill
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ensemble : Tangled in the winding sheets
Ensemble : Serve the meal and serve the maid Serve the meal and serve the maid Serve the master so that
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ensemble : When tables plans and maids are laid
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ensemble : Don Juan triumphs
Carlotta Giudicelli;Ensemble : Once again
Carlotta Giudicelli : Shoo
Ubaldo Piangi : Passarino faithful friend
Ubaldo Piangi : Once again recite the plan
Man : Your young guest believes I'm you
Man : I the master you the man
Ubaldo Piangi : When you met you wore my cloak She could not have seen your face
Ubaldo Piangi : She believes she dines with me
Ubaldo Piangi : In her master's borrowed place
Ubaldo Piangi : Furtively we'll scoff and quaff Stealing what in truth is mine
Ubaldo Piangi : When it's late and modesty
Ubaldo Piangi : Starts to mellow with the wine You come home I use your voice
Man : Slam the door like crack of doom
Ubaldo Piangi : I will say Come hide with me
Ubaldo Piangi : Where oh where Of course my room
Man : Poor thing hasn't got a chance
Ubaldo Piangi : Here's my hat my cloak and sword
Ubaldo Piangi : Conquest is assured if I do not forget myself and laugh
Ubaldo Piangi : Ha Ha Ha
Christine Daaé : No thoughts within her head
Christine Daaé : But thoughts of joy
Christine Daaé : No dreams within her heart
Christine Daaé : But dreams of love
Erik (The Phantom) : Master Passarino
Erik (The Phantom) : Go away for the trap is set
Erik (The Phantom) : And waits for its prey
Erik (The Phantom) : You have come here
Erik (The Phantom) : In pursuit of your deepest urge
Erik (The Phantom) : In pursuit of that wish which till now has been silent
Erik (The Phantom) : Silent
Erik (The Phantom) : I have brought you
Erik (The Phantom) : That our passion may fuse and merge
Erik (The Phantom) : In your mind you've already succumbed to me
Erik (The Phantom) : Dropped all defenses Completely succumbed to me
Erik (The Phantom) : Now you are here with me
Erik (The Phantom) : No second thoughts
Erik (The Phantom) : You've decided
Erik (The Phantom) : Decided
Erik (The Phantom) : Past the point of no return
Erik (The Phantom) : No backward glances
Erik (The Phantom) : Our games of make believe
Erik (The Phantom) : Are at an end
Erik (The Phantom) : Past all thought of if or when
Erik (The Phantom) : No use resisting
Erik (The Phantom) : Abandon thought
Erik (The Phantom) : And let the dream descend
Erik (The Phantom) : What raging fire shall flood the soul
Erik (The Phantom) : What rich desire unlocks its door
Erik (The Phantom) : What sweet seduction lies before us
Erik (The Phantom) : Past the point of no return
Erik (The Phantom) : The final threshold
Erik (The Phantom) : What warm unspoken secrets
Erik (The Phantom) : Will we learn
Erik (The Phantom) : Beyond the point
Erik (The Phantom) : Of no return
Christine Daaé : You have brought me
Christine Daaé : To that moment when words run dry
Christine Daaé : To that moment when speech Disappears into silence
Christine Daaé : Silence
Christine Daaé : I have come here
Christine Daaé : Hardly knowing the reason why
Christine Daaé : In my mind I've already imagined our bodies entwining
Christine Daaé : Defenseless and silent
Christine Daaé : And now I am here with you
Christine Daaé : No second thoughts
Christine Daaé : I've decided
Christine Daaé : Decided
Christine Daaé : Past the point of no return
Christine Daaé : No going back now
Christine Daaé : Our passion play has now
Christine Daaé : At last begun
Christine Daaé : Past all thought of right or wrong
Christine Daaé : One final question
Christine Daaé : How long should we two wait
Christine Daaé : Before we're one
Christine Daaé : When will the blood begin to race
Christine Daaé : The sleeping bud burst into bloom
Christine Daaé : When will the flames at last
Christine Daaé : Consume us
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : Past the point of no return
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : The final threshold
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : The bridge is crossed
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : So stand and watch it burn
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : We've passed the point
Erik (The Phantom);Christine Daaé : Of no return
Erik (The Phantom) : Say you'll share with me
Erik (The Phantom) : One love one lifetime
Erik (The Phantom) : Lead me save me
Erik (The Phantom) : From my solitude
Erik (The Phantom) : Say you want me
Erik (The Phantom) : With you here
Erik (The Phantom) : Beside you
Erik (The Phantom) : Anywhere you go
Erik (The Phantom) : Let me go too
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : That's all I ask of
Erik (The Phantom) : No
Raoul : No Don't shoot
Raoul : No What are you doing there
Raoul : Give me this monsieur Get water monsieur Upstairs monsieur Come
Raoul : Monsieur Firmin come Open the doors monsieur
Madame Giry : Monsieur Vicomte come with me I know where they are
Raoul : Can I trust you
Madame Giry : You must
Madame Giry : But remember keep your hand at the level of your eyes
Raoul : But why
Madame Giry : The Punjab lasso monsieur
Madame Giry : First Buquet now Piangi
Meg Giry : Like this monsieur Look I'II go with you
Madame Giry : No Meg No You stay here
Madame Giry : Come with me monsieur do as I say
Madame Giry : But hurry or we shall be too late
Erik (The Phantom) : Down once more
Erik (The Phantom) : To the dungeon of my black despair
Erik (The Phantom) : Down we plunge to the prison of my mind
Erik (The Phantom) : Down that path into darkness
Erik (The Phantom) : Deep as hell
Erik (The Phantom) : Why you ask was I bound and chained
Erik (The Phantom) : In this cold and dismal place
Erik (The Phantom) : Not for any mortal sin
Erik (The Phantom) : But the wickedness of my abhorrent face
Erik (The Phantom) : Track down this murderer He must be found
Erik (The Phantom) : Hounded out by everyone
Erik (The Phantom) : Met with hatred everywhere
Erik (The Phantom) : No kind word from anyone
Erik (The Phantom) : No compassion anywhere
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine why Why
Madame Giry : Your hand at the level of your eyes
Raoul : At the level of your eyes
Ensemble : At the level of your eyes
Ensemble : Level of your eyes
Madame Giry : He lives across the lake monsieur
Madame Giry : This is as far as I dare go
Raoul : Madame Giry
Raoul : thank you
Ensemble : Track down this murderer He must be found Track down this murderer He must be found
Ensemble : Hunt down this animal who runs to ground
Ensemble : Too long he's preyed on us
Ensemble : But now we know
Ensemble : The Phantom of the Opera is here Deep down below
Ensemble : He's here The Phantom of the Opera
Christine Daaé : Have you gorged yourself at last in your lust for blood
Christine Daaé : Am I now to be prey to your lust for flesh
Erik (The Phantom) : That fate which condemns me to wallow in blood
Erik (The Phantom) : Has also denied me
Erik (The Phantom) : the joys of the flesh
Erik (The Phantom) : This face
Erik (The Phantom) : The infection which poisons our love
Erik (The Phantom) : Which earned a mother's fear and loathing
Erik (The Phantom) : A mask my first
Erik (The Phantom) : Unfeeling scrap of clothing
Erik (The Phantom) : Pity comes too late
Erik (The Phantom) : Turn around and face your fate
Erik (The Phantom) : An eternity of this
Erik (The Phantom) : Before your eyes
Christine Daaé : This haunted face
Christine Daaé : Holds no horror for me now
Christine Daaé : It's in your soul
Christine Daaé : That the true distortion lies
Erik (The Phantom) : Wait I think my dear we have a guest
Christine Daaé : Raoul
Erik (The Phantom) : Sir this is indeed an unparalleled delight
Erik (The Phantom) : I had rather hoped that you would come
Raoul : No
Erik (The Phantom) : And now my wish comes true
Erik (The Phantom) : You have truly made my night
Raoul : Free her
Raoul : Do what you will only free her
Raoul : Have you no pity
Erik (The Phantom) : Your lover makes a passionate plea
Christine Daaé : Please Raoul it's useless
Raoul : I love her
Raoul : Does that mean nothing I love her
Raoul : Show some compassion
Erik (The Phantom) : The world showed no compassion to me
Raoul : Christine Christine
Raoul : Let me see her
Erik (The Phantom) : Be my guest
Raoul : sir
Raoul : Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : Monsieur I bid you welcome
Erik (The Phantom) : Did you think that I would harm her
Erik (The Phantom) : Why should I make her pay
Erik (The Phantom) : For the sins which are yours
Christine Daaé : No
Erik (The Phantom) : Order your fine horses now
Erik (The Phantom) : Raise up your hand to the level of your eyes
Erik (The Phantom) : Nothing can save you now
Erik (The Phantom) : Except perhaps Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : Start a new life with me
Erik (The Phantom) : Buy his freedom with your love
Erik (The Phantom) : Refuse me and you send your lover to his death
Erik (The Phantom) : This is the choice
Erik (The Phantom) : This is the point of no return
Christine Daaé : The tears I might have shed
Christine Daaé : For your dark fate
Christine Daaé : Grow cold
Christine Daaé : And turn to tears of hate
Raoul : Christine forgive me Please forgive me
Raoul : I did it all for you and all for nothing
Christine Daaé : Farewell my fallen idol and false friend
Erik (The Phantom) : Too late for turning back
Christine Daaé : We had such hopes And now such hopes are shattered
Erik (The Phantom) : Too late for prayers and useless pity
Raoul : Say you love him and Past
Erik (The Phantom) : all hopes of cries for help
Raoul : My life is over
Erik (The Phantom) : No point in fighting
Raoul : Either way you choose he has to win
Erik (The Phantom) : Either way you choose you cannot win
Erik (The Phantom) : So do you end your days with me
Erik (The Phantom) : Or do you send him to his grave
Raoul : Why make her lie to you
Raoul : To save me
Erik (The Phantom) : Past the point of no return
Christine Daaé : Angel of Music
Raoul : For pity's sake
Christine Daaé : Who deserve this
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine The final threshold
Erik (The Phantom) : His life is now the prize which you must earn
Raoul : I fought so hard to free you
Erik (The Phantom) : You've past the point of no return
Christine Daaé : Angel of Music
Christine Daaé : You deceived me
Christine Daaé : I gave my mind blindly
Erik (The Phantom) : Blindly
Erik (The Phantom) : You try my patience
Erik (The Phantom) : Make your choice
Christine Daaé : Pitiful creature of darkness
Christine Daaé : What kind of life have you known
Christine Daaé : God give me courage to show you
Christine Daaé : You are not alone
Ensemble : Track down this murderer
Ensemble : He must be found
Erik (The Phantom) : Take her forget me forget all of this
Erik (The Phantom) : Leave me alone Forget all you've seen
Erik (The Phantom) : Go now don't let them find you
Ensemble : Revenge for Buquet
Erik (The Phantom) : Take the boat
Erik (The Phantom) : Swear to me never to tell
Erik (The Phantom) : Of the secret you know
Ensemble : The Phantom of the Opera
Erik (The Phantom) : of this Angel of Hell
Erik (The Phantom) : Go
Erik (The Phantom) : Go now and leave me
Erik (The Phantom) : Masquerade
Erik (The Phantom) : Paper faces on parade
Erik (The Phantom) : Hide your face So the world
Erik (The Phantom) : Will never find you
Erik (The Phantom) : Christine
Erik (The Phantom) : I love you
Christine Daaé : Say you'll share with me
Christine Daaé : One love one lifetime
Erik (The Phantom) : Say the word
Erik (The Phantom) : And I will follow you
Christine Daaé : Share each day with me
Christine Daaé : Each night each morning
Erik (The Phantom) : You alone can make
Erik (The Phantom) : My song take flight
Erik (The Phantom) : It's over now
Erik (The Phantom) : The music
Erik (The Phantom) : Of the
Erik (The Phantom) : night
Thank you
Oh thank you Thank you
Gosh uh do sit down for goodness sake I might talk for too long
Gosh when I was a little boy and I was first brought here by my mother
when I was five I think to a Promenade concert
I think I heard Beethoven's Third Symphony
and I don't think I could have ever ever believed
sitting somewhere up there
that anything like this would ever happen to my music
And I have to thank immediately Cameron Mackintosh What an extraordinary production he's put together
Thank you Cameron We'll meet him in a moment
But before I go any further the wonderful thing about musicals is that
something has to happen that brings them all together
I mean you can have a really great musical and
One aspect of it could be wrong whether it be the production whether it be something to do
With how it's staged or anything and it might get buried and then take years to find again
But what happened so extraordinarily with this is that everything came together with Cameron as the producer
Before we go any further I have to say that
it would have never happened without Maria Bjrnson and of course
Maria Bjrnson
was as all of you know the incredible designer of the show
It was her vision combined I think with everything else
that really brought us along She tragically died some years ago
One of the greatest sadnesses is that she's not here tonight
but I hope we've honoured her spirit in every way
So Maria thank you
And I ought to say tonight's rather extraordinary because I know that there are many companies of The Phantom of the Opera
watching this performance around the world because it's being beamed around the world tonight
And none I suppose more important than the director who made it possible
who's in New York at the moment with the New York Broadway company
Hal Prince So hello Hal
And thank you for everything Hal
So without any more ado let's bring on the original creative team from London
Here they come led by Sir Cameron Mackintosh
Charles Hart our lyricist of course
Andy Bridge our lighting and above all Gillian Lynne who staged tonight
Thank you Gillian
And the creative team from the Albert Hall tonight
Here they all are
Laurence the director in the middle
Now
Next I have to thank our fantastic company What a fantastic show
Ramin Sierra you couldn't have done me more proud
And Anthony Inglis and the fantastic orchestra
Just before we move on
I'm going to introduce you in a second to the original London company but I just would like you to remember John Aron
Steve Barton who of course played Raoul and Mary Millar
who sadly are no longer with us but they were wonderful members of our original team
So a small appreciation to them please
And here is our original London company
We have one other member of the company tonight
who has hotfooted it from the London Palladium
Michael Crawford
Finally
And I suppose this is very special for me
It is a great joy for me to welcome tonight
my Angel of Music Sarah Brightman
But
Without these two we would not be here
Uh we have one slight additional surprise
Sarah has agreed to sing
So I'm going to leave you
in the hands of the Angel of Music
Maestro take it away
In sleep he sang to me
In dreams he came
That voice which calls to me
And speaks my name
And do I dream again
For now I find
The Phantom of the Opera is there
Inside my mind
Sing once again with me
Our strange duet
My power over you
Grows stronger yet
And though you turn from me
To glance behind
The Phantom of the Opera is there
Inside your mind
Those who have seen your face
Draw back in fear
I am the mask you wear
It's me they hear
My spirit and your voice Your spirit and my voice
In one combined
The Phantom of the Opera is there
Inside your mind Inside my mind He's there The Phantom of the Opera
Beware The Phantom of the Opera
In all your fantasies
You always knew
That man and mystery
Were both in you
And in this labyrinth
Where night is blind
The Phantom of the Opera is there
Inside your mind Sing
Sing my Angel of Music He's there
The Phantom of the Opera
Sing for me
We have brought you
To the seat of sweet music's throne
To this kingdom where all must pay homage to music
Music
We have come here
For one purpose and one alone
Since the moment you first heard us sing
We have needed you with us to serve him
To sing for his music
His music
Nighttime sharpens
Heightens each sensation
Darkness stirs
And wakes imagination
Silently the senses
Abandon their defenses
Slowly gently
Night unfurls its splendour
Grasp it sense it
Tremulous and tender
Turn your face away
From the garish light of day
Turn your thoughts away
From cold unfeeling light
And listen to the music of the night
Close your eyes and surrender
To your darkest dreams
Purge your thoughts of the life
You knew before
Close your eyes let your spirit
Start to soar
And you'll live
As you've never lived before
Softly deftly
Music shall caress you
Hear it feel it
Secretly possess you
Open up your mind
Let your fantasies unwind
In this darkness that you know you cannot fight
The darkness of the music
Of the night
Let you mind start a journey
To a strange new world
Leave all thoughts of the world you knew before
Let you soul take you where
You long to be
Only then
Can you belong
To me
Floating falling
Sweet intoxication
Touch me trust me
Savour each sensation
Let the dream begin
Let your darker side give in
To the power of the music
That I write
The power of the music
Of the night
You alone can make
Our song take flight
It's over now
The music of
The night