Jonathan Larson : Hi I'm Jon
Jonathan Larson : I'm a musicaltheater writer
Jonathan Larson : One of the last of my species
Jonathan Larson : Sorry So so you know lately I've been hearing this sound
Jonathan Larson : Everywhere I go like a tick tick tick
Jonathan Larson : Like a time bomb
Jonathan Larson : in some cheesy Bmovie or Saturday morning cartoon The fuse has been lit
Jonathan Larson : The clock counts down the seconds as the flame
Jonathan Larson : gets closer and closer and closer until all at once
Jonathan Larson : Happy anniversary I love you so much
Susan : Before the Pulitzer Prize
Susan : Before
Man1 : We dedicate this opening night and every performance to our friend Jonathan Larson
Susan : Everything you're about to see is true
Susan : Except for the parts Jonathan made up
Jonathan Larson : The date is January 26th 1990
Jonathan Larson : The setting the barren unfashionable noman'sland
Jonathan Larson : between SoHo and Greenwich Village
Jonathan Larson : I have two keyboards a Macintosh computer A cat
Jonathan Larson : An impressive collection of compact discs
Jonathan Larson : cassettes and records of other people's music
Jonathan Larson : Bookshelves sagging under the weight of plays and novels I didn't write
Jonathan Larson : I have an original dystopian rock musical
Jonathan Larson : that I have spent the last eight years of my life writing
Jonathan Larson : and rewriting and rewriting
Jonathan Larson : I have rejection letters from every major and minor producer
Jonathan Larson : theater company record label and film studio in existence
Jonathan Larson : And in just over a week
Jonathan Larson : I will be 30 years old
Jonathan Larson : Older than Stephen Sondheim when he had his first Broadway show
Jonathan Larson : Older than Paul McCartney when he wrote his last song with John Lennon
Jonathan Larson : By the time my parents were 30 they already had two kids
Jonathan Larson : they had careers with steady paychecks a mortgage
Jonathan Larson : And in eight days my youth will be over forever
Jonathan Larson : And what exactly do I have to show for myself
Jonathan Larson : Happy birthday
Jonathan Larson : Stop the clock
Jonathan Larson : Take time out
Jonathan Larson : Time to regroup
Jonathan Larson : Before you lose the bout
Roger Bart;Jonathan Larson : Freeze the frame
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart : Back it up
Jonathan Larson : Time to refocus
Jonathan Larson : Before they wrap it up
Jonathan Larson : Years are getting shorter
Jonathan Larson : Lines on your face are getting longer
Jonathan Larson : Feel like you're treading water
Jonathan Larson : But the riptide's getting stronger
Jonathan Larson : Don't panic don't jump ship
Jonathan Larson : Can't fight it like taxes
Jonathan Larson : At least it happens Only once in your life
Jonathan Larson : They're singing Happy Birthday
Jonathan Larson : You just want to lay down and cry
Jonathan Larson : Not just another birthday it's 3090
Jonathan Larson : Why can't you stay 29
Jonathan Larson : Hell you still feel like you're 22
Jonathan Larson : Turn 30 1990 Bang You're dead
Jonathan Larson : What can you do
Michael : I made ten copies
Jonathan Larson : You are an angel on earth
Michael : This is the last time Seriously
Jonathan Larson : I know Thank you
Jonathan Larson : No no no I got you
Michael : I'm gonna pay
Jonathan Larson : Hey I don't want you
Carolyn : Somebody needs to take out this trash
Freddy : So I hear you're moving out of Jon's place
Freddy : That's the end of an era
Freddy : We hear him sobbing in the fridge most mornings It's very sad
Jonathan Larson : No no no We are not talking about that
Jonathan Larson : Wait Carolyn you're coming next Friday right
Carolyn : What's happening Friday
Michael : Surprised he hasn't mentioned it
Freddy : That sounds vaguely familiar
Jonathan Larson : Guys this is the biggest break I've ever had This is that moment
Jonathan Larson : It's the first time people are gonna see the show that aren't just us
Freddy : It's good you're not putting too much pressure on it
Jonathan Larson : But it's true though It's like you get to a certain age and you stop being a writer who waits tables
Jonathan Larson : and you become a waiter with a hobby
Michael : BooBoo you need to ask yourself in this moment
Michael : are you letting yourself be led by fear or by love
Roger Bart : Clear the runway
Roger Bart : Make another pass
Roger Bart : Try one more approach
Roger Bart : Before you're out of gas
Jonathan Larson : Friends are getting fatter
Jonathan Larson : Hairs on your head are getting thinner
Jonathan Larson : Feel like a cleanup batter
Jonathan Larson : On a team that ain't a winner
Roger Bart : Don't freak out don't strike out
Roger Bart : Can't fight it like City Hall
Jonathan Larson : At least you're not alone
Jonathan Larson : Your friends are there too
Jonathan Larson : And they're singing Happy Birthday
Jonathan Larson;Michael : You just wish you could run away
Jonathan Larson : Who cares about a birthday
Jonathan Larson;Michael : But 3090 hey
Jonathan Larson : Can you be optimistic
Jonathan Larson;Michael : You're no longer the ingénue
Jonathan Larson;Michael : Turn 30 1990
Jonathan Larson : Boom You're passé
Jonathan Larson;Michael : What can you do
Jonathan Larson : What can you do
Susan : You just quit
Jonathan Larson : Well no I didn't just quit quit I gave I gave my notice
Susan : That's exactly the same thing
Jonathan Larson : No I have two weeks left
Jonathan Larson : I'm allowing myself to be led by love
Susan : What
Jonathan Larson : You know Rosa's got another client Craig Carnelia
Susan : This is Rosa your agent who hasn't returned your calls in a year
Jonathan Larson : Yeah yeah That's the one
Jonathan Larson : So she invited the entire theater industry to Craig's musical workshop last year
Jonathan Larson : And by intermission some producer... had already written him a check for ten thousand dollars
Susan : I just wish that you didn't have to think like that
Jonathan Larson : Well it's expensive to make art
Susan : No baby it's expensive to make art here
Jonathan Larson : Yeah but worth every penny
Susan : That's beautiful
Jonathan Larson : I know right
Susan : How are you gonna pay for this Jonathan
Jonathan Larson : Peter Pan and Tinkerbell
Jonathan Larson : Which way to Never Never Land
Jonathan Larson : Emerald City's gone to hell
Jonathan Larson : Since the wizard blew off his command Blew off his command
Jonathan Larson : On the streets you hear the voices
Jonathan Larson : Lost children crocodiles
Jonathan Larson : You're not into
Jonathan Larson : Making choices wicked witches
Jonathan Larson : Poppy fields or men behind the curtain
Jonathan Larson : Tiger lilies ruby slippers
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson;Roger Bart : Clock is ticking that's for certain
Jonathan Larson : They're singing Happy Birthday
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : Happy birthday
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : I just wish it all were a dream
Jonathan Larson : It feels much more like doomsday
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : Fuck 3090 3090
Jonathan Larson : Seems like I'm in for a twister
Jonathan Larson : I don't see a rainbow do you
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : Turn 30 in the 90s
Jonathan Larson : Look into my hands now The ball has passed
Jonathan Larson : I want the spoils but not too fast
Jonathan Larson : The world is calling It's now or Neverland
Jonathan Larson : Why can't I stay a child forever and
Jonathan Larson : 3090 3090
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson;Roger Bart : 3090 3090 3090 30 3090 30 3090
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : What can I do What can I do
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : 3090 30 3090
Karessa Johnson;Roger Bart;Jonathan Larson : What can I do
Jonathan Larson : Ladies and gentlemen please give it up for our band
Jonathan Larson : and also for my very very very dear friends
Jonathan Larson : Roger and Karessa on vocals
Jonathan Larson : Friday night
Deborah : Hi Jonathan it's Deborah Susan dropped off your music for tonight's dance
Jonathan Larson : Hey Pookie
Michael : Hi
Jonathan Larson : How was Philly
Michael : I went from the airport to a conference room and then back to the airport three hours later
Jonathan Larson : Sounds amazing
Michael : Mm
Jonathan Larson : Yeah he was the lead of every play in high school college
Jonathan Larson : And then we moved to New York
Michael : I am sick of waking up at 500 to get in line outside the Equity Building and wait all day
Michael : praying that the director actually even agrees to see anyone that's nonunion and then
Michael : when I finally do get in the room I sing
Michael : I don't know six measures if I'm lucky before they cut me off
Michael : and call me the wrong name Juan Pedro Carlos
Jonathan Larson : And then a week later he got a job at a fancy advertising company
Jonathan Larson : making high five figures
Jonathan Larson : Healthcare dental
Jonathan Larson : He never looked back
Michael : You know for someone who's broke you could probably spend a little bit less on party planning
Jonathan Larson : Well what is the point of money
Jonathan Larson : if you're not gonna spend it on the people you love
Michael : Yeah except you don't have any money
Jonathan Larson : Oh right
Michael : This has been sitting here for a week
Jonathan Larson : I'm on it
Michael : Mmhm Yeah You seem very on it
Michael : Pretty soon you won't have me around to remind you to pay your bills on time
Jonathan Larson : How will I ever survive
Michael : That's a very real question Have you found a new roommate yet
Jonathan Larson : I've been a little busy You know My workshop is next week
Michael : Wait what workshop
Jonathan Larson : That was funny
Michael : What time's the show tonight
Jonathan Larson : Uh
Jonathan Larson : Curtain's at 800
Michael : Mm
Michael : I've heard the dancing's amazing but the music sucks
Jonathan Larson : in a small town in the Midwest She went to college to study biology
Jonathan Larson : she thought she'd become a doctor maybe teach
Jonathan Larson : But then she fell in love
Jonathan Larson : with modern dance instead
Jonathan Larson : Every parent's dream right
Jonathan Larson : She moved to New York without knowing a soul
Jonathan Larson : Four years later she's already danced with every major choreographer in the city Paul Trisha Merce
Jonathan Larson : 1990 This was the year she was finally gonna join a company
Jonathan Larson : Not just go from job to job Actually have a home an artistic family
Jonathan Larson : And she was ready This was her year She knew it
Jonathan Larson : And then she fractured her ankle during a dress rehearsal
Jonathan Larson : she's dancing again it's just
Jonathan Larson : whatever that moment was when she knew
Jonathan Larson : all of a sudden she doesn't know anymore
Jonathan Larson : But Susan is a real artist
Jonathan Larson : She doesn't care about seeing her name in the New York Times
Jonathan Larson : It doesn't matter to her if she's dancing in front of five people
Jonathan Larson : or in front of five thousand
Jonathan Larson : And then there's the matter of us
Radio : Love shack Baby love shack
Love shack Baby love shack
Susan : You know he can't afford all of this right
Michael : Well he loves making a fuss especially about you
Susan : Hm
Freddy : After everything we've done for him
Jonathan Larson : Stop
Freddy : he walks away
Jonathan Larson : Freddy look I'm leaving you my mixtapes
Jonathan Larson : You can play them in remembrance of me
Michael : Jonathan Larson's famous Moondance Diner mixtape
Michael : Who doesn't love showtunes with their French toast
Jonathan Larson : Actually it's not just showtunes It's a very eclectic mix
Carolyn : Someone's very touchy about mixtapes
Michael : Apparently
Freddy : Okay listen I'm happy for you I really am
Jonathan Larson : Oh yeah
Freddy : I'm also extremely bitter and jealous and envious and sort of hateful towards you right now I mean
Freddy : he's getting out
Jonathan Larson : And you're gonna be next
Freddy : Well I got a callback last week
Jonathan Larson : Great
Freddy : For a cruise
Carolyn : What's wrong with a cruise
Freddy : It's an Arctic cruise so pretty much everything
Freddy : Uh every single thing is wrong with that It's in the Arctic
Jonathan Larson : How you feeling
Freddy : Um
Freddy : It's been a really good week
Freddy : Tcell count is good My doctor feels cautiously optimistic
Jonathan Larson : Okay good You look great
Freddy : Oh my God thank you I know
Freddy : But for the cruise I'm gonna have to sort of
Carolyn : Tighten up pull it up Make it tight
Roger Bart : Scott and I we used to sing madrigals in high school
Jonathan Larson : What Really
Scott : I hated singing I just did it for the pussy
Roger Bart : Ran into Scott in SoHo and he really really
Jonathan Larson : Got it
Scott : I never get to go to artist parties you know
Scott : It sucks The drugs there are always the best
Jonathan Larson : Mm Mmhm
Roger Bart : Scott's in finance
Jonathan Larson : Shocking
Scott : Yeah What do you do
Jonathan Larson : I'm the future of musical theater Scott
Jonathan Larson : Welcome I'm gonna get another drink
Scott : That guy's hilarious
Jonathan Larson : This is the life bobo bobo bo
Jonathan Larson : Bohemia
Jonathan Larson : Shower's in the kitchen There might be some soap
Jonathan Larson : Dishes in the sink Brush your teeth if you can cope
Jonathan Larson : Toilet's in the closet
Jonathan Larson : You better hope There's a light bulb in there
Woman1 : Not today
Jonathan Larson : Revolving door roommates Prick up your ears
Jonathan Larson : Fourteen people in just four years
Jonathan Larson : Ann and Max and Jonathan And Carolyn and Kerri
Jonathan Larson : David Tim No Tim was just a guest from June
Jonathan Larson : To January Margaret Lisa David Susie Stephen Joe and Sam
Jonathan Larson : And Elsa the bill collector's dream Who still is on the lam
Jonathan Larson : Don't forget the neighbors Michelle and Gay
Jonathan Larson : More like a family than a family hey
Jonathan Larson : The time is flying And everything is dying
Jonathan Larson : I thought by now I'd have a dog a kid a wife
Jonathan Larson : The ship is sort of sinking So let's start drinking
Jonathan Larson : Before we start thinking Is this the life
Jonathan Larson : This is the life bobo bobo bo
Jonathan Larson;All : This is the life bobo bobo bo
All : This is the life bobo bobo bo
All : Bohemia
All : Bohemia One more time
All;Jonathan Larson : Bohemia
Jonathan Larson : Bobo bobo bo
Scott : That was freaking amazing
Scott : Whoo
Jonathan Larson : Whoa
Jonathan Larson : Hi Everyone's leaving
Susan : I just needed some fresh air
Jonathan Larson : Okay
Jonathan Larson : It's freezing up here
Susan : Where is your coat
Jonathan Larson : Oh I don't know It's uh
Jonathan Larson : It's at the bottom of a very large pile
Jonathan Larson : Oh
Jonathan Larson : Mm
Jonathan Larson : Wow That's pretty
Susan : That's the prison barge
Jonathan Larson : Oh yeah
Susan : I heard uh in Jacob's Pillow they're hiring new teachers for the dance school
Susan : Yeah
Susan : Work a couple of hours a week Then the rest of the time is yours
Susan : Free studio space whenever you want
Jonathan Larson : Hey Whoa Can we just talk for a second
Susan : Mm
Jonathan Larson : Can we just talk about how amazing you were tonight
Susan;Jonathan Larson : Thank you I am not messing around
Jonathan Larson : I could just watch you dancing forever
Susan : I was thinking of maybe applying
Jonathan Larson : Hm
Susan : To the job in Jacob's Pillow
Susan : We went there last summer remember
Jonathan Larson : Oh
We saw the new Mark Morris
Jonathan Larson : Oh yeah
Susan : Yeah
Jonathan Larson : That's the place in the Berkshires
Susan : Mmhm
Jonathan Larson : So you're gonna move to the Berkshires
Susan : And not have to work 30 hours a week doing word processing to pay the rent why not
Susan : I might actually be able to get back into shape
Jonathan Larson : Okay Yeah All right Let's do it Let's move
Susan : I'm being serious
Jonathan Larson : Hey I'm being serious
Jonathan Larson : We're gonna live in a log cabin We're gonna hunt acorns
Jonathan Larson : We're gonna We're gonna gather squirrels
Susan : What are you even talking about
Susan : It's the Berkshires
Susan : People have vacation homes there You've been there
Jonathan Larson : I'm so sorry Can we Can we please go inside
Jonathan Larson : Sorry I just feel like I'm scared
Jonathan Larson : I'm beginning to lose sensation in my extremities
Susan : You are such a baby
Susan : Take this
Jonathan Larson : Whoa Hold on
Susan : You like
Susan : I thought that you were in a hurry to get back inside
Susan : You know that job in the Berkshires
Jonathan Larson : Yeah sounds amazing
Susan : I already applied for it
Jonathan Larson : Oh yeah
Susan : Yeah
Susan : And I got it
Jonathan Larson : Oh
Jonathan Larson : Oh yeah That's great
Susan : It starts in June
Jonathan Larson : Okay So this is just for the summer
Susan : No Mmmm it's permanent
Susan : Jon
Jonathan Larson : Whoa
Michael : the Berkshires That is like so far from Midtown
Jonathan Larson : Yeah Yeah
Jonathan Larson : Why is she doing this right now
Jonathan Larson : And she says I want you to come with me
Michael : What did you say
Jonathan Larson : I said Oh
Jonathan Larson : What am I supposed to say I didn't know what to say I mean like I can't I can't leave New York
Michael : Oh tell her to move in with you
Jonathan Larson : Move in where
Michael : You need a new roommate right
Michael : It's two birds one stone You are very welcome
Jonathan Larson : Okay so what what about the guy that you were dating David I thought you guys were great together
Michael : It didn't work out
Michael : Oh There's a focus group at the office this week and they're  looking for a few more people How about I sign you up
Jonathan Larson : So you can lure me to the dark side
Michael : No So I can introduce you to my colleagues
Michael : and show them how brilliant you are
Jonathan Larson : I don't want a job in advertising
Michael : I don't want you to have a job in advertising I want you to have a job in
Michael : jingle writing
Michael : listen
Michael : You come up with jingles all the time for fun Jon You come up with songs about cereal we're eating
Michael : You could get paid for that
Jonathan Larson : Well you know
Jonathan Larson : I will be getting paid for my music anyway So
Michael : That's true
Michael : And we are here Home sweet home
Jonathan Larson : Oh my God
Jonathan Larson : Michael tosses the keys to the parking attendant
Jonathan Larson : What apartment building has a parking attendant
Jonathan Larson : An old white lady with a tiny dog
Jonathan Larson : Is this real life
Michael : No more
Michael : Walking 13 blocks With 30 pounds of laundry In the freezing dead of winter
Michael : No more Walking up six flights of stairs Or throwing down the key Because there is no buzzer
Michael : No more faulty wiring No more crooked floors
Michael : No more spitting out my Ultra Brite
Michael : On top of dirty dishes In the one and only sink
Michael : Hello to my walking closets
Michael : Tidy as Park Avenue
Michael : Hello my butcher block table
Michael : I could get used I could get used I could get used to you
Michael : No more Climbing over sleeping people Before you get out the door Of your own building
Jonathan Larson;Michael : No more
Michael : Noxious fumes from gas heaters That are illegal
Jonathan Larson : Or will blow up While you are sleeping
Michael;Jonathan Larson : No more Leaky ceilings
Michael;Jonathan Larson : No more Holes in the floor
Jonathan Larson : No more Taking a shower in the kitchen While your roommate's Eating breakfast
Jonathan Larson;Michael : And you're getting water On his cornflakes
Jonathan Larson;Michael : Hello to shiny New parquet wood floors
Jonathan Larson;Michael : As waxed as a wealthy girl's legs
Jonathan Larson;Michael : Hello dear Mr Dishwasher
Jonathan Larson;Michael : I could get used I could get used I could get used I could get Used to you I could get used to you
Jonathan Larson : No more exotic
Michael : No more neurotic
Jonathan Larson;Michael : No more anything But pleasantly robotic
Michael : We're movin on up
Jonathan Larson : We're movin on up
Michael;Jonathan Larson : To the East Side To the East Side
Jonathan Larson;Michael : To a deluxe apartment In the sky
Jonathan Larson;Michael : Hello to dear Mr Doorman
Jonathan Larson;Michael : Who looks like Captain Kangaroo
Jonathan Larson;Michael : Hello dear fellow and how do you do
Michael : I could get used
Jonathan Larson : I could get used
Michael : I could get
Jonathan Larson;Michael : used to you
Michael : yeah I could get used
Jonathan Larson : I could get used
Michael;Jonathan Larson : Even seduced
Jonathan Larson;Michael : Even seduced
Michael : I could get
Michael;Jonathan Larson : Used to you Ow
Michael : ah
man2 : of the closing doors
man2 : I swear to God I'm talking to you in the back
man2 : Stand clear of the closing doors
Ira Weitzman : You still don't have the song
Jonathan Larson : This has never happened to me before I
Jonathan Larson : I don't know
Jonathan Larson : I usually write a song in a day
Jonathan Larson : Last week I wrote a song about sugar It took me three hours
Ira Weitzman : Song about sugar
Jonathan Larson : Sugar
Jonathan Larson : She is refined For a small price
Jonathan Larson : She blows my mind
Ira Weitzman : Why would you do that
Jonathan Larson : An exercise
Ira Weitzman : In what
Jonathan Larson : I like to see if I can write a song about anything
Ira Weitzman : Why don't you try to see if you can write a song for your musical
Ira Weitzman : that's being presented to an audience in six days instead
Jonathan Larson : Eiro Weissman
Jonathan Larson : Head of musical theater at Playwrights Horizons
Jonathan Larson : The first and so far only actual theater person to offer to put on a workshop of
Jonathan Larson : I'm starting to think that maybe I don't need it
Ira Weitzman : You do need it
Jonathan Larson : You know
Jonathan Larson : you're the only person who ever said that
Jonathan Larson : Just so you know
Ira Weitzman : You're telling me in the five years you've been writing this musical
Jonathan Larson : Eight years actually
Ira Weitzman : no one else has told you that you're missing a song for Elizabeth in the second act
Jonathan Larson : No one
Jonathan Larson : One person did say that
Jonathan Larson : For years I was part of this musical theater writing workshop
Jonathan Larson : Liquid crystal digital readout
Jonathan Larson : Floating on a sea of gray
Jonathan Larson : Once a week we would gather the few surviving members of our dwindling tribe
Jonathan Larson : We would watch one of us present what we'd been working on to a panel of well
Jonathan Larson : real writers
Jonathan Larson : The theater legends who created the Broadway shows that we'd grown up dragging our parents into the city to see
Jonathan Larson : Dividing the day away
Jonathan Larson : Counting slowly Measuring moments
Jonathan Larson : The night I presented people began to buzz as soon as we walked through the door
Jonathan Larson : Is it really him
Jonathan Larson : It was
Jonathan Larson : Stephen Sondheim
Walter Bloom : All right I'll start
Walter Bloom : I'm lost
Walter Bloom : I I don't know what the show is
Walter Bloom : Is it social commentary
Walter Bloom : Is it science fiction And the music is the same thing Is it rock Is it Broadway Is it both
Walter Bloom : Is it neither Steve what did you think
Stephen Sondheim : I have to say I disagree pretty strongly Walter
Stephen Sondheim : I think this is a musical that knows exactly what it is
Walter Bloom : Yes Yes Of course yes Abso
Stephen Sondheim : The world that you've created is really original
Stephen Sondheim : It's fascinating
Stephen Sondheim : The problem is it's not particularly easy to follow the
Stephen Sondheim : emotional thread The details distract us from connecting with the characters
Stephen Sondheim : Does that make sense
Jonathan Larson : Okay Okay
Walter Bloom : Yes yes We're on the same page That's exactly how I felt
Walter Bloom : We're saying the same thing just differently
Walter Bloom : But the music okay I'm sorry The music just wasn't there
Stephen Sondheim : I actually I thought the songs were swell
Walter Bloom : Yeah okay Yes Yes
Walter Bloom : The individual songs
Stephen Sondheim : I particularly like the one the young man sings at the end of the first act
Stephen Sondheim : First rate lyric and tune Well done
Jonathan Larson : First rate lyric and tune
Jonathan Larson : Thank you
Jonathan Larson : Those five words were enough to keep me going for the next two years
Stephen Sondheim : You're missing a song for the young woman Uh
Jonathan Larson : Elizabeth
Stephen Sondheim : Elizabeth It's the turning point in the show
Stephen Sondheim : Your protagonist is either gonna go in this direction or that direction
Stephen Sondheim : Someone has to wake him up shake some sense into him
Jonathan Larson : Okay
Walter Bloom : It's so funny because I was gonna say the exact same thing
Jonathan Larson : Can we talk musicians Because if it's only gonna be four
Jonathan Larson : then I gotta figure out how I'm gonna split up the bass parts
Jonathan Larson : This is for you Here you go
Ira Weitzman : Thank you Yeah Uh
Ira Weitzman : Jon this is a reading
Jonathan Larson : Mm
Ira Weitzman : You'll have a piano
Jonathan Larson : I wrote a rock score
Jonathan Larson : So at the very least I'll need a synth and drums and a guitar and
Ira Weitzman : A great song should sound great without any instruments
Jonathan Larson : Mm Okay
Jonathan Larson : Let's just do the song as a cappella
Jonathan Larson : Oh actually you know what Maybe we'll just skip the songs
Jonathan Larson : and then we can get the audience in and out in half an hour
Ira Weitzman : I will take a look at the budget and I will see if I can dig up some money for another musician
Jonathan Larson : Two more
Jonathan Larson : And piano is the absolute bare minimum for this
Ira Weitzman : Have you spoken to Rosa
Jonathan Larson : Hey Rosa this is Jonathan Larson your client
Jonathan Larson : I've left multiple messages with your secretary
Ira Weitzman : Rosa Stevens is still your agent right
Jonathan Larson : Oh yeah No yeah we We talk constantly
Ira Weitzman : Has she sent out the invites for the presentation yet
Ira Weitzman : We haven't gotten a lot of RSVPs
Ira Weitzman : It's fine
Jonathan Larson : Mm
Ira Weitzman : Nobody has more contacts in the industry than Rosa
Ira Weitzman : I'm sure she'll get some good people there for you
Jonathan Larson : Yeah yeah
Ira Weitzman : see you Monday
Jonathan Larson : Yes sir
Ira Weitzman : First day of rehearsal
Ira Weitzman : And finish the song already Please
Jonathan Larson : Thank you Ira Thank you for all this Thank you
Jonathan Larson : Yeah I want to leave a message for Mr Sondheim
Jonathan Larson : This is um my name is Jonathan Larson
Jonathan Larson : Hi there this is a message for Joe Papp
Jonathan Larson : For Bernie Gersten
Jonathan Larson : For the Artistic Director of the Shubert Organization
Jonathan Larson : For La MaMa
Jonathan Larson : So it's Larson LARSON
Jonathan Larson : No not Parson
Jonathan Larson : It's something that's never been done before It's gonna be quite the event
Jonathan Larson : It has tremendous commercial possibility
Jonathan Larson : We're filling up fast I want to make sure you got your spot
Jonathan Larson : I know that his time is limited
Jonathan Larson : Oh It would be such a treat
Jonathan Larson : Zero pressure
Jonathan Larson : Haha I really want you there
Jonathan Larson : So can I count you in
Jonathan Larson : There'll be a seat reserved for him
Jonathan Larson : Superbia It's at 1000 a. m
Jonathan Larson : This Friday at 1000 a. m
Jonathan Larson : I'm so excited about Friday
Jonathan Larson : I wouldn't want you to miss it
Jonathan Larson : That's all the information I can give you
Jonathan Larson : They should put every Sondheim musical on PBS
Man3 : Attention
Jonathan Larson : Well, sunday's a pretty good start
Michael : I don't understand why can't he just tell her he loves her
Michael : Why can't he be an artist and love her
Jonathan Larson : He He does love her
Michael : Yeah but like he can't express it
Jonathan Larson : That's a personal problem Yeah
Jonathan Larson : I'm sayin
Michael : Men
Michael : Bernadette in that corset
Michael : Like that waist is just like
Jonathan Larson : How did he do that
Radio : Day by day Let the sunshine
Radio : It's the end of the world As we know it
Michael : Did you crack it yet
Jonathan Larson : Oh I'm getting so close
Michael : Call me if you need inspiration
Jonathan Larson : No no don't go Hang out
Jonathan Larson : You can you can sleep in your old room
Michael : Write the song BooBoo
TV : North Carolina Senator Jesse Helms is worried the legislation was sending the wrong message
TV : Let me say that if IV drug users and homosexual men would stop their activities today
TV : there would never be another case of AIDS in this country
TV : other than the ones already in progress
TV : Henry Champ at the US Capitol
TV : ... has overwhelmingly approved legislation providing nearly 3 billion dollars
Jonathan Larson;Susan : Hi Hey Oh my God I love you
Susan : Uh they want an answer by Wednesday
Susan : So I was wondering if we could maybe talk about it
Jonathan Larson : Uh
Susan;Jonathan Larson : The job Oh
Jonathan Larson : Yeah Um
Jonathan Larson : Can we uh talk about it tomorrow
Jonathan Larson : Cause I have to finish this song right now Is that okay
Susan : Sure
Jonathan Larson : You sure you're sure
Susan : I'm sure
Jonathan Larson : Okay
Jonathan Larson : You don't seem sure
Susan : Good night Jonathan
Jonathan Larson : Okay good night Um
Jonathan Larson : I'll be in
Jonathan Larson : Break of day the dawn is here
Jonathan Larson : Johnny's up and pacing
Jonathan Larson : Compromise or persevere
Jonathan Larson : His mind is racing
Jonathan Larson : Johnny has no guide
Jonathan Larson : Johnny wants to hide
Jonathan Larson : Can he make his mark
Jonathan Larson : If he gives up his spark
Jonathan Larson : Johnny can't decide
Jonathan Larson : Susan longs to live by the sea
Jonathan Larson : She's through with competition
Jonathan Larson : Susan wants a life with me
Jonathan Larson : Johnny's got a tough decision
Jonathan Larson : Johnny has no guide
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : Johnny wants to hide Can he settle down
Karessa Johnson;Jonathan Larson : And still not drown Drown
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : Johnny can't decide
Jonathan Larson : Michael's gotta have it all
Jonathan Larson : His luck will never end
Jonathan Larson : Johnny's backed against a wall
Jonathan Larson : Can he bend his dream
Jonathan Larson : Just like his friend
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : Johnny sees that Susan's right Susan's right Ambition eats right through you
Roger Bart : Michael doesn't see why
Roger Bart;Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : Johnny Holds so tight I hold so tight To the things That Johnny feels are true
Roger Bart;Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : Johnny has no guide Johnny has no guide Johnny wants to hide Johnny wants to hide
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : How can you soar When you're nailed to the floor
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : Johnny can't decide
Roger Bart;Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : Johnny has no guide Johnny has no guide Johnny wants to hide Johnny wants to hide
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : How do you know When it's time to let go
Jonathan Larson : Johnny can't
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : decide Johnny can't decide Johnny can't decide Johnny can't decide Decide
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : Decide Johnny can't decide Johnny can't decide Johnny can't decide
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : Johnny can't decide Decide Decide
Jonathan Larson;Roger Bart;Karessa Johnson : Decide decide Decide Decide decide
Roger Bart;Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : Decide
Jonathan Larson : Johnny can't decide
Carolyn : What is in the emergency room
Jonathan Larson : What
Carolyn : He woke up Saturday morning with a fever he could
Carolyn : He couldn't stop shivering
Jonathan Larson : Wait wait no Wait
Jonathan Larson : La He told me last week his Tcell count
Jonathan Larson : The doctor said that it was exactly where they wanted it four days ago
Carolyn : I guess it changed
Jonathan Larson : Shit
Jonathan Larson : He's gonna be fine
Carolyn : Yeah you know you're right
Jonathan Larson : I mean it He's gonna be fine Think about it
Jonathan Larson : You know how stubborn he is He's a pain in the ass
Jonathan Larson : Right
Carolyn : Yeah
Jonathan Larson : Frankly we should be pissed at him that he's left us understaffed At Sunday brunch
Carolyn : Right
Jonathan Larson : You know what I'm saying
Carolyn : Yeah
Jonathan Larson : Okay
Jonathan Larson : Friday, shit I should go to the hospital When am I gonna go to the hospital I need to write
Jonathan Larson : When am I gonna write I need to talk to Susan I need to see Freddy I should call Susan Why can't I write this song
Jonathan Larson : How can you possibly be thinking about your show
Jonathan Larson : when your friend is in the hospital
Jonathan Larson : What am I doing here?
Jonathan Larson : I need to leave I need to walk out that door and go
Jonathan Larson : But it's 930 on a Sunday morning at the Moondance Diner
Jonathan Larson : I'm not going anywhere
man4 : Eggs up
Citizen : Do you have any of that wonderful Jewish bread
Citizen : It's holly dear They call it holly bread
Jonathan Larson : Would you like some challah bread
man4 : Somebody pick up these goddamn eggs
man4 : Ya tranquilo Termina tu obra
Jonathan Larson : Harrington for four Harrington Harrington
Citizen : Uh ex
Jonathan Larson : Moondance What do you want
Jonathan Larson : That was a good ...
Jonathan Larson : Do we take reservations No we do not We're a diner
Carolyn : Where's my rye bread
Jonathan Larson : Name please
Citizen : Richard
Jonathan Larson : Richard How many
Citizen : Caplan Richard Caplan
Jonathan Larson : How many in your party
Citizen : With a C
Jonathan Larson : Got it How many in your party
Citizen : C as in cat
Jonathan Larson : I understand
Citizen : Can we order
Jonathan Larson : One second How many in your party
Citizen : It's not a math test
Jonathan Larson : Order
Jonathan Larson : Thank you for your patience
Citizen : I said an omelet with no yolks
Citizen : This is why you're just a waiter
Jonathan Larson : Tension
Carolyn : Major vomit situation in the ladies room
Citizen : Check
Citizen : Can we get two more mimosas please
Citizen : Cause she got a new job okay
Citizen : Either put some Baileys in this coffee or put some vodka in this orange juice please
Citizen : Something
Jonathan Larson : Balance
man4 : BLT up
man4 : Si se quejan de que se enfría no es culpa mía
Jonathan Larson : Fudge
Jonathan Larson : Carolyn
Carolyn : Can we get the check
Citizen : Excuse me Do you have any Baileys One sec Jesus Christ
Jonathan Larson : Brunch
All : Sunday
All : In the blue silver chromium diner
All : On the green purple Yellow red stools
Jonathan Larson : Sit the fools
Jonathan Larson : Who should eat at home
Jonathan Larson : Instead they pay on Sunday Sunday
All : For a cool orange juice or a bagel
All : On the soft green cylindrical stools
Jonathan Larson : Sit the fools
Jonathan Larson : Drinking cinnamon coffee
Jonathan Larson;All : Or decaffeinated tea
All : Forever Forever
All : Forever
All : In the blue silver chromium diner
All : Drips the green orange violet drool
All : From the fools
All : Who'd pay less at home
Citizen : Drinking coffee Light
All : And dark
Jonathan Larson : And cholesterol
Jonathan Larson : And bums bums bums bums Bums bums bums bums
All : bums People screaming for their toast
All : In a small SoHo cafe
All : On an island in Two Rivers
All;Jonathan Larson : On an ordinary
All : Sunday
Jonathan Larson : Brunch
Jonathan Larson : Monday morning
Jonathan Larson : My first day of rehearsals for the
Jonathan Larson : in case you'd forgotten missing its crucial Act Two musical number
Jonathan Larson : I make my way there through the land of the dead
Jonathan Larson : the Theater District
Man5 : Walk through Times Square And what do you see
Man5 : Ugliness where Architecture used to be
Man5 : The glamour and style Have been replaced by gaud
Man5 : Like the sixtydollar spectacle It's all a fraud
Man5 : That's the play game
Man5 : So why do I want To play the play game
Man5 : I must be insane To play the play game
Man5 : Even off Broadway It's no guarantee
Man5 : That some MBA Won't decide what you see
Man5 : Just like America lackin innovation
Man5 : Just gettin by On glitz and reputation
Man5 : Just like America on the decline
Man5 : Unconcerned with the product Just the bottom line
Man5 : Write for the movies write for TV So what if it's crap
Man5 : At least you won't write for free
Man5 : Make thousands of dollars For a first draft
Man5 : Your life won't depend On whether Frank Rich laughed
Man5 : So just forget Shakespeare Beckett Molière
Man5 : That's the play game
Jonathan Larson : That's the play game
Jonathan Larson : Why do I want to play the play game
Jonathan Larson : That's the play game Must be insane To play the play game
Man5 : That's the play game
Man5 : Why do I care
Man6 : I'll be auditioning for the role of Old Deuteronomy
Ira Weitzman : On behalf of Playwrights Horizons I want to welcome everyone
Ira Weitzman : and thank you all for taking part in this very exciting new musical
Ira Weitzman : by a very exciting young writer Jonathan Larson
Ira Weitzman : He's not even 30
Jonathan Larson : Oh wow Thank you Ira
Jonathan Larson : Um this is the first real workshop that this musical has ever had
Jonathan Larson : And now you guys are part of the family So
Jonathan Larson : any questions before we uh get going
Jonathan Larson : Yeah no Yeah
Woman2 : Um
Woman2 : Could you um Could you explain it maybe
Jonathan Larson : Yeah Explain what
Woman2 : Oh just the musical The story
Woman2 : It's a little um confusing in certain places Not in a bad way
Jonathan Larson : Superbia on a poisoned planet Earth
Jonathan Larson : where the vast majority of humanity spend their entire lives
Jonathan Larson : just staring at the screens of their media transmitters
Jonathan Larson : watching the tiny elite of the rich and powerful
Jonathan Larson : who film their own fabulous lives like TV shows
Jonathan Larson : A world where human emotion has been outlawed
Jonathan Larson : This will be the first musical written for the MTV generation
Jonathan Larson : This is my
Man7 : Is it supposed to be aliens I wasn't sure if it was all like aliens
Jonathan Larson : Nope not aliens Um But it is set in the future
Cristin : The color scheme for the day Is blackredblack
Cristin : The drug of course Will be the kilowatt
Cristin : The trend today is to say The adjective fun a lot
Jonathan Larson : It's perfect Keep going Keep going
Cristin : Studd star you have received Two nominations
Cristin : Face of the Year And Best Hair
Cristin : Prepare a speech For your photo opportunity
Cristin : Your agent Tim Pursent will be there
Jonathan Larson : I love it I love it
Jonathan Larson : You told me you needed a drummer Oh my goodness
Jonathan Larson : Hey Good night Wonderful work Really wonderful work
Jonathan Larson : No I I told you I needed a band
Ira Weitzman : It's 100 dollars for every musician
Jonathan Larson : Yeah And your annual operating budget is half a million dollars
Ira Weitzman : So far we're up to 12 RSVPs Jon
Ira Weitzman : You don't need a band with an audience of 12 people You'll outnumber them
Ira Weitzman : If you want more musicians
Ira Weitzman : you're gonna have to find the money for it somewhere else
Ira Weitzman : I'm sorry
Jonathan Larson : Thank you for everything
Jonathan Larson : I went to three friends funerals last year
Jonathan Larson : The oldest one was 27
Jonathan Larson : Pam Gordon Ally
Jonathan Larson : Freddy's not even
Jonathan Larson : He turned 25 two weeks ago
Jonathan Larson : And nobody's doing enough
Jonathan Larson : I'm not doing enough
Jonathan Larson : There's not enough time or maybe I'm just wasting my time
Jonathan Larson : And what about Susan's time When am I gonna talk to Susan
Jonathan Larson : What am I gonna say I don't know what to say
Jonathan Larson : So Susan waits and the time keeps ticking
Jonathan Larson : Tick tick tick
Jonathan Larson : And I have three days left until the workshop
Jonathan Larson : Three days left to write this song And if the song doesn't work
Jonathan Larson : the show doesn't work and then it's all been a waste of time
Jonathan Larson : Who gives a shit about a song
Jonathan Larson : And I miss Michael
Jonathan Larson : I need to talk to Michael
Jonathan Larson : I don't have time to talk to Michael
Singers : Everyone who ever has Or ever will be anyone will be there
Singers : Never in the history Of entertainment will there be an affair
Jonathan Larson;Singers : Make sure you're not speeding up
Singers : Quite like it
Singers : The event of the century
Singers : The quintessential social adventure
Jonathan Larson : I'm missing consonants in quintessential social adventure right
Susan : Hi
Susan : It sounds great
Jonathan Larson : Thanks
Jonathan Larson : Why didn't you tell me you were coming
Susan : I thought it might be a nice surprise
Jonathan Larson : Oh no It is It is
Susan : Okay It's Tuesday
Jonathan Larson : Mm
Susan : I need to give them the decision about the job by tomorrow so
Jonathan Larson : Hmm
Susan : Is there a moment where you can take a break
Jonathan Larson : I can't No the actors take breaks I don't I don't have any breaks
Susan : I just don't know what I'm gonna do So
Jonathan Larson : Um
Jonathan Larson : Can you Can you ask for an extension
Jonathan Larson : I'm sorry can we Can we talk about this tonight
Jonathan Larson : I'm so One second
Jonathan Larson : This is Can we get this section
Cristin : A nomination
Roger Bart;Cristin : A nomination
Cristin : A nomination for a Face Award
Roger Bart;Cristin : A Face Award
Cristin : Let's plug in
Roger Bart : Does this mean That I'll be on the air
Cristin : You already were
Cristin : Last night what a sight you were
Roger Bart : I was
Cristin : You were You played with my laser
Cristin : You thought it was a razor
Cristin : I'm positive that's what Caused such a scene
Roger Bart : We can get on the air My music box on the air
Roger Bart : Where Who What does this mean
Cristin : Everyone who ever has Or ever will be anyone will be there
Citizen : I can give you 50 for everything
Jonathan Larson : You're gonna sell it for five times that amount
Citizen : Fifty's the best I can do
Jonathan Larson : Cash
Citizen : Great
Citizen : Oh no He's keeping the ???
Citizen : Day by Day
Jonathan Larson : Yeah yeah I love it Ah
Jonathan Larson : ah ah
Michael : I'd love to take you to lunch
Michael : Celebrate your birthday
Jonathan Larson : I can't this week
Michael : I could really use your advice on some things
Jonathan Larson : Hey Michael I'm sorry can I call you back later
Jonathan Larson : I'm just I'm right in the middle of something here
Michael : Oh uh that focus group I mentioned
Michael : They're still looking for one more person to sign up
Michael : It's Thursday at eleven, I know money's tight for you right now
Michael : You know what Never mind
Jonathan Larson : Uh wait How much does it pay
Michael : It's only 75 bucks but it could be a thing
Jonathan Larson : I'll be there
Jonathan Larson : Thank you really That's Yeah thank you
Michael : Wow
Jonathan Larson : Okay bye Byebye
Michael : All right see you
Ira Weitzman : You were right I know
Singers : Never in the history Of entertainment will there be An affair quite like it
Singers : The event of the century
Singers : The quintessential social adventure We cannot afford to miss This night of bliss
Singers : The 31st annual Face Awards Presentation ceremony Live via satellite in color
Singers : It's an 18 hour function With commercial interruption From a marvelous glorious Slam bang glamorama
Singers : Everyone who's anyone knows Everyone who's anyone knows Everyone who's anyone knows Everyone who's anyone knows Everyone who's anyone knows everyone will be
Singers : There
Karessa Johnson : Can I hear it
Jonathan Larson : Huh
Karessa Johnson : The new song
Jonathan Larson : Any day now
Karessa Johnson : You're killin me Larson
Jonathan Larson : Oh sh
Jonathan Larson : Shh
Susan : Hey It's me Just pick up the phone
Susan : I know you're screening your calls
Susan : Every light is on in your apartment right now
Susan : I can see you
Jonathan Larson : Hey Hi You could have called first
Susan : I just did
Jonathan Larson : Mm
Susan : It's good to see you too
Jonathan Larson : I didn't mean it like that
Susan : Jesus Jonathan
Susan : I need you to talk to me
Jonathan Larson : I'm writing Susan I'm writing
Susan : You're gonna write a great American musical in the next ten minutes
Jonathan Larson : Thank you for being so supportive of my work
Susan : Because you've been such a champion of mine
Jonathan Larson : What's that supposed to mean
Susan : What do you think it means
Jonathan Larson : And now ladies and gentlemen we present you with
Jonathan Larson : scenes from a modern romance as told in song
Susan : I'm sorry I'm sorry I I'm not allowed to talk about my needs What needs
Jonathan Larson : Did I say that
Susan : You didn't have to say it It's implied
Jonathan Larson : How is it implied
Susan : You're the artist and I'm the girlfriend That's how you feel right
Jonathan Larson : I feel bad That you feel bad
Jonathan Larson : About me feeling bad About you feeling bad
Jonathan Larson : About what I said About what you said
Jonathan Larson : About me not being able
Jonathan Larson : To share a feeling
Jonathan Larson : Can we talk about this later please
Susan : When Jonathan When is later
Jonathan Larson : Not tonight
Karessa Johnson : If I thought that What you thought
Karessa Johnson : Was that I hadn't thought About sharing my thoughts
Karessa Johnson : Then my reaction To your reaction
Karessa Johnson : To my reaction Would have been more revealing
Jonathan Larson : I have been rehearsing all day I have been up since four this morning
Jonathan Larson : I have been trying to write a song for a week and I am nowhere
Jonathan Larson : I was afraid that you'd be afraid If I told you that
Jonathan Larson : I was afraid of intimacy
Susan : I've been telling you how unhappy I am for months
Jonathan Larson : If you don't have a problem With my problem Maybe the problem's Simply codependency
Jonathan Larson : Everyone's unhappy in New York
Jonathan Larson : That's what New York is
Jonathan Larson : I was wrong to
Karessa Johnson : Say you were wrong to
Jonathan Larson : Say I was wrong about
Karessa Johnson : You being wrong
Jonathan Larson : When you rang to say that
Karessa Johnson : the ring was the wrong thing to bring
Jonathan Larson : If I meant what I said When I said rings bored me
Susan : I don't know how to get through to you anymore
Susan : You keep shutting me out you keep putting up these fences
Jonathan Larson : I'm not I'm not shutting you out
Susan : You're a million miles away all the time
Jonathan Larson : Actually I'm right here
Susan : Are you Jonathan
Susan : Actually Because I know you
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : I'm not mad That you got mad
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : When I got mad When you said I should go drop dead
Jonathan Larson : If I were you And I'd done what I'd done
Jonathan Larson : I'd do what you did When I gave you the ring Having said what I said
Jonathan Larson : You're right I've been distracted but I promise you after the workshop I'm I'm gonna
Susan : After the workshop
Jonathan Larson : After the workshop
Susan : Everything is after the workshop
Jonathan Larson : Yeah
Susan : What if the workshop happens and nothing changes
Susan : No producer with a big check
Susan : You don't go straight to Broadway
Susan : You're still a waiter you're still living in this apartment you're still broke
Susan : What then Jonathan What about me
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : I feel bad that you feel bad About me feeling bad About you feeling bad about what I said About what you said About me not being Able to share a feeling Feeling badly about you
Jonathan Larson : I can't move to the Berkshires
Jonathan Larson : I can't leave my career behind
Susan : You think I don't know that
Jonathan Larson : What
Jonathan Larson : What are you What is this What do you want
Susan : I guess I just I wanted you to tell me not to go
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : If I thought that what you thought Was I hadn't thought About sharing my thoughts Then my reaction to your reaction To my reaction Would have been more revealing When I reacted to you
Jonathan Larson : Of course I don't want you to go
Really
Jonathan Larson : Obviously
Susan : Cause this is the first time you've ever said it
Susan : Oh my God
Jonathan Larson : Now it's out in the open
Susan : You're thinking about how you can turn this into a song Aren't you
Karessa Johnson : Now it's off our chest
Jonathan Larson : No What
Susan : You know what Jonathan I'm done
Jonathan Larson : Susan Susan wait
Susan : I hope that you have an amazing workshop
Jonathan Larson : Susan hold on Susan
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : Now it's 400 a. m And we have  therapy tomorrow It's too late to screw
Jonathan Larson;Karessa Johnson : So let's just get some rest
Woman3 : So just waiting on one more person
Woman3 : Enjoy those waters
Woman3 : So
Jonathan Larson : I'm Jon
Woman3 : Yes Mr Larson you're Michael's friend
Jonathan Larson : Yeah How are you
Woman3 : Good You're late
Woman3 : Oh
Jonathan Larson : Okay
Jonathan Larson : Sorry about that
Woman3 : No That's okay
Jonathan Larson : No because of the subway
Woman3 : Yeah I'm sure
Woman3 : Take a seat when you can
Jonathan Larson : Hi
Citizen : Welcome
Jonathan Larson : Thanks
Citizen : You sure there's no way to get into the bathroom
Woman3 : Oh no you're not allowed to use the bathroom
I'm Sorry did she mention when we were gonna get paid
Woman3 : Okay um so now that we're all here
Woman3 : Hi
Jonathan Larson : Hey
Woman3 : Why don't we begin with a quick brainstorming session Right
Woman3 : Just to get those creative juices flowing You know what I mean It'll be fun
Jonathan Larson : Two hours of this
Jonathan Larson : For one extra musician
Woman3 : So why don't we start by you just throwing out some ideas
Woman3 : when you hear me say the word America
Citizen : George Washington
Woman3 : Excellent
Citizen : Abraham Lincoln Abraham Lincoln Okay
Jonathan Larson : Empire racism genocide Vietnam
Jonathan Larson : Grover Cleveland
Citizen : The Constitution
Woman3 : Yes
Citizen : Yeah
Jonathan Larson : Magna Carta
Citizen : The Bill of Rights
Woman3 : Mmhm
Citizen : The right thing to do
Woman3 : Ooh
Citizen : The right stuff
Woman3 : Right stuff
Jonathan Larson : An open road at sunset
Jonathan Larson : Wind in your hair
Jonathan Larson : Nothing in your way except horizon
Woman3 : That is beautiful Mr Larson
Woman3 : Wow Okay That goes on the board
Citizen : The sun
Citizen : Sunrise
Jonathan Larson : The dawn of a new day
Citizen : Oh Where did you come from It all goes back You're amazing That is incredible
Citizen : A window looking out on a field
Citizen : Oh and I look out and I see the bunnies and little squirrelies
Jonathan Larson : The beating heart of the nation
Woman3 : Ooh Oh my gosh
Woman3 : Absolutely That's absolutely what it is
Citizen : Wow I've never even heard that before You are gifted
Jonathan Larson : I could get used to this
Jonathan Larson : I could get paid for this
Jonathan Larson : I could get health care
Jonathan Larson : A 401k
Jonathan Larson : A BMW A luxury apartment
Jonathan Larson : on Central Park West No no no East
Jonathan Larson : I could actually be rewarded for my creativity
Jonathan Larson : instead of rejected and ignored
Jonathan Larson : This could be the rest of my life
Woman3 : Now that we have all those fabulous ideas of yours in our heads
Woman3 : we are going to turn to the task at hand
Jonathan Larson : Umm
Woman3 : We are here to develop a name of a revolutionary consumer product that is just about to hit your shelves
Citizen : Oh Wow
Woman3 : This is where we're gonna need that incredible imagination of yours Mr Larson
Woman3 : So the product we're looking at is a tasteless odorless chemical compound
Woman3 : that will be used as a fat substitute in cooking
Citizen : Mm
Woman3 : And it's been successfully tested on a number of mammals
Citizen : Well that's good Mm
Woman3 : There are some side effects associated with the product that I've been instructed to tell you about
Woman3 : So it's skin scales
Woman3 : Um full hair loss
Woman3 : Hair eyebrows eyelashes
Jonathan Larson : This could be the rest of my life
Woman3 : And finally in a small number of users
Woman3 : there were reports of toxic shock syndrome
Woman3 : resulting in a brief hospitalization
Citizen : Eh no big deal
Woman3 : There are no bad ideas
Citizen;Woman3 : Free oil Love it
Citizen;Woman3 : Oil free Okay
Jonathan Larson : That's the same thing she just said
Citizen : I switched the words around
Woman3 : That's totally fine Kim Thank you so much
Citizen : The American Dream
Woman3 : Okay well
Citizen : Dreams of freedom
Woman3 : Okay
Citizen : Nutraoil
Woman3 : That's not bad Todd
Citizen : Waist oil No
Jonathan Larson : I got it
Jonathan Larson : I have it I have the exact
Citizen : Go go
Jonathan Larson : You wanna hear I got the exact right thing for this product
Jonathan Larson : Chubstitute
Michael : Chubstitute
Jonathan Larson : It's a joke
Michael : It's not funny
Jonathan Larson : Well maybe not to you
Michael : but I recommended you Jon
Michael : I put my name on the line for you
Jonathan Larson : Tell them I had a ???
Michael : That' isn't funny
Michael : This is my life
Jonathan Larson : No it's not your life it's advertising
Jonathan Larson : It's it's figuring out how to trick people into buying shit that they don't want
Michael : Actually it's a lot more complicated than that
Jonathan Larson : I don't understand how you can take any of this seriously
Michael : Because they pay me to
Jonathan Larson : Money isn't everything
Michael : Well it doesn't hurt
Jonathan Larson : Are you sure about that
Michael : What are you doing with your life that's so noble
Jonathan Larson : I'm making art
Michael : Woo That's what the world needs More art
Jonathan Larson : Actually yes And at least I'm not perpetuating a system
Michael : Jon You're writing musicals in your living room
Michael : you're not saving the rainforest
Jonathan Larson : Wow
Jonathan Larson : Gosh I wish I could be more like you
Jonathan Larson : and spend my life caring about driving the right car
Jonathan Larson : and wearing the right suits and living in a doorman building
Michael : Why shouldn't I want those things Jon Not all of us have options you do
Michael : All the things that you take for granted
Jonathan Larson : What Like what
Michael : Like a life with the person you love
Michael : Do you know what I would give for that
Michael : You You turn your nose up at it
Jonathan Larson : If that's what you want what's stopping you
Michael : What's stopping me How about Jesse Helms and the Moral Majority
Michael : How about the people that run this country
Michael : I can't get married I can't have kids
Michael : Half our friends are dying and the other half are scared to death they are next
Michael : So I'm sorry for getting a nice car Jon
Michael : I'm sorry for moving into an apartment with central heating
Michael : I'm sorry for enjoying my life while I still have time
Michael : I gotta go
Jonathan Larson : Hey
Jonathan Larson : You wanna come take the subway
Jonathan Larson : Come take the ...
Michael : I'd rather walk
Jonathan Larson : Michael
Jonathan Larson : Hello
Rosa Stevens : Jonny darling it's Rosa
Rosa Stevens : Hello
Jonathan Larson : Rosa Stevens
Rosa Stevens : Are we excited for tomorrow
Jonathan Larson : Tomorrow
Jonathan Larson : The presentation You remembered the presentation
Rosa Stevens : Remembered it I got every producer in town coming
Rosa Stevens : So it better be good
Jonathan Larson : Yeah it's uh it's gonna be amazing
Rosa Stevens : Let's see
Rosa Stevens : if we can get a bidding war started on this musical of yours What do you say
Jonathan Larson : Yes sure
Rosa Stevens : Okay
Rosa Stevens : doll
Rosa Stevens : Charlie get me Hal Prince on the line
Jonathan Larson : Rosa Um I
Jonathan Larson : I'm so sorry
Jonathan Larson : Yeah I know I know I know
Jonathan Larson : Oh no
Jonathan Larson : Why wouldn't you have called me to tell me my payment was late before you just cut off my power
Jonathan Larson : How is How does that make sense
Man8 : Sir as I explained before you received a notice
Jonathan Larson : No no no listen
Jonathan Larson : You don't understand I have a workshop
Jonathan Larson : I have a public presentation of my musical in 12 hours
man8;Jonathan Larson : Sir if you are going to raise your voice I'm sorry I'm sorry
Jonathan Larson : Look look look I can pay you over the phone right now
Jonathan Larson : I have my credit card right here
Man8 : The billing office is closed
Jonathan Larson : I would love to figure it out right now
Man8 : The billing office is closed for the night
Jonathan Larson : What am I gonna do
Man8 : Sir like I've said call
Jonathan Larson : Hey Beth Hey
Jonathan Larson : How are you It's Jon
Beth : Hi Jon
Jonathan Larson : Hi um is Susan there
Beth : She doesn't wanna talk to you Jon
Jonathan Larson : Yeah
Jonathan Larson : Um
Jonathan Larson : Sure sure Uh
Jonathan Larson : Well can you um can you give her a message for me
Beth : What is it
Jonathan Larson : Well it's just you know
Jonathan Larson : I just I wanted to remind her that tomorrow is my workshop and you know I
Jonathan Larson : I know I don't have any right to ask this It's just that
Jonathan Larson : I would just really love her to be there
Beth : I'll tell her you called
Jonathan Larson : Here I am
Jonathan Larson : The musical to which I have devoted my youth is about to be put on public display for every producer in New York
Jonathan Larson : I haven't written a single note
Jonathan Larson : or a single lyric of the most important song in the show
Jonathan Larson : I have no electricity
Jonathan Larson : My best friend is furious with me My girlfriend isn't speaking to me
Jonathan Larson : And there is only one thing I can think of to do
Jonathan Larson : Swim
Jonathan Larson : I hate this locker room Why won't Susan answer my calls
Jonathan Larson : Sweat wet echo Smell hell rap
Jonathan Larson : Pump up the volume Hot wet hot sweat
Jonathan Larson : How's the water
Jonathan Larson : Stretch stretch Spit in the mask
Jonathan Larson : Cloudy vision Test the water
Jonathan Larson : Contemplate the dive The shock to the skin
Jonathan Larson : Anticipate the pain the pain the pain The pain the pain now
Jonathan Larson : One two three Oh bite the air seven
Jonathan Larson : There's that girl One two three
Jonathan Larson : Oh bite the air Smooth soft skin
Jonathan Larson : Two three Oh bite the Thirteen
Jonathan Larson : Long legs brown skin and wet hair
Jonathan Larson : Whoa and wet hair
Jonathan Larson : Has Rosa even listened to my tape
Jonathan Larson : Kick stretch windmill arms See the hand point the feet
Jonathan Larson : Wet hair Relax this guy's too slow
Jonathan Larson : Fifteen Can I make it to 40
Jonathan Larson : Too slow Touch his heel move
Jonathan Larson : Answer my calls Red thin stripe
Jonathan Larson : Fifty feet sixty feet She looks like Susan
Jonathan Larson : Susan's beautiful
Jonathan Larson : Out don't think out out Let it out
Jonathan Larson : Keep the shoulder down down
Jonathan Larson : Easy not too hard
Jonathan Larson : Find the movement's origin
Jonathan Larson : Hands no Shoulder no
Jonathan Larson : Elbows no
Jonathan Larson : Lower from the back Yes lower
Jonathan Larson : Thirtynine 40
Jonathan Larson : Center center
Jonathan Larson : Forward motion
Jonathan Larson : Through the water
Jonathan Larson : Come to your senses
Jonathan Larson : Escape
Jonathan Larson : I am soaring
Jonathan Larson : I'm the water
Jonathan Larson : You're on the air
Jonathan Larson : You as the knight
Jonathan Larson : Escape
Jonathan Larson : I'm underground
Jonathan Larson : Me as the queen
Jonathan Larson : The show is about to begin
Jonathan Larson : The room is completely empty
Jonathan Larson : The show is about to begin and I am looking
Jonathan Larson : at 60 empty folding chairs
Jonathan Larson : Hi
Karessa Johnson : Hey boy genius
Jonathan Larson : I'm turning 30 on Sunday you know
Karessa Johnson : Oh well happy birthday
Jonathan Larson : Thank you
Karessa Johnson : Thirty's still young you know
Jonathan Larson : No one's here
Karessa Johnson : Oh It's not even nine
Karessa Johnson : The presentation doesn't start till ten
Jonathan Larson : Oh
Jonathan Larson : That's good
Jonathan Larson : Cool
Jonathan Larson : Okay
Jonathan Larson : Can you sight read
Karessa Johnson : Yeah
Jonathan Larson : Slowly, miraculously
Jonathan Larson : people start to show up
Jonathan's parents : Johnny
Jonathan's parents : Be right back
Jonathan's parents : This is phenomenal Look at the space it's just phenomenal
Jonathan Larson;Jonathan's parents : It's a rehearsal studio Dad It's a Broadway rehearsal studio
Jonathan's parents : This is the real thing
Jonathan's parents : so excited for you dear
Jonathan Larson : Thank you thank you thank you
Jonathan's parents : Are they paying you ???
Jonathan Larson : No
Jonathan's parents : Next time
Jonathan Larson : Sure
Jonathan's parents : Oh look for us
Jonathan Larson : No that's not
Jonathan Larson : That's for someone else actually
Jonathan's parents : Mm Do you like that
Jonathan Larson : You can you can  literally sit in any other seat
Jonathan's parents : Okay
Jonathan's parents : Shall we sit there
Jonathan's parents : Break a leg
Jonathan Larson : I love you
Jonathan Larson : Thank you
Jonathan's parents : His hair is ridiculous
Michael : Good turnout
Jonathan Larson : Yeah mostly friends
Michael : Mm what a nightmare
Jonathan Larson : Thank you for being here
Michael : Wild horses Jon You know that
Jonathan Larson : Oh Okay
Michael : Break legs
Jonathan Larson : Yeah
Rosa Stevens : Oh Thank you Thank you
Rosa Stevens : Ira you son of a gun Jonathan how are you
Jonathan Larson : Rosa
Jonathan Larson : Jon Larson
Rosa Stevens : Oh there he is
Rosa Stevens : Just the man I'm looking for You nervous Don't be nervous
Jonathan Larson : Yeah A little nervous Sure
Rosa Stevens : Of course you're nervous The first presentation of your musical is like
Rosa Stevens : having a colonoscopy in Times Square
Rosa Stevens : Only with a colonoscopy the worst thing that could happen is you find out you have cancer
Rosa Stevens : With a musical you find out you're already dead
Rosa Stevens : Have a good show Can't wait to see what you did
Ira Weitzman : We can't keep waiting It's quarter past
Jonathan Larson : I know I know I know
Ira Weitzman : Break a leg
Jonathan Larson : Okay
Jonathan Larson : Come here Thank you
Jonathan Larson : Hello Hi welcome
Jonathan Larson : I'm Jonathan Larson
Jonathan Larson : Hey well
Jonathan Larson : You don't have to do that Thank you so much that was very kind Uh
Jonathan Larson : Thank you for being here um this morning
Jonathan Larson : This is um
Singers : That's Stephen Sondheim
Jonathan Larson : Right Like I was saying
Jonathan Larson : Thank you all for being here This is my musical Superbia
Jonathan Larson : and I've been working on it for a little while now
Jonathan Larson : And I just really hope you all like it
Jonathan Larson : Thank you
Jonathan Larson : And the next hour and a half are a blur
Singers : Everyone who ever has Or ever will be anyone will be there
Singers : Never in the history of entertainment Will there be an affair quite like it
Singers : The event of the century
Singers : The quintessential social adventure
Singers : We cannot afford to miss This night of bliss
Singers : Everyone who's anyone knows Everyone who's anyone knows
Singers : Everyone who's anyone Everyone who's anyone knows
Singers : Everyone will be there
Jonathan Larson : And then
Jonathan Larson : Karessa steps forward to sing my new song
Jonathan Larson : Not even 12 hours old
Jonathan Larson : I close my eyes
Jonathan Larson : I brace myself
Jonathan Larson : I don't dare take a breath
Jonathan Larson : But when I open my eyes
Jonathan Larson : I don't see Karessa there
Susan : You're on the air
Susan : I'm underground
Susan : Signal's fading
Susan : Can't be found
Susan : I finally open up
Susan : For you I would do anything
Susan : But you've turned off the volume
Susan : Just when I've begun to sing
Susan : Come to your senses Defenses are not the way
Susan : to go And you know or at least you knew
Susan : Can't you recall when this all began
Susan : It was only you and me
Susan : It was only me and you
Karessa Johnson : I have to laugh
Karessa Johnson : We sure put on a show
Karessa Johnson : Love is passé in this day and age
Karessa Johnson : How can we expect it to grow
Karessa Johnson : You as the knight
Karessa Johnson : Me as the queen
Karessa Johnson : All I've got tonight
Karessa Johnson : Is static on a screen
Susan : Come to your senses Suspense is fine
Susan : If you're just an empty image Emanating out of a screen
Susan : Baby be real You can feel again
Susan : You don't need a music box melody
Susan : To know what I mean
Karessa Johnson : Deep in my eyes What do you see
Karessa Johnson : Deep in my sighs Listen to me
Susan : Let the music commence from inside
Susan;Karessa Johnson : Not only one sense but use all five
Susan : Come to your senses
Karessa Johnson : Come to your senses
Karessa Johnson;Susan : Come to your senses
Karessa Johnson;Susan : Baby come back
Susan;Karessa Johnson : Alive
Jonathan's parents : Whoo
Jonathan Larson : Hello
Rosa Stevens : Hi honey it's Rosa
Jonathan Larson : Hi Rosa Thank you so much for calling
Rosa Stevens : Well you already left six messages
Jonathan Larson : Yeah Um So have you heard anything yet
Rosa Stevens : Honey I have heard nothing but raves all day long
Rosa Stevens : I'm getting call after call after call
Jonathan Larson : Wow
Jonathan Larson : Okay Yes That's great news
Rosa Stevens : Everyone is telling me the same thing That Jonathan Larson
Rosa Stevens : I can't wait to see what he does next
Jonathan Larson : What do you mean what I do next What about
Rosa Stevens : I always told you it was a tough sell
Rosa Stevens : It's too arty for Broadway
Rosa Stevens : Tourists aren't gonna shell out 50 dollars to see a show about spaceships and robots
Jonathan Larson : Um That's not what it's about
Rosa Stevens : Well of course I know that Jonathan
Rosa Stevens : But you know these producers they care about one thing and one thing only
Jonathan Larson : Okay Uh So what about OffBroadway
Rosa Stevens : It's too expensive for Off
Rosa Stevens : You got a cast of thousands with the special effects
Rosa Stevens : Uh Charlie tell him I'll be on in a sec Listen sweetie I gotta run
Jonathan Larson : I'm sorry Rosa
Rosa Stevens : Congratulations on a terrific presentation
Jonathan Larson : Rosa Rosa hold on
Jonathan Larson : So okay
Jonathan Larson : So what am I supposed to do now
Rosa Stevens : You start writing the next one
Rosa Stevens : And after you finish that one you start on the next
Rosa Stevens : And on and on and that's what it is to be a writer honey
Rosa Stevens : You just keep throwing them against the wall and hoping against hope that eventually something sticks
Rosa Stevens : Listen
Rosa Stevens : Little advice from someone who's been in this business a long long time
Rosa Stevens : On the next one maybe try writing about what you know
Rosa Stevens : Okay kiddo
Jonathan Larson : Yeah
Rosa Stevens : Start sharpening those pencils
Jonathan Larson : Yeah yeah
Michael : I think let's give it a minute and see what happens next week
Jonathan Larson : Hey I need a job
Michael : Can you hold on a second
Jonathan Larson : I'll apologize to the focus group lady
Jonathan Larson : I will never say anything bad about marketing research ever again I swear to God
Michael : I'm gonna call you right back
Jonathan Larson : I wanna do what you do I wanna have what you have I want the BMW I want the doorman I want it I want all of it Okay
Michael;Jonathan Larson : What's going on Oh it's good It's good I just spent the last eight years killing myself on a musical that's never gonna happen
Michael : I find that very hard to believe It was incredible this morning
Jonathan Larson : But not incredible enough
Jonathan Larson : I can't do it again Mike
Jonathan Larson : I can't stomach five more years of waiting tables
Jonathan Larson : five more years of writing things that no one will ever see
Jonathan Larson : while Broadway just churns out megamusicals without a hint of even the slightest thing original or
Jonathan Larson : God forbid something to actually say about the world
Michael : Are you done
Jonathan Larson : No actually
Michael : The presentation Jon it was amazing
Michael : It would be a tragedy to give up what you have
Jonathan Larson : You did it
Michael : Please
Michael : I was a mediocre actor
Michael : Do you know how many mediocre actors there are in New York City
Michael : Do you know how many Jonathan Larsons there are
Michael : One
Jonathan Larson : I can't keep wasting my time Mike
Jonathan Larson : I turn 30 in two days
Michael : And
Jonathan Larson : And Stephen Sondheim was 27 when he had his first show on Broadway
Michael : Well guess what You're not Stephen Sondheim Wait a little longer
Jonathan Larson : I'm not waiting anymore I can't keep waiting This is my life
Michael : I understand
Jonathan Larson : No you don't I'm running out of time
Michael : You are not running out of time
Jonathan Larson : You don't know anything about it
Michael : I'm HIV positive
Jonathan Larson : What
Jonathan Larson : How long... How long have you known
Michael : A few days
Michael : Who knows
Michael : I might get lucky People do
Michael : Live a year longer even
Michael : Anyway I think I might know a thing or two about running out of time
Jonathan Larson : Why didn't you tell me sooner
Jonathan Larson : You tried
Michael : I have to take that
Michael : I can't talk about this now please
Michael : Jill Hey it's Michael
Michael : Yeah I just want to see how the Downy account was going
Michael : Mmhm
Jonathan Larson : I think of the day I met Michael
Jonathan Larson : at sleepaway camp 22 years ago
Jonathan Larson : We were eight
Jonathan Larson : I think of high school all the shows we did together
Michael : Is this real life
Jonathan Larson : I think of the summer that our parents decided to stay in the same town in Cape Cod a mile away from each other
Jonathan Larson : And we'd meet on the beach every night and um
Jonathan Larson : we'd just sit there talking till three in the morning about our plans
Jonathan Larson : About how one day we were gonna move to the city together and
Jonathan Larson : find a cheap apartment and be discovered and change the world
Beth : Hey you've reached Susan Beth
Jonathan Larson : I think of the first summer back from college
Jonathan Larson : We smoked a bowl on Kennedy breakwater and Michael told me he was gay
Michael : Is this real life
Jonathan Larson : I think of our friends so many
Jonathan Larson : I think of their funerals
Jonathan Larson : I think of their parents not even 50   saying the Kaddish over their children
Michael : Is this real life
Jonathan Larson : I think of them and I think of Michael
Jonathan Larson : And before I understand what's happening I start running
Michael : Is this real life
Jonathan Larson : Past the pond past the carousel
Jonathan Larson : The ticking is so loud now I can't hear anything
Michael : Is this real Is this real
Michael : Is this real
Jonathan Larson : My heartbeat is pounding in my throat The wind is shrieking through the trees The sky is darkening
Jonathan Larson : I want it to stop I want it all to stop
Jonathan Larson : When I was nine
Jonathan Larson : Michael and I
Jonathan Larson : Entered a talent show down at the Y
Jonathan Larson : Nine a. m Went to rehearse by some stairs
Jonathan Larson : Mike couldn't sing
Jonathan Larson : I said No one cares
Jonathan Larson : We sang Yellow Bird
Jonathan Larson : And Let's Go Fly a Kite
Jonathan Larson : Over and over and over
Jonathan Larson : Till we got it right
Jonathan Larson : When we emerged
Jonathan Larson : From the YMCA
Jonathan Larson : Three o'clock sun Had made the grass hay
Jonathan Larson : I thought Hey what a way to spend the day
Jonathan Larson : Hey what a way to spend the day
Jonathan Larson : I make a vow
Jonathan Larson : Right here and now
Jonathan Larson : I'm gonna spend
Jonathan Larson : My time this way
Jonathan Larson : When I was sixteen
Jonathan Larson : Michael and I
Jonathan Larson : Got parts in West Side
Jonathan Larson : At White Plains High
Jonathan Larson : Three o'clock Went to rehearse in the gym
Jonathan Larson : Mike played duck Who did not sing
Jonathan Larson : Fine with him
Jonathan Larson : We sang Got a rocket in your pocket
Jonathan Larson : And The Jets are gonna Have their day
Jonathan Larson : tonight  Over and over and over
Jonathan Larson : Till we got it right
Jonathan Larson : When we emerged
Jonathan Larson : Wiped out by that play
Jonathan Larson : Nine o'clock stars
Jonathan Larson : And moon lit the way
Jonathan Larson : I thought hey
Jonathan Larson : What a way to spend the day
Jonathan Larson : Hey what a way to spend the day
Jonathan Larson : I made a vow
Jonathan Larson : I wonder now
Jonathan Larson : Am I cut out To spend my time this way
Jonathan Larson : I'm twentynine
Jonathan Larson : Michael and I
Jonathan Larson : Live on the West Side of SoHo NY
Jonathan Larson : Nine o'clock I write a lyric or two
Jonathan Larson : Mike sings his song now on Mad Avenue
Jonathan Larson : I sing Come to your senses
Jonathan Larson : Defenses are not the way to go
Jonathan Larson : Over and over and over And over and over And over
Jonathan Larson : and over Till I get it right
Jonathan Larson : When I emerge from B Minor or A
Jonathan Larson : Five o'clock diner calls
Jonathan Larson : I'm on my way
Jonathan Larson : I think hey
Jonathan Larson : What a way to spend a day
Jonathan Larson : Hey what a way to spend a day
Jonathan Larson : I make a vow
Jonathan Larson : Right here and now
Jonathan Larson : I'm gonna spend
Jonathan Larson : My time this way
Jonathan Larson : Hey Whatever happens next I'm here I promise
Jonathan Larson : There's um there's a support group it's called Friends In Deed
Jonathan Larson : I just called them They have a meeting tomorrow morning
Michael : You look like shit
Jonathan Larson : I'm so cold
Michael : Come on
Jonathan Larson : Oh Mike
Jonathan Larson : I'm sorry
Jonathan Larson : Sunday
Jonathan Larson : My 30th birthday
Stephen Sondheim : Jon Steve Sondheim here
Stephen Sondheim : Rosa gave me this number I hope it's okay to call you
Stephen Sondheim : I didn't get a chance to speak with you after the reading but I just wanted to say it was really good
Stephen Sondheim : Congratulations
Stephen Sondheim : I'd love to get together and talk to you about it if you have any interest
Stephen Sondheim : No pressure
Stephen Sondheim : The main thing though is that it's firstrate work and has a future
Stephen Sondheim : And so do you
Stephen Sondheim : I'll call you later with some thoughts if that's okay
Stephen Sondheim : Meanwhile be proud
Carolyn : You know there was a small very very small piece of me
Carolyn : that was the teensiest bit happy to hear you're not leaving
Jonathan Larson : I'd have been sad not to see you every Sunday morning
Carolyn : Oh Cheers
Carolyn : I told Freddy He's pissed off at your agent
Jonathan Larson : How is he
Carolyn : He should be going home soon
Jonathan Larson : Really
Carolyn : Yes Yes
Jonathan Larson : God
Carolyn : Oh
Jonathan Larson : Uh I'll be Yeah
Carolyn : You go handle that
Jonathan Larson : Hi
Susan : Hi
Jonathan Larson : I didn't know you were um
Susan : I wasn't sure whether you would want me here
Jonathan Larson : I'm so happy you're here
Susan : So how was the reading Did anybody
Susan : I'm sorry
Jonathan Larson : No it's okay
Susan : I really wanted to be there I just
Jonathan Larson : Susan
Jonathan Larson : I know
Susan : What are you gonna do now
Jonathan Larson : I'm gonna start the next one
Susan : I decided to take the job
Jonathan Larson : Okay
Jonathan Larson : I'm happy for you
Susan : Happy birthday
Jonathan Larson : Thank you
Jonathan Larson : You really didn't have to get me anything
Susan : It's for the next one
Susan : Got any ideas
Jonathan Larson : Just questions
Susan : That seems like a really good place to start
Susan : Goodbye Jonathan
Susan : The next one was Tick Tick Boom
Susan : After that he went back to a project he'd started and put away called Rent
Susan : It ran on Broadway for 12 years
Susan : It changed the definition of what a musical could be
Susan : What it could sound like
Susan : The kinds of stories it could tell
Susan : Jonathan never got to see it
Susan : The night before first public performance he died
Susan : from a sudden aortic aneurysm
Susan : He was 35 years old
Susan : He still had so many questions
Jonathan Larson : Why do we play with fire
Jonathan Larson : Why do we run our finger Through the flame
Jonathan Larson : Why do we leave Our hand on the stove
Jonathan Larson : Although we know We're in for some pain
Jonathan Larson : Oh why do we refuse To hang a light
Jonathan Larson : When the streets are dangerous
Jonathan Larson : Why does it take an accident
Jonathan Larson : Before the truth gets through to us
Jonathan Larson : Cages or wings Which do you prefer
Jonathan Larson : Ask the birds
Jonathan Larson : Fear or love baby
Jonathan Larson : Don't say the answer
Jonathan Larson : Actions speak louder than words
Jonathan Larson : Why should we try to be our best
Jonathan Larson : When we can just get by And still gain
Jonathan Larson : Why do we nod our heads
Jonathan Larson;Michael : Although we know
Michael : The boss is wrong as rain
Jonathan Larson : Why should we blaze a trail
Jonathan Larson : When the wellworn path Seems safe and
Jonathan Larson;Susan : So inviting
Susan : How as we travel
Jonathan Larson;Susan : Can we see the dismay
Jonathan Larson;Susan : And keep from fighting
Jonathan Larson;Susan : Cages or wings Cages or wings Which do you prefer
Jonathan Larson : Ask the birds
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Fear or love baby Don't say the answer
Jonathan Larson : Actions speak louder than words
Michael;Susan;Jonathan Larson : Louder than louder than
Jonathan Larson : What does it take To wake up a generation
Susan;Michael : How can you make someone Take off and fly
Jonathan Larson : If we don't wake up And shake up the nation
Jonathan Larson : We'll eat the dust Of the world wondering
Susan;Jonathan Larson;Michael : Why Why Why
Susan : Why do we stay with lovers
Susan : Who we know down deep
Susan : Just aren't right
Susan : Why Would we rather
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Put ourselves through hell
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Than sleep alone at night
Jonathan Larson : Why do we follow leaders Who never lead
Michael : Why does it take catastrophe To start a revolution
Susan;Michael : If we're so free tell me why
Jonathan Larson : Someone tell me why So many people bleed
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Cages or wings Cages or wings Which do you prefer Ask the
Jonathan Larson : birds
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Fear or love baby Don't say the answer
Jonathan Larson : Actions speak louder than
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Louder than louder than Louder than louder than
Jonathan Larson;Susan : Cages or wings
Jonathan Larson;Susan : Which do you prefer
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Ask the birds
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Fear or love baby Don't say the answer
Jonathan Larson : Actions speak louder
Susan;Michael : Louder than louder than
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : They speak louder
Jonathan Larson;Susan;Michael : Actions speak louder than
Michael : Make a wish
You're on the air
I'm underground
Signal's fading
Can't be found
I finally open up
For you I would do anything
But you've turned off the volume
Just when I've begun to sing
Come to your senses
Defenses are not the way to go
And you know Or at least you knew
Everything's strange you've changed
And I don't know what to do To get through
I don't know what to do
I have to laugh
You sure put on a show
Love is passé in this day and age
How can we expect it to grow
You as the knight
Me as the queen
All I've got tonight
Is static on a screen
Come to your senses
The fences inside are not for real
If we feel as we did and I do
Can't you recall when this all began
It was only you and me
It was only me and you
But now the air is Filled with confusion
We replace care with illusion
How come it's cool to be cold
When nothing lasts anymore
When love becomes disposable
This is the shape of things We cannot ignore
Come to your senses Suspense is fine
If you're just an empty image
Emanating out of a screen
Baby be real you can feel again
You don't need a music box melody
To know what I mean
So come to your senses
Will you come to your senses
Yeah come to your senses
Come to your senses
Deep dark velvet hugs your silhouette
Black silk stockings you're my Juliet
Soft long hair Baby beautiful blue eyes
Cool me down before I jump Into your thighs
The green green dress Twenty buttons and a strap
The green green dress What a pleasure to unwrap
Green dress oh what it can do
What the green green dress Does to me on you
Me on you
Let's find a chair Where we can sit and talk
Or get some fresh air Maybe we could take a walk
Tell me what you're thinkin Talk about your day
Tell me what to do I'll do anything you say
Yeah the green green dress Twenty buttons and a strap
The green green dress What a pleasure to unwrap
The green dress oh what it can do
What the green green dress Does to me on you
Me on you You
Can I hear you laugh babe Can you make me smile
I'll forget what's on my mind For a while
Can I tie you up love If you tell me yes
I'll unbutton every button Down your green green
Dress
The green green dress Twenty buttons and a strap
The green green dress What a pleasure to unwrap
Green dress oh what it can do
What the green green dress Does to me on you
Me on you You
Me on the green green dress Green green dress
The green green dress
The green green dress Green green dress
One two
Almost missed this one he said I stared at the honkytonk piano
Sure beats living in town The beach is a half a mile away
Not much of the cat I said He stared down underneath the couch
It doesn't matter much to me Not gonna beat it anyway
It only takes a few cents more To go first class
First class only takes a few