Diana Ross : Do you know Where you're going to
Diana Ross : Do you like the things That life is showing you
Diana Ross : Where are you going to
Diana Ross : Do you know
Diana Ross : Ladies and gentlemen I want to thank you for being here tonight
Diana Ross : Thank you for the love
Diana Ross : and for making this a really special evening for me
Diana Ross : But thank you most of all for this fabulous young man
Trevor : Me Well
Diana Ross : that's right
Diana Ross : Well come on love Join me
Diana Ross : Well now don't be shy darling You know what I say after all
Trevor : I know everything you say
Diana Ross : Well then you know you can't just sit around and wait for people to give you that golden dream
Trevor : You've gotta get out there and make it happen for yourself
Diana Ross : Precisely
Diana Ross : Do you get what you're hopin for
Diana Ross : When you look behind you There's no open door
Diana Ross : What are you hopin for Do you know
Diana Ross : Now tell us what we'll soon be saying in every household across the country
Diana Ross : shouting from every rooftop around the world
Diana Ross : Tell us your name
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor what are you doing
Trevor : Telling everyone my name
Mr.Nelson : Well can you tell everyone a little bit to the left kiddo
Mr.Nelson : You're blocking the TV
Trevor : That's my mom and dad
Trevor : Their relationship with the television is out of hand
Trevor : I don't think they would care If I stop breathing air
Trevor : Unless some guy on the news Told them it was so
Trevor : Even then they'd just say
Mr.Nelson : Trevor out of the way
Mrs.Nelson : Ronald Reagan was shot
Trevor : Like a week ago
TV : In day six of our continuing coverage
TV : of John Hinckley's assassination attempt on the president we delve
Trevor : But I won't let TV Be as far as I see
Trevor : Cause my future won't fit On a little screen
Trevor : Once I light up the stage I'll be all of the rage
Trevor : And this Friday they're gonna see What I mean
Trevor : I've been patiently waiting
Trevor : For all the world to know What I always knew
Trevor : But now just like Diana
Trevor : Out of nowhere I will be discovered too
Ensemble : Oh
Ensemble;Trevor : Cause I know where I'm going And I'm going far
Ensemble : Going far
Trevor;Ensemble : Gonna shoot out of here Like a shooting star
Trevor;Ensemble : Whoa
Trevor;Ensemble : Right now is just the beginning Of watching me go
Trevor;Ensemble : Cause once I'm on I'm on and on
Trevor : And on with the show
Trevor : Cathy they're announcing who got picked for the talent show today
Cathy : I know but Trevor I heard they had tons of people try out
Cathy : and I felt like Mrs Kerr didn't really appreciate your reenactments of those scenes from Fame
Trevor : Don't worry Cathy
Trevor : Diana Ross was discovered at a talent competition too
Trevor : This is how it happens
Ensemble : Every day's just a day That's been ticking away
Trevor : Leading up to the day of my destiny
Trevor : Now it's all taking shape Soon I'll finally escape
Trevor : Every day of this middle school misery
Teacher : All right ladies and ladies
Teacher : That's it for today
Teacher : but we're gonna make the rest of the week a little more fun
Trevor : When Coach Gregory says fun
Trevor : it usually turns out to be one of the most traumatic experiences of my existence
Teacher : No more wussy aerobics
Teacher : I'm gonna pair everyone up for oneonone basketball
Teacher : And then the winners will continue to advance until we have our ultimate competitor
Teacher : I call it the Ultimate Competitor Competition
Trevor : Help me
Ensemble;Trevor : Every game is the same
Trevor;Ensemble : With another dumb name
Ensemble : Whoa
Trevor : For embarrassing me When I try to play
Trevor : Nothing else I can do Except pray to get through
Trevor : Without having to play
Ensemble : Pinky Farraday
Ensemble : Ah ah
Ensemble;Trevor : He's like some kind of hero
Trevor : Like in a Greek play That takes place in a gym
Ensemble : Whoa whoa
Trevor;Ensemble : Cause there's nothing he can't play
Trevor;Ensemble : So it's a tragedy To play against him
Teacher : Pinky Farraday your competitor tomorrow will be Trevor Nelson
Trevor : No
Trevor : Way
Trevor : No way
Trevor;Ensemble : I've gotta keep on going Through this tragedy
Ensemble : Oh
Trevor : Gotta hold on until it's all history
Ensemble : Oh oh
Trevor;Ensemble : Till everything right now
Trevor;Ensemble : Right now is ages ago
Trevor;Ensemble : I am on and on and on na na na na On and on
Trevor;Ensemble : On and on and on and on Na na na na
Trevor;Ensemble : On and on and on and on
Trevor : And on with the show
Trevor : Mrs Kerr about the talent show this Friday
Trevor : are you posting the participant list before or after lunch
Trevor : Cause if you wanted to see any portion of my audition again
Trevor;Mrs.Nelson : I can always show you
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor you do understand you'd be in front of the entire school
Mrs.Nelson : And you were playing all the roles even the women
Trevor : Yeah you can't do Fame without Coco
Trevor : She has all the best songs
Mrs.Nelson : Well I'm not sure Principal Gordon and the PTA would understand that
Trevor : But the football team dances in those pink tutus every year
Mrs.Nelson : Well that's just a joke Trevor You were being serious
Trevor : Well I can make Coco a boy
Trevor;Mrs.Nelson : I can change whatever you
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor
Mrs.Nelson : The program is set And there's just no place in it for you
Trevor : Diana says I can't lay down and die Cause my golden dream is up to me
Trevor;Ensemble : Diana says to get back up and try
Trevor;Ensemble : Cause there's so much more I've gotta be
Trevor;Ensemble : Diana says a valley
Trevor;Ensemble : Is there for getting through
Trevor : Diana says
Trevor;Ensemble : Don't give up
Trevor : And I'm not going to
Diana Ross : Where you going to
Diana Ross;Trevor;Ensemble : Where are you going to
Ensemble : Where are you going
Trevor;Ensemble : Where are you going Where are you going
Trevor : Do you know
Where are you going
Trevor;Ensemble : I'm going and I'm going
Trevor;Ensemble : Like Diana goes
Trevor;Ensemble : On and on and on and on On and on and on till everybody knows
Whoa oh oh oh
Trevor;Ensemble : Cause just like Diana
Trevor;Ensemble : Oh oh oh I'll never turn back now
Trevor;Ensemble : I'll find a way Into the talent show somehow
Trevor;Ensemble : No I'll never stop going
Trevor;Ensemble : Till that's where I go
Ensemble : Going going going going go
Trevor;Ensemble : And I am on and on and on
Trevor;Ensemble : Na na na na
Ensemble : On and on and on and on
Trevor;Ensemble : So let's go on
Trevor;Ensemble : So let's go on and on and on
Ensemble : Na na na na na na na Na na na na na
Ensemble : Let's go let's go let's go
Trevor : Let's go on
Trevor : On with the show
Walter : Trevor where's the microscope
Trevor : That's Walter Stiltman He lives next door
Walter : I was able to collect a specimen pretty quickly thanks to 7B
Trevor : I guess since his mom's divorced
Trevor : she has to buy this weirdly elaborate underwear out of magazines
Walter : Do you think Cathy wears stuff like this
Trevor : She wears a flannel navy nightgown with long sleeves I've seen it
Walter : Lucky
Trevor : Hardly
Walter : Whoa Get over here
Trevor : It's not fair
Trevor : Why is Mrs Kerr in charge of putting together the talent show
Trevor : She can't even put together an outfit
Trevor : You know
Walter : I like what Mrs Kerr wears
Walter : Especially that green dress with the loose button
Trevor : Okay
Walter : Would you just look at this already
Trevor : It looks like tadpoles
Walter : Here Your turn
Trevor : But we already observed yours
Walter : It's a scientific experiment
Walter : You can't learn anything from just one specimen
Walter : You're the second variable
Trevor : What are we learning again
Walter : I'm working on a hypothesis that mine are abnormally strong
Walter : Like top10 strong
Walter : But given that I have limited data
Walter : my adjusted hypothesis is that mine are just way stronger than yours
Trevor;Walter : No they're not Prove it
Trevor : Is it true it can make me go deaf
Walter : No
Walter : Trust me
Trevor : Do I need to use the same girl as you
Walter : Look I was very happy with my choice
Walter : You should be equally happy with yours
Trevor : Right
Trevor : Okay
Trevor : She's got nice eyes They go with her bra
Walter : Okay
Trevor : And with that strap across her thighs
Walter : I guess
Trevor : But wouldn't it itch Sitting on straw
Walter : She's in a barn
Trevor : That seems a little unwise
Walter : So what
Trevor : Walter I don't want a girl who isn't smart
Walter : Trevor you realize it's not about hay Or if her bra goes with her eyes
Trevor : I was kidding
Walter : Stop being polite
Trevor : I'm not being polite
Walter : She's not here to stay
Trevor : She's not even naked
Walter : Just while you fantasize
Walter : So turn the page turn the page To what you wanna see
Walter : Till it feels like thunder If her outfit makes you wonder
Walter : Just turn the page turn the page Into your fantasy
Walter : Cause you gotta see what's under It's all about what's under underneath
Walter : Oh whoa Whoa oh
Walter : Oh whoa
Trevor : Like inner beauty you mean
Walter : Not at all No
Walter : Stop goofing off
Walter : Open the prize In the pages of this magazine
Walter : Forget the bras and turn your eyes Into an Xray machine
Walter;Trevor : And turn the page turn the page Turn turn the page
Walter : Till it's not rated PG
Walter : It'll blow your mind like thunder Cause you found the next world wonder
Walter;Trevor : Yeah turn the page turn the page Turn turn the page
Walter : Into your fantasy
Walter;Trevor : Cause you gotta see what's under It's all about what's under underneath
Walter : Oh whoa Whoa oh
Walter : Oh whoa
Walter : Bow chicka bow wow
Mrs.Nelson : Knock knock
Trevor : Mom saying knock knock after you walk in isn't actually knocking
Walter : Hi Mrs Nelson
Mrs.Nelson : What are you guys up to
Trevor : Homework
Walter : Science
Trevor : Science
Walter : Homework
Walter;Trevor : Nothing
Mrs.Nelson : Well I just popped our Swanson dinners in the oven
Mrs.Nelson : Pot roast
Walter : Ah
Mrs.Nelson : Or potpie
Walter : Oh
Mrs.Nelson : Pot something
Mrs.Nelson : Anyway they'll be ready in time for the news
Mrs.Nelson : so finish up what you're doing and come downstairs
Walter : Yes ma'am
Walter : All you gotta do is
Trevor;Walter : Turn turn turn Turn turn turn turn
Trevor;Walter : Whoa gross What
Walter : The last two pages have underwear for guys and he looks like Pinky Farraday
Trevor : Which one
Walter : The one on the tractor It's pretty disgusting
Trevor : Yuck
Walter;Trevor : Turn the page turn the page Until it's Mrs Kerr
Whoa whoa
Trevor : Yes saying it was all a blunder
Trevor : Cause my audition stunned her
Walter : And I bet that's what she's wearing Underneath
Walter;Trevor : Oh whoa Whoa oh
Trevor;Walter : Oh whoa
Walter : Bow chicka bow wow
Trevor;Walter : Oh whoa Whoa oh
Trevor;Walter : Oh whoa
Trevor;Walter : It's all about what's under It's all about what's under underneath
Ensemble : Every day is a day That keeps ticking away
Ensemble : Every day is an echo of yesterday
Ensemble : Every move that we make From the time we're awake
Ensemble : Is a step we'll be following
Ensemble : Every day Every day
Ensemble : Every day Every day Every day Every day
Mary : Frannie Laugh at me
Frannie : What
Mary : Jason's right over there and I want him to think I'm funny
Mary : Now
Frannie : Ahahahahahaha Oh my God
Jason;Frannie : What's funny Mary
Mary : Something I said she means
Jason : Oh I thought you guys were laughing about Pinky
Frannie : No Why would I laugh about Pinky
Jason : He got paired up with some wimp today at gym
Cathy : Trevor's not a wimp He's artistic
Jason : Same thing
Frannie : Not really
Frannie : I mean I know Trevor
Frannie : He's okay We went to Carter together
Jason : Right
Mary : Frannie don't remind people that you went to Carter
Mary : It's the same thing as telling them that you live west of Route 9
Cathy : What's wrong with living west of Route 9
Mary : Need I say more
Frannie : No sorry
Ensemble : Every day we keep going On and on and on Like we know the way
Ensemble : On and on and on Every day we keep showing
Ensemble : We know just enough To get through today
Ensemble : On and on and on Get me through today
Ensemble : Na na na na na na na Get me through today
Ensemble : Na na na na na na
Trevor : Get me through today
Trevor;Pinky : Travis right Actually it's Trevor
Trevor : Which is kind of like Travis so I'd understand why you'd
Trevor : Um but it is actually Trevor Which is different
Pinky : Right
Trevor : Now what
Pinky : Coach Gregory said round one's HORSE
Trevor : I thought we were playing basketball
Pinky : Right
Trevor : Right
Pinky : If you miss a shot Then you get a letter
Trevor : If you make a shot
Pinky : You don't get a letter
Trevor : So you got a point Or you got a letter
Pinky : No I made the shot
Pinky : I get none
Trevor : What's better
Trevor : And where's the horse
Pinky : The name of the game is HORSE But you don't want the letter E
Pinky : Cause you don't wanna spell it out
Pinky : Let's play and you'll see
Pinky : Cause the way it goes The rules aren't a lot It's hard to get it wrong
Pinky : You just plant your toes In at that spot
Pinky : Make my pose and take the shot
Pinky : And you play along
Pinky : Play along Play along
Trevor : I'm more of a performer than an athlete
Pinky : Oh come on
Pinky : This is barely even sports You don't even gotta try
Pinky : Cause any real guy Already knows the way it goes
Pinky : You just gotta follow me I've gotta follow you
Trevor : Just gotta follow me
Trevor : Just gotta follow you
Pinky : Follow me
Trevor : I've gotta follow you
Pinky : Follow me and play I've gotta play
Pinky : Ho
Pinky : Whoa
Pinky;Ensemble : Hey Hey
Pinky;Ensemble : Ho
Pinky;Ensemble : Whoa
Trevor : This is hopeless If I miss this I've got HORSE
Trevor : And you don't even have H
Pinky : It could be worse At least you don't have to dance around in a pink tutu on the talent show on Friday
Trevor : That's a talent You sound like my dad
Pinky : It's what the eighthgrade team does every year But it's gonna be humiliating
Trevor : Wait Do you need someone to reimagine it
Trevor : Cause I could definitely do that And I could direct it and choreograph it
Trevor : But I'd have to be credited in the program
Trevor : as creator and director and choreographer
Trevor : See the way it goes
Trevor : We practice it a lot Till you can't get it wrong
Trevor : You just plant your toes In at that spot
Trevor : Make my pose and take the shot
Trevor : And then play along
Trevor : Play along Play along
Pinky : What Like Saturday Night Fever or something
Trevor : Right You could be John Travolta
Pinky : Yeah I don't think so
Trevor : But you showed me how to play HORSE You can do anything
Pinky : Not that No way
Trevor : Hey
Frannie : Hi
Frannie : Um uh Trevor Hey Trevor
Frannie : I wanted to say that I like that dance you were doing
Frannie : I love Saturday Night Fever
Pinky : Me too John Travolta right
Frannie : Yeah Right
Frannie : So yeah
Pinky : Okay you're on
Trevor : What
Pinky : You can try to Whatever you said you were gonna do
Pinky : For the talent show Yeah We can figure it out after practice
Pinky : See ya there Trevor
Trevor : Yeah okay
Trevor : Play along
Jason : Hey How was the freak show
Pinky : Huh
Jason : Trevor Oh
Pinky : He's funny
Jason : No kidding
Jason : And hey I figured out how to get us out of wearing those tutus on Friday
Jason : Come on man What's the big deal It's what the team always does
Pinky : Probably because they never had a way around it
Jason : What A way around it
Pinky : Trevor He's gonna teach us something
Pinky : Something real so we're not a joke
Jason : What
Jason : Um you're not serious right
Pinky : Frannie Antonicelli saw him dance and she said it was cool
Jason : Pinky
Jason : He's weird
Pinky : No he's not
Pinky : He's just more of a performer than an athlete
Diana Ross : It's my turn To see what I can see
Diana Ross : I hope you'll understand
Diana Ross : This time's just for me And now it's
Diana Ross : my turn To reach and touch the sky
Diana Ross : No one's gonna say
Trevor;Mrs.Nelson : Mom Knock knock
Trevor : That isn't knocking
Mrs.Nelson : Oh it looks like your diary is filling up
Mrs.Nelson : Time for a new one
Trevor : It's not a diary It's an ideainspiration journal
Trevor : For when I'm inspired by ideas
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor is there anything you want to talk about
Trevor : Mom the stuff in here is a little difficult to explain if you don't understand the artistic influences
Mrs.Nelson : No I mean
Mrs.Nelson : about President Reagan being shot
Trevor : She's obsessed
Mrs.Nelson : You know they say the man that shot him he did it to get the attention of an actress he was infatuated with
Mrs.Nelson : Jodie Foster
Mrs.Nelson : What do you think of that
Trevor : That's crazy She can't even sing
Walter : Hey Trevor where'd you put the
Trevor : The what
Walter : The uh... science magazine
Trevor : Thanks Mom I'll put the rest of this stuff away
Mrs.Nelson : Okay Then come downstairs
Mrs.Nelson : You can do science in the living room
Walter : She's onto us
Walter : Let's just go to the TasteeFreez
Walter : Cathy's working there with her mom tonight
Walter : Maybe she can get us some free stuff
Trevor : I can't
Trevor : I've got rehearsal
Walter : Huh
Trevor : For the talent show
Walter : Wait you mean Mrs Kerr actually let you in
Trevor : No
Trevor : Pinky Farraday is letting me work with them
Walter : No he's not
Trevor : How about I meet you at the TasteeFreez tomorrow after we finish
Trevor : Tonight's our first rehearsal so I feel like I should stay until
Walter : Wait so you're being serious
Walter : You're doing the talent show with Pinky Farraday
Trevor : Creating directing and choreographing
Walter : But I thought they just danced around in those dumb tutus every year while everyone laughs at them
Trevor : Not anymore
Trevor : This won't be the same joke They've done ten years in a row
Trevor : I won't go for laughs Just cause it's somewhere safe to go
Trevor : We've gotta use this moment To build character and grow
Trevor : And we've gotta show some talent Cause it's called a talent show
Jason : Sorry I don't dance
Trevor : Standing still's a habit That you've gotta learn to break
Trevor : It comes from overthinking Every move you ever make
Trevor : But the music's gonna tell ya Each and every step to take
Trevor : It's simple as a piece of pie And easier than cake
Trevor : It's just a one two three four Five six seven eight
Trevor : Now it should be like nothing When you do it all again
Jason : One two
Pinky : One ttwo then three and then
Trevor : It's gonna make more sense With all the costumes and the lights
Trevor : Your feet will take these wooden floors On up into new heights
Trevor : So better keep your eyes up Cause that's where I set my sights
Trevor : And better get accustomed To a lot of sleepless nights
Trevor : Oh my God Okay
Trevor : You've gotta one two three four Five six seven eight
Trevor : Now don't get too offended when I say Not good enough so try again
Trevor : Gotta get it Don't forget it
Trevor : Practice in your bed
Trevor : Once you got it
Trevor : Start forgetting everything I said Because you've gotta start to
Trevor : Start to get it In your blood instead
Trevor : Cry it sweat it Till you get it
Trevor : Get what I've got in my head
Trevor : Cue the lights
Trevor : It's begun
Trevor : That's your cue
Trevor : And start at one and then
Trevor;Ensemble : It's just a
Trevor;Ensemble : One two three four Five six seven eight
Trevor;Ensemble : It's just a one two three four Five six seven eight
Trevor;Ensemble : One through eight again and then
Trevor;Ensemble : One through eight again and then One through eight again
Trevor;Ensemble : And you do it do it do it all again
Trevor : Do it all again
Trevor : Thank you No no please Oh thank you for the love
Trevor : Oh my goodness
Trevor : Trevor
Frannie : Oh Hi Frannie Antonicelli
Trevor : Hey Trevor Nelson
Trevor : Uh how's it going Rehearsals I mean
Trevor : Amazing It will be Eventually
Trevor : It's amazing in my head
Trevor : Oh
Frannie : Well good
Frannie : Um Trevor has Pinky
Frannie : Uh did he say anything about me or who he's asking to the Quality Courts on Thursday
Frannie : And if it's me
Trevor : Asking to where
Frannie : The Quality Courts
Frannie : Where the team always goes the night before the show
Frannie : You know to prove they're men and not well
Trevor : Not what
Frannie : Dancing pansies is what Mary says
Trevor : Men dance
Trevor : Gene Kelly Fred Astaire
Trevor : Tommy Tune
Frannie : That's just That's what Mary said
Frannie : I didn't mean to bother you with it
Frannie : I just thought if he said anything then
Frannie : Are you taking Cathy
Trevor : Do people rehearse monologues there
Frannie : Okay Well Trevor I'll see you
Frannie : Hey it's nice what you're doing for them With the talent show
Frannie : I saw a little of the end and it seems really cute
Trevor : Cute
Trevor : That's what polite moms say to delusional children
Trevor : Diana Ross was not discovered because someone thought she was cute
Trevor : We have to do better
Trevor : We have to practice like no one has ever practiced before
Trevor : We have to be
Ensemble;Trevor : Do it all again
Trevor : amazing
Trevor : Just a few things
Trevor : Todd the ground isn't going anywhere Don't be afraid to pick up your feet
What
Trevor : Luke bend your arm
Trevor : Now your leg
Trevor : See Your joints work Use them
Trevor : Jason you're a natural Everyone should be watching Jason
No I'm not No you shouldn't Oh
Trevor : Look I know it's scary
Trevor : But just remember how brave Diana Ross was when she abandoned her signature look and wore almost no makeup at all
Trevor : On the cover of her album diana
Jason : Wait The album is called Diana
Trevor : No it's called diana With a lowercase d
Jason : What
Trevor : I know She's incredible
Trevor : But we should stop for the day in accordance with our bylaws
Trevor : Thanks everyone
Trevor : and practice practice practice
Trevor : I'll see you tomorrow
It's a mistake
Trevor : Oh except Luke
We just need a quick minute to go over your relationship with your cane
Oh Someone's in trouble
Pinky : Hey we can't tomorrow Trevor
Pinky;Jason : We gotta go Pinky
Jason : You're not gonna tell him about the Quality Courts are you
Pinky : Yeah We're all supposed to go That's the tradition right
Jason : For the team Trevor's not one of us
Jason : I mean what are we even doing This is nothing like Saturday Night Fever
Pinky : Yeah Trevor says we can't do Travolta with an ensemble
Jason : Pinky every other team for the last ten years
Jason : put on those dumb tutus and they all survived
Jason : But no one's ever done whatever this is
Pinky;Jason : He's weird Pinky He's fine okay
Pinky : Besides what are you worried about
Pinky : You're a natural
Jason : No I'm not
You're a natural
Stop
What
Jason : Think about it
Pinky : Hey uh Trevor
Pinky : You wanna take a walk together
Trevor : What Where
Pinky : Home
Pinky : Unless you have somewhere else to
Trevor : No I mean yes
Trevor : No But yes II'll walk with you Yes
Trevor : Cause no So yes
Pinky : Okay
Trevor : I thought everyone did a lot better today right
Trevor : I mean except Luke
Trevor : My God If he doesn't hurt himself it's gonna be someone else
Trevor : Maybe we should take his cane away
Trevor : How do you think he'd be with a tambourine
Pinky : Trevor Hey do you think
Trevor : The tambourine was just an idea
Trevor : It seemed less dangerous but I
Pinky : No I know It's not that
Pinky : It's just
Pinky : Well
Pinky : Some of the guys they're not so sure we should do your dance
Trevor : Oh
Pinky : But my dad says anything's better than a guy named Pinky in a pink tutu
Trevor : But then why did he
Pinky : Oh Pinky was the nickname of some baseball player he loved
Pinky : He was young and stupid when he had me That's another thing he says
Trevor : Well Diana Ross says
Trevor : Instead of looking in the past I put myself years ahead
Trevor : and try to look at what I need to do now in order to get there then
Pinky : Huh
Trevor : She's saying you should do what you want not what your dad says or Jason
Trevor : Because you have to do whatever is going to get you to your golden dream
Trevor : Not anyone else's
Pinky : My golden dream
Trevor : You know your life's passion
Trevor : Like what gets you out of bed in the morning
Pinky : My mom
Trevor : No I mean
Trevor : what do you imagine yourself being when you're old like in ten years
Pinky : Uh
Trevor : Don't think Just go
Trevor : In another ten years I Pinky Farraday
Trevor : The first thing that comes into your brain
Trevor : In another ten years
Pinky : I won't be standing here
Trevor : Great
Trevor : In another ten years
Pinky : I'll be standing in another spot
Trevor : Okay More specific
Trevor : In another ten years
Pinky : I'm gonna be somewhere And I'm gonna get
Pinky : I'm gonna get a shot
Trevor : Yes
Trevor;Pinky : Cause one of these days
Trevor : I'll be a star
Trevor : And people will say I've got it all
Trevor;Pinky : And one of these days
Pinky : Inside a bar Oh I'm gonna get I'm gonna get some alcohol
Pinky : One of these days
Trevor : Wait, Alcohol?
Pinky : Yeah
Pinky : Like I said I'm gonna get a shot
Pinky : Probably tequila
Trevor : Sorry I was unclear
Trevor : I don't just mean what you'll be able to do
Trevor : I mean something more like
Trevor : In another ten years I'll still be looking back
Trevor : At the talent show That made my golden dream come true
Pinky : It did
Trevor : And in another ten years
Pinky : I'm gonna show them all
Pinky : I can do stuff no one thought I'd do
Trevor : Yes
Trevor;Pinky : Cause one of these days
Trevor : I'll reach the top
Trevor : And if there's more Then I'll reach that too
Pinky;Trevor : Yeah one of these days
Pinky : Their jaws will drop
Pinky : When they all see They're gonna see my rad tattoo
Pinky : One of these days
Trevor : A tattoo
Pinky : Yeah My dad will freak out but that won't matter anymore
Trevor : Okay Rad
Trevor : But a decade's too big To be thinking small
Trevor : A decade's forever And that's how far you gotta see
Trevor;Pinky : A decade and I could be having it all
Pinky : With Frannie right there next to me
Trevor : Frannie Antonicelli
Pinky : Yes I get it now
Pinky : The way I feel about Frannie that's how you feel about this talent show
Trevor : I don't know about that
Trevor : Frannie's just a girl and the show is
Pinky : Just a girl She's everything you said
Pinky : She makes me excited to get up in the morning
Pinky : She even makes me excited to go to school you know
Pinky : Come on There's gotta be someone like that for you too
Pinky : Who you can't stop thinking about being with someday
Trevor : Uh
Pinky : Don't think Just go The first thing that comes to your brain
Pinky : In another ten years
Trevor : I'll be with someone
Trevor : It will be someone really great
Pinky : More specific
Pinky : In another ten years
Trevor : I'll find someone more Than my fantasies create
Pinky : Better
Pinky;Trevor : And one of these days
Pinky : She'll make my day so much better
Pinky : Than any I've had yet
Trevor;Pinky : Cause one of these days
Trevor : She'll learn the way to join me In singing a great duet
Pinky;Trevor : One of these
Pinky : Wait What
Trevor : A duet
Trevor : You know a song we sing together
Trevor;Pinky : With harmonies And that's what you want to do with her
Trevor : Uh well and
Trevor : I'd get her this weirdly elaborate underwear from this magazine I totally looked at
Pinky : Okay That could work I guess
Pinky : Hey Trevor
Pinky : I'll tell the guys we have to try harder at your dance
Trevor : Really
Pinky : Yeah
Pinky : Let's do something we can be proud of in ten years
Pinky : Without tutus
Trevor : Pinky
Trevor : She likes you too
Pinky : Huh
Trevor : Frannie Antonicelli
Trevor : She wants you to ask her to go to the Something Courts with her tomorrow
Pinky : The Quality Courts
Trevor : That's it
Pinky : Seriously No way This is amazing Tell her yes
Trevor;Pinky : Me No I have to ask her, right?
Trevor;Pinky : I think so Unless you don't want to
Pinky : I'll call her
Or if you want to think about it more
Pinky : Who are you bringing
Trevor : Me
Pinky : Yeah
Pinky : Everyone on the team has to go It's tradition
Trevor : The team
Trevor : Oh
Trevor : Right Of course
Trevor : I'll be there With someone
Trevor;Pinky : Cause one of these days It's crystal clear
Pinky : She's gonna see
Pinky;Trevor : Totally see we're meant to be
Pinky : You're the best Trevor
Cathy : Hey
Cathy : You're still waiting for Trevor
Walter : Nope Here want a melted sundae
Cathy : Walter you know he's super busy for his golden dream
Walter : Yeah but
Walter : I mean aren't you a little worried about
Walter : you know those people and Trevor together
Cathy : You mean that Frannie's gonna like him
Cathy : II know But you don't think he'll like her back do you
Cathy : I mean I've watched every Tony Awards with him since 1976
Walter : What
Walter : Uh no I don't think that'll happen I don't think that at all
Cathy : But Frannie is like strawberry Bubblicious
Walter : Huh
Cathy : Like
Cathy : It doesn't matter what other type of bubble gum is in the room if
Cathy : strawberry Bubblicious is around
Cathy : You know
Cathy : I haven't had gum in a really long time
Walter : Nineteen months and 23 days
Cathy : What
Walter : Oh uh since you got your braces on
Cathy : Okay
Walter : WWell no
Walter : I just always remember cause that's the day I started
Walter : Well growing out my mustache and beard
Walter : See
Cathy : Yeah
Cathy : Well I wouldn't worry Walter There must be a logical explanation
Walter : Testosterone
Cathy : No I mean for Trevor
Walter : Trevor
Walter : Logical
Walter : He's been lost in makebelieve Since the day we met
Walter : So anything but logical Is probably our best bet
Cathy : But meeting you is something Trevor never would forget
Cathy : What if he's with Frannie And we just don't know it yet
Cathy : This is weird
Cathy : Maybe we should try to find him
Walter : Yeah it's weird
Walter : Like our friendship's all behind him So he made a fool of me
Cathy : You know Trevor wouldn't do that
Walter;Cathy : When he gets here then you'll see
Walter;Cathy : Something's weird
Frannie : Hello Mary it's Frannie Guess what
Frannie : You'll never guess Try You won't
Cathy : Pinky asked you to go to the Quality Courts with him tomorrow
Frannie : How did you know
Frannie : And why do I feel sick
Cathy : Don't worry It's just a place
Cathy : Kissing is the same there as it is anywhere
Frannie : Kissing
Cathy : Yeah
Cathy : What were you planning to do
Frannie : I don't know I just wanted him to ask me
Frannie : Can't we just talk
Cathy : Frannie it's Pinky Farraday
Cathy : I mean he could have his pick
Cathy : And Lindsay's been after him too you know and
Cathy : she knows how to do way more than talk
Frannie;Cathy : But I Frannie
Cathy : I've been doing everything I can to help you fit
Cathy : But I can't help your past When you're not over it
Cathy : Stop acting like a weirdo And grow up somehow
Cathy : Cause everything is different
Frannie : Everything is changing
Cathy;Frannie : Everything is different now
Mrs.Nelson : Wasn't it just yesterday When he was singing movie scenes
Mrs.Nelson : Instead of hiding magazines
Mrs.Nelson : With men on farms In nothing but their underwear
Mrs.Nelson : And who farms in their underwear
Mrs.Nelson : And why would Trevor even care
Mrs.Nelson : And wasn't it just yesterday When I was simply unaware
Mrs.Nelson : That this was ever even there
Mr.Nelson : What was where
Mrs.Nelson : Nothing Where This Nothing
Mr.Nelson : What You're looking at this In the middle of the living room
Mrs.Nelson : It was under Trevor's mattress
Mr.Nelson : But this is a man In his underwear
Mrs.Nelson : On a tractor
Mr.Nelson : Well you should probably talk to him about it
Mrs.Nelson : Me
Mr.Nelson : You're the one who lets him keep a diary and act like Diana Ross
Mrs.Nelson : Well you never showed him how to throw a ball
Mr.Nelson;Mrs.Nelson : Really Yeah
Mrs.Nelson : And it's not a diary it's a
Mrs.Nelson : Um
Mrs.Nelson : Oh fine I'll deal with it
Mr.Nelson : No Wait You're right I should do it
Mr.Nelson : You'll go back to yesterday Acting like he's still a kid
Mr.Nelson : Excusing everything he did
Mr.Nelson : But that won't work We can't ignore it now or wait
Mr.Nelson : You've done all a mother can But now it's gonna take a man
Mr.Nelson : I'll talk to him And set things straight
Mrs.Nelson;Mr.Nelson : Wasn't it just yesterday
Mr.Nelson;Mrs.Nelson : I'll set it straight
This is weird weird
Mrs.Nelson : Yesterday
Mr.Nelson : It's gonna take a man
Ensemble : Everything is changing
Yesterday
Everything is different everything
I'll set things straight
Yesterday
Frannie : Everything is different
It's so weird
Cathy : Everything is changing
Mrs.Nelson : Yesterday is over
Everything is different
Walter;Cathy : Everything is weird
Mrs.Nelson;Mr.Nelson;Cathy : Oh
Trevor : One of these days
Trevor : I'd like to thank everyone involved
Trevor : in the Lakeview Junior High 17th Annual Celebration of Talent
Trevor : for declaring our routine the best directed choreographed
Trevor : and reimagined routine in the history of the show
Trevor : One of these days
Trevor : And I'd like to thank Pinky Farraday
Trevor : Pinky remember the day we walked home together and both realized how special this performance was going to be
Trevor : And you hugged me
Trevor : Also thanks Bob Fosse Michael Bennett and Debbie Allen for inspiring me
Trevor : Also Pinky do you hug people a lot
Trevor : I mean whatever I just wondered
Trevor : Cause it felt like I don't know I just wish I'd hugged you back you know
Trevor : Cause I thought Oh you're gonna shake my hand
Trevor : But then you were like
Ensemble : Turn turn turn
Trevor : And I was like
Trevor : And we were like
Ensemble : Turn turn turn turn
Ensemble : Turn the page turn the page Into your fantasy
Pinky;Ensemble : Whoa
Trevor;Ensemble : Turn the page turn the page
Trevor;Ensemble : Cause you gotta see what's under
Ensemble : Turn the page turn the page
Ensemble : Turn turn turn Turn turn turn turn
Ensemble : Turn turn turn turn
Ensemble : Upside down
Diana Ross : Boy you turn me Inside out
Diana Ross : And round and round
Diana Ross : I know you got charm and appeal You always play the field
Diana Ross : I'm crazy to think you're all mine
Diana Ross : As long as the sun continues to shine
Diana Ross : There's a place in my heart for you That's the bottom line
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Upside down
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Boy you turn me Inside out
Ensemble : Whoo
Diana Ross : Round and round
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Upside down you're turning me
Diana Ross;Ensemble : You're giving love instinctively
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Around and round you're turning me
Trevor : Stop
Trevor : That was weird
Trevor : Did everybody see that It was weird
Trevor : Like why would I even dream that And what could it even mean
Trevor : Something's got my brain all mixedup From that stupid magazine
Mrs.Nelson : Knock knock
Trevor : Something's Not a knock!
Mr.Nelson : Trevor Hey Look
Mr.Nelson : I need to
Mr.Nelson : It's time we
Mr.Nelson : Your mother was cleaning around the house today
Mr.Nelson : All over The kitchen the bathroom our bedroom the living room
Mr.Nelson : the front steps
Mr.Nelson : the other bathroom
Mr.Nelson : the linen closet
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor are you talking to any girls at school
Trevor : What do you mean
Mrs.Nelson : Anyone special
Trevor : Special how
Mr.Nelson : Girls
Mrs.Nelson : What your father means to say is
Mrs.Nelson : sometimes around your age things get confusing
Mrs.Nelson : and well maybe you look at farming magazines that are a little
Walter : Farming magazines
Mrs.Nelson : Someone needs to learn to knock
Walter : Please don't tell my mom
Mr.Nelson : Your mom
Walter : About the magazine
Walter : She gets em in the mail and we just We thought it was funny
Walter : That's all I swear
Trevor : I swear too
Mr.Nelson : You mean it wasn't Trevor's? So he didn't...
Mrs.Nelson;Mr.Nelson : Oh so they were your mother's magazines not Trevor's?
Mr.Nelson : Wait You mean
Mr.Nelson;Mrs.Nelson : Peggy
Mrs.Nelson : Well that's a little funny I suppose
Mr.Nelson : A little bit Maybe
Mrs.Nelson : No It's not Yes
Very immature No So
Mrs.Nelson : It's not a joke
Mr.Nelson : Yes
Mrs.Nelson : Mmhmm
Mr.Nelson : I think we're good here
Mrs.Nelson : Good
Mr.Nelson : Good
Walter : Well Trevor first you ditch me
Walter : now you're gonna get me grounded for the rest of my life
Trevor : Walter I'm sorry There's just a lot on my mind Like
Trevor : Have you heard of the Quality Courts
Walter : You mean the hotel they've been building forever on Route 9
Cathy : There's a spot behind the construction zone where people go make out
Cathy : I know things
Trevor : Cathy You're a girl
Cathy : Thanks
Walter : What are you talking about
Trevor : Do you wanna go there With me
Cathy : What
Walter : What
Walter : No
Cathy : Yes yes yes
Cathy : Oh I'll go I'll go
Cathy : This is gonna be awesome
Trevor : This is gonna make everything okay
Walter : This is totally screwed up
Trevor;Walter;Cathy : I can't believe This is happening today
Trevor : The Quality Courts is a pretty bizarre place
Trevor : I mean yes it would be an incredible place to stage West Side Story
Trevor : But aside from that I'm not really sure why anyone would find it romantic
Trevor : What are you doing
Cathy : I've gotta take out my rubber bands
Trevor : Right
Trevor : This is gonna be easy
Cathy : This is gonna be too good to forget
Cathy : This is gonna be nothing
Trevor;Cathy : Can't believe we haven't started yet
Trevor : What's wrong
Cathy : Nothing
Frannie : I guess I just thought
Frannie : it would be a little more romantic here and less dirty
Pinky : What do you mean If
Pinky : From here we can see the water tower
Pinky : and we can sit on these cinder blocks which is way better than the ground
Pinky : This is really romantic
Frannie : This is gonna be really really nice
Pinky;Cathy : This is gonna be sexy
Pinky;Cathy : And I bet that we're gonna do it twice
Trevor;Cathy : Twice Twice
Cathy : Yeah right after we do it once
Cathy;Walter;Frannie : I can't wait can't wait I can't wait for us to start
Trevor : But I'm scared I'll be a monster Once I finally get the bait
Trevor : Cause I can't wait
Walter;Frannie;Cathy : Can't wait I can't wait for that one part
Walter;Cathy;Frannie : It's right around the corner It's right around the corner
Walter;Cathy;Frannie;Trevor : And I I can't wait
Cathy : What are they doing here
Jason : Trevor's still trying to prove he's not a freak and Pinky's buying it
Mary : That's so funny
Mary : Wait Are you like jealous
Jason : What No it's just You wouldn't get it
Mary : Calm down Jason What's the big deal
Mary : All we have to do is show Pinky that Trevor's a freak by tomorrow Right
Jason : You could do that
Mary : This is gonna be easy
Cathy : This is gonna be
Trevor;Pinky;Mary;Jason;Frannie : Wait a second please
Frannie : This should go like a romance
Pinky;Trevor : This is gonna be gone Like it's a breeze
Trevor : And I can't wait
Ensemble : Can't wait
Ensemble : I can't wait
Trevor : Till this is through
Trevor : I just mean this stupid part Where we anticipate
Trevor : Cause I can't stand
Ensemble : Can't stand
Ensemble : I can't stand not kissing you
Trevor;Walter;Pinky;Mary;Jason;Frannie : It's gonna be like everything
Trevor;Walter;Pinky;Mary;Jason;Frannie : And I
Trevor;Walter;Pinky;Mary;Jason;Frannie : My heart is in my ears And I hear my blood flowing
Trevor;Walter;Pinky;Mary;Jason;Frannie : Maybe all I need is you To get me going
Trevor : Maybe I'll be different Once we make it through this
Trevor;Walter;Pinky;Mary;Jason;Frannie : So take a good deep breath And then we'll do this
Trevor;Walter;Pinky;Mary;Jason;Frannie : Let's get to this
Ensemble : Ah ah Ah
Ensemble : Can't wait ah Ah ah
Ensemble : Can't wait ah Ah
Frannie : There's a pimple under my nose
Frannie : Every second that goes It keeps on growing
Cathy : Check me out in all of these poses
Jason : Are we really gonna keep going
Mary : Make a move fast Or else it's like See ya
Trevor : That's where Tony Would first see Maria
Ensemble : Time is short Now it's getting urgent
Ensemble : You smell like my grandma's Laundry detergent
Ensemble : Can't wait
Cathy : It's Woolite
Cathy : Gentle cycle
Trevor : And I can't wait
Trevor;Walter;Pinky;Mary;Jason;Frannie;Ensemble : Can't wait Can't wait to make this real
Ensemble : I'm ready to get moving From this endless limbo state
Ensemble : And I can't wait I can't wait to feel
Ensemble : It's gonna be like I don't know
Ensemble : And I
Ensemble : Ah ah ah ah Ah ah ah
Ensemble : I can't wait
Ensemble : Ah Ah ah ah Ah ah
Ensemble : I can't ah
Ensemble : Ah Ah ah Ah ah
Ensemble : I
Trevor : Run
Ensemble : Oh wait
Ensemble : Oh Oh oh
Ensemble : Wait
Trevor : What happens if they catch us
Pinky : I've never been caught
Trevor : So how do we get away
Pinky : I've never gotten away either
Trevor : You mean you've never
Pinky : Shh
Pinky : Okay We should be safe back here
Pinky : They're just driving through the main lot now
Pinky : Hey how'd it go with Cathy
Trevor : Huh
Trevor : Oh great Yeah Really really great
Trevor : How about Frannie
Pinky : She was pretty nervous
Trevor : Cathy wasn't nervous Not at all
Pinky : I don't get it
Pinky : I thought Frannie liked me but it was like she was scared of me
Trevor : You can be a little scary sometimes
Pinky : What do you mean
Trevor : Something about your eyes or the way you talk
Trevor : I can't really explain it But I'm sure she wanted to
Trevor : You know
Pinky : Yeah well I don't really know if I want to anymore
Trevor : Why not
Pinky : I don't know I guess there's someone who's sorta changing my mind
Trevor : Really Who
Pinky : It's embarrassing
Pinky : I don't think they feel the same
Trevor : Yes they do
Trevor : I mean of course they do Why wouldn't they
Pinky : Easy for you to say You've got Cathy
Trevor : No I like someone else too Someone who
Trevor : I can't say either
Pinky : That makes two of us then
Trevor : Yeah
Trevor : Pinky why are you so nice to me
Trevor : It's just You don't have to be but you are
Pinky : I don't know
Pinky : It's sort of hard to explain
Pinky : You're not like anyone else I know
Pinky : It's like
Pinky : You're like
Pinky : I don't know
Pinky : But not afraid just to let it show
Pinky : And I could never do that
Pinky : With everyone always telling me
Pinky : Who I should be
Pinky : But when I'm talking to you I'm never thinking of that stuff
Pinky : It's like I'm like
Pinky : I don't know
Pinky : But somehow I'm always good enough
Pinky : Cause even when I sound dumb Or I don't play along
Pinky : You look at me And it's like you see
Pinky : Who I should be
Pinky : And I don't know who that is yet
Pinky : I didn't know I could even know
Pinky : I thought the only place I'd get Was nowhere
Pinky : Like my dad said I'd go
Pinky : But thanks to you
Pinky : Now I know if I look ten years ahead
Pinky : And I start getting there now
Pinky : I could go somewhere instead
Pinky : Somehow
Trevor : Actually it was more Diana Ross who said that
Pinky;Trevor : Right Sorry
Trevor : I just can't take credit for her amazingness
Pinky : Well I guess what I'm trying to say then is Thanks Diana Ross
Trevor : I know right
Trevor : Pinky can I tell you something
Pinky : Oh hey I think they're gone I should probably go find Frannie
Trevor : Yeah me too
Trevor : But Cathy
Pinky : What were you gonna say
Trevor : Oh
Trevor : I was gonna say just
Trevor;Pinky : break a leg Huh
Trevor : Tomorrow At the talent show
Trevor : Good luck is bad luck in theater so break a leg
Pinky : Thanks
Pinky : Hey Trevor Break a leg too okay
Trevor : Yeah okay
Trevor : I will
Trevor : It's sort of hard to explain
Trevor : I've never felt like this before
Trevor : It's like
Trevor : I'm like
Trevor : I don't know
Trevor : But I just wanna know even more
Trevor : I play it over again And again and again
Trevor : And for a second it's like I see
Trevor : Who I should be
Diana Ross : Once we were standing still In time
Diana Ross : Chasin the fantasies That filled our minds
Diana Ross : And you knew how I loved you But my spirit was free
Diana Ross : Laughin at the questions That you once asked of me
Diana Ross : Do you know
Trevor : I don't know I don't know How to say what I know
Trevor : But I think now I know You are thinking it too
Trevor : And I don't know I don't know Why I thought all along
Trevor : I was feeling wrong For just feeling true
Trevor : It's like everything turned upside down And finally right
Trevor : And daylight doesn't mean a thing Cause everything's bright
Trevor : And I don't have the room For all I'm feeling right now
Trevor : I wish that I could find the way To tell you
Trevor : I've gotta tell you Can't wait to tell you somehow
Walter : Hey you and Cathy have a nice time last night
Trevor : Walter I'm sorta busy right now with something a little more serious
Walter : Something serious Really
Walter : You mean like living in a daydream all week
Walter : Or obsessing over this talent show
Walter : Or like writing Pinky's name all over your diary
Trevor : It's not a diary Walter just because you're jealous
Walter : Jealous Of Pinky
Walter;Trevor : Have you completely lost it I can't right now
Trevor : It's a really important day and
Walter : No it's not
Walter : It's the Lakeview talent show Who cares
Walter : What do you think is gonna happen You're not even in the show
Trevor : I am in the show
Trevor : It's my vision and once people see what I did they'll all know
Walter : Know what
Trevor : That I'm worth something
Trevor : Even though I don't have muscles or play football or go on dates
Trevor : That I'm more than someone
Trevor : who sits around this stupid town doing nothing but weird science experiments
Walter : Trevor
Mary : Hey
Mary;Walter : Is that Trevor's Um
Mary : You're his friend right
Walter : I don't know about that anymore
Mary : True Trevor's friends with Pinky Farraday now
Mary : I guess he just can't be hanging around with anyone who's so weird
Walter;Mary : Me That's what Trevor told Pinky
Mary : Right
Walter : What But I'm not the one who
Walter : I mean talk about weird
Mary : What do you mean
Walter : Well he
Walter : Um
Mary : Frannie
Frannie : Walter um he went to the Quality Courts with Cathy
Frannie : He's not being a good friend
Walter : You found it in his chair if anyone asks
Mary : Nicely done
Frannie : What are you gonna do
Mary : Let's see
Mary : Stupid Boring So sad
Mary : Oh my God Wait
Mary : Jason was right Look Pinky Pinky Pinky
Mary : I don't know I don't know If my heart is to blame
Mary : When I'm writing your name On the page next to mine
Mary;Frannie : And I don't know I don't know How your eyes are so blue
Mary : And if it's me or you Who's making them shine
Mary : It's like everything turned upside down And finally right
Mary;Frannie : And daylight doesn't mean a thing Cause everything's bright
Lindsey : And I don't have the room For all I'm feeling right now
Lindsey;Frannie;Mary : I wish that I could find the way To tell you
Mandy;Ensemble;Frannie;Mary : I gotta tell you Can't wait to tell you somehow
Trevor : I wanna go where you're going Wherever you are
Mandy;Ensemble;Frannie;Mary : I wanna be where you're standing No matter how far
Mary;Frannie;Ensemble;Mandy;Trevor : I'm lost for words for explaining They may never be found
Trevor : It's beyond anything I can say with a sound
Trevor : It's like
Ensemble : Oh oh
Ensemble : Oh oh Oh oh oh
Trevor : I'm like
Ensemble : Oh oh oh oh
Trevor : And you're like
Ensemble : Oh oh
Ensemble : Oh oh Oh oh oh
Trevor : And we're like
Ensemble : Oh oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Ensemble : Ah ah
Mary;Jason;Frannie;Ensemble;Mandy : This is weird Way too weird
Even weirder than it could be
Mary;Ensemble;Mandy;Frannie : Jackpot weird Super weird
Mary : So let's get it where it should be Jason needs this yesterday
Mary : Cause the second Pinky sees it There's no way he cannot say
Mary : Trevor's weird
Weird weird weird Trevor's weird Trevor's weird
Jason;Ensemble : Now he's totally caught This is better than I thought
Jason : He's been making us look stupid But that isn't lasting long
Jason;Ensemble : All it takes is a glance And he doesn't stand a chance
Jason;Ensemble : The second Pinky realizes Something's really wrong
Jason : Always knew I was right But now it's there in blackandwhite
Jason : And anyone can see he's acting
Ensemble : Anyone can see he's acting Oh
Jason : Like I said he's acting
Jason : Like a girl Like a girl
Ensemble : Like a girl like a girl Like a girl just like a girl
Jason : Like a
Jason : Like I told you all along
Trevor : One of these days is here today
Trevor : My golden dream is coming true
Trevor : And after this show I'll break away
Trevor : Just like Diana said I'd do
Trevor;Ensemble : And I'll be on and on and on and on
Trevor;Ensemble : And on on on Na na na na
Ensemble : On and on and on on on Na na na na na
Trevor : And on with the show
Teacher : Oh
Teacher : Too bad
Teacher : But let's give a big hand for Lindsay Gibbons and her Rubik's Cube
Teacher : Yeah There you go Aw
Teacher : Aw
Teacher : I really thought she was gonna solve it
Teacher : Okay as you all know it's a Lakeview tradition
Teacher : that our eighth grade football team closes the show
Teacher : But instead of the hilarious pink tutus we've all come to know and love
Teacher : they'll be doing something else
Teacher : Yes
Teacher : But first Jason has asked me to ask Trevor to say a few words
Teacher : So come on up Trevor
Trevor : Well first I'd like to thank you for being here tonight
Trevor : Thank you for the love and for making this a really special evening for me
Trevor : But thank you most of all to Pinky Farraday for making this all possible
Trevor : I think it's safe to say
Trevor : this will be like nothing Lakeview Junior High has ever seen before
Trevor : Cue the lights
Trevor : It's begun
Trevor : That's your cue And start at one and then
Football Team : One two three four
Trevor : What Wait No
Football Team : Five six seven eight
Trevor : No
Football Team : One two three four Five six seven eight
Ensemble : I don't know I don't know
Trevor : I don't know I don't know
Trevor : Stop
Trevor : Diana says I can't lay down and die Cause my golden dream is up to me
Trevor : It's up to me
Trevor : Diana says a valley Is there for getting through
Trevor : Diana says Diana says
Ensemble : I don't know I don't know
Ensemble : Oh oh oh
Ensemble : Oh oh I don't know I don't
Ensemble;Trevor : I don't know I don't
Diana Ross : Do you know Where you're going to
Trevor : I don't know
Ensemble : Oh oh oh oh
Ensemble : Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Ensemble : Oh oh oh oh oh
Ensemble : Oh
Trevor : Yesterday was the worst day in the history of time
Ensemble : Your life is over
Jason : How can you ever show your face again At Lakeview Junior High
Jason : I just keep on reliving it And then I wanna die
Trevor : Trevor I'm sorry that Pinky didn't do your dance yesterday
Trevor : While everyone watched
Trevor : And after you worked so hard on it all week
Trevor : Cause if everyone had just seen it
Trevor : it would've made everything happen for you
Trevor : But instead
Cathy;Jason : Your life is over
Cathy : Your golden dream was coming true But now the dream is dead
Cathy : Why can't it be yesterday So I could have said
Cathy : Trevor if I could tell you one thing
Cathy : it would be how much Pinky regretted everything the second he saw your face
Cathy : And how he ran after you
Cathy : But you were gone by the time he got through everyone
Cathy : And how he shouted at the top of his lungs
Cathy;Jason : My life is over
Pinky : A world without you in the world Is no world anymore
Ensemble : My life is over
Mrs.Nelson : Knock knock
Ensemble : Saying knock knock Isn't really knocking on the door
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor why are you burning candles in here
Trevor : Ambience which you're ruining
Mrs.Nelson : What's this all about dear
Trevor : It's just
Trevor : Pinky did something
Trevor : Or didn't do something
Mrs.Nelson : Pinky That boy from school
Trevor : He's more than just that
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor
Mrs.Nelson : No burning candles in the bedroom okay
Ensemble : It's a tragedy What a tragedy
Ensemble : How could life do such a thing to me
Ensemble : Like an open wound All full of salt
Ensemble : How can I get through Living in a world without you
Ensemble : And it's all my fault all my fault It's all my fault my fault
It's all my fault all my fault It's all my fault it's all my fault
Ensemble : All my fault All my fault
Ensemble : All my fault It is all my fault
Ensemble : All my fault
Ensemble : Your life is over
Walter : And what the future could've been Is everybody's loss
Cathy : Just in time for this appearance From Diana Ross
Ensemble : Ooh
Diana Ross : My dearest Trevor my greatest fan
Diana Ross : I was so saddened to hear how you perished of complete humiliation
Diana Ross : at the Lakeview Junior High 17th Annual Celebration of Talent
Diana Ross : I was nearly too consumed by grief to be here today
Diana Ross : But no
Diana Ross : For there's no mountain so high no river so wide
Diana Ross : and no valley so low it could keep me away
Diana Ross : Because I know your pain Trevor
Diana Ross : After I left The Supremes people said I was wrong and over
Ensemble : No
Diana Ross : Mmm
Diana Ross : But Trevor no matter how humiliated abandoned or confused you may be
Diana Ross : you must get up
Diana Ross : Because love
Ensemble : Love
Diana Ross : is still alive
Diana Ross : Love
Ensemble : Love
Diana Ross : is not defeated And love
Ensemble : And love
Diana Ross : is always worth the fight
Diana Ross : And you know what I say Trevor
Ensemble;Diana Ross : Ain't no mountain high enough
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Ain't no valley low enough
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Ain't no river wide enough
Diana Ross;Ensemble : To keep me from you
Diana Ross;Ensemble;Trevor : Ain't no mountain high enough
Ensemble : Nothing can keep me Keep me from you
Trevor : Diana's right Pinky wouldn't do this
Trevor : There's gotta be a logical explanation
Diana Ross : If you need me call me
Trevor : Hello Mrs Farraday this is Trevor for Pinky
Diana Ross : No matter where you are no matter how far
Trevor;Diana Ross : Trevor Just call my name
Trevor : Trevor Nelson
Trevor : Oh Well can you just tell him
Trevor : I know he can't be to blame
Trevor : for what happened at the show
Trevor : and that it hasn't changed anything between us And
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor
Trevor : Mom? Where are you?
Mrs.Nelson : On the living room phone
Mrs.Nelson : Mrs Farraday I am so sorry
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor please hang up
Trevor : Mrs Farraday just tell Pinky I'll be there in 15 minutes
Ensemble : No wind
Trevor : This is even better No rain
Trevor : Once I talk to Pinky facetoface it'll all be okay
Ensemble : If you're my goal
Trevor : I know it
Ensemble : Ain't no mountain high enough
Ensemble : Nothing can keep me Keep me from you
Ensemble : Ain't no mountain high enough Ain't no valley low enough
Ensemble : Ain't no river wide enough To keep me from you
Ensemble;Trevor;Diana Ross : Ain't no river wide enough To keep me from you
Trevor;Ensemble : Ain't no mountain high enough Ain't no valley low enough
Ensemble : Ain't no river wide enough To keep me from you
Ensemble : Ain't no mountain high enough
Ensemble : Ain't no mountain high enough Ain't no valley low enough
Ensemble : Ain't no river wide enough To keep me from you
Ensemble : Ain't no mountain high
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor you remember Father Joe from church
Mrs.Nelson : Every Sunday
Mrs.Nelson;Trevor : Uh Of course you do
Mrs.Nelson : Trevor Father Joe is gonna take you over to the TasteeFreez
Mrs.Nelson : because well we thought it might be good for the two of you to just you know
Mrs.Nelson : talk about some things to talk to
Trevor : But I really need
Mrs.Nelson : No buts
Mrs.Nelson : Now don't order anything too extravagant or too sweet
Mrs.Nelson : Or too salty
Father Joe : How is your water
Trevor : Warm
Father Joe : You could've gotten ice cream you know
Father Joe : Or at least ice
Father Joe : It's not a sin
Father Joe : Trevor you know someday you'll look back and be amazed by how much you've changed
Father Joe : And the whole world too
Father Joe : You won't even recognize yourself
Father Joe : And you'll understand how your parents feel right now
Father Joe : because well I know that you'll have kids of your own
Father Joe : And
Trevor : How
Father Joe : Well Trevor
Father Joe : What happens is first a man and a woman who are very much in love get married
Trevor : No I mean
Trevor : how do you know I'll have kids of my own
Father Joe : Of course you will
Trevor : You don't
Father Joe : I've sworn a vow of celibacy
Father Joe : Do you know what celibacy is
Father Joe : It means abstinence from marriage and sexual relations
Father Joe : Do you understand what that is
Trevor : It wasn't until that moment
Trevor : and halfway through my salivawarm holy water
Trevor : that I realized the purpose of this miserable setup between my mom and Father Joe
Father Joe : Trevor did you ever have any desires
Father Joe : and I'm talking about sexual desires
Father Joe : for another boy
Father Joe : Be honest with me
Father Joe : I can help you if you're honest with me
Father Joe : Did you ever for example ever want to touch another boy
Father Joe : Like and I don't mean to suggest anything here
Father Joe : but like Pinky Farraday
Trevor : What
Trevor : No he's just
Trevor : He's the kind of person that makes me
Trevor : and everyone feel you know really happy
Trevor : So happy that you think about him all the time
Trevor : Like an older brother you never had
Trevor : And you write about him in your notebook because he makes you so happy that you can't keep it inside
Trevor : And you just want to be sure it's going to be like this forever
Trevor : That happens with friends sometimes
Trevor : Right
Father Joe : Well Trevor friends are people who make us happy yes
Father Joe : But just in our hearts
Father Joe : And not well
Father Joe : in certain other places
Father Joe : Because if anyone's making you happy there well then that's not happy like a friend
Father Joe : But if it's anywhere else then well yes That's a friend
Father Joe : Probably
Father Joe : But if not
Father Joe : No
Father Joe : Make sense
Trevor : Yes
Trevor : Definitely
Trevor : Thank you
Trevor : That was weird
Trevor : In every way it could be Really weird
Trevor : Like I'm not who I should be
Trevor : But the more I play along
Trevor : The more somebody's telling me I'm doing something wrong
Trevor : Something weird
Cathy : Trevor
Cathy : Are you okay
Cathy : Did you want a milkshake It was a mistake so it's free
Trevor : No thanks
Cathy : I couldn't find you after the show yesterday
Cathy : I looked everywhere
Trevor : I left
Trevor : Right away
Cathy : Yeah I guess it was pretty
Cathy : Um but probably not as bad as you thought it was
Cathy : I bet most people don't even believe it
Trevor : Believe what
Cathy : Um Um nothing Never mind
Cathy : Cathy
Cathy : It's so stupid
Cathy : I mean like so what if you like dancing and singing and Diana Ross It doesn't mean that
Cathy : you're what people are saying
Trevor : What are people saying
Trevor : Who said that
Cathy : I heard Lindsay saying it to Mandi
Cathy : But they're wrong
Cathy : We can prove it
Trevor : What do you mean
Cathy : We can
Cathy : finish what we started at the Quality Courts
Trevor : Uh but we're in the parking lot There's people around
Cathy : Exactly So by Monday all they'll be talking about is you
Cathy : and me
Cathy : And our strawberry milkshake Just one strawberry milkshake
Cathy : That we sipped Out of two different straws
Trevor : What are you talking about
Cathy : Us
Cathy : Together
Cathy : Right here out in the open
Cathy : In the middle of public
Cathy : And probably breaking some laws
Cathy : Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Trevor : Great Now you can tell everyone that we kissed
Cathy : We nothing You turned on purpose
Trevor : Cathy I can't get to semantics
Trevor : I have to find Pinky and make sure
Cathy : Pinky
Cathy : What's wrong with me
Cathy : Why can't I be anyone to you What do you always see
Cathy : I've been sending signals Loud and strong
Cathy : So tell me what is wrong with me
Cathy : I've been trying Everything I can think of Anything I can think of
Cathy : To make us more than just friends
Cathy : You invite me To a place for French kissing
Cathy : And we're almost French kissing
Cathy : And then suddenly that's where it ends
Cathy : What's wrong with me
Cathy : I wanna be Together like the couples I see on TV
Cathy : But you would trade me For a song
Cathy : So tell me what is wrong with me
Cathy : I said that everyone was crazy When they said I was crazy
Cathy : For saying you're totally not
Cathy : I kept on giving you defenses When you went out of style
Cathy : And nothing is all that I got
Trevor;Cathy : Whoa whoa whoa
Cathy : Nothing is all that I got
Cathy : Oh
Cathy : Yeah nothing is all that I got
Cathy : What's wrong with me I never knew
Cathy : The problem's always been I never had a clue
Cathy : When the real question all along is Trevor what is wrong with you
Walter : What's wrong with you
Cathy;Mrs.Nelson : What's wrong what's wrong What is wrong with you
Jason;Cathy : What is wrong with you
Ensemble : Oh What is wrong
Ensemble : What is wrong with you
Cathy;Ensemble : What is wrong with you
Tell me Trevor What is wrong with you
Ensemble : What is wrong with you
Cathy;Ensemble : Come on tell me
Come on tell me
Come on tell me What is wrong with you
Come on tell me Come on tell me
Cathy;Ensemble : What is wrong What is wrong
Cathy;Ensemble : What is wrong with you
Pinky : Trevor
Pinky;Trevor : What are you doing at my house Pinky
Trevor : I thought
Trevor : Cause I know you wouldn't
Trevor : I mean it can't be your fault
Trevor : What happened at the show right
Pinky : You need to go
Trevor : But
Pinky : Bye Trevor
Trevor : Wait
Trevor : You said you liked someone who you couldn't say
Pinky : What
Trevor : At the Quality Courts
Trevor : Why couldn't you say who it was
Pinky : Mary is Frannie's best friend
Trevor : Mary
Pinky : Yes
Pinky : Did you actually think
Pinky : I mean how could you even write that stuff
Trevor : What stuff
Pinky : About me In your notebook
Trevor : My notebook But how did you
Pinky : Everyone saw it
Trevor : What
Pinky : Are you even living in the real world
Trevor : Pinky it was just
Trevor : I was only
Pinky : What is wrong with you
Trevor : Everyone at school is saying that I'm a gay
Trevor : But I look in the mirror and I don't see anything different
Trevor : So maybe
Trevor : There's these doctors I heard about
Trevor : They use electricity on people's brains to completely reset them back to normal
Trevor : I think it could work on me too
Diana Ross : Bye baby See you around
Diana Ross : Didn't I tell you I wouldn't hold you down
Diana Ross : Take good care of yourself you hear
Diana Ross : Don't let me hear About you shedding a tear
Diana Ross : You're gonna make it
Diana Ross : Remember me as a sunny day
Diana Ross : That you once had Along the way
Diana Ross : Didn't I inspire you a little higher
Remember me as a funny clown
Ensemble;Diana Ross : As a funny clown
Diana Ross;Ensemble : That made you laugh When you were down
Diana Ross : Didn't I boy Didn't I boy
Diana Ross : Remember me as a big balloon
Diana Ross : At a carnival that ended too soon
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Remember me as a breath of spring
Diana Ross : Remember me as a good thing
Diana Ross : Oh oh
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Remember me as a sunny day
Diana Ross : Please darling
Ensemble : Remember me as a good thing
Diana Ross : Remember me when you drink the wine
Diana Ross : Oh yeah
Ensemble : Remember me as a good thing
Diana Ross : Baby oh yeah
Diana Ross;Ensemble : Remember me as a big balloon
Diana Ross : Don't forget me darlin
Ensemble : Remember me as a good thing
Ensemble : Remember me as a
Mr.Nelson : Trevor
Mr.Nelson : Hey
Mr.Nelson : What happened to your posters
Trevor : I'm living in the real world now
Mr.Nelson : Oh
Mr.Nelson : Well
Mr.Nelson : Good
Mr.Nelson : Hey
Mr.Nelson : I know that tomorrow's your first time back at school since that show on Friday
Mr.Nelson : and I thought if you wanted to we could talk
Mr.Nelson : I know you have that report to give
Trevor : Dad
Trevor : It's all under control
Mr.Nelson : Oh
Mr.Nelson : Okay
Mr.Nelson : You and Walter working on another science project
Trevor : Sort of
Trevor : I mean
Trevor : I am
Mr.Nelson : Good
Mr.Nelson : Well I hope it works out
Mr.Nelson : Yeah
Mr.Nelson : Me too
Ensemble : Every day keeps on going
Ensemble : On and on and on
Jason : Hey Did Trevor actually come to school today
Pinky : I don't know Who cares
Jason : Pinky if he's here we have to do something about it
Jason : We can't just let him walk around like
Pinky : Jason
Pinky : Just forget it all right
Pinky : Really Cause no one else has
Ensemble : Everybody is talking Talking
Ensemble : On and on and on
Pinky : But he was the one who I never
Jason : So do something about it
Pinky : No
Pinky : I don't want to talk to him again
Jason : Pinky
Jason : Do you wanna be remembered as the guy who won half these trophies
Jason : Or the guy who acted like a fairy with Trevor
Pinky : What do I do
Jason : You don't even have to talk to him about it
Jason;Pinky : Just write down what you'd say Okay
Ensemble : Get me through today
Ensemble : Na na na na na na
Jason : That's it
Pinky : No Also
Ensemble : Get me through today
Ensemble : Na na na na na na
Jason : Yes Perfect
Jason : Hey Mary
Jason : For Trevor
Jason : The long way around
Mary : Got it
Trevor : Get me through today
Ensemble : Snap Flip
Ensemble : Turn Snap
Teacher : Trevor your report is next
Teacher : The Loss of Innocence as Reflected in Literature
Teacher : In front of the class like everyone else dear
Ensemble : Turn Tip
Ensemble : Slip Turn
Trevor : The loss of innocence is brought about by an experience with no explanation
Trevor : The character must experience this loss
Trevor : Must react with natural spontaneity
Trevor : Must be hurt
Trevor : The experience must be potent enough to be remembered
Trevor : Pinky Pinky wait up
Trevor;Pinky : Trevor cut it out But I'm okay now
Trevor : I promise I had the procedure Well I performed it myself
Trevor : But I feel different Better Normal
Pinky : Pinky told you what he thought in his note
Pinky;Trevor : It hasn't changed Note
Trevor : What note
Pinky : Look you're sick
Pinky : And anyone who'd even talk to you now is as sick as you are
Trevor : I'm not sick
Pinky : You are And you'll never get better
Ensemble : Snap Slip
Ensemble : Turn Snap
Ensemble : Look the other way
Ensemble : No one there to see
Ensemble : You are yesterday
Ensemble : And you don't know me
Ensemble : No you don't know me
Frannie : Mary You let everyone see this note
Mary : Hilarious right But you can give it to Trevor now
Frannie : But it's horrible
Mary : Yeah He deserves it
Frannie : No You're wrong
Frannie : And you're just mean
Mary : Pinky's right You're just as weird as Trevor
Mary : Frannie
Frannie;Trevor : Did you have a note for me From Pinky Pinky's not talking to me
Trevor : Mary gave it to Lindsay who gave it to Mandi who gave it to you
Frannie : Trevor Please Just forget it okay
Ensemble : Turn Tip
Ensemble : Run Turn
Ensemble : Get away fast
Ensemble : Nothing else to do But keep on walking past
Ensemble : Cause I don't know you
Ensemble : No I don't know you
Ensemble : Snap turn Slip tip
Ensemble : Turn run
Ensemble : Tip snap Run slip
Teacher : Trevor there's no running in the hallways
Ensemble : You're invisible invisible to me
Ensemble : Oh oh oh oh You're invisible
Ensemble : You're invisible
Ensemble : Oh oh oh Invisible invisible
Frannie : Walter Cathy You guys need to talk to Trevor
Walter : We're not really talking
Frannie : What But you're his friends
Cathy : And you'd know all about that
Cathy : as long as it's on the right side of Route 9
Frannie : Cathy I'm sorry things changed but we still all know Trevor
Frannie : And someone has to get him to stop asking about Pinky's note
Walter : Why
Frannie : Because
Ensemble : Duck dodge slide You won't catch my eye
Ensemble : You're not worth the risk
Ensemble : Go ahead and try
Ensemble : Slide check skid duck
Ensemble : I'll be walking light
Like a mystery I'll be out of sight
Ensemble : You won't notice me You won't notice me
Trevor : Walter Walter
Ensemble : Duck slide dodge sneak Turn run
Trevor : Wait I need to talk to you
Ensemble : Turn run
Trevor : Walter please There's nobody nowhere
Ensemble : No one you ever knew Turn run
Ensemble : I'm invisible invisible to you
Trevor : Frannie told you about Pinky's note didn't you
Walter : Trevor I can't talk to you
Trevor : Walter
Trevor : I'm sorry
Trevor : I know I haven't been a good friend I know it
Trevor : But that doesn't mean
Walter : You're sorry Now
Trevor;Walter : Cause you need something from me Walter please
Trevor : Pinky might've said something important
Walter : He didn't
Trevor : You know
Walter : Trevor trust me
Trevor : Trust you After you showed my notebook to everyone
Walter : Well I didn't know it got so much worse past the cover okay I mean geez why do you have to act so weird all the time
Walter : We're not little kids anymore Trevor Can't you just start acting like a normal person and stop
Trevor : Can't I act normal
Trevor : You're the one who looks at your sperm under a microscope
Walter : Trevor
Trevor : He wanted to look at mine too
Walter : Shut up
Trevor : for your experiment!
Walter : Fine Trevor fine Here Here's your wonderful important note from your best best best friend
Ensemble : I learned about stranger danger
Ensemble : And nothing is stranger than you
Ensemble : I gotta save Gotta save myself now
Ensemble : And that means making Making you you you you
Ensemble : No one
Pinky : Trevor don't call me don't talk to me
Pinky : You're a faggot
Pinky : A weak person
Pinky : You probably don't deserve to live
Ensemble : No one nothing nowhere I can see
Ensemble : No one nothing nowhere I can see Invisible invisible invisible
Ensemble : No one nothing nowhere Invisible invisible invisible
Ensemble : And you're nobody to me
Trevor : I thought I was someone Going somewhere
Trevor : I thought everything about me Was gonna get me there
Trevor : And everybody would follow along
Trevor : I thought they would
Trevor : But I was wrong
Trevor : Cause all I thought is a fantasy
Trevor : A daydream of who I should be
Trevor : Ignoring every part of me
Trevor : I didn't wanna know
Trevor : I never knew my heart at all
Trevor : But now I know that it can fall
Trevor : And when it does I know it doesn't have a place to go
Trevor : Oh
Trevor : Oh oh
I thought I could fix it I tried every way
Trevor : But something in me is too broken To try another day
Trevor : I thought I'd be someone
Trevor : I thought I was strong
Trevor : That I was right
Trevor : Dear Mom and Dad
Trevor : I don't want you to think I haven't given this a lot of thought
Trevor : I have
Trevor : I tried to cure myself but nothing worked
Trevor : And don't think it's your fault
Trevor : It just happened
Trevor : And please if it's possible
Trevor : play Endless Love at my funeral
Trevor : It's my absolute fave
Diana Ross : My first love
Diana Ross : You're every breath that I take
Diana Ross : You're every step I make
Trevor;Diana Ross : And I I
Trevor : I want to share
Trevor;Diana Ross : All my love with you
Diana Ross : No one else will do
Diana Ross : Your eyes
Trevor : Your eyes your eyes
Trevor;Diana Ross : They tell me how much you care
Trevor;Diana Ross : Oh yes
Trevor;Diana Ross : You will always be
Trevor;Diana Ross : My endless love
Diana Ross : Two hearts Two hearts that beat as one
Diana Ross : Our lives have just begun
Diana Ross : Oh oh oh oh oh oh
Diana Ross : My love my love
Diana Ross : My endless love
Trevor : Hello
Jack : Hey there
Trevor : Who are you
Jack : Jack I work here
Jack : Your parents went to meet with the doctor after you fell asleep
Jack : but they should be back soon
Jack : You look better than you did last night
Jack : How do you feel
Trevor : Sick
Trevor : And sore from being sick
Trevor : Over and over
Jack : Well it's a good thing you were though
Trevor : Aren't nurses supposed to be girls
Jack : Um I'm a candy striper
Trevor : What's that
Jack : Like a volunteer
Trevor : And they're not girls
Jack : Some are Some aren't
Jack : There's no rule
Trevor : Oh
Trevor : So I guess you know why I'm here then
Jack : I know you took way too many aspirin and you won't have a headache for a year
Trevor : I won't
Trevor : That's not true
Trevor : But I shouldn't be here At all
Jack : Trevor Dr Harris spoke with you right
Trevor : Yes A hundred times
Trevor : And he says we have to keep talking but
Trevor : Did anyone say
Trevor : am I going to try again to do what I did
Jack : I think I should get the doctor
Trevor : It doesn't matter
Trevor : People like me are sick and never get better
Trevor : We're better off gone
Jack : Who said that
Trevor : It's true isn't it
Jack : No it's not
Trevor : But wouldn't it be easier
Jack : Trevor I know it might not seem like it right now but once you get out of here
Trevor : Everything will be the same
Trevor : You don't know what you're talking about You don't know anything
No one does
Jack : I know that this isn't where you wanna be in a hospital
Jack : But I guess you're right
Jack : I don't know much else besides that so
Jack : help me out
Jack : Where would you rather be
Trevor : What
Jack : When you're far away from here and old
Jack : Like in ten years
Jack : Don't think Just go Off the top of your head
Jack : In another ten years
Trevor : You won't be talking still
Jack : Okay that's positive for you I guess
Jack;Trevor : In another ten years I'll be sitting in another spot
Jack : More specific
Jack : In another ten years
Trevor : I'm gonna be some guy no one knows Some freak they all forgot
Jack : Okay I was thinking something more like
Jack : In another ten years I'm gonna see the world
Jack : In another ten years I'll make my biggest dreams look small
Jack : And when I come home
Jack : They'll all look at me Like I'm the greatest star of all
Trevor : I don't think so
Trevor : It's just that'll always be Diana Ross
Jack : I think you mean Donna Summer
Trevor : I don't
Jack : Oh
Jack : I mean I saw Diana in concert once She was good
Trevor : Good She's the best
Jack : Second best
Trevor : Okay are you sure you're not actually a patient here Like for a head injury or something
Jack : Are you sure you've ever heard a Donna Summer song
Trevor : Hot Stuff is cute
Trevor : But Diana's work with The Supremes alone puts Donna to shame
Trevor : And then there's
Trevor : I mean not that I like her
Trevor : Cause Diana's for
Trevor : Um And I'm not
Trevor : I just had this friend who's really seriously committed to her
Jack : Mmm
Trevor : But he's weird
Jack : Ten years ago I used to hate that word
Jack : Ten years ago In whispers up and down the halls
Jack : I knew what it meant But I couldn't let it show
Jack : So I faded back into the walls
Jack : Ten years ago I used to hide myself
Jack : My every move was trying Just to fall in line
Jack : I changed how I walked
Jack : And when I would talk I used a voice that wasn't mine
Jack : And back in those days
Jack : I used to dream I'd wake up as somebody new
Jack : Back in those days
Jack : I'd cry and scream That every day would just be through
Jack : Oh back in those days
Jack : I'd pray and pray To be another life away
Jack : Where one of these days would be okay
Jack : Just like I heard Diana say
Jack : Oh never mind
Trevor : What Why
Jack : Well you wouldn't wanna hear what Diana Ross had to say at her concert
Trevor : It's okay
Trevor : You can still say it
Jack : Well she said
Jack : My darlings always remember
Jack : no matter how difficult it may seem at the time
Jack : it's always easier to live the truth than live a lie
Diana Ross : So be true because I'll love you no matter what
Diana Ross : but I love you happy most of all
Trevor : She didn't say that
Trevor : Uh it's just my friend told me everything she ever said
Jack : Well okay Well it wasn't anything famous
Jack : just something she said
Jack : at her concert that I saw
Trevor : Really Do you have a pen or something I can write that down with
Trevor : Uh Just for...
Jack : For your friend
Mrs.Nelson : Knock knock
Mrs.Nelson : Oh Is it okay if
Jack : Mmhmm
Mr.Nelson : You look a little less pale bud
Mrs.Nelson : Oh honey I am so
Trevor : Mom
Trevor : Not now
Mrs.Nelson : Oh Well
Mrs.Nelson : It's time to go dear
Mrs.Nelson : Back home and um
Mrs.Nelson : I just wanted to say
Mrs.Nelson : Uh
Mrs.Nelson : They say the president is going to make a full recovery and should be back in the White House by next week
Mrs.Nelson : So I just wanted you to know
Mrs.Nelson : how much I admire that kind of courage
Mrs.Nelson : Okay
Trevor : Okay
Mr.Nelson : And hey
Mr.Nelson : that bag of posters is still in the garage
Mr.Nelson : And well it may take a while for the wrinkles to go away
Mr.Nelson : but over time you know
Mr.Nelson : So you get dressed and we'll bring the car around and get you back home
Mr.Nelson : Okay
Trevor : Sorry They're really
Jack : Trying
Jack : They're really trying
Trevor : Yeah I guess
Trevor : But how can I
Trevor : What if
Trevor : What happens now
Jack : Tomorrow
Jack : The next day The next one
Jack : A decade's just time And you'll see how it goes
Jack : It's gone in a minute
Jack : And any minute now This all will be one of those days
Jack : Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
Trevor : One of these days
Trevor : Jack it's nice to meet you
Jack : You too
Trevor : Is it my imagination
Trevor : Like it sometimes always is
Trevor : Was I hearing my own story
Trevor : When I heard him telling his
Trevor : Like a signal out of nowhere
Trevor : Like a light I've never known
Trevor : Showing me I could be Something more than alone
Trevor : Is it my imagination
Trevor : Making daydreams out of dust
Trevor : Are the feelings I'm feeling
Trevor : Something I can really trust
Trevor : Like a world that finally opened
Trevor : From a whisper to a scream
Trevor : Telling me this could be Something more than a dream
Trevor : What if someday isn't someday
Trevor : What if it's right now
Trevor : What if who I hid is Who I get to be somehow
Trevor : What if weird is only different
Trevor : What if different isn't wrong
Trevor : What if normal isn't How I have to play along
Trevor : Play along
Trevor : Is it my imagination
Trevor : Like it always was before
Trevor : Will I hold on to this feeling
Trevor : When I walk out of that door
Trevor : Is it too much to believe now
Trevor : That it isn't only me
Trevor : Is it my imagination
Diana Ross : Oh oh oh
Trevor : Or could it be
Walter : Hey
Trevor : Hey
Walter : Oh uh and it's late The bus So you didn't miss it
Trevor : Oh
Trevor : Good
Walter : Uh you know I thought you moved or something
Walter : You were gone for so long
Walter : Nothing changed
Walter : Except um Frannie's hanging out with Cathy now instead of Mary
Walter : Pinky's hanging out with Mary now instead of Frannie
Walter : And I'm hanging out with no one now instead of you
Walter : And I'm sorry
Trevor : Walter
Walter : Yeah
Trevor : The bus is here
Ensemble : Na na nana nanana Na na nana nanana On and on
Cathy : Were you sick
Trevor : What
Cathy : You weren't in school
Trevor : Oh no it was just
Cathy : Food poisoning
Cathy : Was it bacterial viral or a parasite
Cathy : I know things
Cathy : Like I know Trevor
Cathy : I know friends is the best thing we can ever be
Cathy : Which is better than anything else
Trevor : Yeah well
Trevor : Besides I don't kiss people who my other best friend wants to kiss
Cathy : What
Walter : Trevor
Walter : I don't know what he's talking about He must have another other best friend
Trevor : Nope Still Walter
Walter : Uh what's she doing
Trevor : Taking out her rubber bands
Cathy : Here!
Walter : What is...
Cathy : Bubblicious Strawberry
Cathy : Chew it
Trevor : That's not part of the show Cause we don't need to know
Trevor : What it looks like When Walter and Cathy kiss
Trevor : But I'm still glad to see Well not literally
Trevor : But I guess this is something I would have missed
Teacher : Okay you little Pudding Pops
Teacher : We're gonna make the rest of the week a little more fun
Teacher : I'm gonna pair you each up for oneonone rapidfire dodgeball matches
Teacher : and then the winner of each match will progress
Trevor : But I would like to miss Every second of this
Trevor : Yes I know every day Can't all go my way
Trevor : But I really don't know Where to go with the show
Trevor : When I still have to face
Teacher : Pinky Farraday Your first competitor will be Trevor Nelson
Jason : Careful She might want a kiss
Trevor : I'm right back in the game now And I've gotta get through Another marathon
Trevor : And he acts like a stranger
Trevor : But how can I forget And keep moving on
Ensemble : On and on and on and on and on
Pinky : You can just forfeit you know
Pinky : Come on I don't wanna hurt you
Trevor : You don't
Pinky : Trevor everyone was saying I
Pinky : I mean they thought I was
Pinky : Trevor I'm so
Jason : What's going on
Jason : You flirting again
Trevor : What No I just
Jason : You just what
Jason : Come on Let's forget this What a weirdo
Trevor : Wait
Trevor : You don't even know me But I know you now
Trevor : And in ten years you're going to be just the same
Trevor : And I'll be so much weirder than you can even imagine
Trevor : And I can't wait
Jason : Let me guess
Jason : Diana Ross said that right
Trevor : No
Trevor : I did
Trevor : I've gotta keep on going
Trevor : Don't know where I'll be
Ensemble : Oh oh oh oh oh
Trevor : And there's no one to follow there Except for me
Trevor : Cause all I am right now Is right now
Trevor : All I am right now is right now
Trevor : All I am right now is right now And right now I know
Ensemble : Oh oh oh oh
Trevor;Ensemble : And I am on and on and on and on On and on and on
Trevor;Ensemble : And I'll be On and on and on and on and on On and on and on and on and on
Trevor;Ensemble : And I'll be On and on and on and on and on
Trevor;Ensemble : I'm going on Na na na na na na na
Trevor;Ensemble : I'm going on and on and on Na na na na na na na
Trevor : I'm going on
Trevor : On with the show
Trevor;Ensemble : On and on and on On with the show
I'm coming out
I want the world to know Got to let it show
There's a new me coming out And I just have to live
And I wanna give I'm completely positive
I think this time around I am gonna do it
Like you never knew it Oh I'll make it through
The time has come for me To break out of this shell
I have to shout That I am coming out
I'm coming out
I want the world to know Got to let it show
I've got to show the world All that I wanna be
And all my abilities There's so much more to me
Somehow I've got to make them Just understand
I got it well in hand And oh how I have planned
I'm spreading love There is no need to fear
And I just feel so fine Every time I hear
I'm coming out
I want the world to know Got to let it show
You've got to let it show I'm coming out
I'm coming out